<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-01-02T20:38:39+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strength Training for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/strength-training-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-02T14:16:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/strength-training-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/strength-training-for-weight-loss/strength-training-for-weight-loss.jpg" title="Strength training for weight loss" alt="Strength training for weight loss">How to lose weight? The first thing that comes to mind for most people - you need to go on a diet and running every day. But not only cardio training, such as jogging or swimming, contribute to weight loss. One of the methods to reduce body fat - it is strength training. It is to lose weight used by both men and women. It is advisable to work out in the gym, where there are all necessary: &#8203;&#8203;shells, trainers, coaches, moral support and competent advice. But at home to lose weight using weight training is also possible, although the results will be worse.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>The mechanism of action of strength training</h2>

<p>Strength training affects the body fat mass by means of several mechanisms:</p>

<ol>
<li><em>Energy consumption during the workout</em>. Rising iron or doing other exercise, you expend calories. Spend an extra 400-500 calories per day, you will lose weight faster.</li>
<li><em>Accelerate metabolism</em>. Surely you&rsquo;ve noticed that even after 1-2 hours after exercise, you still feel like you are out of the heat. This is a consequence of accelerated metabolism. Increased heat indicates an increased calorie consumption per unit time. That is, even in a state of rest after returning from the gym, you lose weight.</li>
<li><em>Build muscle</em>. Regular classes are usually weightlifting increases muscle mass man. The higher it is, the greater will be the average daily calorie consumption.</li>
</ol>


<p>We should not suppose that only one sport can give yourself a great figure. If your body a lot of fat, in addition to strength training diet is necessary. Classes burn an average of 500 kcal per day in addition to the primary energy consumption. At the same time with the diet can be reduced energy input into the body to 1000 kcal per day and more.</p>

<p>The diet is more effective for weight loss than weight training. But these methods of weight loss can not be opposed to each other. You will achieve maximum results, combining them. Combining sport, proper nutrition, supplementation, adjusting lifestyle, you will lose weight more quickly, and this process will become more natural.</p>

<p>Men are much more likely to engage in weight training than women. This is quite a natural phenomenon, because the stronger sex to have a good figure, should have developed musculature. At the same time big biceps women scare men rather than attract, so the girls better to lose weight with the help of kardionagruzok.</p>

<p>Strength training for men may include:</p>

<ul>
<li>Training with a barbell: bench press, deadlift, wide grip pull-up to his chest, curl with reverse grip barbell bench press standing because of the head;</li>
<li>Training with dumbbells: lunges, squats, curl with dumbbells standing on a bench, dumbbells swings to the side lying, divorce dumbbells;</li>
<li>Exercises using own weight: twisting, pulling on the bar, push-ups, sit-ups.</li>
</ul>


<p>It is advisable to go to the gym and worked under the guidance of coach as weight training require specific knowledge and skills. They help to achieve higher sports results while avoiding overtraining, injury and loss of motivation. Although the house is also possible to lose weight and be sure to purchase this post with a bench and dumbbells.</p>

<p>Women can also be used for weight loss weight training. It should be remembered that too much muscle hypertrophy, especially in the back and arms, will not make the figure more beautiful. Therefore, exercise must be carried out primarily at strengthening the muscles of the legs, buttocks, abdomen, chest.</p>

<p>Women weight training can achieve the following results:</p>

<ul>
<li>Make the legs more slender;</li>
<li>Become more confident, get rid of complexes.</li>
</ul>


<p>For successful weight loss is recommended for women to alternate weight training and cardio training. Catching weightlifting, girls can not build muscle as well as men. This prevents both hormones, and differences in the structure of the muscle fibers. Women have less endurance-they are not able to exercise for one to burn as many calories as men.</p>

<p>Optimum training schedule for weight loss:</p>

<ul>
<li>1-2 times a week - trip to the gym and doing exercises with dumbbells and barbell;</li>
<li>2-3 times a week - cardio training (bike, running, skating);</li>
<li>Every day - walking 30 minutes or more.</li>
</ul>


<p>Be aware of the need for dieting. Training usually increase the appetite, so you have to control your diet conscious.</p>

<p>Strength training may be used as a method of weight loss. It allows you to spend a lot of energy during exercise, temporarily speeds up the metabolism, it helps to build muscle mass. As a method of weight loss, strength training are more suited to men than to women, because the beauty of their figures is largely dependent on the amount of muscle. In addition, they have more stamina for regular and sustained exercise. Women desirable to combine strength training with cardio: running, training on a stationary bike, swimming, skating, aerobics.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corrective Underwear Abdomen and Waist]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/corrective-underwear-abdomen-and-waist/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-02T13:58:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/corrective-underwear-abdomen-and-waist</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/corrective-underwear-abdomen-and-waist/corrective-underwear-abdomen-and-waist.jpg" title="Corrective underwear abdomen and waist" alt="Corrective underwear abdomen and waist">Corrective underwear - is clothing for women, which hides figure flaws. More often than not buy it because of the extra weight. Corrective underwear hides fat folds, reduce the number of waist circumference, to give a figure more slender look. Some manufacturers of such clothing argue that it promotes weight loss or getting rid of cellulite, which is not true.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Linen can be of different types, depending on the problem area, where it will be used.</p>

<p>To improve the appearance of the abdomen is the best choice corsets, kombidressy, shorts with a high waist.</p>

<p>The main mechanism of action of corrective underwear abdomen and waist - is concealing folds of fat and improve body contours. Some unscrupulous manufacturers also indicate in the advertisement that the clothes by nanotechnology or massage promotes weight loss and improvement of women. It is not true.</p>

<p>Benefits of using corrective underwear, compared with the actual weight loss:</p>

<ul>
<li>Immediate effect - it does not need to wait for weeks or months;</li>
<li>You can quickly improve the figure before the holiday, corporate, date or an important business meeting.</li>
</ul>


<p>The disadvantages of using corrective underwear:</p>

<ul>
<li>There is no improvement of health;</li>
<li>There is no significant change in body contours - the effect is very moderate;</li>
<li>Uncomfortable to wear - underwear compresses the body.</li>
</ul>


<p>The correct choice of corrective underwear - this is very important as picking the wrong size, you can not improve, but on the contrary, visually impair the figure. Apart from the size, you should pay attention to:</p>

<ul>
<li>Fabric - Linen has slimming properties, and it should not lose elasticity after a few days of use;</li>
<li>An inner layer - underwear should be comfortable to wear, not to provoke sweating, do not rub the skin;</li>
<li>The thickness of the fabric - do not buy the warm summer corrective underwear;</li>
<li>The degree of tightening - if necessary, buy rigid correction underwear corset with black inserts and a silicone impregnation;</li>
<li>Absence of seams, which can be seen under clothing.</li>
</ul>


<p>Note that corrective underwear vendors often provide unreasonable promises about the results of its use. In particular, it is often argued that visually you reduce 2 sizes. That&rsquo;s not true, this effect is not possible. Reducing waist circumference will be minimal. The main purpose of corrective underwear - it is smoothing the contours of the body, rather than contraction.</p>

<p>It is not necessary to wear a corrective underwear abdomen and waist during pregnancy, damaged or rash on the skin at the site of the alleged contact with the tissue. It should not be too zealous in the use of such clothing. No need to wear it for too long and too often - it can negatively affect the skin condition. Exerting pressure on the body, corrective underwear thereby impairs blood circulation and may eventually worsen the appearance of cellulite.</p>

<p>Corrective underwear is designed to improve the appearance of women. It hides the fat folds, smoothing the contours of the body. This significant reduction in waist circumference does not occur. Shaping lingerie gives a temporary result. It can not be an alternative to weight loss and is not conducive to it. The clothes should be taken only in size. If it is less or more than you need, you can worsen rather than improve the appearance of the figure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tea Weight Loss Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/tea-weight-loss-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-02T09:53:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/tea-weight-loss-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/tea-weight-loss-diet/tea-weight-loss-diet.jpg" title="Tea weight loss diet" alt="Tea weight loss diet">Tea diet - it is a method of losing weight by drinking tea for several days. It is presented in different versions, and almost all of them are designed for rapid weight loss due to the complete failure of the food or the strong reduction of caloric intake. Estimated fat burning effect is achieved both through the restrictions in food, and because of the beneficial effects of tea on the figure.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The essence of the most popular tea diet is only one use of tea for 3 days. There are many versions of this diet where the drink is chosen black or green, used with or without sugar, restricted or permitted in any quantity.</p>

<p>There are varieties of tea diets designed for a longer period - 7 or 14 days, and some embodiments include, in addition to the use of beverage foodstuffs. But the most common is still a tea diet for 3 days. Its rules:</p>

<ul>
<li>The day you can drink six cups of tea;</li>
<li>Black tea should be taken - in which case an additional fat-burning effect is provided by the presence of caffeine in it;</li>
<li>Relies on a cup of tea spoon of sugar.</li>
</ul>


<p>This diet is too short to be able to talk about significant weight loss. Maybe it can help you get rid of 0.5 kg of fat per 3 days, but better results can hardly count. Although the scale, you will see more impressive numbers, in fact pitches due to a greater extent the devastation of the intestine, for you for three days without eating, although there continue to visit the toilet.</p>

<p>Positive aspects of the tea diet:</p>

<ol>
<li>Quick results. Tea diet can be used in cases where the 3 days you will visit an important event where you want to look a little better than it really is. Due to the devastation you have multiple bowel reduced belly, which will get into smaller clothes. But keep in mind that after the return of the form of diet, because the intestine is filled again.</li>
<li>With respect to good tolerability when compared to other diets generally do not provide meals. Lack of strong hunger is provided on one side of caffeine contained in tea leaves, on the other - sugar. It comes in small portions at regular intervals, thereby allowing time to time to reduce hunger by increasing the level of glucose in the blood.</li>
<li>A small duration. Tea diet is harmful to health. Well, it only lasts for 3 days. Perhaps, during this time you will not have time to earn gastritis and disrupt your metabolism.</li>
</ol>


<p>There is a diet in which the tea is used in conjunction with milk. It is believed that it itself has fat burning properties and impact positively on the figure even without dieting. But this is nothing more than rumors - milk tea has the same effect on weight, such as milk and tea, drunk alone.</p>

<p>Recipe tea with milk to the diet is very simple: take the tea leaves, place in a teapot, but does not fill with water as you usually do, and boiled milk.</p>

<p>There are plenty of diets based on the consumption of tea with milk. They mainly involve the reception throughout the day 1.5 liters of the drink without eating food. The difference lies in the duration. Sometimes diet offered to observe three days, sometimes - 5 or 7 days.</p>

<p>Some advise once a week to arrange a fasting day on milk and tea, and this option is the most preferred. It is not harmful to health, reduces the total number of calories consumed per week, and most importantly - constantly promotes weight loss and long-term, if you practice these regularly fasting days.</p>

<p>Most tea diets are stupid, harmful and ineffective. They come only to those who are on his body only 1-2 kg of excess weight. In this way, they can be quickly reset, and this is really hungry enough for only 3-4 days. All other tea diet, including the use of milk is not recommended because:</p>

<ul>
<li>The effect of these weak and temporary;</li>
<li>Such diets harmful to health;</li>
<li>A number of consecutive days, hungry and poorly tolerated at all discourage the human desire for further weight loss.</li>
</ul>


<p>Thus, from the tea diet can get more harm than good. Moreover, not only for health but also for the figure, because the diet with poor tolerability undermine motivation.</p>

<p>However, the above does not apply to schemes slimming day using the tea with sugar or milk. Fasting days on this drink once a week to help control weight. In combination with other measures aimed at reducing body weight, they contribute to the full normalization of the figure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alzheimers Disease Called Diabetes Brain]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/alzheimers-disease-called-diabetes-brain/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-14T21:50:22+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/alzheimers-disease-called-diabetes-brain</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It was found that the human brain has evolved in the direction of finding food that has a high amount of fat and sugar, but the advantage has arisen for survival in times of plenty deformed into an irresistible craving to self-destruct, according to New Scientist.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The link between Alzheimer&rsquo;s and diabetes in an article number in the printed edition. Title of the publication of &quot;Diabetes brain: the perfect food nightmare&quot;, carried on the cover of the magazine.</p>

<p>Obesity and diabetes is improper diet. New Scientist notes that &quot;in recent years become known to more and more data pointing to the identical nature of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease/" title="Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease">Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease</a>, and so some researchers regard this disease of neurodegeneration as another form of diabetes&quot;.</p>

<p>&quot;If this is indeed the case, then the relationship between these two diseases is simply disastrous consequences&quot;, - stated in the publication. &quot;Today the world is faced with an unprecedented epidemic of diabetes, and the prospect of a parallel epidemic of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease more terrible for the suffering that the disease causes to people and material costs really scared&quot;, the newspaper writes.</p>

<p>One way to prevent this threat, according to the New Scientist, - the intervention of lawyers. Earlier attempts had to prosecute companies that provide catering services, because they contribute to the <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a> epidemic. Now, if it is confirmed the causal link between the sweet, fatty foods with Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease, while the number of such claims will certainly rise, confident authors of the publication.
A little earlier, in the same year by 2 independent groups of researchers published the results of scientific experiments that show the relationship between changes in protein metabolism and insulin signaling pathway structures inherent in Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease - the appearance of amyloid plaques in neurons. Thus, it has been shown that increasing the concentration of the protein beta-amyloid, which is a cause of amyloid plaques occurs because of irregularities of the base level of activity of various molecules of insulin signaling pathway in the human brain.</p>

<p>The results of other experiments, was the idea that insulin resistance cells in the brain can be regarded as a characteristic early sign of the same Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease. This finding allowed scientists to classify conditionally neurodegenerative disease to diabetes of the third type.</p>

<p>The researchers predict that by 2015. Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease is able to hit about 115 million. people on the planet.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mortally Dangerous Dengue Fever Returns to Greece]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/mortally-dangerous-dengue-fever-returns-to-greece/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-14T21:47:43+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/mortally-dangerous-dengue-fever-returns-to-greece</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In Greece, the old man died, presumably from a forgotten dengue. This is the first recorded human cases of dengue in Greece, more than 80 in recent years, the country&rsquo;s health authorities reported.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The man, whose age was more than 80 years, died in late August. According to the Hellenic Centre for Disease Control, the man developed severe kind of infamous <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/dengue-fever.html" title="dengue fever">dengue fever</a>, which is almost always accompanied by a hemorrhagic syndrome.</p>

<p>Now tests are made to determine whether other people are infected.</p>

<p>Recall that the dengue <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/fever.html" title="fever">fever</a> in Greece was defeated after the epidemic of 1920. She later reappeared in Europe, which has entered the Asian tiger mosquito. Several cases of the disease recorded in 2010 in France and Croatia.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Government Is Struggling With Obesity Among Lesbians]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/the-us-government-is-struggling-with-obesity-among-lesbians/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-14T21:44:06+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/the-us-government-is-struggling-with-obesity-among-lesbians</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>According to studies by the National Institutes of Health, three-quarters of lesbians in the United States are overweight. As noted in the publication of Daily Mail, the Institute for research and study of the relationship between <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a> and sexual orientation of the patient from the US budget allocated about half a million dollars.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The grant, the award of the National Institute of Health noted that the study of the issue of obesity among lesbian women, compared with gay men is crucial for health.</p>

<p>The researchers emphasize that previously none of the scientists did not address the issue. However, they managed to find out that women with a different sexual orientation are disproportionately affected by the epidemic of obesity that will allow physicians not only to study the problem and find a way out of it.</p>

<p>The entire project is designed for five years, but the first findings are expected to receive within three years, they have developed a strategy to include the fight against obesity among women or lesbians.</p>

<p>Who led the study will be the director of the medical center, and a professor at Harvard Medical University, Bryn Austin.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Scientists Named Apricot Most Valuable in the World of Fruit]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/scchinese-scientists-named-apricot-most-valuable-in-the-world-of-fruit/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-14T21:40:26+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/scchinese-scientists-named-apricot-most-valuable-in-the-world-of-fruit</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Researchers in China conducted a large-scale testing of different fruits with the aim to find out which of them is not only delicious, but also the most useful and vitamins. The first contest took place in the apricot.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>This fragrant and sweet fruit has a very positive effect on the cardiovascular system and helps the human heart. In addition, the regular use of apricot help in the prevention of many diseases. The fact is that the apricot contains large amounts of potassium and potassium, is known to play a crucial role in the healthy functioning of the cardiovascular system. In addition, potassium helps rid the body of harmful toxins, and normalizes blood pressure in the arteries.</p>

<p>Scientists have noted that most needed potassium and iron, which are contained in apricots and dried apricots, during <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a> and lactation. Eating a little bit of dried apricots every day, pregnant or nursing mother fill the lack of mineral salts in the body, improve metabolism and make bones strong.</p>

<p>It is also recommended to regularly feast on fresh apricots people who suffer from diseases of the cardiovascular system. Dried apricots also help with poor circulation, reduced cardiac arrhythmia and eventually are an excellent preventive measure against heart attack.</p>

<p>Apricots contains vitamins and <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/solar-capsules-beta-carotene-to-better-tan/" title="beta-carotene">beta-carotene</a>, which help fight <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/" title="infectious diseases">infectious diseases</a> and even cancer diseases. So include in your diet apricots, moreover, that during Lent she will help the body to get enough vitamins and not to succumb to the spring beriberi.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists Have Questioned the Benefits of Organic Products]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/scientists-have-questioned-the-benefits-of-organic-products/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-14T21:31:53+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/scientists-have-questioned-the-benefits-of-organic-products</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Organic food is no longer useful and safe for human health than the ordinary. To this conclusion was reached by researchers from Stanford University (USA), after an analysis of 240 publications, which have been devoted to food that have appeared in the scientific literature since 1966. The work group was headed by Dan Bravat, it has become the most extensive research in this area, and was published September 4 in the journal Annals of Internal Medicine.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The so-called organic food - food is grown without the use of pesticides, antibiotics, hormones, etc. - Positioned as much more useful and safer than usual because it is more pure and contains more vitamins, minerals and other nutrients. Organic foods are sometimes almost twice as expensive as products grown using traditional methods, but, despite this, their popularity, especially among the population of developed countries has multiplied over the past decade. For example, in the United States since 1997. by 2011. organic food market has increased from $3600000000 to $24400000000.</p>

<p>To confirm or refute the thesis regarding the significant advantage of one of two types of food over another, the authors conducted a systematic study of the results of 240 reports. 223 of these reports were devoted to a comparison grown by organic or conventional fruits, grains, vegetables, meat, eggs and milk on the content of trace elements, fungal and bacterial contamination and pesticide. The remaining 17 publications covered the health indicators in the context of food consumed. Fully entire array analyzed data published in the scientific literature since January 1966.</p>

<p>The only significant advantage over conventional organ`ic products, in terms of their content of vitamins and minerals, was a higher content of phosphorus, which, according to the authors, can be very useful for people who suffer a deficit of this trace element.</p>

<p>As vitamins, and other beneficial agents for humans, there is clinically significant for human health differences were found. Thus, the authors note that protein and fat composition of organic and ordinary milk were approximately the same, although in some publications and held assumption that organic milk may contain higher amounts of unsaturated fatty acids.</p>

<p>Also, the authors found no convincing evidence that conventional food is much more harmful to health than organic. However, the latter, with 30% less likely contaminated with pesticides than usual, although they can not be called completely free of toxic chemicals. In addition, this difference is hardly noticeable in the case of exceeding the shelf life of products. As bacterial contamination indicators are also approximately equal. The authors suggest that the use of organic chicken and pork reduces the risk of developing resistance to antibiotics, and note that the clinical evidence of this assumption does not exist.</p>

<p>Commenting on the results, the authors noted that they could easily affect the heterogeneity of research methods used in the studies, as well as various factors that affect the safety and quality of products, such as weather, soil composition, methods of farming, etc.
It should be noted that the conclusions made by experts at Stanford University, the same, in general, the results of a study conducted by scientists at the London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine in 2009.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alcohol and Energy Drinks: Bad Combination]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/alcohol-and-energy-drinks-bad-combination/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-27T14:57:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/alcohol-and-energy-drinks-bad-combination</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/alcohol-and-energy-drinks-bad-combination/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="alcohol energy drinks" alt="Alcohol and energy drinks: bad combination"><strong>This is not the first time that energy drinks are singled out, especially in alcoholic evenings.</strong></p>




<p>A new Australian study confirms these fears of dangerous liaisons&hellip;</p>




<!--more-->




<h2>Overconsumption of alcohol</h2>




<p>For the purposes of the study, seventy five young people aged 18 to 30 were invited to drink cocktails in the context of a party held in a laboratory: they received either 60 ml of a mixture Vodka &ndash; Red Bull, 60 ml of a mixture Vodka &ndash; carbonated water, plus 200 ml of a fruit drink in each of these mixtures. Nobody knew what he received as a beverage, but people with the habit of consuming energy drinks have easily recognized. Young also had to take a test and complete questionnaires on which researchers have relied.</p>




<p><strong>It is clear from this experience that those receiving alcohol cocktail with energy drinks were also those who were more inclined to continue to drink alcohol.</strong></p>




<p>However, all is not taken action, some arriving to reason&hellip;</p>




<h2>A trap for the most vulnerable?</h2>




<p>The fact that all those who received the alcohol cocktails and energy drinks, have not drank more than others even if they had more desire can reassure this proves that it is always possible not to succumb! However, proving that the desire to drink alcohol is increased by energy drinks, this study suggests also fear that the most vulnerable to alcohol people have trouble resisting. Indeed, we are not equal face the risk of addiction. And vulnerable people often have trouble recognizing they have a problem with alcohol, because they may very well do without alcohol for several days in a row. This is true, but can not help but consume much always in identical circumstances (such as partying with friends) shows that there is already a problem and it is time to talk to his doctor!</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[38% of Americans Have a Child Who Suffers From an Allergy]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/38-percent-of-americans-have-a-child-who-suffers-from-an-allergy/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-26T13:36:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/38-percent-of-americans-have-a-child-who-suffers-from-an-allergy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/38-percent-of-americans-have-a-child-who-suffers-from-an-allergy/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="allergy, allergic child" alt="38% of Americans have a child who suffers from an allergy">The results of the FIFG/Stallergenes Foundation study revealed that 38% of Americans have a child who suffers from allergies.</p>




<p><strong>Among these allergic children, 28% suffer from respiratory allergies, 12% develop food allergies and 12% of drug allergies.</strong></p>




<p>This is more than 1 in 3 children.</p>




<!--more-->




<h2>Allergies strong growth</h2>




<p>&ldquo;Children are a slice of the population at risk because more sensitive to allergens, chemicals as well as viral infections&rdquo; explains Dr. Pham Thi Nhan, allergist, pneumo-pediatrician, Necker Hospital &ndash; Sick Children, New York.</p>




<p>According to the results of the FIFG/Stallergenes Foundation study, 94% of Americans believe that there are more allergies now than in the past. Confirmed by a WHO felt. In France, from 25 to 30% of people suffer from allergies, or double the number 20 years ago, particularly among children and adolescents. More worryingly, the WHO predicts that by 2050, 1 in 2 will be allergic in the world. &ldquo;It is known that severe cases of allergies are increasing worldwide. This is not only due to a more accurate diagnosis but phenomena that progress in the population&rdquo;, declare the allergist.</p>




<p>What are the factors responsible for the increase in allergies?</p>




<ul>
<li>73% of Americans people point the finger at pollution;</li>
<li>34% pesticide use;</li>
<li>28% changes in supply mode;</li>
<li>25% overprotection of infants;</li>
<li>22% increase in awareness of the organization;</li>
<li>18% climate change.</li>
</ul>




<p>&ldquo;Pollution is a co-precipitant and aggravating allergies: it increases our sensitivity and our susceptibility to the environment and therefore increases the risk of developing allergies. When pollution peaks in March, we have seen an impressive number of allergies: new cases and cases of severe rhino<a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/ophthalmology/conjunctivitis.html" title="conjunctivitis">conjunctivitis</a> including pollens, excluding asthma attacks. The days that followed pollution peaks, the number of health care utilization has risen sharply&rdquo;, says Dr. Nhan Pham Thi.</p>




<h2>Good reflexes to reduce allergens</h2>




<p>In addition to the necessary consultation with a specialist and the establishment of appropriate treatment following the allergen to which the child is sensitive, simple steps can significantly reduce the impact of respiratory allergies.</p>




<p>It is recommended that parents of children with respiratory allergies:</p>




<ul>
<li>ventilate the room (84%);</li>
<li>do not put carpet (69%);</li>
<li>to regularly clean (62%);</li>
<li>do not use a pillow or feather duvet (52%);</li>
<li>to avoid contact with dogs/cats (32%);</li>
<li>not to houseplants or some trees in the garden (30%).</li>
</ul>




<p>&ldquo;Patient education is a mainstay of treatment that allows to change lifestyle to adapt to his new state of sensitivity requires support chronic and often long if not life treatment. A food allergic must learn to avoid food and control its aid kit. For a child with chronic rhinitis, nasal care are needed daily. Finally, asthma, adherence background is essential&rdquo; said Dr. Pham Thi Nhan.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[1.5 Million Died of AIDS in 2013: A Figure Much Lower]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/1-dot-5-million-died-of-aids-in-2013-a-figure-much-lower/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-25T10:59:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/1-dot-5-million-died-of-aids-in-2013-a-figure-much-lower</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/15-million-died-of-aids-in-2013-a-figure-much-lower/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="AIDS deaths" alt="1.5 million died of AIDS in 2013: a figure much lower"><strong>According to the 2013 report on the <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/aids.html" title="AIDS">AIDS</a> epidemic recently published UNAIDS, the number of deaths due to AIDS for the first time dropped significantly.</strong></p>




<p><strong>However, the number of people living with HIV has increased slightly.</strong></p>




<!--more-->




<h2>Very sharp decrease in the number of people who died of AIDS in 2013</h2>




<p>The results of UNAIDS published in July 2014 indicates that 1.5 million people died of AIDS in 2013, against 1.7 million in 2012, a decrease of 11.8% in a year, the highest drop recorded since the peak of the epidemic in 2005.</p>




<p><strong>In total, ten years, deaths from AIDS have declined by 35%.</strong></p>




<p>Regarding people worldwide with HIV, their number increased slightly, rising to 35 million today, against 34.6 million the previous year. That said, since 2005, there has been a decrease of 33%.</p>




<h2>New infections also fall</h2>




<p><strong>The number of people newly infected each year with HIV continues to fall:</strong> 2.1 million in 2013, against 2.2 million in 2012. But since 2001, new HIV infections have fallen by 38%.</p>




<p><strong>Children born with the AIDS virus are also decreasing:</strong> 240,000 in 2013 against 270,000 in 2012, a decrease of 27.6% since 2005.</p>




<p><strong>The most affected region is sub-Saharan Africa</strong> (South Africa and Nigeria in particular): 70.8% of those affected and still predominantly women (58%). In this part of the world totalling 1.1 million people died of AIDS, 24.7 million people living with HIV, including 2.9 million children.</p>




<p>To this day still, 22 million people have no access to treatment. 38% of adults have, against 24% of children.</p>




<p>Finally, $19.1 billion (14 billion euros) were made available in 2013, against 18.9 million in 2012 and $4.6 billion 10 years ago.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hydronephrosis: Symptoms Diagnosis Treatment]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/hydronephrosis-symptoms-diagnosis-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-24T00:16:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/hydronephrosis-symptoms-diagnosis-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/hydronephrosis-symptoms-diagnosis-treatment/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="urology, hydronephrosis, hydronephrosis symptoms, diagnosis of hydronephrosis, hydronephrosis treatment, treatment of hydronephrosis, renal tissue thinning, accumulation of urine in the renal pelvis, reduced kidney function" alt="Hydronephrosis: Symptoms, Diagnosis, Treatment">The disease is caused by violation of the outflow of urine from the kidneys, resulting in the pelvis and calices increased hydrostatic pressure.</p>




<p>Allocate congenital hydronephrosis and acquired. Moreover, the disease has three stages. The first stage is characterized by compensated or negligible accumulation of urine in the renal pelvis and its small stretch. At this stage, the kidney function is preserved. In the second stage, the thinning of kidney tissue, while its function is substantially reduced. For the third or end-stage hydronephrosis characterized by a complete shutdown of the affected kidney.</p>




<!--more-->




<h2>Symptoms of hydronephrosis</h2>




<p>It often happens that the onset of the disease goes unnoticed. Hydronephrosis has no specific symptoms, so at an early stage due to the cause of symptoms that it caused. For example, in urolithiasis may cause attacks of renal colic, which are characterized by acute severe pain along the ureter. Sometimes the only symptom of the disease is haematuria (blood in the urine). This symptom is also characteristic of those cases where there was hydronephrosis on the background of urolithiasis.</p>




<p>The most stable sign of hydronephrosis &ndash; a constant aching pain blunt nature. Pain can arise in this case irrespective of the position of the body or time of day. Localization of pain right or left depending on which kidney affected. On the background of painful episodes occasionally occur bloating, nausea, vomiting, increased blood pressure. Upon accession of infection increases body temperature.</p>




<p>With the development of end-stage hydronephrosis, especially bilateral, have symptoms of chronic renal failure. This decreases the amount of urine, appear edema, hypertension.</p>




<h2>Diagnosis of hydronephrosis</h2>




<p>During the visual inspection and palpation with hydronephrosis doctor can detect swelling and deformation of the lumbar region. In order to diagnose this disease conducted laboratory analyzes: urinalysis, complete blood count, tests for Nichiporenko and Zimnitskiy and other.</p>




<p>From instrumental diagnostic methods performed with hydronephrosis renal ultrasound, which allows to define the extension pyelocaliceal complex, increasing the kidney, as well as to measure the thickness of the renal parenchyma.</p>




<p>Appointed radiography &ndash; it is the main method of diagnosis of hydronephrosis. Survey radiography reveals stones, determine the size of the kidneys. Intravenous urography contrast, a series of images, determines the rate of formation of urine and its excretion. When hydronephrosis has slowed revenue contrast agents in renal pelvis complex expansion cups and pelvis, which acquire rounded contours. End-stage hydronephrosis contrast can not come to the affected kidney. Occasionally you can discover the nature and level of patency of the urinary tract.</p>




<p>To characterize the extent of damage to each kidney is assigned radioisotope urography. To clarify the diagnosis in difficult cases used angiography, magnetic resonance and computed tomography.</p>




<h2>Treatment of hydronephrosis</h2>




<p>Correctly chosen and spent treatment helps to compensate for the state and improve kidney function. The main goal of therapy &ndash; the elimination of the cause of the hydronephrosis. In each case, except for cause, you must also consider the degree of hydronephrosis and the pace of its development. When hydronephrosis can be carried out medical and surgical treatments.</p>




<p>Conservative treatment for symptomatic hydronephrosis and used at an early stage of the disease. Depending on the symptom such therapy includes anti-inflammatory, anti-hypertensive, and other painkillers. Upon accession infection antibiotics are shown. Typically, conservative therapy precedes operation.</p>




<p>When hydronephrosis in most cases surgery is shown. It is performed to eliminate the causes of illness and recover kidney. Better to do the operation in the early stages of the disease (in particular, congenital anomalies) when still reversible kidney changes. Surgical therapy includes renewal patency of the urinary tract, and terminally ill &ndash; plastic pelvis, the restoration of its size. By removal of the affected kidney resort exclusively in advanced cases, when the organ has completely lost its function and its preservation may cause inflammatory complications.</p>




<p>Efficacy of hydronephrosis depends on the stage of the disease. Hydronephrosis &ndash; a serious pathology, but timely diagnosis and appropriate treatment given to help maintain and improve the health.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meaning Barium Enema in the Diagnosis of Diseases of the Large Intestine]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/meaning-barium-enema-in-the-diagnosis-of-diseases-of-the-large-intestine/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-22T23:56:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/meaning-barium-enema-in-the-diagnosis-of-diseases-of-the-large-intestine</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/meaning-barium-enema-in-the-diagnosis-of-diseases-of-the-large-intestine/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="s colitis, tumor, polyp" alt="Meaning barium enema in the diagnosis of diseases of the large intestine">Irrigoscopy &ndash; one of radiological methods of investigation of the colon using a radiopaque substance. Barium enema is performed after the introduction into the rectum of barium sulfate (contrast material) or barium suspension in combination with air (double contrast method).</p>




<p>Double contrast reveals the small size of the tumor, particularly polyps and mucosal changes that occur in the early stages of inflammatory diseases of the large intestine.</p>




<!--more-->




<p>With the barium enema can be visualized colon almost an entire length, but for the most effective research rectosigmoid zone applies sigmoidoscopy.</p>




<p>Irrigoscopy not performed after radiographic contrast studies of the upper gastrointestinal tract. Used with barium is excreted within a few days, and the remnants of this substance may distort the results irrigoscopy.</p>




<h2>The information that can be accessed by barium enema</h2>




<p>During the barium enema doctor receives the following information about the patient&rsquo;s colon:</p>




<ul>
<li>The location, shape and diameter of the colon;</li>
<li>The degree of extensibility and flexibility of the intestinal wall;</li>
<li>Define the function bauginievoy flap. Bauginievaya flap &ndash; is a fold, which is located between the ileum and colon. Normally bauginievaya damper must pass the intestinal contents in only one direction (from the small intestine into the large), but there may be a violation of the intestinal contents throw in the opposite direction. Movement in contrast barium enema shows clearly whether there are irregularities in the bauginievoy flap;</li>
<li>Relief mucosa of the colon walls. This indicator is particularly important in the diagnosis of ulcerative lesions of the bowel, fistulas, tumors, diverticulosis, scars and congenital malformations;</li>
<li>Functional state departments of large intestine.</li>
</ul>




<h2>Why is it important to conduct irrigoscopy?</h2>




<p>As a rule, barium enema is used to confirm the diagnosis in suspected those or other diseases of the colon. Barium enema is often decisive diagnostic method for tumors and colon diverticula.</p>




<p>During the barium enema using the technique of double -contrast study diagnostic capabilities are significantly increased. With barium enema can indirectly confirm the presence of diseases such as colitis and tuberculosis.</p>




<h2>Which diseases carried irrigoscopy?</h2>




<p>When irrigoscopy estimated rate of change of the intestinal mucosa in ulcerative colitis, Crohn&rsquo;s disease, as well as visualized tumors, fistulas, malformations and diverticula.</p>




<p>Unlike colonoscopy, barium enema and less traumatic and less likely to cause complications. Furthermore, barium enema is possible to investigate with the &ldquo;blind&rdquo; to the field of colonoscopy, for example, portions in the folds of the mucosa, and also bends in the colon and the sigmoid colon.</p>




<p>Application irrigoscopy shown if the patient following symptoms:</p>




<ul>
<li>Bleeding from the rectum;</li>
<li>Mucous or purulent discharge from the intestines;</li>
<li>Pain in the anus and in the course of the colon;</li>
<li>Chronic disorder stool (constipation or diarrhea).</li>
</ul>




<h2>How is barium enema?</h2>




<p>Barium enema is performed in a specially equipped medical facility office. A few days before the scheduled study patient should prepare for barium enema. Must be made within 3-4 days follow a special cleansing diet and the use of additional methods for bowel cleansing. This patient doctor tells in detail.</p>




<p>Before the study, the patient is laid down on the couch on its side. In the anus enema tip is introduced, which contains a radiopaque substance. In the future, under fluoroscopy intestines filled contrast agents and conduct a series of reviews and sighting shots in different positions of the patient.</p>




<p>After emptying of barium mixture is produced as air filling bowel under fluoroscopy. So can investigate the organic and functional disorders of the intestinal wall.</p>




<p>Duration of the procedure is a few minutes. During double contrast examination may take 30 to 40 minutes.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genital Herpes: 4 Out of 5 Patients Unaware of Being Infected With This Virus]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/genital-herpes-4-out-of-5-patients-unaware-of-being-infected-with-this-virus/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-22T23:50:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/genital-herpes-4-out-of-5-patients-unaware-of-being-infected-with-this-virus</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/genital-herpes-4-out-of-5-patients-unaware-of-being-infected-with-this-virus/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="herpes, genital herpes" alt="Genital herpes : 4 out of 5 patients unaware of being infected with this virus!">Two million americans are affected by the virus that causes <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/genital-herpes.html" title="genital herpes">genital herpes</a>.
Worse, four out of five do not know! In side The drug prescription information and patient education are therefore key stages of care.</p>




<!--more-->




<h2>Herpes types</h2>




<p><strong>Herpes labialis</strong>
He is responsible for cold sores. Frequent, nearly 10 million americans suffer at least one thrust per year. It preferentially affects women (3 women to 2 men).</p>




<p><strong>Genital herpes</strong>
Number of herpes infection carriers subjects estimated 2 million against only 350,000 cases diagnosed! Thus, four out of five are unaware of being infected.</p>




<h2>An impaired life quality</h2>




<p>Genital herpes diagnosis is often difficult because of the lesions diversity or too late consultation and outside attacks. However, the impact on quality of life is very important.</p>




<p>Patients are afraid to have sex because of pain or disease transmitting fear. They are 34% to easily manage their social life and 33% have <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/depression.html" title="depression">depression</a>.</p>




<p>However, drug treatments exist.</p>




<h2>A little known illness surrounded by taboos</h2>




<p>It is necessary to open the dialogue and break the taboos surrounding this little known disease patients. As well as medication, inform and educate patients is an management integral part. Contamination must be explained, as well as the potential for treatment to facilitate compliance. This stops the immediate effect in virus replication, pain and shortens the surge duration, but virus remains in body.</p>




<p><strong>Infection is severe in late <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a></strong>
In addition, this infection can be very serious in late pregnancy. It entails a neonatal infection risk (1-2 cases per 100,000 births), the consequences can be serious for infants if treatment is not started quickly.</p>




<h2>How to prevent transmission  herpes virus?</h2>




<p>During a herpes outbreak:</p>




<ul>
<li>Wash hands after touching the lesions and do not scratch the lesions.</li>
<li>Do not share his towels.</li>
<li>Avoid sexual intercourse, even protected by a condom.</li>
<li>Avoid physical contact with newborns, pregnant women, people with skin lesions (eczema, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/psoriasis.html" title="psoriasis">psoriasis</a>, etc.)., Immunocompromised individuals (AIDS, organ transplant, chemotherapy).</li>
</ul>




<p>Outside breakouts, use a condom if the partner has never come into contact with the herpes virus.</p>




<p>In case of herpes labialis (cold sores) to avoid oral-genital sex (sex/mouth) because this virus on the lips can be transmitted to the partner genitals.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fungus Toenails. Onychomycosis]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/fungus-toenails-onychomycosis/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-21T09:30:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/fungus-toenails-onychomycosis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/fungus-toenails-onychomycosis/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="nail fungus, fungus toenails, onychomycosis" alt="Fungus toenails, onychomycosis">If you find they thicken, become brittle, change color, check out quickly.</p>




<p>The fungus toenails is extremely contagious and can lead to the loss of the nail, then there are effective treatments.</p>




<!--more-->




<h2>The fungus toenails is common</h2>




<p>The fungus toenails is common and transmissible. It affects 3-10% of the French population. Professionals use the term of onychomycosis, which designates a nail infection caused by fungi of three kinds (dermatophytes, yeasts Candida, molds).</p>




<h2>First signs of a nail fungus</h2>




<p>The infection settles slowly. It reaches first the skin between the toes forming a fissure that does not heal. Gradually, the nail is reached. It thickens, crumbles, changes color (yellow or white spots) and becomes painful. In the absence of treatment, it may peel off.</p>




<h2>What are the risk factors for nail fungus?</h2>




<p>Older age, male sex, sports, trauma and repeated injury, a humid environment and certain diseases (bone and joint diseases, diabetes, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>, peripheral <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/vascular-disease/" title="vascular disease">vascular disease</a>, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/psoriasis.html" title="psoriasis">psoriasis</a>?).</p>




<p>The infection is caught easily in collective public places humid and warm where you walk barefoot (pool, sauna, dance halls, dressing rooms, etc..).</p>




<p>You can also pass the family, walking barefoot on the carpet, suitable slippers or in the bathroom, including towels or nail clippers. Maceration in shoes, especially sport shoes or boots, is also a major risk factor. Also predispose strain nails or toes that overlap (common in older people).</p>




<h2>In case of nail fungus, early treatment is essential</h2>




<p>A <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nail-fungus-fungal-nail-disease-symptoms-and-prevention/" title="nail fungus">nail fungus</a> does not heal on its own and instead risk spreading to other nails.</p>




<p>Similarly, the more care is delayed, the more healing is long and difficult. Hence the importance of regularly inspecting her nails, especially if you are part of those at risk.</p>




<p>At the slightest anomaly, talk to your doctor.</p>




<p>A sample of the nail for a mycological examination is necessary to identify the fungus cause and prescribe the appropriate antifungal therapy. Depending on the degree of achievement of the nail, it will be local (application of a varnish) and/or oral. However, be patient and be sure to follow your doctor&rsquo;s instructions. Indeed, the treatment is long (often more than 6 months), as the nail grows very slowly.</p>




<h2>Tips to avoid a nail fungus</h2>




<ul>
<li>Systematically and thoroughly dry your feet, especially between each toe.</li>
<li>Avoid walking barefoot.</li>
<li>Wear personal sandals by the pool, in the locker room&hellip;</li>
<li>Do not lend your slippers.</li>
<li>Do not pay either your towel.</li>
<li>Disinfect with alcohol scissors, nail files and nail clippers used for toenails.</li>
<li>Cut your toe nails short and straight.</li>
<li>Limit wearing sneakers your physical activity.</li>
<li>Wear leather shoes, which limit maceration.</li>
<li>Avoid tight shoes, too tightly in plastic.</li>
<li>Try not to your shoes, especially sport.</li>
<li>Adopt cotton socks, especially for sports.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect From Alzheimer's Disease?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-20T12:21:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="s disease" alt="How to protect from Alzheimer">We&rsquo;ve all heard that stimulate our brain functions, including intellectual could protect us from Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>




<p>Thus, crosswords and all kinds of learning are recommended.</p>




<p>Today, studies suggest that there are other protective factors.
Was even identified risk factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease&hellip; And it appears that we could halve the number of people affected.</p>




<!--more-->




<h2>Alzheimer&rsquo;s, prevent long as we do not know how to cure</h2>




<p>The research was mobilized for years to develop treatments that will cure Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease. Similarly, researchers are busy around prevention. An analysis of all publications focused on this subject gave particularly interesting results.</p>




<p>In fact, risk factors and protective factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease have been identified.</p>




<p>The good news is that all are modifiable, meaning that acting on each of these factors could reduce by half the number of people affected by Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>




<h2>6 risk factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease</h2>




<ul>
<li>Diabetes;</li>
<li>Excess <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a> in midlife;</li>
<li>Smoking.</li>
</ul>




<p>But another study points 3 other additional risk factors (1)</p>




<ul>
<li>Hypertension;</li>
<li>Obesity;</li>
<li>Depression.</li>
</ul>




<h2>5 of protective factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease</h2>




<ul>
<li>The Mediterranean diet;</li>
<li>The folic acid or vitamin B9;</li>
<li>Low or moderate alcohol consumption;</li>
<li>Cognitive activities;</li>
<li>Physical activity.</li>
</ul>




<p>For example, diabetes increases the risk of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease by 39%. Knowing that 6% of the world population is affected by diabetes, the disease is alone responsible for 2% of cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>




<p>Another example, physical inactivity increases the risk of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease by 82%. If we consider that 18% of the world population is physically inactive, sedentary lifestyle is responsible for 13% of cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>




<p>Smoking increases the risk of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease by 59%. If we consider that 27% of the population smokes, smoking is responsible for 14% of cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>




<p>Finally, knowing that many of these factors are related, act on one of them can simultaneously have a significant impact on others. <strong>For example, by acting only on physical inactivity, can simultaneously reduce the risk of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/cardiology/hypertension.html" title="hypertension">hypertension</a> and diabetes&hellip;</strong></p>




<p><strong>You can see that all these factors are modifiable. In other words, we can all take action and protect us from Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</strong></p>




<p>Thus, nearly half of the cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease could be prevented by modifying these factors.</p>




<p>Recall that in the world, the number of people affected by Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease is estimated at 34 million. In USA, the figure is estimated at nearly 1 million. In the current absence of treatment to cure this disease, prevention is a huge challenge.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anorexia and Bulimia]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/anorexia-and-bulimia/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-19T13:15:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/anorexia-and-bulimia</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/anorexia-and-bulimia/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="anorexia, bulimia, eating behavior, eating disorder, eating, restrictions on food, diet" alt="Anorexia and bulimia">Anorexia &ndash; a pathological condition in which there was a complete lack of appetite in the presence of the objective necessity of the body in the diet. Anorexia may occur due to various reasons, such as parasitic infestations and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/" title="infectious diseases">infectious diseases</a>, diseases of the digestive system. Usually considered separately anorexia nervosa.</p>




<!--more-->




<p>Anorexia nervosa is an eating disorder in which a person willfully refuses to eat for weight loss purposes. This disease occurs more often in girls. Nevertheless, it can be observed not only in the young, but also in adulthood, both women and men.</p>




<p>Anorexia nervosa is characterized by the occurrence of a pathological desire to lose weight, which is accompanied by the development of intense fear of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>. People suffering from anorexia, there is distortion of the own body, there is a concern about weight gain, even if in reality it is not marked. The causes of anorexia are divided into psychological (internal conflicts, the impact of the family), biological (genetic predisposition) and social (the impact of society &ndash; popular diets imitation idols).</p>




<p>Anorexia is phasing flow &ndash; isolated dismorfomanicheskuyu, anorectic and cachectic stage. The first stage &ndash; dismorfomanicheskaya &ndash; characterized by the emergence of thoughts of inferiority because of imaginary completeness. In this patient develops anxiety, depressed mood, he sees himself in the long mirror. Also at this stage following the first attempt to limit in food.</p>




<p>In the second stage the patient has resorted to a strict diet and grueling physical <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a>. However, he loses much weight, but does not stop fasting, since it can not objectively assess the degree of weight loss. Due to continuous malnutrition occur in the body pathological reactions. There are features such as <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/hair-loss.html" title="hair loss">hair loss</a>, dry skin, decreased sexual desire, syncope, arrhythmia, stomach pain, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/constipation.html" title="constipation">constipation</a>, nausea, and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/depression.html" title="depression">depression</a>. Infertility occurs: women due to amenorrhea (cessation of menstruation), men &ndash; due to the suppression of spermatogenesis.</p>




<p>Body weight of the patient has been steadily declining in the body degenerative changes occur, and there comes a cachectic period. This stage usually develops anorexia after two years of onset. Pathological changes in the body leads to irreversible inhibition of the functions of all organs and systems, and result in death. In connection with this incessant flow and severe consequences, anorexia is a serious disease that requires mandatory treatment.</p>




<h2>Bulimia</h2>




<p>Another uncommon <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/eating-disorders.html" title="eating disorders">eating disorders</a> is <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/bulimia.html" title="bulimia">bulimia</a>. Bulimia occurs due to mental disorders, diseases of the endocrine and central nervous systems. This pathology often leads to obesity.</p>




<p>Bulimia nervosa is characterized by sudden significant increase in appetite, feeling really hungry. Typically, bulimia occurs in the form of attacks or last time. Seizures are characterized by the absorption of huge amounts of food. They can occur suddenly or develop at a certain time (eg at night).</p>




<p>People with bulimia often resorted to the use of laxatives and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/vomiting.html" title="vomiting">vomiting</a> to control weight. However, the use of large amounts of food and the subsequent forced cleaning of the stomach cause severe complications.</p>




<p>Bulimia can develop independently or arise against the background of anorexia nervosa. As people with anorexia and bulimia patients control their weight become the overriding purpose in life. Bulimia, emerged against the background of anorexia nervosa is characterized by periodic episodes of binge eating occurrence that alternate periods of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/starvation.html" title="starvation">starvation</a>. During these episodes the patient will eat huge amounts of food in a short time, while he usually swallows food without chewing. Typically, after a bout of bulimia patient vomits or takes large amounts of diuretics or laxatives, not thinking about the consequences for your health.</p>




<p>Bulimia and anorexia are life-threatening conditions, so people suffering from these diseases, needs appropriate treatment. Unfortunately, patients are often hospitalized for anorexia able drastic depletion, whereas in the early treatment of the disease can be performed on an outpatient basis. It must be remembered that the earlier therapeutic interventions will be carried out, the less the risk of irreversible changes.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crohn's Disease: What Are Symptoms?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/crohns-disease-what-are-symptoms/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-18T10:47:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/crohns-disease-what-are-symptoms</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/crohns-disease-what-are-symptoms/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="s disease causes, and colon, from anus" alt="Crohn"><strong>In USA, there are 120,000 people with Crohn&rsquo;s disease, both men and women.</strong></p>




<blockquote><p>Each year 4-5 new cases per 100,000 are diagnosed.
<strong>Crohn&rsquo;s disease causes chronic inflammation of digestive system. Any segment of the gastrointestinal tract may be affected, from anus esophagus. But more often, it is bowel that is achieved by inflammation: colon, small intestine terminal portion.</strong></p></blockquote>




<!--more-->




<p>Illness progresses in spurts interspersed with remission periods.</p>




<p>Signs are mainly gastrointestinal, but not only, depend on the segments achieved location.</p>




<h2>In Crohn&rsquo;s disease, the symptoms are mostly gastrointestinal</h2>




<p><strong>Crohn&rsquo;s disease causes:</strong></p>




<ul>
<li>Anal pain (fistulas, abscesses).</li>
<li>An issue of blood or mucus from anus.</li>
<li>Abdominal pain (sometimes very strong up to think appendicitis).</li>
<li>There may be heavy, watery diarrhea.</li>
<li>Nausea, vomiting.</li>
</ul>




<blockquote><p>These digestive symptoms lead to poor general condition: fatigue, loss of appetite, weight loss with faltering growth in children and adolescents, fever, paleness, breathlessness due to a anemia risk and vitamin B12 deficiency.</p></blockquote>




<h2>Other non-digestive signs&hellip;</h2>




<p><strong>Crohn&rsquo;s disease can also cause other symptoms as digestive, including joint, skin and eye.</strong></p>




<ul>
<li>Articular rheumatism: ankylosing spondylitis&hellip;</li>
<li>Dermatological disorders: ulcers, erythema nodosum&hellip;</li>
<li>Ocular: uveitis&hellip;</li>
</ul>




<p>It is estimated that these extraintestinal manifestations affect one third of patients during their illness. Knowing they can appear before the gastrointestinal signs, they should be considered as warning signs to get see.</p>




<h2>Crohn&rsquo;s disease Diagnosis and treatment</h2>




<p><strong>Diagnosis is based on examination and in particular on signs, supplemented by:</strong></p>




<ul>
<li>A biological balance sheet;</li>
<li>A colonoscopy (rectum and colon examination, terminal portion of small intestine, assessing damage extent);</li>
<li>Upper gastrointestinal endoscopy (to determine the high illness location);</li>
<li>Video capsule ingestion.</li>
</ul>




<p>Other tests may be required or placed under surveillance:</p>




<ul>
<li>MRIs;</li>
<li>Abdominal CT;</li>
<li>Abdominal ultrasound,</li>
<li>Radio.</li>
</ul>




<p>As for treatment, they are based on anti-inflammatory drugs target (5-ASA, corticosteroids, immunomodulators, antibiotics, iron). If unsuccessful, surgery may be necessary. A balanced diet is necessary to risk malnutrition reduce. During severe outbreaks, a restricted diet in fruits and vegetables can not increase gastrointestinal symptoms. Only tobacco should be avoided.</p>




<blockquote><p>Care is multidisciplinary, involving the intervention of various specialists: physician, gastroenterologist, rheumatologist, dietician, doctor or school work, social worker, psychiatrist or psychologist, etc..
It aims to ease outbreaks, prevent relapses, complications and improve life quality.</p></blockquote>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Too Much Cholesterol: What Symptoms?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/too-much-cholesterol-what-symptoms/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-17T10:19:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/too-much-cholesterol-what-symptoms</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/too-much-cholesterol-what-symptoms/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="cholesterol, symptoms, excess cholesterol, calibrate their cholesterol" alt="Too much cholesterol : what symptoms? What are the signs?">Some people wonder if cholesterol is accompanied by symptoms indicative.</p>




<p>If so, then these signs could indicate that it is time to calibrate their cholesterol.</p>




<p>This is unfortunately not the case&hellip;</p>




<!--more-->




<blockquote><p><strong>There are no specific symptoms manifested when an cholesterol excess in the blood.</strong>
We can not rely on any evidence to decide whether to calibrate their cholesterol checked and if all goes well on this side.</p></blockquote>




<p><strong>Excess cholesterol is a silent phenomenon as hypertension.</strong></p>




<h2>Symptoms of cholesterol are those complications</h2>




<p>It was only after years of evolution of symptoms may be too late, because the signs are then those complications of high cholesterol.</p>




<p>Recall that the long, excess cholesterol tends to be deposited in the arteries (plaque), narrowing their diameter and impeding proper blood circulation potentially causing arteritis members lower. This plaque can harden and cause angina. A blood clot can also form and detach, then going to butcher a coronary artery is myocardial or cerebral artery and is the stroke or renal artery is insufficient kidney.</p>




<p><strong>The symptoms of these accidents are well known</strong> (or should be because of the vital urgency):</p>




<p>What are the signs of angina?
Stroke or Heart Attack? Warning symptoms differ!</p>




<p>Overall, all symptoms suggestive of cardiovascular disease involving excess cholesterol are:</p>




<ul>
<li>Calves pain;</li>
<li>Chest pain with tightness;</li>
<li>Nausea, dizziness;</li>
<li>Fever, headache;</li>
<li>Shortness of breath, palpitations;</li>
<li>Feeling cold extremities;</li>
<li>Loss of strength in the face, arms, legs, especially on one side;</li>
<li>Slurred speech;</li>
<li>Blurred vision;</li>
<li>Etc..</li>
</ul>




<h2>So when do calibrate their cholesterol?</h2>




<blockquote><p><strong>The cholesterol assay based on a simple fasting blood test</strong> (after 12 hours without food and drink intake).
We can measure total cholesterol, HDL-cholesterol (&ldquo;bad&rdquo;) and triglycerides, while LDL-cholesterol is calculated from previous values.</p></blockquote>




<p>It is recommended to calibrate their cholesterol once before the age of 30 to screen for familial hypercholesterolemia. Then the pace is every 5 years to 50 years and then every 3 years beyond because the arteries naturally harden with age. In case of diabetes, cholesterol is dose every year at least.</p>




<blockquote><p><strong>Thin also may have too much cholesterol!</strong>
If overweight and obesity increase the risk of having too much bad cholesterol due to an unbalanced diet, thin people can also suffer from high cholesterol and then it is usually a family phenomenon&hellip;</p></blockquote>




<p>In addition to age and diabetes, there are other risk factors that can lead to monitor your cholesterol more closely: family history of premature coronary heart disease, smoking, hypertension, overweight (or obese), waist excessive, etc&hellip;</p>




<p><strong>It is noteworthy that what characterizes excess cholesterol is precisely symptoms absence. This is why regular monitoring is required!</strong></p>




<p><strong>For more information</strong></p>




<ul>
<li>Why do an assessment of blood lipids?</li>
<li>What is lipid?</li>
<li>Determination of total cholesterol: manual.</li>
<li>Why and how to HDL and LDL cholesterol balance?</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solar Capsules (Beta-carotene) to Better Tan?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/solar-capsules-beta-carotene-to-better-tan/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-15T09:17:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/solar-capsules-beta-carotene-to-better-tan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/solar-capsules-beta-carotene-to-better-tan/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="beta-carotene, solar capsules, discoloration of the skin" alt="Solar capsules (beta-carotene) to better tan?">Expected to prepare the skin for tanning, what is the actual effect of food supplements beta-carotene?
Do they tan, can you be more exposed to the sun and they protect cancer?
Focus on solar capsules.</p>




<!--more-->




<h2>Tanning and dietary supplements beta-carotene</h2>




<p><strong>Beta-carotene is a pigment that belongs to the family of carotenes.</strong>
It is found naturally in many plants very colorful, especially yellow-orange, like carrots, melons, peppers, apricots, as well as green leafy vegetables eg.</p>




<p><strong>Beta-carotene: an orange color of the skin</strong>
High doses of dietary supplements of beta-carotene (from 30 mg/day) or a very high consumption of foods rich in beta-carotene cause yellow/orange discoloration of the skin that doctors call &ldquo;carotenodermie&rdquo;. Such coloration is not hazardous to health and resolves when the amount of carotenoids absorbed decreases.</p>




<p><strong>An antioxidant against aging skin</strong>
Beta-carotene, also called provitamin A, is a precursor of vitamin A, which plays a role as an antioxidant, that is to say, it helps to fight against the excessive production of free radicals responsible for aging. Golden sun exposure are well known to accelerate the aging of the skin.</p>




<blockquote><p>For example, taking a dietary supplement beta-carotene (or adopt a diet rich in beta-carotene, and therefore rich in colorful fruits and vegetables) could accelerate the discoloration of the skin and therefore the tan, while protecting the skin from aging!</p></blockquote>




<p><strong>This is how many solar capsules are now available to enhance your tan, but their effectiveness in this area has not been formally demonstrated scientifically and without bias, as the duration of treatment and dosage to use.</strong></p>




<h2>Take solar capsules before going on vacation?</h2>




<p><strong>In the current state of knowledge, we can not recommend for or against solar capsules.</strong></p>




<blockquote><p>What is certain is that a cure of beta-carotene, even 15 days before exposure, during and after, does not relieve apply every two hours sunscreen with high protective index or n authorizes to expose longer or the hottest hours of the day.</p></blockquote>




<p>In other words, with or without beta-carotene, the main rules of prevention of skin cancer and accelerated skin aging are needed.</p>




<p>Finally, if you want to buy solar capsules should not exceed the manufacturer&rsquo;s recommended daily dose. Also note that these supplements are cons-indicated in children, pregnant or nursing women.</p>




<h2>Beta-carotene and cancer: protective effect or a negative effect?</h2>




<blockquote><p>These are: an excess of vitamin A can be toxic to the body, but this is not the case with beta-carotene, the vitamin A transformation is blocked as if the vitamin A status is already high. Overdosing seems so limited with beta-carotene.</p></blockquote>




<p><strong>For twenty years, studies consistently highlight the existence of a link between cancer prevention and beta-carotene</strong>: regular consumption, sometimes at high doses of beta-carotene would protect certain cancers.</p>




<p><strong>But, according to a study published in 2005 Inserm, this relationship is reversed in the case of smoking. Beta-carotene would be harmful.</strong>
Thus, smokers supplemented women see their risk of smoking-related cancers increase in proportion to the amount of beta-carotene consumed (20, 30, or 50 mg/day): lung cancer, gastrointestinal cancers, head and neck, thyroid, ovary, cervix, etc.. It is as if significant absorption of beta-carotene favored the formation of &ldquo;unusual cleavage products of carotenoids involved in the development of cancer&rdquo;. Note that this increase was observed both in smokers than in former smokers.
However, not all studies attest to this carcinogenic effect of beta-carotene dose in case of smoking. Thus, in 2012 the European Food Safety Authority (EFSA) concluded reassuringly to the lack of increase of lung cancer in heavy smokers to levels of beta-carotene supplementation &ldquo;reasonable&rdquo; (6 to 15 mg/day).</p>




<p><strong>So, do I take it or not solar capsules if I smoke?</strong>
To date, there is no reason to ban supplements beta-carotene for smokers, if consumed in reasonable amounts, ie less than 15 mg/day.
The best way to protect against cancer is to not smoke or stop!</p>




<p><strong>In summary:</strong></p>




<blockquote><p>If you want to prepare your skin to the sun and enhance your tan, you can of course make solar capsules, but no guarantee of effectiveness except to have a more colorful skin! By cons, apply the dose indicated on the instructions of dietary supplement and in any case, apply sunscreen to protect you from UV.</p></blockquote>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
