<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-11-19T20:02:59+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Therapeutic exercise for patients with diabetes]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/therapeutic-exercise-for-patients-with-diabetes/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:49:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/therapeutic-exercise-for-patients-with-diabetes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/exercise-therapy-for-patients-with-diabetes/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Exercise therapy for patients with diabetes" alt="Therapeutic exercise for patients with diabetes"> Exercise therapy for patients with diabetes helps to offset the disease. Exercise therapy (physical therapy) for patients with diabetes, along with other essential elements of treatment (insulin therapy, medication drugs, diet and self-control), plays a critical role in the compensation of the disease and has a beneficial effect on the patient, helping to maintain good health and performance.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>The role of physical therapy for patients with diabetes</h2>

<p>The violation of protein and fat metabolism in the body accumulates toxins and it is poisoning products of incomplete combustion of fats. In addition, disturbance of lipid metabolism leads to the fact that blood fat filled, it increases bad cholesterol, thereby repeatedly increased risk of atherosclerosis and other cardiovascular diseases.</p>

<p>Exercise therapy is shown not only in all types of diabetes (except for depleted due to untreated or poorly the treatment of diabetes patients), but also when prediabetnom condition. Modern research shows that, if we strictly adhere to the prescribed diet, exercise and give up bad habits &ndash; overeating, smoking and alcohol, then go into pre-diabetes mellitus can be avoided.</p>

<p>According to currently available data, the most common occurrence and development of diabetes contributes to overeating. That is why a person full-bodied and with disturbances in metabolism, need to understand that once in a painful exchange process will involve carbohydrate metabolism, inevitably develop diabetes.</p>

<p>In connection with this, people with excess body weight, being at risk of diabetes, must periodically tested for the presence of sugar in the blood and urine, to detect the first time the symptoms of the disease and to begin treatment. In addition to weight loss, you should pay attention to the following common symptoms of incipient diabetes &ndash; long nezazhivlenie wounds, abrasions resistant to treatment, itching, bleeding gums, loosening of teeth, impotence.</p>

<h2>Features of physical therapy for patients with diabetes</h2>

<p>The main objectives of physical therapy for patients with diabetes:</p>

<p>Improving cardiovascular and respiratory systems;
Improving patients&#8217; health;
Reducing hyperglycaemia in non-insulin (type 2 diabetes) and the potentiation of insulin in patients with insulin-dependent (type 1 diabetes);
Opposition to the development of micro-and macrovascular.</p>

<p>In diabetes, insulin deficiency addition, broken oxidative processes in the muscle due to which they can not utilize glucose. At the same physical stress oxidative enzyme activity is significantly enhanced in the blood are increased alkaline reserves, thereby increasing the uptake and consumption of glucose by muscles, decreases hyperglycemia and increased tolerance of the organism in carbohydrates. In addition, exercise in combination with insulin increase the therapeutic effect of insulin, strengthen the nervous and cardiovascular system of the patient, increase the body&rsquo;s resistance and prevent the development of atherosclerosis.</p>

<p>The distinctive feature of LFC in diabetes is that the recommended exercises should be performed in a moderate (Slower) rate, as well as muscular effort. In the anaerobic organism not occur and oxidation processes that contribute to the increase of glucose by muscles.</p>

<p>Classes begin physiotherapy is recommended to elementary exercises for the muscles of the legs, arms and torso with no encumbrances, combining with breathing exercises.  In addition to physical therapy, are useful dosed walking, rowing, cycling, swimming pool, skiing, gardening, light physical work.</p>

<p>When doing physical therapy you need to carefully monitor their well-being &ndash; if after playing the feeling of weakness or fatigue, the load must be reduced. If training were to shake hands, there was a strong feeling of hunger and weakness, you need to eat 1 to 2 pieces of sugar and immediately stop training. Resuming workout just a day after the disappearance of the symptoms of hypoglycemia, while reducing the dosage. Patients with diabetes who are on insulin therapy, in the days of long and intense physical activities recommended to reduce the dose of insulin (after consultation with the attending physician).</p>

<p>LFC need to conduct studies in a well-ventilated room or outdoors, breathing in this case should be free and rhythmic, through your nose and exhale longer inspiratory time. Physical exercise is necessary to alternate the different muscle groups and perform with a large amplitude in the joints.</p>

<p>Repeat each exercise should be 5-6 times in the future, to the extent of fitness, you can enhance the load by reducing breaks, increasing the rate and number of repetitions. Age is not a barrier to practice physical therapy, monitoring the patient&rsquo;s state of health is the only changes and hyperglycemia and weight.</p>

<p>Since the blood sugar level rises patient after a night&rsquo;s sleep, (which partly explains quiet sleep) are most useful gymnastics, and light walking exercise in the morning, as they not only lower blood glucose, but also promote the release of insulin in a more  But, if possible, try to exercise and in the evening (for 1.5 &ndash; 2 hours before bedtime) to secure an equivalent exercise for the day.</p>

<h2>Complex physiotherapy for patients with diabetes</h2>

<p>Starting position &ndash; the main counter. Set aside the leg back, put your hands up &ndash; inhale, return to the initial position &ndash; Exhale. Repeat 4-5 times.</p>

<p>Within 2-4 minutes walk alternately with high lifting hips, with the movements of the arms up and to the side, with the attacks. Breathe freely.</p>

<p>Stand up straight, hands behind head, elbows pinch the face. On the 1-2 dissolve in hand, inhale. On the 3-4 return to the starting position, tilt your head forward, exhale.</p>

<p>Feet shoulder width apart. Spread your arms out to the side, turn the body all the way to the left, the right hand should be in front of the chest. Then turn to the full right (left arm in front of chest, right assigned to the side). Lean forward to the left leg, pulling the sock right hand. Repeat on the other hand.</p>

<p>Starting position &ndash; arms out, legs apart. Make 3 springy lean to the left (right leg bent, left arm behind his back, right arm is raised up).</p>

<p>Mahi legs, pulling his hands in front summarized hands.</p>

<p>Starting position &ndash; the main counter. Lean forward, trying to get his hands floor without bending your legs. Then fall to focus on her knees, feet alternately move back please stop lying. Without bending your arms and legs and moving them from place, lift the hips higher by tilting forward, lower your head between hands. Lower the pelvis, taking the emphasis lying. Then alternate movement of the feet take forward the emphasis on his knees, lift your pelvis up, straighten your legs and arms.</p>

<p>Emphasis sitting, fingers pull back. Cave in to stop lying behind. Without moving your heels and hands with room, sit down to the heels of the bent leg, then without removing your hands from the floor, straighten your legs and put them apart. Connect and bend your legs and then straighten (without moving from the place of the heel), and return to starting position. Repeat 6-8 times.</p>

<p>Lie on your back, bend your arms at chest (forearms parallel to the one above the other). Lift them up, without straightening and does not disconnect (inhalation) and lower into place (exhale).</p>

<p>Lie on your stomach, hands under shoulders. Arms out to the sides (palms down on the floor), bend your back, and then straighten them and cave in, off the floor straight legs and hands, his head laid back. Hold this position for a few seconds, re-dissolve and bring feet back to its original position.</p>

<p>Lie on your back, raise your legs vertically. At the 1 &ndash; 2 dilute and bring your feet on the 3-4 bend and straighten. Repeat 4-6 times, not holding my breath.</p>

<p>Starting position &ndash; the main counter. Lift your arms to the shoulders (inspiration), and then relaxed &ldquo;drop&rdquo; them, head down, shoulders rounded off with.</p>

<p>Perform a peaceful walk for 2 minutes.</p>

<p>At the end of lessons useful to take a cool shower, bath or sponging, as well as water treatment activate the oxidative processes in the body. Start to cool off with a towel soaked in water at room temperature (not below), gradually lowering the temperature of water by one degree in a few days. Motion for a rubdown should be directed from the periphery to the heart.</p>

<p>Despite the fact that diabetes is a life-long illness, with good self-control and respect for all the doctor&rsquo;s appointments, diabetics can keep working and socially useful life on a par with healthy and live to a ripe old age.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Therapeutic exercises in spinal osteochondrosis]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/therapeutic-exercises-in-spinal-osteochondrosis/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:48:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/therapeutic-exercises-in-spinal-osteochondrosis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/physical-therapy-in-spinal-osteochondrosis/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Physical therapy in spinal osteochondrosis" alt="Therapeutic exercises in spinal osteochondrosis"> Physical therapy reduces stress on the joints and helps the deposition of salts. Many people who have the first symptoms of joint disease &ndash; the crunch and clicks, believe that they have a &ldquo;simple&rdquo; salt deposits &ndash; a trifle, which is observed in almost all and therefore do not require treatment. However, the deposition of salt, as it is popularly called low back pain, the disease is not as harmless as it may seem at first glance.</p>

<p>The fact that the starting salt deposited only at inappropriate salt metabolism in the body. A healthy body can absorb salts only as much as is necessary for normal functioning, and the excess output.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>If you violate a salt exchange surpluses are deposited in various parts of the body, causing certain diseases, often low back pain, gout, kidney stones and gall stones.</p>

<p>For osteochondrosis deferrable salt are often formed in sharp spikes that compress the nerves and cause severe pain with movement, causing a person is suffering, can not turn his head, torso, and the robot has to move, protecting yourself from the pain. In addition, osteochondrosis of the cervical spine may be accompanied by severe headaches, and in the period of acute lumbar degenerative disc disease and sciatica people and is completely bedridden.</p>

<p>Due to the fact that the joints begin to undergo similar changes already 20 years old, everyone should regularly engage in the prevention of salt deposits, which includes the cleaning of joints, proper diet (read the article diet for gout, osteochondrosis and salt deposits in the joints), and clear the joints folk remedies, such as using rice or bay leaf, carried out in order to prevent a year and gives a good effect. Therapeutic diet should be organized to remove excess weight, which is an additional burden on joints and provide the body with all the necessary vitamins and trace elements, especially calcium for strong bones and cartilage.</p>

<h2>Physical therapy in spinal osteochondrosis</h2>

<p>Gymnastics spinal osteochondrosis plays a major role, as well strengthens and tones the muscles of the back. With weak muscles of the body burden is &ldquo;hanging&rdquo; on one spine, flattening and deforming discs. If the muscles of the back and loins are well fortified, as they would create an additional corset and take on the weight of the body.</p>

<p>In addition, therapeutic exercises in spinal osteochondrosis helps get rid of extra salt, because if you exercise the bone and muscle tissue using them to compensate for the physiological loss. Finally, regular active movements, with which physiotherapy is the deposition of salts, gradually, as it were &ldquo;polished&rdquo; salt spikes, making them less sharp and painful.</p>

<p>Physical therapy will be effective only if it is done regularly, every day for 10-15 minutes. The following is a universal set of exercises that will suit everyone. We need to start small, gradually complicating every move &ndash; increasing the number of repetitions, strength and amplitude of slopes and turns. To enhance the effect of the exercises you can use a stick, holding her elbows behind his back. The first four are preparatory exercises complex and prepare the cardiovascular system to the load, and four of the latter, on the contrary, contribute to bringing the body to a calm state after a workout.</p>

<h2>Versatile set of exercises with osteochondrosis</h2>

<h3>Preparatory exercises</h3>

<p>Raise your hands, stretch up (breath), and then lower down, returning to the starting position (exhale).</p>

<p>Grasp the support and rise from heel to toe.</p>

<p>Stand with your feet shoulder width apart, hands on his belt. Move the arms back, reducing the maximum blade (inhalation). Bring elbows to the first starting position and then forward as far as you can (exhale).</p>

<p>Tread on the spot, raising his knees.</p>

<p>Stand erect with your feet shoulder width apart. The maximum stretch up, raising his hands (breath), then lean forward (exhale).</p>

<h3>Arms down at your sides</h3>

<p>Stand erect. Turn around in different directions, arms relaxed at the same time and how would overwhelm the body.</p>

<p>Circular rotation to the right and left lower part of the body.</p>

<p>The circular rotation of hands alternately in different directions.</p>

<p>Stand erect, hands on waist, feet shoulder width apart. Take your right hand back, looking at her (inspiration), go back (exhalation). Similarly, perform the other hand.</p>

<p>Standing upright or sitting in a chair doing Reclining head turns to the right, left, back and forth, then a circular motion.</p>

<p>Sit on a chair and slowly slide your feet on the floor back and forth alternately.</p>

<p>Stand up straight, stretch up with your hands (inhalation), scroll down (exhale).</p>

<p>By the universal set of exercises with osteochondrosis can be added to the selection of specific additional exercises for the cervical, thoracic or lumbar spine, as well as for large joints most affected by the deposition of salts &ndash; shoulder, hip, and knee.</p>

<h3>Exercises for the cervical spine</h3>

<p>Starting position &ndash; lying on his stomach, head turned to the side. Lift up on the hands, throwing his head back (inspiration), go back (exhale).</p>

<p>Tilt your head back, touching the back. Draw your shoulders vertically.</p>

<p>Tilt your head forward and touching his chest, chin slide up and down, simulating the movement of birds to clean the feathers.</p>

<h3>Exercises to help relieve the chest department</h3>

<p>Sit in a chair, hands behind his head rewound (inhalation), cave as possible back, shoulders touching the chair back (exhale).</p>

<p>Get on all fours, cave in the back, keep your head straight, stay in this position for a few seconds, then return to starting position.</p>

<p>Exercise &ldquo;Boat&rdquo;. Lie on your stomach, arms along the body. Cave in &ldquo;boat&rdquo;, taking his head and legs as high as possible off the floor.</p>

<h3>Exercise for the lumbar spine</h3>

<p>Lie on your back, press down bent knees as close to your chest.</p>

<p>Lying on his stomach, rest on the floor bent arms. Straightening your arms, push-ups on the floor, keeping the legs.</p>

<p>Get on your knees, resting his hands on the floor straight. Maximum Flex the back up, then return to starting position.</p>

<p>Stand with your feet shoulder width apart. Lean down, trying to get the floor with his hands. Then stand up straight, raise your arms above your head cave in and make the most.</p>

<p>Exercise &ldquo;cat&rdquo; perfectly relieves tension from the back. Get on all fours, leaning on his knees and hands. Arms and back should be straight, do not tilt your head, look forward. Tilt your head back down and forecasting arc up like a cat, stay in this position for 10 seconds, then go back and relax.</p>

<p>It is also useful to hang out at every opportunity on the bar for 1-2 minutes.</p>

<h3>Exercises for the shoulder joints</h3>

<p>Sit on a chair, put his hands on his belt and spread to the sides. Slowly lift your shoulders up to the stop and gently lowered down slightly pulling down.</p>

<p>Sit on a chair, a push to the back, hands on his waist, elbows divorced. Follow the movement of the shoulders gently back and forth.</p>

<p>In the same starting position alternately follow the circular movement of the shoulders.</p>

<p>Sit on a chair and slide as far back as the patient&rsquo;s hand, healthy, grabbed her wrist and pull toward your buttocks until the pain. Stay in this position for 10 seconds and strain the patient&rsquo;s hand. Then relax and try to move it a few more inches to the onset of pain. Repeat 3-5 times.</p>

<p>Get a hands behind his back and locked in a castle. Then pull in different directions, as if trying to break the lock. Alternately, drag them to the right and to the left, not disengaging.</p>

<p>Stand erect, flattened behind the castle as his hands slowly allot up and back, trying to take as much as possible, but without sharp pain. In this case, the patient remains passive hand.</p>

<h3>Exercises for the hip joints</h3>

<p>Lie on your side with your right leg at the knee and remove the floor in front of him. Then do the same with the other hand.</p>

<p>Lie on your stomach. Bend your right leg, pull it to the side and push the knee to the floor, as if crawling &ldquo;on their bellies.&rdquo; Then do the same with the left hand.</p>

<p>Lying on his stomach, focusing on the bent arm. Then straighten your arms and sit on your heels.</p>

<p>Sit on the floor cross-legged with his legs crossed. Swing your body back and forth.</p>

<h3>Exercises for the knee</h3>

<p>Movement &ldquo;Bicycle&rdquo;. Lying on his back, legs mimic the movement while riding a bike, do not touch the floor.</p>

<p>Lie on your stomach. Without lifting your hips off the floor, bend your legs alternately, trying to touch their buttocks. If there are no sharp pains, you can perform up to 50 times.</p>

<p>Lying on your stomach, bend your leg at the knee at 90 degrees with respect to the body and hold a few seconds. Follow by turns both feet until you get tired (you can up to 50 times).</p>

<p>Sitting on the floor and holding exactly back, dangling his feet at a moderate speed. This exercise is useful to carry out during the day for a lot of times.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Herpes simplex virus types I and II]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/herpes-simplex-virus-types-i-and-ii/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:47:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/herpes-simplex-virus-types-i-and-ii</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/herpes-virus-type/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Herpes virus type" alt="Herpes simplex virus types I and II. Prevention of herpes"> A good immune system &ndash; the best prevention of herpes. At the household level, people used to think that herpes &ndash; an ordinary &ldquo;cold&rdquo; or &ldquo;fever on the lips,&rdquo; but it is actually not so simple. Herpes (from the Greek herpes &ndash; creeping) &ndash; a viral disease that affects the mucous membranes and the skin of a person.</p>

<p>It has been known to mankind for a long time and was described by Hippocrates, who gave him the name because of the &ldquo;creeping&rdquo; nature of the spread of the disease. Among the huge number of viral diseases herpes is a leader because, according to the scientists, latent, that is hidden, &ldquo;sleeping&rdquo; form, it affects about 90% of the entire population of the planet.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>There are about 100 species gerpevirusa, but only eight of these are able to cause diseases in humans, the most common herpes first and second type.</p>

<h2>Herpes virus type</h2>

<p>Herpes virus (HSV-1) is passed as influenza, via droplets &ndash; coughing, sneezing and by contact with the skin or mucous membranes of an infected person. The people he called the &ldquo;common cold on the lips,&rdquo; because, though striking the whole body, outwardly manifested mainly on the lips and nose wings.</p>

<p>The first time it enters the body of the first type of herpes virus does not manifest itself clinically, people do not even realize that he is infected. Before the acute phase of the illness is called the incubation period lasting from 2 to 14 days, during which the virus is actively propagated and implemented.</p>

<p>When the virus starts to become more active on the lips appear very painful blisters with fluid, severe itching, burning, swelling, often increased body temperature and increased lymph nodes. Then the bubbles begin to burst, sores scab, which is also very painful and can last up to 10 days. After healing of wounds virus again &ldquo;hiding&rdquo; in the body and is waiting for a chance for recurrence, the timing of which can not be predicted.</p>

<p>Infection with the first type initially occurs most often between the ages of 3-4 years, and the children of the first years of life almost never get sick herpes because they have immunity from the mother, and by 5 years of age, as a rule, already have in your body  Antibodies to genital virus most often appear in adolescence, around 15 years, initially infection penetrates not only through sexual organs, but also through the mucous membranes of the mouth and skin.</p>

<p>Earlier traditionally believed that the first type of virus affects the upper part of the body &ndash; the face, mouth, eyes and lips, and the second type of virus &ndash; the lower half of the body, usually the genitals. But, now, this division is purely conditional, since there are cases genital lesions gerpevirusom first type.</p>

<h2>Herpes second type</h2>

<p>Second type of herpes virus (HSV-2), more commonly called genital because, unlike the first type, it affects mainly genital mucosa. Transmitted mainly through sex, but also there may be cases of infection through saliva, oral-genital contact. Less common infection through casual through linen and personal care products, as well as through medical procedures such as blood transfusions and organ transplants.</p>

<p>If it affects the human genital herpes incubation period ranging from 1 to 10 days, then comes the acute phase, characterized by fever, malaise, weakness and increased inguinal lymph nodes, which is extremely painful. On the genitals appear painful blisters, itching and pain. Primary genital gerpevirus can last a very long time to heal 3-5 weeks.</p>

<p>A particularly dangerous genital gerpevirus for pregnant women, because the child becomes infected it either in the womb or during childbirth when passing through an infected birth canal.  They are very common neurological disorders, blindness and death. In this regard, it is vital for women planning pregnancy, tested for the presence of viral infections to its occurrence, and if necessary undergo treatment.</p>

<p>Someone gets sick herpes every few years, and someone every few weeks, often the virus affects the same areas. And, if the first type of herpes manifests itself quite rare, mostly not more than three times a year, the second type of herpes recurrences gives every couple of months, and sometimes several times a month, delivering huge human physiological, moral and social issues. According to studies, one in two women suffering from genital gerpevirusom, lonely and Neustroev in his personal life, which often leads to depression and a variety of neuropsychiatric disorders.</p>

<h2>Prevention of herpes</h2>

<p>Despite the enormous prevalence of herpes, most people are passive carriers of it and only 20% of people observed symptoms. Scientists have found that the whole family gerpevirusov is our constant companion throughout life &ndash; to introduce into the body one day, they&rsquo;ll never leave. And only on the condition of the immune system depends on how the virus will behave in the body &ndash; whether it will just live quietly, without letting themselves known, or will regularly remind yourself endless recurrence.</p>

<p>From the primary contact virus gets into the bloodstream and lymph nodes, and future behavior is entirely dependent on the state of the human immune system. When good immunity develops local, or local form of herpes. If, however, reduced immunity, the virus penetrates further into the body, affecting such important organs such as the liver, kidney, spleen, adrenal glands.</p>

<p>The virus accumulates in the cells and in response to various trigger factors will periodically cause permanent relapses. It is promoted by exposure to cold, chronic fatigue, poor diet, excessive exercise, stress, alcohol, antibiotics.</p>

<p>Since the medicine of today has in its arsenal of medicines that allow to completely heal cold sores, it becomes clear that in the first place there is the problem of prevention of infections and the overall strengthening of the immune system. Protect against genital herpes, in contrast to the first type of herpes that is transmissible through airborne droplets, it is possible, respecting the rules of personal hygiene: Do not use someone else&rsquo;s lipstick, do not smoke a cigarette for two, drink, and eat only with their dishes, use a condom and do not in any way engage in oral sex if your partner has gerpevirusa blisters on the lips.</p>

<p>In order to prevent the insidious virus of the herpes host in your body and spoil your life, will make every effort to maximize strengthen your immune system and viruses then no you are not afraid. To do this, use the entire arsenal of tools for healthy living &ndash; nutrition with the presence of all necessary for the body of vitamins and minerals, the correct drinking regime, moderate exercise, healthy sleep, as well as smoking cessation and alcohol.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vegetative - vascular dystonia (VVD)]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/vegetative-vascular-dystonia-vvd/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:46:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/vegetative-vascular-dystonia-vvd</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/vegetative-dystonia/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Vegetative-vascular dystonia" alt="Vegetative-vascular dystonia (VVD) Causes, types and treatment"> Vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia (VVD), and neuro-circulatory dysfunction &ndash; the pathological state of the autonomic nervous system, which results in insufficient supply of oxygen to tissues and organs. According to doctors, with one or other signs of VSD face about 80% of people of all ages.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Vegetative &ndash; dystonia symptoms and signs</h2>

<p>Vegetative (autonomic) nervous system located in the brain and spinal cord, is an essential part of the human body &ndash; it is fully coordinate the activities of all internal organs, blood vessels and glands of internal secretion and provides them to adapt with changes in the external environment.</p>

<p>In particular, the autonomic nervous system regulates blood pressure, heartbeat, body temperature, and composition of extracellular fluid volume, blood flow, metabolic rate, thirst, hunger and satiety, sweat gland function, kidney function, muscle tone internal organs, circadian (daily</p>

<p>For dystonia, which is a consequence of a breach of vascular tone, characterized by the following symptoms:</p>

<p>Neuropsychiatric &ndash; weakness, lethargy, fatigue, low efficiency, dizziness, headaches, sleep disorders, fainting, decreased sexual activity, and panic attacks;
Thermoregulatory action for breach of sweating and thermoregulation &ndash; spontaneous fever, excessive sweating, fever, flushing, or, on the contrary, sensitivity to cold extremities;
Spider &ndash; the instability of the arterial and venous pressure;
Cardiology &ndash; disruption of the heart, frequent heart contractions and pain in the heart;
Breathing (respiratory) &ndash; shortness of breath, chest tightness and a feeling of lack of air;
Dyspeptic &ndash; a disorder of the stomach &ndash; intestinal tract (constipation, diarrhea), voiding dysfunction and gallbladder dyskinesia.</p>

<h2>Vegetative &ndash; dystonia types and causes</h2>

<p>Despite the fact that the uniform classification of the IRR does not exist, the following types are divided vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia:</p>

<p>The nature of the disease:</p>

<ul>
<li>Permanent form &ndash; occurs without abrupt jumps in the patient&rsquo;s condition;</li>
<li>Paroxysmal or paroxysmal &ndash; manifested in the form of attacks (or panic attacks crises), in the intervals between attacks manifestations of the disease are almost invisible;</li>
<li>Mixed ESP (permanently-paroxysmal) &ndash; combines the features of a permanent and paroxysmal forms;</li>
<li>Latent, or hidden form &ndash; in this type of VSD disease may not manifest themselves for quite a long time, until the trigger factors (stress, illness, fatigue).</li>
</ul>


<p>Depending on violations of cardio &ndash; vascular system:</p>

<ul>
<li>Hypertensive type or vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia of hypertensive type. Accompanied by a significant rise in blood pressure (145/90 &ndash; 175/95 mm Hg. c.), sometimes with heart palpitations, sudden excitement, fever, symptoms of a panic attack, and, the pressure can be increased not only in times of emotional stress, but also in a state of complete rest;</li>
<li>Hypertensive type or vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia hypotonic type. In this case, the blood pressure is substantially lower than normal and reaches 100/50 and even up to 90/45 mm Hg. Art. and is accompanied by lethargy, weakness, shortness of breath, nausea, sweating, fatigue patient, sometimes fainting;</li>
<li>Normotensive or heart (cardiac) does not depend on the type of blood pressure and heart disorders defined by the (slow heart rate, or, conversely, rapid, feelings fade and disruptions of the heart), as well as pain in the chest area;</li>
<li>Mixed type of VSD combines multiple symptoms and signs typical for any type.</li>
</ul>


<p>Depending on the cause of vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia, the following types of VSD: genetic, infectious &ndash; allergic, traumatic, psychogenic (as a reaction to stress or traumatic situations), and arose as a result of excessive emotional or physical stress.</p>

<h2>Vegetative &ndash; dystonia treatment and prevention</h2>

<p>From the timely and correct diagnosis of VSD depends largely on the success of further treatment. If you have frequent attacks of headache, weakness, dizziness, fatigue, insomnia, unfounded anxiety, fear, jumps in blood pressure and heart rate, &ldquo;lump&rdquo; in the throat, shortness of breath, pain in the heart and stomach, as well as grow cold and numb limbs &ndash;</p>

<p>Do not listen to bad advice of friends and acquaintances in an &ldquo;ESP is not a disease and will pass without treatment.&rdquo; Doctors claim that untreated dystonia is very dangerous because it can be complicated by panic attacks and other serious disorders that occur on the wrong team, the autonomic nervous system and debilitating nervous system.</p>

<p>When panic attacks (Sympathoadrenal crisis) a person starts suddenly (often in a public place) to shake, choke and breaking into a cold sweat. At the same time, he has a wild fear of death, heart pounding jumps and pressure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ankylosing spondylitis]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/ankylosing-spondylitis/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:45:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/ankylosing-spondylitis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/ankylosing-spondylitis/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Ankylosing spondylitis" alt="Ankylosing spondylitis: causes, symptoms, diagnosis"> Modern methods of treatment of ankylosing spondylitis help stop the inflammation of the joints. Ankylosing spondylitis, or ankylosing spondylitis (ankylosing spondylitis) &ndash; a chronic inflammatory disease of the spine and joints, accompanied by pain, stiffness and deformity and progressive ossification of the joints, including the formation of irreversible changes in them and complete immobility.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Ankylosing spondylitis causes</h2>

<p>Causes of ankylosing spondylitis is not thoroughly understood, but it is known that people who are carriers of the gene HLA-B27, a genetic predisposition to the disease Ankylosing Spondylitis Disease (BB).</p>

<p>The immune system of such people &ldquo;mistakenly&rdquo; believes tissue of the joints and ligaments, and alien attacks them, causing inflammation and damage.</p>

<p>However, even in the presence of this gene, ill ankylosing spondylitis is not all that is a mystery and the subject of further research for doctors &ndash; Rheumatology. Additional factors that may trigger the development of the disease are considered to change the immune status of the &ndash; for colds, colds, viral and infectious &ndash; allergic diseases and injuries of the pelvis and spine.</p>

<p>In addition, the latest research scientists have shown that ankylosing spondylitis is a psychosomatic illness and because, more than a third of cases the first symptoms began to appear after heavy and prolonged stress.</p>

<h2>Diagnosis and distinctive symptoms of ankylosing spondylitis</h2>

<p>Because some of the symptoms of ankylosing spondylitis is very similar to the symptoms of degenerative disc disease in the early stages of these diseases are often confused, as ankylosing spondylitis often starts as a normal low back pain &ndash; pain in the lower back and painful back muscle strain.</p>

<p>Therefore, for correct diagnosis and start early treatment, it is important to identify the disease early in its development, to prevent the complete immobilization of the spine and associated threatening complications. The most dangerous complication of ankylosing spondylitis include:</p>

<p>Amyloidosis &ndash; degeneration of the kidneys, leading to kidney failure;
Defeat heart and aorta, leading to shortness of breath and chest pain provoking and disruption of the heart;
Tuberculosis and other diseases of the lung, derived from &ndash; the decrease in the mobility of the chest;
Uveitis &ndash; inflammation of the choroid, leading to blurred vision, eye pain and sensitivity to light;</p>

<p>Among the primary symptoms of ankylosing spondylitis is the most characteristic periodic pain (in 75% of cases). But if osteochondrosis pain is permanent and increases when moving, then in ankylosing spondylitis is different &ndash; the pain is much worse at night and several subside during the day, after the start of active movements.</p>

<p>If osteochondrosis person can lean on at least one side, or turn to the right &ndash; to the left, then the movement of ankylosing spondylitis usually fails in all directions. In addition, the most frequent symptom of ankylosing spondylitis is swelling and tenderness of the joints, as well as the characteristic change of posture, posture called the &ldquo;petitioner&rdquo;.</p>

<p>In the formation of an asylum patient poses a gradual straightening of the normal curvature of the spine &ndash; the back is straight and flat. A little later freezes thoracic, there is a strong slouch, and the legs when walking instinctively bend at the knees. Over time, spinal stiffness reaches such a degree that the person begins to move as if he rather inflexible spine stick.</p>

<p>Properly diagnose disease helps the spine x-ray in which an experienced physician may notice the early signs of changes of bones and joints, magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) and a blood test for C-reactive protein, erythrocyte sedimentation rate (ESR), and the presence of the antigen HLA-B27. ESR parameter greater than 30 mm/h and the presence of HLA-B27 antigen confirm the validity of the diagnosis of ankylosing spondylitis.</p>

<h2>Ankylosing spondylitis treatment</h2>

<p>As the basis of therapy in the treatment of ankylosing spondylitis patients assigned to longer courses (from 1 year to 5 years) of non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs, which help to significantly slow down the progression of the disease, as well as anti-rheumatic drugs, corticosteroids, and necrosis factor blockers. Sometimes, in particularly severe cases, shows the assignment of immunosuppressive drugs.</p>

<p>In addition, it is important to sanitize all the centers of chronic infections in the body and carry out strengthening therapy &ndash; it is well to prevent cases of relapse. As an alternative treatment successfully used acupuncture, reflexology, magnet, pchelolechenie, hirudotherapy, physiotherapy and massage.</p>

<p>Girudoterapiya (leech therapy) has a good anti-inflammatory, analgesic and anti-bacterial effect, as contained in the saliva of leeches enzymes (hirudin, Eglin, destabilaza) soften and make more plastic stiff spine, relieve inflammation and tissue damage of the joints and ligaments, and normalize blood flow.</p>

<p>In addition, leech therapy has a beneficial effect on the entire body &ndash; by improving the blood circulation and better blood oxygen saturation, dissolve blood clots, normal metabolism, improved sleep, appetite and mood, and increases immunity.</p>

<h2>Physiotherapy</h2>

<p>Exercise therapy for ankylosing spondylitis is very important, as regular exercise and exercise increase blood flow in the joints, help maintain flexibility of the spine and lower extremities, stop the progression of the disease and prevent disability.</p>

<p>However, you should remember that exercise should be a feasible and gentle, so as not to lead to poor health. So, absolutely contraindicated in patients with BB running, jumping, shaking in the transport and hypothermia. On the contrary, it is very useful to calm walking (up to 3 &ndash; 5 kilometers), including skiing on flat terrain. Swimming in ponds and pools allowed at water temperatures below 23 &ndash; 22 degrees, and leave recommended in areas with warm and dry climate.</p>

<p>If you have a long time to be in the same position, it is necessary to change the position of each hour of the body. During the day, preferably several times to lie on a hard bed without a pillow when lying on stomach with legs straight. If this position is not straighten up, you can put a small pillow under her stomach.</p>

<p>Therapeutic exercises should be mandatory daily procedure, even if you do not feel well and have no hope of restoring spinal mobility. The fact that, due to splices and joints chest stiffness deteriorates ventilation, which may lead to pneumonia, pulmonary fibrosis and other diseases. Therefore, in order to prevent serious complications, the patient is required breathing exercises (daily, 3-4 times a day, inflate a balloon) and regular walks in the fresh air.</p>

<h2>Complex physiotherapy in ankylosing spondylitis</h2>

<p>Initial position (and. etc.) &ndash; sitting on a chair.
Turns head to the right and to the left, half circles and head tilts his ear to the shoulder.
Hands on waist, shoulder blades are brought together, back straight &ndash; chin stretch ahead.
Hands separated the sides, fingers clenched in a fist &ndash; chin hug the neck and connect the blades.</p>

<p>Starting position &ndash; lying on his back
Raise your head and stretch your chin to her stomach.
Hands pull at your sides, legs join together &ndash; relying on the heel, neck and hands, lift the hips as high as possible and forecasting.
Rewound Hands behind your head, legs together, feet on yourself &ndash; lift the body by 45 degrees, a little linger in this position, and slowly lower to the starting position.
Lift straightened legs and work out them alternately in different directions circular motion.
Bend your legs, arms behind his head rewound &ndash; lift the pelvis, cave in and slowly lower.</p>

<p>Starting position &ndash; lying on its side
Both the knee to the chest, move and try to reach out to their forehead. Then straighten your legs and cave in back.
Follow alternately mahi straight leg forward &ndash; back and leg lifts straight up.
Fold the leg at the knee and follow the circular motion of the hip.</p>

<p>However, it is worth noting that the set of physical exercises can not be yourself, it must be paired with your doctor, who will take into account the individual characteristics of the course of ankylosing spondylitis and the general condition of the body.</p>

<h2>Massage, diet and prevention of complications</h2>

<p>Massage in ankylosing spondylitis, used in conjunction with physical therapy, good pain relief and muscle fatigue, strengthens the muscular system, normalizes skin tone and helps to preserve the ability of the vertebral motor.</p>

<p>However, massage is just beyond the acute phase should be easy and gentle, with no hard techniques (cutting, effleurage) and carried out by a qualified technician. The total duration of the massage treatments should not exceed 25 minutes, after the course of treatment (20 &ndash; 25 sessions) needed a break for 3 &ndash; 4 weeks.</p>

<p>Nutrition in ankylosing spondylitis, as with any other chronic inflammatory disease must be balanced, but not excessive, so as not to lead to obesity. Caloric intake should closely match the physiological needs of the body and exercise patient as overweight creates a dangerous extra strain on the joints of the spine and lower extremities.</p>

<p>In the menu there should be enough protein foods, especially fish and low-fat dairy products, salads with fresh vegetables with the addition of unrefined sunflower or corn oil, fruits and herbs. Ordinary table salt substitute on the marine containing many useful trace elements. Nutritionists advise instead of salt to add to ready-made meals seaweed powder, which contains all necessary for the normal functioning of the bones and cartilage of trace elements.</p>

<p>In addition, the diet should be excluded sharp, smoked, fried and salty foods, alcohol and refined foods, preferring healthy homemade food &ndash; whole grain porridge, stewed and pureed vegetables and soups. Doctors say if you stick to eating right, just get treatment and begin to actively engage in physical therapy, the inflammation in the joints can significantly slow down and you will be able to lead a full life.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Total bilirubin in the blood]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/total-bilirubin-in-the-blood/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:43:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/total-bilirubin-in-the-blood</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-lower-bilirubin/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Direct bilirubin, indirect bilirubin, elevated bilirubin, how to lower bilirubin" alt="Total bilirubin in the blood, direct, indirect"> Increased bilirubin &ndash; a source of dangerous intoxication of the brain. Bilirubin &ndash; the pigment saturated yellow-brown color, is produced in many organs and tissues and is the end product of the breakdown of hemoglobin and other proteins heme-containing in the cells of the liver, bone marrow and spleen.</p>

<p>The physiological role of bilirubin is not completely understood, but according to recent research, it is necessary not only for the disposal of hemoglobin, as previously thought, but is also a powerful natural antioxidant that gives great promise for the discovery of new treatments for cancer, cardiology and many other diseases.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Bilirubin direct, indirect and total</h2>

<p>In the human body bilirubin is present in two forms &ndash; direct (related) and indirect (Free). Total bilirubin in its pure form does not exist, and is defined as the sum of direct and indirect, and, normally, direct bilirubin should be 75% of the total. Every day, the body is made of about 250 &ndash; 350 mg of bilirubin, wherein, about 80% erythrocytes formed during decomposition (1 gram of hemoglobin &ndash; about 36 grams bilirubin).</p>

<p>It is known that human blood is a rapidly renewing connective tissue composed of plasma cells and uniform elements: erythrocytes (provide tissues with oxygen), white blood cells (responsible for the immune system and fight infections) and platelets (responsible for blood clotting).</p>

<p>The erythrocytes, or red blood cells &ndash; the most numerous of the blood cells. They live in an average of about 120 days, after which decompose, releasing the hemoglobin contained in them. Hemoglobin, after complex chemical reactions, originally converted into a free or indirect bilirubin is insoluble in water and is extremely poisonous. It is concentrated in the liver by gripping it from the blood of liver cells.</p>

<p>Unconjugated bilirubin in the liver as a &ldquo;neutralized&rdquo; &ndash; under the influence of special enzymes, it connects to the glucuronide and get involved. Due to the effect of glucuronic acid, direct bilirubin, in contrast to indirect becomes soluble and less toxic &ndash; easily soluble in bile, it falls along with it in the intestine and then removed from the body naturally with faeces, giving it a brown color.</p>

<h2>Increased bilirubin in the blood causes and symptoms</h2>

<p>In the normal metabolism of bilirubin in the blood gets very little direct bilirubin. However, under pathological failure, it can significantly increase the concentration in blood (hyperbilirubinemia) and urine (bilirubinuria) penetrating into the surrounding tissue and causing yellowing of the skin, sclera eyes and mucous membranes. In addition, frequent signs of the disease &ndash; nausea, weakness, vomiting, bitter belching, heaviness in the right upper quadrant, bleached almost white feces, urine, beer color and itchy skin.</p>

<p>Primary cause of bilirubin metabolism:</p>

<p>Diseases of the blood in which there is a sharp increase in the number of non-viable red blood cells (anemia), the immune aggression toward normal red blood cells (hemolytic disease of the newborn rhesus &ndash; conflict with the child&rsquo;s mother), and exposure to toxic chemicals and blood cells.</p>

<p>Liver disease (viral, bacterial, autoimmune, toxic and drug hepatitis, jaundice), striking or destroy liver cells. When severe jaundice yellowing not only the skin and the sclera eyes, but also saliva, sweat, tears, breast milk, and all the internal organs.</p>

<p>Violation of the free passage of bile on biliary pathways &ndash; gallstones, gallbladder dyskinesia, pakreatit, the presence of tumors, scars or enlarged lymph nodes in close proximity to bile ways.</p>

<p>Poisoning by alcohol, chemicals and medicines.
A lack of vitamin B12.
Hereditary lack of liver enzyme &ndash; Gilbert&rsquo;s syndrome.
Physiological neonatal jaundice.</p>

<h2>Normal bilirubin in children and adults</h2>

<p>Determining the level of bilirubin in the blood is an important tool for the diagnosis of many diseases, especially of the liver, biliary tract and the hematopoietic system, and is one of the key indicators of the biochemical analysis of blood. Refferentnye values ​​of normal levels of total, direct and indirect bilirubin levels for adults and children are shown in the table below</p>

<h3>In adults and children older than 1 month</h3>

<p>Birth 51-60 mmol/l, with 2 days to the end of the first week may increase to 256 mmol/l by indirect (preterm and 170 pmol/l).</p>

<p>3 By the end of the week approaches the indicator for vzroslyhNepryamoydo 15.4 mmol/l (75% of the total) in the peak period of not less than 90% of the obschegoPryamoydo 5.1 mmol/l (25% of the total) in the peak period of not more than 10%.</p>

<h2>Physiological neonatal jaundice</h2>

<p>Increased bilirubin in neonates is not a disease and in most cases takes place independently and does not require treatment. This phenomenon is called physiologic jaundice (jaundice) in infants and children is associated with the adaptation of the organism to changing environmental conditions.</p>

<p>Fact that blood first days of life of children comprises a so-called fetal hemoglobin (formed in utero) which differs in composition from adult human hemoglobin and is active replacement for the first month of life.</p>

<p>Due to the fact that the replacement of a significant amount of released hemoglobin degradation products of erythrocytes, and the liver and biliary system infant has not yet fully operational, approximately 3 &ndash; 4 days of age his skin and mucous membranes may be colored yellow. Afraid of this state do not have to &ndash; as soon as the enzyme system of the child is fully working, skin color changes to pale &ndash; pink, this is usually a 7 &ndash; 8 day of life.</p>

<p>A slightly longer and expression can occur in rhesus jaundice &ndash; conflict (Rh negative mother and an infant positive) or in the presence of mothers in the first group of blood, and the child&rsquo;s second (sometimes third). At the same time children become overly drowsy and need to wake up for feedings.</p>

<p>To reduce the toxicity effects of high levels of bilirubin and accelerate its excretion in feces and urine, modern medicine is widely used method of light therapy (phototherapy). Infant is placed under a special lamp, close your eyes and cover the bandage, if possible, on both sides. Typically, after the 4 &ndash; day fotolecheniya, jaundice symptoms completely disappear.</p>

<p>The positive effect of the treatment has zheltushki breastfeeding and earlier attachment baby to the breast &ndash; it promotes more rapid discharge of meconium and reduces the likelihood of complications. In more severe cases, with severe jaundice may require donor blood transfusion, allowing the nervous system and save a child&rsquo;s life from the toxic effects.</p>

<h2>How to lower bilirubin?</h2>

<p>To reduce the bilirubin in the blood, it is first necessary to establish the root cause of its increase. Otherwise, it will continue to rise since hyperbilirubinemia is not a separate disease but a symptom of a disease.</p>

<p>In particular, if the fault stagnation of bile, sufficient to remove the obstacle, for example, remove the stone in the gall bladder or a course of treatment with drugs that improve bile secretion. In viral hepatitis need antiviral treatment, hemolytic anemia &ndash; a means to warn increased breakdown of red blood cells. If the reason is due to intoxication of the body, will help welcome the adsorbents bind toxic substances and getaprotektorov, which serve to protect the liver.</p>

<p>In addition, to reduce the rate of the enzyme in blood, it is necessary to unload the liver and gallbladder, changing his diet toward healthy diet. From the menu to exclude acute, smoked and fried foods, carbonated drinks, alcohol, strong tea, sweets. Choose more fresh, boiled and baked foods, especially vegetables &ndash; this will help to eliminate the causes of constipation, restore useful microflora and provide quick removal of toxins from the intestines.</p>

<p>In order not to disturb the functioning of the digestive tract, eat often, but little by little, do not overeat and avoid long breaks between meals. In addition, during the acute banned starvation diets for weight loss, showing compliance with therapeutic diet for gallstones.</p>

<p>For the correct diagnosis needs to know how to properly prepare for the tests. Blood is drawn from a vein in the morning on an empty stomach is not recommended to eat and drink coffee (caffeine reduces bilirubin levels) for 8 hours before the procedure, otherwise the results may be unreliable.</p>

<p>In previous blood donation day give up fatty foods (not to overload the liver) and from excessive exercise, provoking pain in the right upper quadrant. To obtain accurate figures, sometimes requires the prior cancellation (within 2 weeks), certain drugs, in particular vitamin C and anti-epileptic drugs.</p>

<p>If the research is carried out correctly and showed enzyme levels significantly below normal, it also should be alerted. Causes of low bilirubin insufficiently studied, because, more often than not, people are suffering from high enzyme content, not low. However, according to some medical studies, a direct link between between its reduced level of disease and coronary heart disease, that is, the risk of heart attack and stroke is much lower at high bilirubin than at low.</p>

<p>Finally, we note that high levels of bilirubin requires careful and rigorous, as it is highly toxic to the central nervous system and causes a variety of ailments &ndash; persistent headaches, fatigue, slowing of heart rate (bradycardia). Therefore, the best way to avoid poisoning the brain and body &ndash; at the first symptoms to seek medical attention.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banana diet for 3 days and 7 days]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet-for-3-days-and-7-days/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:41:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet-for-3-days-and-7-days</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/banana-diet/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="banana diet, banana and milk, cottage cheese-banana, kefir-banana" alt="Banana diet for 3 days and 7 days. Menus, reviews, results"> Banana Diet &ndash; minus 5-6 pounds per week. Banana Diet is one of the most popular short-term mono-diet of fruit, allow a few days without much trouble to get rid of extra pounds. An estimated nutritionists, 3 days prior to the banana diet lost 3 &ndash; pounds overweight, and this week &ndash; about 5 &ndash; 6 pounds.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Banana Diet Reviews and contraindications</h2>

<p>Reviews of the banana diet for both patients and physicians, the most positive. The fact that by means of bananas can not only &ldquo;eat&rdquo; and satisfying lose weight, but also greatly improve the condition of the gastro &ndash; intestinal tract, cardio &ndash; vascular system and blood circulation.</p>

<p>From &ndash; due to the high content of potassium in the pulp of banana (360 mg per 100 g product), magnesium (27 mg), and fiber, this miracle &ndash; the fruit greatly improves the water &ndash; salt metabolism in the body, good displays excess fluid (edema), toxins, toxins, excess glucose and bad cholesterol and stimulates the smooth operation of the intestine.</p>

<p>Because bananas almost do not cause allergic reactions, are an excellent source of energy and the supplier of many essential vitamins and minerals, they are often included as complementary foods into the diet of infants, pregnant women and nursing mothers. Assign them as well as dietary and impaired postoperative patients, the elderly and athletes.</p>

<p>In addition, bananas are useful for depression (from &ndash; for the content of pleasure hormone serotonin), chronic fatigue syndrome, hypertension, intestinal problems (constipation, diarrhea), gastritis, reduced hemoglobin, diseases of the bladder and biliary tract, arthritis, heartburn.</p>

<p>Banana days, in contrast to other severe handling fruit monodiets days (cucumber, apple, carrot), due to the presence of large amounts of natural fruit sugars (fructose, glucose, sucrose) are less hungry and promote more rapid and prolonged saturation.</p>

<p>Do not stick to the banana diet for people with individual intolerance to bananas, as well as in diseases of thrombophlebitis and varicose veins. The fact that bananas are a group of products, thickening the blood, so they should be avoided when varicose veins and circulatory disorders of blood vessels. List of products, blood thinners and advice on therapeutic nutrition to varicose veins, read the article on our website.</p>

<p>In diabetes of both types of banana diet is not contraindicated, but because of the high sugar content, it must be agreed upon with the attending physician to correctly calculate individual daily amount of carbohydrates (bread units BU) and eliminate sudden increases in blood glucose levels. Detailed treatment recommendations for patients with diabetes first and second types are described in the articles about diets for diabetics.</p>

<h2>Features choice of fruit for the banana diet</h2>

<p>Pick the fruit for banana mono-diet is of great importance. Slimming perfect ripe &ldquo;fruit&rdquo; Bananas &ndash; rich yellow color, soft, thin-skinned and of medium length. If you bought a slightly unripe fruit, do not rush to use them, first wrap in plastic paper and leave for a few days in a dark place to ripen.</p>

<p>Do not buy so-called &ldquo;feed&rdquo; bananas &ndash; long, green and thick rind and dried, which is several times high-calorie fresh. Before use, the fruit must be thoroughly clean not only on the skin, but also on the white threads, leaving only the pulp of a ripe.</p>

<h3>Strong banana diet for 3 days</h3>

<p>Banana diet for 3 days, often referred to as a banana &ndash; milk diet is the easiest and one banana a strict diet. Daily menu milk &ndash; banana diet consists of 3 &ndash; bananas and 3 &ndash; cup of skim milk or yogurt (1%).</p>

<p>Divide the specified amount of food for 5 &ndash; 6 portions and eat at regular intervals throughout the day &ndash; split meals to avoid the appearance of a strong sense of hunger. Fruits and dairy products can be used as separate from each other, and as a banana yogurt or neck &ndash; whip banana yogurt or milk using a blender.</p>

<p>Additionally, throughout the day as possible drink plain water and herbal teas without sugar, it promotes better bowel cleansing and normalization of the gastro &ndash; intestinal tract. The last meal plan no later than 3 hours before bedtime.</p>

<h3>Banana Diet 7 days</h3>

<p>The seven-day option is not as strict as three days, and does not limit the amount of fruit consumed &ndash; are allowed to eat per day to 1.5 kg of peeled ripe bananas. However, slimming process in this embodiment is quite effective for night out on average about 1 kilogram of body weight.</p>

<p>As soon as you feel hungry, Eat one fruit at once. If it is a very &ldquo;hungry&rdquo;, as a source of complete protein can be added to the menu 1 boiled egg. From drinks are allowed in unlimited quantities of water and herbal tea without sugar, consumption of dairy products with the exception.</p>

<h3>Curd &ndash; banana diet</h3>

<p>Curd &ndash; banana slimming option for up to 4 days, involves alternation of banana and cheese fasting days and makes it quite effectively reduce weight, up to 3 &ndash; 4 pounds. Since cheese is quite a varied and useful product, banana &ndash; curd alternation transferred easily and is therefore very popular with losing weight.</p>

<p>The first and third days &ndash; cheese:</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; 120 g low-fat cottage cheese (up to 5% fat), fruit;
Lunch &ndash; 120 g cottage cheese, vegetable salad without oil;
Dinner &ndash; 120 grams cottage cheese, grapefruit.</p>

<p>The second and fourth days &ndash; banana:</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; banana, 120 g low-fat yogurt or cottage cheese;
Lunch &ndash; 2 banana, 1 boiled egg;
Dinner &ndash; 200 grams of cooked lean meat, 1 &ndash; 2 bananas.</p>

<h2>Exit after the banana diet tips and advice</h2>

<p>Longer than the recommended 3 &ndash; 7 days to comply with the banana mono-diet is not recommended. First, despite the usefulness of the product, banana slimming, like any other mono-diet is not completely balanced and can cause serious injury.</p>

<p>A in &ndash; Second, our body is designed wisely and in a few days can adapt to any conditions and, if necessary, the power-saving mode. Therefore, for more than the recommended terms of losing weight is not only harmful but also impractical because the weight will fall either very slow or it hard to stand still &ndash; nutritionists effect of this phenomenon is called a &ldquo;plateau&rdquo; (described in more detail in the diet roller coaster diet and Ladder).</p>

<p>Exit after kefir &ndash; the banana diet, as well as following any diet, despite the achieved effect, must be smooth and gradual &ndash; is necessary in order to permanently fix the result. Within a week, gently insert the usual foods and observe moderation &ndash; if you start to eat off of hungry days, the weight comes back very quickly.</p>

<p>If losing weight on bananas was comfortable for you, start to practice weekly unloading banana days &ndash; this will easily support the weight without the stress and shocks. To the menu was not too severe, it offers a variety of delicious and hearty recipes.</p>

<p>Banana &ndash; fruit salad &ndash; cut slices of banana and add the slices of apple, pear or peach. The second option salad &ndash; add walnuts and lettuce.</p>

<p>Oatmeal with banana &ndash; Boil water for oatmeal, add back milk and finely chopped banana slices.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[American diet for weight loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/american-diet-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:39:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/american-diet-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/diet-roller-coaster-diet-dinner-minus/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Diet roller coaster, diet dinner minus" alt="American diet for weight loss. Roller coaster and minus the dinner diets"> Diet Rollercoaster allows you to securely lose weight by speeding up metabolism.</p>

<p>Diet roller coaster developed by American nutritionist Martin Cathan more than 30 years ago and in that time has gained wide popularity. It is one of the most effective ways to reduce weight and allows the presence of physical activity, reduce up to 7 pounds in a week.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>The essence of the diet roller coaster</h2>

<p>There is a simple explanation. The fact is that our body is able to quickly adjust and adapt to any diet. To do this, it is enough to just a few days, after which it includes saving mode (power saving), so the metabolism (metabolism) slows down and stops weight plummeted.</p>

<p>Dr. Martin Katan take into account this feature, and developed the technique in such a way as to literally &ldquo;confuse&rdquo; the body, preventing it &ldquo;remember&rdquo; the amount of calories consumed and not allowing to adapt to the new regime.</p>

<p>Recommended them daily caloric intake ranges up &ndash; down, from minimum to maximum, which gave the name of a popular diet roller coaster ride. Through this approach to nutrition he managed to lose about 30 pounds of dead weight and to help numerous people lose weight.</p>

<h2>Diet Rollercoaster menu</h2>

<p>Follow the diet roller coaster is simple, you have to do only the willpower to break away and not to follow through, and meticulous counting calories. Product Composition, unlike most other programs weight reduction is not critical. That is, you can eat all you want, above all, to keep within the recommended number of calories.</p>

<p>The most severe and difficult from a psychological point of view, are the first three days, which are allowed to eat only 600 calories. These days will be very hungry all the time and will want to eat, but you have to strictly follow your plan and understand that it will be easier. To do this, try to choose the daily caloric not chocolates, biscuits and light carbohydrate and low-calorie vegetables, fruits, low-fat dairy products and cereals on the water.</p>

<p>Since these products are made up of fiber and slowly digestible carbohydrates, they provide a feeling of satiety for a long time and do not give a break to &ldquo;Jordania&rdquo;. In addition, fiber helps avoid the inevitable with insufficient food constipation, thoroughly clean the intestines and populate it useful microflora.</p>

<p>Do not forget about the copious drinking regimen, drink plenty of simple and non-carbonated mineral water and herbal tea (without sugar). This will not only enhance the cleansing process in the intestine, but also help to avoid excessive hunger. Because we all know that people often confuse hunger with a feeling of thirst. Sometimes it is enough to drink a glass of water, and there is no longer want to.</p>

<p>Thus, the scheme of alternation calories, designed for 3 weeks:</p>

<p>The first &ndash; the third day &ndash; 600 calories;
Fourth &ndash; the seventh day &ndash; 900 calories;
The eighth &ndash; the fourteenth day &ndash; 1200 calories;
The fifteenth &ndash; seventeenth day &ndash; 600 calories;
Eighteen &ndash; twenty-one days &ndash; 900 kcal.</p>

<p>Daily menu, as already mentioned, can be anything from any of the products, dishes and combinations. But to you it was easier to navigate, give an approximate daily food intake by 600, 900 and 1200 kcal. You can take it as a basis and change the components in its sole discretion, according to the energy value of foods (see table on the caloric content of products and labels) and the individual taste preferences.</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; unsweetened tea, a small piece of rye bread;
Lunch &ndash; 100 grams of boiled beef and cooked rice, a salad of radish and cucumber without oil;
Dinner &ndash; 1 boiled egg and a glass of low-fat yogurt.</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; black tea (you can add 1 liter. sugar) with rye crackers, apple green;
Dinner &ndash; boiled or steamed fish, pasta and vegetable salad (100 g). Tea (sugar content not exceeding 1 tsp);
Dinner &ndash; 1 boiled egg, 100 grams of cottage cheese (low-fat), and a small banana.</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; 200 grams of oatmeal (on the water and no oil), tea (sugar 1 tsp) with rye croutons;
Dinner &ndash; boiled chicken (200 g), buckwheat porridge with a small piece of butter (100 g);
Dinner &ndash; Assorted fruit salad of apples, grapes, bananas, pineapple.</p>

<p>During the day, between meals, snacks are permitted &ndash; 1 cup low-fat yogurt, a small banana.</p>

<p>After a full course of 21 days, you can gradually return to your normal diet. According to Dr. Katana, during this period can not reliably &ldquo;confuse&rdquo; the body, so the result is stored for a long period of time and will have to repeat the whole cycle will not soon.</p>

<p>It should be noted that to observe the &ldquo;roller coaster&rdquo; only healthy people, the beauty and harmony should not be achieved at the expense of health. Slimming prohibited under the scheme &ldquo;600-900-1200&rdquo; with the gastro &ndash; intestinal tract, pregnant women, nursing mothers, as well as any chronic illnesses. Even if you feel perfectly healthy, losing weight before check with your doctor.</p>

<p>Despite the fact that physical exercise can significantly, by almost 2-fold, to enhance the effect of the diet (with exercise you can lose up to 10 pounds, without them &ndash; to 6 pounds), heavy physical exertion banned because they can lead to a sharp deterioration  It is useful to practice yoga, walking, pilates, aerobics and leisurely cycling. To distract from the food, walk a little more in the fresh air and get enough sleep, at least 8 &ndash; 9 hours a day.</p>

<h2>American diet &ldquo;Dinner minus&rdquo;</h2>

<p>The American Diet Dinner minus does not promise weight loss in 3 days, but it is very comfortable to compliance and requires meticulous counting calories eaten each piece as a roller coaster. In addition, during the follow-up system, &ldquo;dinner minus&rdquo;, the body produces the correct and healthy eating habits &ndash; consume a major amount of fat in the first half of the day, when the active hormones are responsible for their split.</p>

<p>It is based on the familiar childhood postulates that at night there are harmful and need to be fed in accordance with the well-known saying &ldquo;Eat breakfast yourself, share dinner with a friend, a dinner give to the enemy.&rdquo; That is, the authors offer a methodology completely forget about this concept as dinner and after 17 hours is recommended to drink only ordinary water.</p>

<p>Thus, the basic principles of the diet minus dinner:</p>

<ul>
<li>Copious drinking regime &ndash; drink at least 2 liters of water daily;</li>
<li>Last meal be carried out not later than 17 hours;</li>
<li>Decrease in the consumption of animal fat diet, replacing them with vegetable. Just keep in mind that fats can not be completely ruled out, suitable for all common sense;</li>
<li>Choose a menu for only quality products without trans fats, dyes, preservatives, emulsifiers, preferring fast food nutrition healthy homemade food.</li>
</ul>


<p>Composing your diet, avoid distortions in any direction. If you strongly want something sweet, do not deny yourself &ndash; eat a small piece of dessert in the first half of the day. Do not focus only on choosing low-calorie foods, pay more attention to their usefulness and naturalness. Remember, the beauty and harmony can only give a healthy body, provided a balance of everything necessary for the normal functioning &ndash; proteins, fats, carbohydrates, vitamins and trace elements.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surgical treatment of hemorrhoids: the cost of surgery to remove nodes]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/surgical-treatment-of-hemorrhoids-the-cost-of-surgery-to-remove-nodes/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:22:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/surgical-treatment-of-hemorrhoids-the-cost-of-surgery-to-remove-nodes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoids-surgery-cost/14.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="hemorrhoids surgery cost" alt="Surgical treatment of hemorrhoids: the cost of surgery to remove nodes"> If a man appeared for the first time in the life of hemorrhoids, he usually tries to take all measures to get rid of the unpleasant symptoms. If the patient in time refers to the proctologist, complaining of discomfort during bowel movements, itching, cracking or bleeding from hemorrhoids, you can quickly get rid of the early stages. However, the disease often becomes extremely sleazy. Almost all patients go to the doctor already after conservative treatment of hemorrhoids is no longer effective. In this case, the doctor carefully examines the patient and determines the future strategy of the treatment of the disease. Often, the final stage of this process is the surgical treatment of hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>If doctors detect external hemorrhoids requiring mechanical removal, to begin the patient is usually prescribed minimally invasive techniques that do not require surgical intervention. However, they are not suitable for all patients, so a large percentage of people suffering from hemorrhoids, gets on the operating table.</p>

<p>Do I need surgery if you have hemorrhoids? As mentioned above, the doctors try to minimize the chances of radical treatments. If there is a chance to eliminate the disease conservative or non-surgical method, the doctor uses all techniques that can have an effect. Most often, the operation shall be appointed, if a person is present hemorrhoids grade 3 complications. If the disease is the first or second step, the patient may help non-surgical hemorrhoid sclerotherapy.</p>

<h2>How do the surgery and what to choose?</h2>

<p>Today in medicine there are two main types of surgery to remove hemorrhoids. First &ndash; this is a hemorrhoidectomy for Milligan-Morgan. Second &ndash; gemorroidopeksiya by Longo. Longo operation differs from the operation of Milligan-Morgan. With this procedure, the hosts themselves are not deleted, but removes part of the rectum. By removing a portion of mucosal blood flow is disturbed nodes, whereupon they atrophy. The intervention on the Milligan-Morgan exterior and interior nodes are excised and then sewn sutures.</p>

<p>How much surgery? Data close to the end of the article. On the appropriateness of the procedure you can tell your doctor. As for the criteria for the appointment of each of the types of intervention, they can be represented as a simple table.</p>

<h2>Do I need to prepare?</h2>

<p>Preparation for surgery is performed in both cases. Both types of procedures performed in a hospital, so patients necessarily prepared for anesthesia and the surgery in advance. Hemorrhoidectomy and operation Longo require prior hospitalization. As for anesthesia, then the operation can Longo local anesthesia, although most often it is performed under general intravenous anesthesia. Hemorrhoidectomy for Milligan-Morgan performed only under intravenous anesthesia. Also, the patient can make epidural anesthesia. Local anesthesia is hardly found. Preparing for Surgery Hemorrhoids usually are not too durable, but you can not avoid this step.</p>

<h2>How long is the surgery?</h2>

<p>Another criterion &ndash; the duration of the procedure. The operation to Milligan-Morgan takes about half an hour, and the operation Longo lasts no more than twenty minutes. Tolerated both procedures are equally good, but after the surgery the patient requires medical supervision. Treatment after surgery includes preventive tools for toning the veins.</p>

<h2>Stay in a hospital</h2>

<p>After the surgery, the patient remains Longo in hospital under observation for 2-3 days. When hemorrhoidectomy hospital stay may increase up to a week. Deserve special attention, patients who develop complications of thrombosed hemorrhoids: surgery in this case should only start after the relief of the inflammatory process. Do not put the patient on the operating table during an exacerbation. It should be noted that the cost of surgery to remove hemorrhoids almost never include the cost of hospital stays. If you are being treated at a private clinic, check in advance how much are the day following hospital treatment.</p>

<h2>Terms of rehabilitation</h2>

<p>In contrast to the non-invasive techniques, after which the patient can go to work the next day, after surgical treatment of hemorrhoids patient must comply with bed rest to a week. Temporary disability after intervention by Milligan-Morgan can reach months, and after the operation is issued weekly Longo hospital.</p>

<h2>Pain</h2>

<p>How to be a painful operation? This question is asked all the patients who were prescribed surgical excision or removal of nodes of the rectal mucosa. According to experts, in operation Longo pain is negligible. In the case of the operation for Milligan-Morgan pain observed in the postoperative period in almost all patients. This procedure is a significant drawback, however, this does not diminish its effectiveness. While the patient is in the hospital, doctors removed the pain with the help of powerful analgesics. Absolutely painless surgical removal of hemorrhoids does not exist. The only option &ndash; a minimally invasive procedure. With their help, you will get a low-cost and rapid treatment of hemorrhoids &ndash; the prices of these procedures are low. However, many advanced cases surgery is the only curative treatment of the disease.</p>

<p>It should be noted also that the operation Longo is assigned only when an internal hemorrhoid. If you are running outside or combined hemorrhoids, then applied to eliminate the disease hemorrhoidectomy by Milligan-Morgan.</p>

<h2>Contra</h2>

<p>Advantage Longo operation is that it is practically no contraindications. It is quite easy to carry, even if the patient is suffering from a serious illness. With this method it is possible to eliminate even postpartum hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>As for the Milligan-Morgan, then to her, there are a range of contraindications. Among them are the following:</p>

<ul>
<li>HIV;</li>
<li>Crohn&rsquo;s Disease;</li>
<li>Pregnancy and lactation</li>
<li>Cancer;</li>
<li>The aggravation of chronic diseases;</li>
<li>Acute inflammation in the body.</li>
</ul>


<h2>How much is hemorrhoid surgery?</h2>

<p>Both methods require a certain investment, but the Milligan-Morgan different low cost, unlike the method Longo, since the latter requires expensive equipment surgeons.</p>

<p>The average price for an operation to remove hemorrhoids is:</p>

<ul>
<li>The method of Longo &ndash; the cost of surgery is about $ 1,200;</li>
<li>The method of Milligan-Morgan &ndash; 650 &ndash; $ 800</li>
</ul>


<h2>Complications</h2>

<p>As with any surgical procedure, surgery to treat hemorrhoids can be followed by subsequent complications. The most common complications</p>

<ul>
<li>Bleeding</li>
<li>Rectal and vaginal fistula</li>
<li>An infectious infestation of the affected tissues</li>
<li>An inflammatory process</li>
</ul>


<p>Doctors tend to avoid complications, and for which there is a post-operative hospital.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suppository for Hemorrhoids - what is best for treatment?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/suppository-for-hemorrhoids-what-is-best-for-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:21:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/suppository-for-hemorrhoids-what-is-best-for-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/suppository-for-hemorrhoids/13.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Suppository for hemorrhoids" alt="Suppository for Hemorrhoids - what is best for treatment?"> Suppository from hemorrhoids are a conservative method of getting rid of the disease. Therefore, they can not always be used in the treatment of this disease. Apply suppository should be started only after having been accurately diagnosed. In this paper we describe in general what the existing market more efficient suppository, how best to use them, by treating the condition. To know the specific list of suppository for hemorrhoids with a description of their properties and recommendations &ndash; click on a link (you can open a new tab if you first want to finish reading this article).</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>It is important to understand &ndash; to the question &ldquo;what is better spark&rdquo; in a particular case, the answer can only be a specialist conducting the diagnosis of your condition. In drugstores are very different &ndash; they differ among themselves on the nature of the action. Some are designed to reduce the pain that causes the disease. Other suppositories have a healing effect. This means that these suppository for hemorrhoids help wounds heal faster and existing cracks in the rectum and anus. Still others &ndash; these are the best suppository for hemorrhoids bleeding. They are able to stop the flow of blood for couples of improving its clotting.</p>

<h2>What are the suppository from hemorrhoids to choose?</h2>

<p>Sold suppository for hemorrhoids and fissures, from internal and external forms of the disease vary in price. But this is often an indication that cheap suppository worse than their more expensive counterparts. Usually cures for hemorrhoids local production cost less than importations, imported. Price consists of several parameters. In the case of foreign drugs, their price increases due to shipping costs, customs duties, and so on</p>

<p>What suppository for hemorrhoids, you choose yourself. It all depends on your financial capabilities. Somebody&rsquo;s power to obtain the most effective suppository imported at a high enough price. And someone can buy only cheap, chinese.</p>

<h2>What are the suppository and their composition?</h2>

<p>Pain suppository with hemorrhoids. Their main purpose is to reduce the pain that causes the disease of the rectum. They consist of novocaine or anestezina. These chemical elements are very well remove all the existing discomfort, itching and pain. However, the use of anesthetics has a number of contraindications. First, they are very much increase blood pressure. Therefore, these suppository can not be used in the treatment of patients with hypertension disease. Also avoid the use of suppositories in the elderly, when increased pressure is normal because of age-related changes in the human body.
Hemostatic suppository. The composition of these suppository are such components as Dicynone, menadione, calcium chloride. All of these chemical elements increase blood clotting. This is a very important fact in the treatment of bleeding hemorrhoids. Blood loss, if not stop, can cause anemia. This disease is not only dangerous to human health, but also for his life.
Anti-hemorrhoids suppository. The composition of the suppository includes various components which have a bactericidal effect. The best preparations of this group contain sea buckthorn oil. It not only helps speed the healing of wounds and fractures in the rectum and anus, but also kills bacteria, germs and other microorganisms that caused the inflammation. Have a similar effect and such components of vegetable appointment as propolis, tea tree oil, an extract of St. John&rsquo;s wort, yarrow, and so on</p>

<h2>Suppository for hemorrhoids treatment &ndash; how to use?</h2>

<p>Of course, suppository today are effective in the treatment of the disease, along with pills. However, even the best of them will not have the desired effect if they are not properly used. It is important to know what you need suppository, how to insert them when it is best to carry out medical procedures and how many times.</p>

<p>Suppository for hemorrhoids need to put in the evening before you are going to go to bed. Well, if the procedure before you empty the bowel. After the act of defecation is necessary to make water treatments. The anal opening must be clean prior to treatment. The suppository is necessary to open and remove the protective cover. This should be done as early as fully finished state, so you can directly enter into the anus of a candle. Otherwise, it will start to melt. After the candle was introduced into the rectum, you should immediately lie down on your back and lie down so at least thirty minutes. This is usually sufficient to ensure that the drug has melted and fell into the bloodstream. More specific nuances about the use of suppository for hemorrhoids can be read in the instructions that came with a particular drug.</p>

<p>Recommend suppository may only your doctor who knows the specific features of the disease. Even if you have a whole list of these drugs, it does not guarantee that they will help you. Only your doctor is aware of your particular state of diseases of the rectum and can choose the right treatment.</p>

<p>Hemorrhoid Treatment folk remedies possible. But any recipe before you start using it, must be approved by your doctor. Most methods of folk medicine used in combination with traditional therapies, help accelerate recovery person.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Constipation and hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/constipation-and-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:20:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/constipation-and-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoids-and-constipation/12.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Hemorrhoids and constipation" alt="Constipation and hemorrhoids"> Chronic constipation and hemorrhoids, is the most frequent combination, and related hemorrhoids condition. Sometimes impossible to determine the priority of hemorrhoids and constipation secondary and vice versa. Hemorrhoids without constipation is rare, while those suffering from chronic constipation, almost without exception, noted bleeding during bowel movements, pain, itching in the anus and in the long history, prolapsed hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>If the hemorrhoids in a certain number of cases can occur quite early in young adults (usually a family history of hereditary), the constipation often develop later in connection with chronic jetlag nutrition and diets desired composition.
Constipation greatly exacerbate the development of hemorrhoids, accelerate the emergence of its clinical manifestations. The complaints are typical of hemorrhoids, there are patients, usually after a period of difficulty chair, and one of the biggest complaints &ndash; constipation themselves. Thus, the struggle with constipation at any stage of manifestation of hemorrhoids and even before any of its manifestations in patients with identified during routine inspections hemorrhoid symptoms (asymptomatic stage) is the most important conservative measure of prevention and treatment of this disease.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, some of the doctors to whom falls sick hemorrhoids, do not pay sufficient attention to the treatment of constipation in this population, which largely negates the efforts of conservative therapy and have a negative impact on the outcomes of operations for hemorrhoids. With all of the many facilities offered by the treatment of hemorrhoids, including the application of sclerosing injections and surgical interventions, relapse is likely unless the patient will or encounter constipation. So treat constipation in patients with hemorrhoids is necessary, regardless of the underlying cause.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First aid for hemorrhoids and its exacerbation or bleeding]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/first-aid-for-hemorrhoids-and-its-exacerbation-or-bleeding/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:19:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/first-aid-for-hemorrhoids-and-its-exacerbation-or-bleeding</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-help-hemorrhoids/11.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="How to help hemorrhoids" alt="First aid for hemorrhoids and its exacerbation or bleeding"> Normally the development of hemorrhoids is gradual, but there are cases when the disease suddenly catches. The aggravation of hemorrhoids, accompanied by bleeding, may be triggered by excessive physical work and heavy lifting, often &ndash; poor diet and processes such as childbirth in women. In such cases, first aid for hemorrhoids need no less than any other disease.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Bleeding, sharp pain in the anus, stool problems, constipation &ndash; all manifestations of an exacerbation of the disease. Typically, the cause of bleeding is hard stool that their sharp edges damage pile. After the damage of blood hemorrhoids and is accompanied by a sharp pain, itching.</p>

<h2>First Aid with acute hemorrhoids &ndash; what to do</h2>

<p>Despite the fact that in most cases with acute hemorrhoids is no serious threat to the organism does not occur at the sight of blood patients begin to panic and often exacerbate the situation by their own actions. Also not to be confused with hemorrhoids prolapse of the rectum.</p>

<p>Here are the basic steps for first aid in case of aggravation of hemorrhoids:</p>

<ul>
<li>Remain calm and do not in any way straining with constipation, try to get rid of the remnants of feces. This way, you can avoid additional damage and reduce the bleeding sites.</li>
<li>Change the position of the body of standing or sitting on the escalation try to lie more &ldquo;face up&rdquo; by removing the stress on the muscles of the anus.</li>
<li>To avoid getting an infection in the body &ndash; most often use the bath with cool (room temperature) water. On the road or on a business trip or cleaning the help cool off. It will also reduce the pain manifestations.</li>
<li>Make an enema &ndash; it will download the intestines and promotes the healing of wounds aggravated.</li>
<li>Immediate start a diet, eating prunes and fiber, the exclusion from the diet of &ldquo;heavy&rdquo; foods, alcohol and starchy foods will lead to the fact that the next time the process of defecation is not constipation, hemorrhoids will not be damaged and begin to heal.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Folk remedies to help</h2>

<p>Since the constant aggravation help coming stool, damaged areas simply do not have time to heal, then in such cases it is recommended to use special herbal teas. For example, the infusion of herbs pochechuynoy has a strong laxative and hemostatic effect.</p>

<p>Will be able to help with bleeding following extracts: yarrow, cranberry bark, bloodroot goose. It is also recommended to take sea buckthorn oil. Use oil can be both inside and outside. Lubrication of the anus, and the use of enemas with oils will help reduce pain, heal hemorrhoids.</p>

<h2>Surgical treatment of acute hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>The first and most necessary condition for successful treatment &ndash; a distinction hemorrhoids from rectal prolapse. At home, perform this procedure, you can not do, so you should consult a doctor in the shortest possible time. During the examination, the doctor will determine the state of the anal area, and the presence of hemorrhoids dropped.</p>

<p>Following the procedure of collecting the necessary data, the doctor will prescribe a treatment. In cases where conservative treatment is ineffective, surgical intervention. The goal of this therapy will be to excision of hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>Even this operation can not always guarantee 100% results. It all depends on the many features of the disease. In this case, complications may give the late stages of developing hemorrhoids, pathological features of the structure of the rectum and anus.</p>

<h2>Treatment of bleeding hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>The main symptom of hemorrhoids &ndash; a bright red color of blood. Color blood indicates that the blood flows from the injured arteries. To stop the bleeding often use enemas.</p>

<p>Enemas sodium tannin promote partial coagulation of proteins and form a protective film. Due to this, there is a reduction of pain and narrowed blood vessels of the rectum. Also possible enema 3% hydrogen peroxide. The time an enema is 2 &ndash; 3 days.</p>

<p>In the event of prolonged bleeding continued urgent need to see a doctor who will prescribe the necessary examination.</p>

<h2>Lifestyle hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Hemorrhoids &ndash; this is not a death sentence. When the first symptoms of the disease is urgently think about changing lifestyles. Very often acute hemorrhoids catches people pursuing &ldquo;sedentary&rdquo; lifestyle. Under these conditions increases the risk of congestion in the rectal area. Avoid similar situations and bleeding will help: swimming, running, frequent walking, dancing.</p>

<p>Do not neglect the rules of personal hygiene. When hemorrhoids after each toilet visit, it is recommended to wash the perineum with cool water. The use of toilet paper may enhance the already strong pain.</p>

<p>It is also worth diet. In the treatment of hemorrhoids is necessary to settle a chair, because it should not be hard. It is recommended to eat fruits and vegetables that contain a sufficient amount of fiber. Dietary fiber in this case will help to improve the formation of stools. It is necessary to limit the use of sharp and salty foods.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which specialist to seek help with hemorrhoids?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/which-specialist-to-seek-help-with-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:18:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/which-specialist-to-seek-help-with-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoids-specialist/10.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Hemorrhoids specialist" alt="Which specialist to seek help with hemorrhoids?"> Presumably, you have hemorrhoids: which doctor to go? How can he be able to help you? Consider these questions in this section. It happens that people like and would love to go to a medical professional, but to what exactly &ndash; do not know&hellip; It complexes: ask for advice from someone ashamed and bear &ndash; strength is not enough. It is a vicious circle, a chain which we now will help you break!</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>If you want to help was the most complete, you&rsquo;ll like this doctor: treating hemorrhoids quickly and at a professional level that it has experience in this specialization. And, most importantly, who is not ashamed to apply, since for him the disease from the category of ordinary! As many have already guessed, this is a proctologist.</p>

<p>It coloproctologist treats hemorrhoids any stage. He examines, if necessary, appoint additional surveys, analyzing the situation, and eventually prescribe effective treatment.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hemorrhoids may burst]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoids-may-burst/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:17:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoids-may-burst</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/burst-hemorrhoid/9.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="burst hemorrhoid" alt="Hemorrhoids may burst"> Hemorrhoids &ndash; an extension of the veins of the rectum and anus (therefore distinguish between internal and external hemorrhoids). Internal hemorrhoids are most often associated with constipation. Solid excrement put pressure on blood vessels of the rectum and extend it. At a pressure vessel can burst and starts bleeding. If nothing is done, inflamed tissue and form nodes. These vessels can also quickly irritated and inflamed.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>The risk factors &ndash; obesity and primarily sedentary lifestyle with sedentary work.</p>

<p>Prevention:</p>

<ul>
<li>Follow the regular chair, with the anus good grease, do not sit too long &ldquo;on the throne&rdquo; as a result of high pressure can burst blood vessels in the rectum.</li>
<li>Proper diet, rich in dietary fiber. Reduce weight.</li>
<li>Enough movement in the fresh air, walking and gymnastics.</li>
<li>Squeeze and relax the muscles of the rectum. &ndash; Anal hygiene, cold shower.</li>
</ul>


<p>Self:</p>

<ul>
<li>All measures taken for constipation.</li>
<li>Herbal therapy: dandelion juice (root) and leaves (broth), bloodroot goose (compress), yarrow and chamomile (sitz bath), crushed buckeye or calendula (wraps and bathing), oak bark (sitz bath).</li>
<li>Essential oils: geranium oil or rosemary (internal use).</li>
<li>Sitz bath with pine needles.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get rid of hemorrhoids and fast forever?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-get-rid-of-hemorrhoids-and-fast-forever/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:16:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-get-rid-of-hemorrhoids-and-fast-forever</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-get-rid-of-external-hemorrhoids/8.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="How to get rid of external hemorrhoids" alt="How to get rid of hemorrhoids and fast forever?"> Hemorrhoids varicose veins, located in the rectal area, is familiar to numerous people. Suffer from hemorrhoids and women and men, regardless of age and social status. Once established, the disease causes considerable discomfort to the patient. Because of the fear of going to the doctor many launch illness, resulting in getting rid of the hemorrhoid becomes a time-consuming process, it becomes chronic and causes more severe symptoms. However, there are ways to get rid of hemorrhoids for good.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Is it possible to quickly get rid of hemorrhoids?</h2>

<p>The answer to this question is yes, but only if you do not just perform the procedure at home, but also follow the doctor&rsquo;s recommendations. Visit the doctor is even if you manage to find out how to get rid of the unpleasant symptoms quickly. As you know, there are hidden varieties of the disease, in which almost no symptoms, but that does not mean that at the slightest risk factor for the disease does not remind you again about yourself.</p>

<p>In particular, the hidden internal forms often manifest themselves in the form of postpartum hemorrhoids in pregnant women, pelvic veins who are experiencing severe pressure during the passage of the child through the birth canal. If time does not track the subtle signs of internal flow, increases the probability of occurrence of acute external hemorrhoids, the treatment of which is a rather unpleasant process &ndash; get rid of the hemorrhoid will be more difficult.</p>

<p>The sooner you begin treatment, the less the likelihood of external hemorrhoids at an advanced stage. Any doctor will confirm that in the early stages of the disease can actually be cured in a short period of time.</p>

<p>It is important to follow the rules of prevention: diet, normalizing bowel, personal hygiene, lack of serious exercise, regular walks and easy exercises that promotes blood flow to the pelvic organs.</p>

<p>In addition to doctor&rsquo;s appointments, you can learn how to get rid of hemorrhoids for good in the home folk remedies.</p>

<p>In particular, getting rid of unpleasant and painful symptoms occur, if you regularly do hip baths with anti-inflammatory herbal decoction: chamomile, calendula, sage, oak bark. Furthermore, to get rid of hemorrhoids outer cone can, if regular addition to ointments and creams applied compresses herbs. If the packs are cool, the effect is more prominent and fast.</p>

<p>Another folk remedy &ndash; garlic compress. Mashed garlic mixed with a small amount of water at room temperature and applied to the area of ​​the anus. You can also enter into balls, smeared with garlic mixture.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prevention of hemorrhoids exercise]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/prevention-of-hemorrhoids-exercise/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:15:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/prevention-of-hemorrhoids-exercise</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoids-and-exercise/7.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Hemorrhoids and exercise" alt="Prevention of hemorrhoids exercise"> Hemorrhoids are a serious and severe disease. It is often accompanied by excruciating pain and may even end serious operation, if not treated in time. It is a very serious and sensitive disease, and many are ashamed to even talk to your doctor.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Gram prevention is worth pounds of hemorrhoid treatment.</p>

<p>And so, hemorrhoids easier to prevent than to cure. For this reason, you need to learn how to do therapeutic exercises for hemorrhoids.
The main group at risk are people sedentary work, drivers, and those who have digestive problems and constipation as a result.
Also, if you do not exercise, a little walk in the fresh air, or do not do, or at least some gymnastics.</p>

<p>What these exercises for hemorrhoids for you and need to learn to do them without fail.</p>

<h2>Physical therapy for hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Lie on your back, bend your knees, the feet placed shoulder-width and not together, palm to rest on the floor, arms open. With a deep breath, lift your pelvis up straining buttocks, the load of the body at the same time try to tilt the chin, exhale down.</p>

<p>This exercise combines several medical factors, it is primarily changing the pressure in the chest, known as hemorrhoids is due to varicose veins.</p>

<p>Doing these movements by muscle tension during inspiration, the pressure in the chest falls, there is a siphon effect that helps drain blood from the abdominal cavity and thus to prevent the filling veins with blood.</p>

<p>The following exercises should be performed for hemorrhoids immediately after the first. Lying on his back legs to clasp his hands closer to his knees with his head on the floor, exhale, pull the knees to the chest lifting your buttocks off the floor, with inspiration to go back to the starting position. It is necessary to imagine that the back is glued to the tape to the floor and when you exhale you unstick it, and when inhaling glue the back. The chin is slightly pressed to stretched neck and his head is on the floor.</p>

<p>This therapeutic exercises for hemorrhoids is very useful for the reason that stimulates colonic motility, as is well known chronic constipation is one of the risk factors for which there is a hemorrhoid.</p>

<h2>Exercise therapy for hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Sit down, place the palms shoulder-width apart, take steps back propped up on his toes, pelvis in the top position. Then pushing hard to breath hands and one leg to lift up, exhale on the lower, then the other leg, and so alternately.</p>

<p>Flip this situation improves venous drainage by gravity, the blood that used to work was to go up against the force of gravity, in this case very easily rushes toward the heart. And those varicose veins, which are in the pelvic area and are the basis for the emergence of hemorrhoids, they are fallen down. Accordingly, this leads to a reduction in pain symptoms in people who already have hemorrhoids, and in whom he had just run into.</p>

<h2>Time to preventive exercises</h2>

<p>10-15min and such exercises for hemorrhoids &ndash; this is what you can spend, so you did not have it. Also, do not forget that if you have a sedentary job, you also need to do a little every hour break, walking for a few minutes. At the weekend try as often as possible to visit the open air. And as his time Arnold Schwarzenegger said: &ldquo;Do periodically abdominal exercises abdominal and two months later his muscles will thank you&rdquo;.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Severe pain of hemorrhoids - how to fight?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/severe-pain-of-hemorrhoids-how-to-fight/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:14:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/severe-pain-of-hemorrhoids-how-to-fight</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/relieve-hemorrhoid-pain/6.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Relieve hemorrhoid pain" alt="Severe pain of hemorrhoids - how to fight?"> Hemorrhoids are a serious disease that occurs almost every second. Disease begins all different for different reasons:</p>

<!-- more -->


<ul>
<li>Sedentary work;</li>
<li>The common cold;</li>
<li>Chronic digestive diseases;</li>
<li>Frequent emotional distress;</li>
<li>After giving birth.</li>
</ul>


<p>Some long period suffer from constipation, and only later appears varicose wreath in the anus and in the rectum. Sometimes the first start strong the pain of hemorrhoids, and then distressing effects.</p>

<p>No matter how quickly the disease develops and what factors contributed to the development of the disease, hemorrhoids cause pain, discomfort, and often profuse bleeding. A person who has a disease should be able to without the help of experts to remove the pain, or at least know how to relieve hemorrhoid pain.</p>

<h2>What are the pain of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Depending on the cause of hemorrhoids, how it occurs, by means and methods of treatment and the individual patient&rsquo;s age and tolerance, pain, haemorrhoids are of different nature. In the early stages of the disease usually experience pain during and after defecation. The pain is short-term, the intensity of the weak.</p>

<p>A man with a &ldquo;sit-down&rdquo; work at first, begins to feel uncomfortable, and only much later appear severe pain in certain parts of the body and the anus.</p>

<p>When the disease is far from being in its infancy, patients experience headache, back pain in the lumbar region, noticed cutting pain in the abdomen, there is a heaviness in the gut. No matter what kind of pain you are experiencing at the moment, if you do not start early treatment, the pain will only increase gradually.</p>

<p>Do not forget that at different ages the disease is transferred in many ways, the older a person is, the stronger the pain, intense and longer.</p>

<h2>How to relieve hemorrhoid pain</h2>

<p>When there is pain, even minor, it is advisable to take the right position, lying or half-sitting and try to relax. In a relaxed state, you can ease the pain and it almost did not feel it. Need to get away and stop to focus on the pain.</p>

<h2>How can I relieve hemorrhoid pain</h2>

<p>Painful spasms of hemorrhoids can not be avoided, but you should know some tricks to trick your body and how to relieve hemorrhoid pain:</p>

<ul>
<li>A cold compress of ice cubes can significantly ease the pain;</li>
<li>Candles from aloe plant is peeled (1-2 cm) and inserted into the rectum;</li>
<li>The patient can be &ldquo;planted&rdquo; on the steam bath of cranberries, brewed in boiling water;</li>
<li>Cranberry &ldquo;porridge&rdquo; wrapped in gauze is applied to the inflamed area.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Removing the pain of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Removal of minor pain, perhaps in many ways, for example</p>

<ul>
<li>Inflamed area smeared with lecithin;</li>
<li>Applied a cold compress;</li>
<li>Squatting in relaxation of the muscles of the anus, the pain goes away almost immediately;</li>
<li>Apply a special cream for hemorrhoids or binding agents;</li>
<li>Use a medicated wipes or swabs.</li>
</ul>


<p>When the pain becomes severe and progressive, most often to remove it by yourself will not work. Therefore, relieve hemorrhoid pain is better to carry out jointly with specialists or under their control.</p>

<p>Today the whole set of physical exercises to help with hemorrhoids, which prepares the muscles and at the right time is compressed or relaxation, which reduces the pains of hemorrhoids.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What kind of doctor treats hemorrhoids?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/what-kind-of-doctor-treats-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:13:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/what-kind-of-doctor-treats-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/what-doctor-treats-hemorrhoids/5.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="What doctor treats hemorrhoids" alt="What kind of doctor treats hemorrhoids?"> The above articles deal directly hemorrhoid disease, its symptoms and treatments. However, for many patients, the biggest problem is the very visit the proctologist &ndash; a doctor who treats hemorrhoids. So if you asked the question: &ldquo;What kind of doctor treats hemorrhoids?&rdquo;  This article is devoted to the doctors this narrow specialty.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery &ndash; one of the most restrictive in the areas of medicine &ndash; is the direction of diagnoses, working to prevent and cure diseases of the rectum. Unfortunately, in today&rsquo;s society is quite a high percentage of disease is associated with colorectal profilem.Gemorroy &ndash; a disease that is mostly associated with thrombosis and abnormal veins that form hemorrhoids around the rectum. It hemorrhoids is the most common of all diseases of the small intestine.</p>

<p>Once a proctologist to receive the first time you will spend in his office about an hour. Pre-you should not observe any special diet or cleanse the intestines &ndash; this will Specialist directly at the reception, where it will be most of the time your visit to the proctologist&rsquo;s office. Typically, the medical examination takes place at the proctologist several positions that are occupied by patients: or it is the knee-elbow position, or the patient lies on his left side and his knees bent. The last digit is used more often. It proctologist after examination, if necessary, then assigns a method of treatment of hemorrhoids according to the stage of its development.</p>

<p>Proctologists recommend check-ups to all the people after 40 years. Next inspection must take place after 5 years if the first inspection does not reveal any signs of the disease. If proctologist find you have a tendency to the development of hemorrhoids, you should be tested every year.</p>

<p>Timely access to the proctologist will help you avoid not only the hemorrhoid as the most widespread disease of the small intestine, but other, less frequently occurring diseases. For example, polyps, and even cancer of the rectum.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treating hemorrhoids with salt Epsom]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/treating-hemorrhoids-with-salt-epsom/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:11:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/treating-hemorrhoids-with-salt-epsom</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/epsom-salt-hemorrhoids/4.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Epsom salt hemorrhoids" alt="Treating hemorrhoids with salt Epsom"> There are more than twenty kinds of hemorrhoid treatment of folk remedies, but this article will describe the most effective form of treatment for hemorrhoids is hemorrhoid treatment with Epsom salt.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Salty warm bath</h2>

<p>For the manufacture of the trays you need:</p>

<p>2-3 liters of boiled water, which should be the presence of 500 grams of salt. After that, you will be required to cool the solution to such a temperature that you are able to survive, it is desirable, the lower, the better. Then you pour the mixture of water and salt in a bowl and dive into it. This procedure is performed before you go to bed. The course shall consist of not less than three days. This method does not give you a guarantee that the pile will disappear, but we can say for sure that the pain you leave.</p>

<p>Also there is another use of salt, which will help you to get rid of unpleasant feelings, but the process is simple, though, but still long. You will be required for two weeks every day after meals dissolve by gram of salt.</p>

<p>If the patient has not seen a strong blood flow, then it is possible to put an enema with a solution of water and salt through which &ndash; while it will act very well.</p>

<p>There is also a large-scale version of the hemorrhoids treatment with Epsom salt. For this option, you will need two pounds of salt, which you will need to pour into a bath filled with warm water, and then there will plunge themselves. This method is excellent impact on treatment of hemorrhoids.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 7 conditions for victory over hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/top-7-conditions-for-victory-over-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-10T19:22:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/top-7-conditions-for-victory-over-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/top-hemorrhoid-treatment/3.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Top hemorrhoid treatment" alt="Top 7 conditions for victory over hemorrhoids"> Medical experts from the Office of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), the United States, called the 7 rules that will help prevent and cure hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Do not read in the bathroom. The study showed that 35% of Americans take with them into the toilet Ipad.
Use the special napkins during a visit to the toilet or wet toilet paper. This protects the sore from too much stimulation sites. Avoid paper and napkins with an aromatic fragrance and alcohol.
Be aware of hygiene: take a warm bath and then take care of the dryness of the anus to avoid friction sensitive tissues.
Go to the toilet every time when you feel the urge to defecate. Delay chair helps increase pressure on the weakened veins, ie, worsening of hemorrhoids.
Avoid constipation: Drink plenty of water, eat foods rich in fiber.
Move more. Activity helps to reduce the pressure on the veins, as well as get rid of the excess weight that contributes to hemorrhoids.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
