<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-18T16:45:54+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alcohol and energy drinks: bad combination]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/alcohol-and-energy-drinks-bad-combination/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-27T14:57:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/alcohol-and-energy-drinks-bad-combination</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/alcohol-and-energy-drinks-bad-combination/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="alcohol energy drinks" alt="Alcohol and energy drinks: bad combination"><strong>This is not the first time that energy drinks are singled out, especially in alcoholic evenings.</strong></p>

<p>A new Australian study confirms these fears of dangerous liaisons&hellip;</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Overconsumption of alcohol</h2>

<p>For the purposes of the study, seventy five young people aged 18 to 30 were invited to drink cocktails in the context of a party held in a laboratory: they received either 60 ml of a mixture Vodka &ndash; Red Bull, 60 ml of a mixture Vodka &ndash; carbonated water, plus 200 ml of a fruit drink in each of these mixtures. Nobody knew what he received as a beverage, but people with the habit of consuming energy drinks have easily recognized. Young also had to take a test and complete questionnaires on which researchers have relied.</p>

<p><strong>It is clear from this experience that those receiving alcohol cocktail with energy drinks were also those who were more inclined to continue to drink alcohol.</strong></p>

<p>However, all is not taken action, some arriving to reason&hellip;</p>

<h2>A trap for the most vulnerable?</h2>

<p>The fact that all those who received the alcohol cocktails and energy drinks, have not drank more than others even if they had more desire can reassure this proves that it is always possible not to succumb! However, proving that the desire to drink alcohol is increased by energy drinks, this study suggests also fear that the most vulnerable to alcohol people have trouble resisting. Indeed, we are not equal face the risk of addiction. And vulnerable people often have trouble recognizing they have a problem with alcohol, because they may very well do without alcohol for several days in a row. This is true, but can not help but consume much always in identical circumstances (such as partying with friends) shows that there is already a problem and it is time to talk to his doctor!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[38% of Americans have a child who suffers from an allergy]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/38-percent-of-americans-have-a-child-who-suffers-from-an-allergy/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-26T13:36:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/38-percent-of-americans-have-a-child-who-suffers-from-an-allergy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/38-percent-of-americans-have-a-child-who-suffers-from-an-allergy/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="allergy, allergic child" alt="38% of Americans have a child who suffers from an allergy">The results of the FIFG/Stallergenes Foundation study revealed that 38% of Americans have a child who suffers from allergies.</p>

<p><strong>Among these allergic children, 28% suffer from respiratory allergies, 12% develop food allergies and 12% of drug allergies.</strong></p>

<p>This is more than 1 in 3 children.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Allergies strong growth</h2>

<p>&ldquo;Children are a slice of the population at risk because more sensitive to allergens, chemicals as well as viral infections&rdquo; explains Dr. Pham Thi Nhan, allergist, pneumo-pediatrician, Necker Hospital &ndash; Sick Children, New York.</p>

<p>According to the results of the FIFG/Stallergenes Foundation study, 94% of Americans believe that there are more allergies now than in the past. Confirmed by a WHO felt. In France, from 25 to 30% of people suffer from allergies, or double the number 20 years ago, particularly among children and adolescents. More worryingly, the WHO predicts that by 2050, 1 in 2 will be allergic in the world. &ldquo;It is known that severe cases of allergies are increasing worldwide. This is not only due to a more accurate diagnosis but phenomena that progress in the population&rdquo;, declare the allergist.</p>

<p>What are the factors responsible for the increase in allergies?</p>

<ul>
<li>73% of Americans people point the finger at pollution;</li>
<li>34% pesticide use;</li>
<li>28% changes in supply mode;</li>
<li>25% overprotection of infants;</li>
<li>22% increase in awareness of the organization;</li>
<li>18% climate change.</li>
</ul>


<p>&ldquo;Pollution is a co-precipitant and aggravating allergies: it increases our sensitivity and our susceptibility to the environment and therefore increases the risk of developing allergies. When pollution peaks in March, we have seen an impressive number of allergies: new cases and cases of severe rhino<a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/ophthalmology/conjunctivitis.html" title="conjunctivitis">conjunctivitis</a> including pollens, excluding asthma attacks. The days that followed pollution peaks, the number of health care utilization has risen sharply&rdquo;, says Dr. Nhan Pham Thi.</p>

<h2>Good reflexes to reduce allergens</h2>

<p>In addition to the necessary consultation with a specialist and the establishment of appropriate treatment following the allergen to which the child is sensitive, simple steps can significantly reduce the impact of respiratory allergies.</p>

<p>It is recommended that parents of children with respiratory allergies:</p>

<ul>
<li>ventilate the room (84%);</li>
<li>do not put carpet (69%);</li>
<li>to regularly clean (62%);</li>
<li>do not use a pillow or feather duvet (52%);</li>
<li>to avoid contact with dogs/cats (32%);</li>
<li>not to houseplants or some trees in the garden (30%).</li>
</ul>


<p>&ldquo;Patient education is a mainstay of treatment that allows to change lifestyle to adapt to his new state of sensitivity requires support chronic and often long if not life treatment. A food allergic must learn to avoid food and control its aid kit. For a child with chronic rhinitis, nasal care are needed daily. Finally, asthma, adherence background is essential&rdquo; said Dr. Pham Thi Nhan.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[1.5 million died of AIDS in 2013: a figure much lower]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/1-dot-5-million-died-of-aids-in-2013-a-figure-much-lower/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-25T10:59:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/1-dot-5-million-died-of-aids-in-2013-a-figure-much-lower</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/15-million-died-of-aids-in-2013-a-figure-much-lower/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="AIDS deaths" alt="1.5 million died of AIDS in 2013: a figure much lower"><strong>According to the 2013 report on the <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/aids.html" title="AIDS">AIDS</a> epidemic recently published UNAIDS, the number of deaths due to AIDS for the first time dropped significantly.</strong></p>

<p><strong>However, the number of people living with HIV has increased slightly.</strong></p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Very sharp decrease in the number of people who died of AIDS in 2013</h2>

<p>The results of UNAIDS published in July 2014 indicates that 1, 5 million people died of AIDS in 2013, against 1.7 million in 2012, a decrease of 11.8% in a year, the highest drop recorded since the peak of the epidemic in 2005.</p>

<p><strong>In total, ten years, deaths from AIDS have declined by 35%.</strong></p>

<p>Regarding people worldwide with HIV, their number increased slightly, rising to 35 million today, against 34.6 million the previous year. That said, since 2005, there has been a decrease of 33%.</p>

<h2>New infections also fall</h2>

<p><strong>The number of people newly infected each year with HIV continues to fall:</strong> 2.1 million in 2013, against 2.2 million in 2012. But since 2001, new HIV infections have fallen by 38%.</p>

<p><strong>Children born with the AIDS virus are also decreasing:</strong> 240,000 in 2013 against 270,000 in 2012, a decrease of 27.6% since 2005.</p>

<p><strong>The most affected region is sub-Saharan Africa</strong> (South Africa and Nigeria in particular): 70.8% of those affected and still predominantly women (58%). In this part of the world totaling 1.1 million people died of AIDS, 24.7 million people living with HIV, including 2.9 million children.</p>

<p>To this day still, 22 million people have no access to treatment. 38% of adults have, against 24% of children.</p>

<p>Finally, $19.1 billion (14 billion euros) were made available in 2013, against 18.9 million in 2012 and $4.6 billion 10 years ago.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hydronephrosis: symptoms diagnosis treatment]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/hydronephrosis-symptoms-diagnosis-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-24T00:16:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/hydronephrosis-symptoms-diagnosis-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/hydronephrosis-symptoms-diagnosis-treatment/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="urology, hydronephrosis, hydronephrosis symptoms, diagnosis of hydronephrosis, hydronephrosis treatment, treatment of hydronephrosis, renal tissue thinning, accumulation of urine in the renal pelvis, reduced kidney function" alt="Hydronephrosis: Symptoms, Diagnosis, Treatment">The disease is caused by violation of the outflow of urine from the kidneys, resulting in the pelvis and calices increased hydrostatic pressure.</p>

<p>Allocate congenital hydronephrosis and acquired. Moreover, the disease has three stages. The first stage is characterized by compensated or negligible accumulation of urine in the renal pelvis and its small stretch. At this stage, the kidney function is preserved. In the second stage, the thinning of kidney tissue, while its function is substantially reduced. For the third or end-stage hydronephrosis characterized by a complete shutdown of the affected kidney.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Symptoms of hydronephrosis</h2>

<p>It often happens that the onset of the disease goes unnoticed. Hydronephrosis has no specific symptoms, so at an early stage due to the cause of symptoms that it caused. For example, in urolithiasis may cause attacks of renal colic, which are characterized by acute severe pain along the ureter. Sometimes the only symptom of the disease is haematuria (blood in the urine). This symptom is also characteristic of those cases where there was hydronephrosis on the background of urolithiasis.</p>

<p>The most stable sign of hydronephrosis &ndash; a constant aching pain blunt nature. Pain can arise in this case irrespective of the position of the body or time of day. Localization of pain right or left depending on which kidney affected. On the background of painful episodes occasionally occur bloating, nausea, vomiting, increased blood pressure. Upon accession of infection increases body temperature.</p>

<p>With the development of end-stage hydronephrosis, especially bilateral, have symptoms of chronic renal failure. This decreases the amount of urine, appear edema, hypertension.</p>

<h2>Diagnosis of hydronephrosis</h2>

<p>During the visual inspection and palpation with hydronephrosis doctor can detect swelling and deformation of the lumbar region. In order to diagnose this disease conducted laboratory analyzes: urinalysis, complete blood count, tests for Nichiporenko and Zimnitskiy and other.</p>

<p>From instrumental diagnostic methods performed with hydronephrosis renal ultrasound, which allows to define the extension pyelocaliceal complex, increasing the kidney, as well as to measure the thickness of the renal parenchyma.</p>

<p>Appointed radiography &ndash; it is the main method of diagnosis of hydronephrosis. Survey radiography reveals stones, determine the size of the kidneys. Intravenous urography contrast, a series of images, determines the rate of formation of urine and its excretion. When hydronephrosis has slowed revenue contrast agents in renal pelvis complex expansion cups and pelvis, which acquire rounded contours. End-stage hydronephrosis contrast can not come to the affected kidney. Occasionally you can discover the nature and level of patency of the urinary tract.</p>

<p>To characterize the extent of damage to each kidney is assigned radioisotope urography. To clarify the diagnosis in difficult cases used angiography, magnetic resonance and computed tomography.</p>

<h2>Treatment of hydronephrosis</h2>

<p>Correctly chosen and spent treatment helps to compensate for the state and improve kidney function. The main goal of therapy &ndash; the elimination of the cause of the hydronephrosis. In each case, except for cause, you must also consider the degree of hydronephrosis and the pace of its development. When hydronephrosis can be carried out medical and surgical treatments.</p>

<p>Conservative treatment for symptomatic hydronephrosis and used at an early stage of the disease. Depending on the symptom such therapy includes anti-inflammatory, anti-hypertensive, and other painkillers. Upon accession infection antibiotics are shown. Typically, conservative therapy precedes operation.</p>

<p>When hydronephrosis in most cases surgery is shown. It is performed to eliminate the causes of illness and recover kidney. Better to do the operation in the early stages of the disease (in particular, congenital anomalies) when still reversible kidney changes. Surgical therapy includes renewal patency of the urinary tract, and terminally ill &ndash; plastic pelvis, the restoration of its size. By removal of the affected kidney resort exclusively in advanced cases, when the organ has completely lost its function and its preservation may cause inflammatory complications.</p>

<p>Efficacy of hydronephrosis depends on the stage of the disease. Hydronephrosis &ndash; a serious pathology, but timely diagnosis and appropriate treatment given to help maintain and improve the health.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meaning barium enema in the diagnosis of diseases of the large intestine]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/meaning-barium-enema-in-the-diagnosis-of-diseases-of-the-large-intestine/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-22T23:56:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/meaning-barium-enema-in-the-diagnosis-of-diseases-of-the-large-intestine</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/meaning-barium-enema-in-the-diagnosis-of-diseases-of-the-large-intestine/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="s colitis, tumor, polyp" alt="Meaning barium enema in the diagnosis of diseases of the large intestine">Irrigoscopy &ndash; one of radiological methods of investigation of the colon using a radiopaque substance. Barium enema is performed after the introduction into the rectum of barium sulfate (contrast material) or barium suspension in combination with air (double contrast method).</p>

<p>Double contrast reveals the small size of the tumor, particularly polyps and mucosal changes that occur in the early stages of inflammatory diseases of the large intestine.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>With the barium enema can be visualized colon almost an entire length, but for the most effective research rectosigmoid zone applies sigmoidoscopy.</p>

<p>Irrigoscopy not performed after radiographic contrast studies of the upper gastrointestinal tract. Used with barium is excreted within a few days, and the remnants of this substance may distort the results irrigoscopy.</p>

<h2>The information that can be accessed by barium enema</h2>

<p>During the barium enema doctor receives the following information about the patient&rsquo;s colon:</p>

<ul>
<li>The location, shape and diameter of the colon;</li>
<li>The degree of extensibility and flexibility of the intestinal wall;</li>
<li>Define the function bauginievoy flap. Bauginievaya flap &ndash; is a fold, which is located between the ileum and colon. Normally bauginievaya damper must pass the intestinal contents in only one direction (from the small intestine into the large), but there may be a violation of the intestinal contents throw in the opposite direction. Movement in contrast barium enema shows clearly whether there are irregularities in the bauginievoy flap;</li>
<li>Relief mucosa of the colon walls. This indicator is particularly important in the diagnosis of ulcerative lesions of the bowel, fistulas, tumors, diverticulosis, scars and congenital malformations;</li>
<li>Functional state departments of large intestine.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Why is it important to conduct irrigoscopy?</h2>

<p>As a rule, barium enema is used to confirm the diagnosis in suspected those or other diseases of the colon. Barium enema is often decisive diagnostic method for tumors and colon diverticula.</p>

<p>During the barium enema using the technique of double -contrast study diagnostic capabilities are significantly increased. With barium enema can indirectly confirm the presence of diseases such as colitis and tuberculosis.</p>

<h2>Which diseases carried irrigoscopy?</h2>

<p>When irrigoscopy estimated rate of change of the intestinal mucosa in ulcerative colitis, Crohn&rsquo;s disease, as well as visualized tumors, fistulas, malformations and diverticula.</p>

<p>Unlike colonoscopy, barium enema and less traumatic and less likely to cause complications. Furthermore, barium enema is possible to investigate with the &ldquo;blind&rdquo; to the field of colonoscopy, for example, portions in the folds of the mucosa, and also bends in the colon and the sigmoid colon.</p>

<p>Application irrigoscopy shown if the patient following symptoms:</p>

<ul>
<li>Bleeding from the rectum;</li>
<li>Mucous or purulent discharge from the intestines;</li>
<li>Pain in the anus and in the course of the colon;</li>
<li>Chronic disorder stool (constipation or diarrhea).</li>
</ul>


<h2>How is barium enema?</h2>

<p>Barium enema is performed in a specially equipped medical facility office. A few days before the scheduled study patient should prepare for barium enema. Must be made within 3-4 days follow a special cleansing diet and the use of additional methods for bowel cleansing. This patient doctor tells in detail.</p>

<p>Before the study, the patient is laid down on the couch on its side. In the anus enema tip is introduced, which contains a radiopaque substance. In the future, under fluoroscopy intestines filled contrast agents and conduct a series of reviews and sighting shots in different positions of the patient.</p>

<p>After emptying of barium mixture is produced as air filling bowel under fluoroscopy. So can investigate the organic and functional disorders of the intestinal wall.</p>

<p>Duration of the procedure is a few minutes. During double contrast examination may take 30 to 40 minutes.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genital herpes: 4 out of 5 patients unaware of being infected with this virus]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/genital-herpes-4-out-of-5-patients-unaware-of-being-infected-with-this-virus/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-22T23:50:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/genital-herpes-4-out-of-5-patients-unaware-of-being-infected-with-this-virus</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/genital-herpes-4-out-of-5-patients-unaware-of-being-infected-with-this-virus/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="herpes, genital herpes" alt="Genital herpes : 4 out of 5 patients unaware of being infected with this virus!">Two million americans are affected by the virus that causes <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/genital-herpes.html" title="genital herpes">genital herpes</a>.
Worse, four out of five do not know! In side The drug prescription information and patient education are therefore key stages of care.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Herpes types</h2>

<p><strong>Herpes labialis</strong>
He is responsible for cold sores. Frequent, nearly 10 million americans suffer at least one thrust per year. It preferentially affects women (3 women to 2 men).</p>

<p><strong>Genital herpes</strong>
Number of herpes infection carriers subjects estimated 2 million against only 350,000 cases diagnosed! Thus, four out of five are unaware of being infected.</p>

<h2>An impaired life quality</h2>

<p>Genital herpes diagnosis is often difficult because of the lesions diversity or too late consultation and outside attacks. However, the impact on quality of life is very important.</p>

<p>Patients are afraid to have sex because of pain or disease transmitting fear. They are 34% to easily manage their social life and 33% have <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/depression.html" title="depression">depression</a>.</p>

<p>However, drug treatments exist.</p>

<h2>A little known illness surrounded by taboos</h2>

<p>It is necessary to open the dialogue and break the taboos surrounding this little known disease patients. As well as medication, inform and educate patients is an management integral part. Contamination must be explained, as well as the potential for treatment to facilitate compliance. This stops the immediate effect in virus replication, pain and shortens the surge duration, but virus remains in body.</p>

<p><strong>Infection is severe in late <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a></strong>
In addition, this infection can be very serious in late pregnancy. It entails a neonatal infection risk (1-2 cases per 100,000 births), the consequences can be serious for infants if treatment is not started quickly.</p>

<h2>How to prevent transmission  herpes virus?</h2>

<p>During a herpes outbreak:</p>

<ul>
<li>Wash hands after touching the lesions and do not scratch the lesions.</li>
<li>Do not share his towels.</li>
<li>Avoid sexual intercourse, even protected by a condom.</li>
<li>Avoid physical contact with newborns, pregnant women, people with skin lesions (eczema, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/psoriasis.html" title="psoriasis">psoriasis</a>, etc.)., Immunocompromised individuals (AIDS, organ transplant, chemotherapy).</li>
</ul>


<p>Outside breakouts, use a condom if the partner has never come into contact with the herpes virus.</p>

<p>In case of herpes labialis (cold sores) to avoid oral-genital sex (sex/mouth) because this virus on the lips can be transmitted to the partner genitals.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fungus toenails. Onychomycosis]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/fungus-toenails-onychomycosis/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-21T09:30:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/fungus-toenails-onychomycosis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/fungus-toenails-onychomycosis/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="nail fungus, fungus toenails, onychomycosis" alt="Fungus toenails, onychomycosis">If you find they thicken, become brittle, change color, check out quickly.</p>

<p>The fungus toenails is extremely contagious and can lead to the loss of the nail, then there are effective treatments.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>The fungus toenails is common</h2>

<p>The fungus toenails is common and transmissible. It affects 3-10% of the French population. Professionals use the term of onychomycosis, which designates a nail infection caused by fungi of three kinds (dermatophytes, yeasts Candida, molds).</p>

<h2>First signs of a nail fungus</h2>

<p>The infection settles slowly. It reaches first the skin between the toes forming a fissure that does not heal. Gradually, the nail is reached. It thickens, crumbles, changes color (yellow or white spots) and becomes painful. In the absence of treatment, it may peel off.</p>

<h2>What are the risk factors for nail fungus?</h2>

<p>Older age, male sex, sports, trauma and repeated injury, a humid environment and certain diseases (bone and joint diseases, diabetes, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>, peripheral <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/vascular-disease/" title="vascular disease">vascular disease</a>, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/psoriasis.html" title="psoriasis">psoriasis</a>?).</p>

<p>The infection is caught easily in collective public places humid and warm where you walk barefoot (pool, sauna, dance halls, dressing rooms, etc..).</p>

<p>You can also pass the family, walking barefoot on the carpet, suitable slippers or in the bathroom, including towels or nail clippers. Maceration in shoes, especially sport shoes or boots, is also a major risk factor. Also predispose strain nails or toes that overlap (common in older people).</p>

<h2>In case of nail fungus, early treatment is essential</h2>

<p>A <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nail-fungus-fungal-nail-disease-symptoms-and-prevention/" title="nail fungus">nail fungus</a> does not heal on its own and instead risk spreading to other nails.</p>

<p>Similarly, the more care is delayed, the more healing is long and difficult. Hence the importance of regularly inspecting her nails, especially if you are part of those at risk.</p>

<p>At the slightest anomaly, talk to your doctor.</p>

<p>A sample of the nail for a mycological examination is necessary to identify the fungus cause and prescribe the appropriate antifungal therapy. Depending on the degree of achievement of the nail, it will be local (application of a varnish) and/or oral. However, be patient and be sure to follow your doctor&rsquo;s instructions. Indeed, the treatment is long (often more than 6 months), as the nail grows very slowly.</p>

<h2>Tips to avoid a nail fungus</h2>

<ul>
<li>Systematically and thoroughly dry your feet, especially between each toe.</li>
<li>Avoid walking barefoot.</li>
<li>Wear personal sandals by the pool, in the locker room&hellip;</li>
<li>Do not lend your slippers.</li>
<li>Do not pay either your towel.</li>
<li>Disinfect with alcohol scissors, nail files and nail clippers used for toenails.</li>
<li>Cut your toe nails short and straight.</li>
<li>Limit wearing sneakers your physical activity.</li>
<li>Wear leather shoes, which limit maceration.</li>
<li>Avoid tight shoes, too tightly in plastic.</li>
<li>Try not to your shoes, especially sport.</li>
<li>Adopt cotton socks, especially for sports.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to protect from Alzheimer's disease?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-20T12:21:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="s disease" alt="How to protect from Alzheimer">We&rsquo;ve all heard that stimulate our brain functions, including intellectual could protect us from Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>

<p>Thus, crosswords and all kinds of learning are recommended.</p>

<p>Today, studies suggest that there are other protective factors.
Was even identified risk factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease&hellip; And it appears that we could halve the number of people affected.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Alzheimer&rsquo;s, prevent long as we do not know how to cure</h2>

<p>The research was mobilized for years to develop treatments that will cure Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease. Similarly, researchers are busy around prevention. An analysis of all publications focused on this subject gave particularly interesting results.</p>

<p>In fact, risk factors and protective factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease have been identified.</p>

<p>The good news is that all are modifiable, meaning that acting on each of these factors could reduce by half the number of people affected by Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>

<h2>6 risk factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease</h2>

<ul>
<li>Diabetes;</li>
<li>Excess <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a> in midlife;</li>
<li>Smoking.</li>
</ul>


<p>But another study points 3 other additional risk factors (1)</p>

<ul>
<li>Hypertension;</li>
<li>Obesity;</li>
<li>Depression.</li>
</ul>


<h2>5 of protective factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease</h2>

<ul>
<li>The Mediterranean diet;</li>
<li>The folic acid or vitamin B9;</li>
<li>Low or moderate alcohol consumption;</li>
<li>Cognitive activities;</li>
<li>Physical activity.</li>
</ul>


<p>For example, diabetes increases the risk of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease by 39%. Knowing that 6% of the world population is affected by diabetes, the disease is alone responsible for 2% of cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>

<p>Another example, physical inactivity increases the risk of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease by 82%. If we consider that 18% of the world population is physically inactive, sedentary lifestyle is responsible for 13% of cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>

<p>Smoking increases the risk of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease by 59%. If we consider that 27% of the population smokes, smoking is responsible for 14% of cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>

<p>Finally, knowing that many of these factors are related, act on one of them can simultaneously have a significant impact on others. <strong>For example, by acting only on physical inactivity, can simultaneously reduce the risk of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/cardiology/hypertension.html" title="hypertension">hypertension</a> and diabetes&hellip;</strong></p>

<p><strong>You can see that all these factors are modifiable. In other words, we can all take action and protect us from Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</strong></p>

<p>Thus, nearly half of the cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease could be prevented by modifying these factors.</p>

<p>Recall that in the world, the number of people affected by Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease is estimated at 34 million. In USA, the figure is estimated at nearly 1 million. In the current absence of treatment to cure this disease, prevention is a huge challenge.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anorexia and bulimia]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/anorexia-and-bulimia/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-19T13:15:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/anorexia-and-bulimia</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/anorexia-and-bulimia/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="anorexia, bulimia, eating behavior, eating disorder, eating, restrictions on food, diet" alt="Anorexia and bulimia">Anorexia &ndash; a pathological condition in which there was a complete lack of appetite in the presence of the objective necessity of the body in the diet. Anorexia may occur due to various reasons, such as parasitic infestations and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/" title="infectious diseases">infectious diseases</a>, diseases of the digestive system. Usually considered separately anorexia nervosa.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Anorexia nervosa is an eating disorder in which a person willfully refuses to eat for weight loss purposes. This disease occurs more often in girls. Nevertheless, it can be observed not only in the young, but also in adulthood, both women and men.</p>

<p>Anorexia nervosa is characterized by the occurrence of a pathological desire to lose weight, which is accompanied by the development of intense fear of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>. People suffering from anorexia, there is distortion of the own body, there is a concern about weight gain, even if in reality it is not marked. The causes of anorexia are divided into psychological (internal conflicts, the impact of the family), biological (genetic predisposition) and social (the impact of society &ndash; popular diets imitation idols).</p>

<p>Anorexia is phasing flow &ndash; isolated dismorfomanicheskuyu, anorectic and cachectic stage. The first stage &ndash; dismorfomanicheskaya &ndash; characterized by the emergence of thoughts of inferiority because of imaginary completeness. In this patient develops anxiety, depressed mood, he sees himself in the long mirror. Also at this stage following the first attempt to limit in food.</p>

<p>In the second stage the patient has resorted to a strict diet and grueling physical <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a>. However, he loses much weight, but does not stop fasting, since it can not objectively assess the degree of weight loss. Due to continuous malnutrition occur in the body pathological reactions. There are features such as <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/hair-loss.html" title="hair loss">hair loss</a>, dry skin, decreased sexual desire, syncope, arrhythmia, stomach pain, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/constipation.html" title="constipation">constipation</a>, nausea, and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/depression.html" title="depression">depression</a>. Infertility occurs: women due to amenorrhea (cessation of menstruation), men &ndash; due to the suppression of spermatogenesis.</p>

<p>Body weight of the patient has been steadily declining in the body degenerative changes occur, and there comes a cachectic period. This stage usually develops anorexia after two years of onset. Pathological changes in the body leads to irreversible inhibition of the functions of all organs and systems, and result in death. In connection with this incessant flow and severe consequences, anorexia is a serious disease that requires mandatory treatment.</p>

<h2>Bulimia</h2>

<p>Another uncommon <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/eating-disorders.html" title="eating disorders">eating disorders</a> is <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/bulimia.html" title="bulimia">bulimia</a>. Bulimia occurs due to mental disorders, diseases of the endocrine and central nervous systems. This pathology often leads to obesity.</p>

<p>Bulimia nervosa is characterized by sudden significant increase in appetite, feeling really hungry. Typically, bulimia occurs in the form of attacks or last time. Seizures are characterized by the absorption of huge amounts of food. They can occur suddenly or develop at a certain time (eg at night).</p>

<p>People with bulimia often resorted to the use of laxatives and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/vomiting.html" title="vomiting">vomiting</a> to control weight. However, the use of large amounts of food and the subsequent forced cleaning of the stomach cause severe complications.</p>

<p>Bulimia can develop independently or arise against the background of anorexia nervosa. As people with anorexia and bulimia patients control their weight become the overriding purpose in life. Bulimia, emerged against the background of anorexia nervosa is characterized by periodic episodes of binge eating occurrence that alternate periods of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/starvation.html" title="starvation">starvation</a>. During these episodes the patient will eat huge amounts of food in a short time, while he usually swallows food without chewing. Typically, after a bout of bulimia patient vomits or takes large amounts of diuretics or laxatives, not thinking about the consequences for your health.</p>

<p>Bulimia and anorexia are life-threatening conditions, so people suffering from these diseases, needs appropriate treatment. Unfortunately, patients are often hospitalized for anorexia able drastic depletion, whereas in the early treatment of the disease can be performed on an outpatient basis. It must be remembered that the earlier therapeutic interventions will be carried out, the less the risk of irreversible changes.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crohn's disease: what are symptoms?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/crohns-disease-what-are-symptoms/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-18T10:47:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/crohns-disease-what-are-symptoms</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/crohns-disease-what-are-symptoms/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="s disease causes, and colon, from anus" alt="Crohn"><strong>In USA, there are 120,000 people with Crohn&rsquo;s disease, both men and women.</strong></p>

<blockquote><p>Each year 4-5 new cases per 100,000 are diagnosed.
<strong>Crohn&rsquo;s disease causes chronic inflammation of digestive system. Any segment of the gastrointestinal tract may be affected, from anus esophagus. But more often, it is bowel that is achieved by inflammation: colon, small intestine terminal portion.</strong></p></blockquote>

<!--more-->


<p>Illness progresses in spurts interspersed with remission periods.</p>

<p>Signs are mainly gastrointestinal, but not only, depend on the segments achieved location.</p>

<h2>In Crohn&rsquo;s disease, the symptoms are mostly gastrointestinal</h2>

<p><strong>Crohn&rsquo;s disease causes:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Anal pain (fistulas, abscesses).</li>
<li>An issue of blood or mucus from anus.</li>
<li>Abdominal pain (sometimes very strong up to think appendicitis).</li>
<li>There may be heavy, watery diarrhea.</li>
<li>Nausea, vomiting.</li>
</ul>


<blockquote><p>These digestive symptoms lead to poor general condition: fatigue, loss of appetite, weight loss with faltering growth in children and adolescents, fever, paleness, breathlessness due to a anemia risk and vitamin B12 deficiency.</p></blockquote>

<h2>Other non-digestive signs&hellip;</h2>

<p><strong>Crohn&rsquo;s disease can also cause other symptoms as digestive, including joint, skin and eye.</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Articular rheumatism: ankylosing spondylitis&hellip;</li>
<li>Dermatological disorders: ulcers, erythema nodosum&hellip;</li>
<li>Ocular: uveitis&hellip;</li>
</ul>


<p>It is estimated that these extraintestinal manifestations affect one third of patients during their illness. Knowing they can appear before the gastrointestinal signs, they should be considered as warning signs to get see.</p>

<h2>Crohn&rsquo;s disease Diagnosis and treatment</h2>

<p><strong>Diagnosis is based on examination and in particular on signs, supplemented by:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>A biological balance sheet;</li>
<li>A colonoscopy (rectum and colon examination, terminal portion of small intestine, assessing damage extent);</li>
<li>Upper gastrointestinal endoscopy (to determine the high illness location);</li>
<li>Video capsule ingestion.</li>
</ul>


<p>Other tests may be required or placed under surveillance:</p>

<ul>
<li>MRIs;</li>
<li>Abdominal CT;</li>
<li>Abdominal ultrasound,</li>
<li>Radio.</li>
</ul>


<p>As for treatment, they are based on anti-inflammatory drugs target (5-ASA, corticosteroids, immunomodulators, antibiotics, iron). If unsuccessful, surgery may be necessary. A balanced diet is necessary to risk malnutrition reduce. During severe outbreaks, a restricted diet in fruits and vegetables can not increase gastrointestinal symptoms. Only tobacco should be avoided.</p>

<blockquote><p>Care is multidisciplinary, involving the intervention of various specialists: physician, gastroenterologist, rheumatologist, dietician, doctor or school work, social worker, psychiatrist or psychologist, etc..
It aims to ease outbreaks, prevent relapses, complications and improve life quality.</p></blockquote>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Too much cholesterol: what symptoms?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/too-much-cholesterol-what-symptoms/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-17T10:19:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/too-much-cholesterol-what-symptoms</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/too-much-cholesterol-what-symptoms/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="cholesterol, symptoms, excess cholesterol, calibrate their cholesterol" alt="Too much cholesterol : what symptoms? What are the signs?">Some people wonder if cholesterol is accompanied by symptoms indicative.</p>

<p>If so, then these signs could indicate that it is time to calibrate their cholesterol.</p>

<p>This is unfortunately not the case&hellip;</p>

<!--more-->


<blockquote><p><strong>There are no specific symptoms manifested when an cholesterol excess in the blood.</strong>
We can not rely on any evidence to decide whether to calibrate their cholesterol checked and if all goes well on this side.</p></blockquote>

<p><strong>Excess cholesterol is a silent phenomenon as hypertension.</strong></p>

<h2>Symptoms of cholesterol are those complications</h2>

<p>It was only after years of evolution of symptoms may be too late, because the signs are then those complications of high cholesterol.</p>

<p>Recall that the long, excess cholesterol tends to be deposited in the arteries (plaque), narrowing their diameter and impeding proper blood circulation potentially causing arteritis members lower. This plaque can harden and cause angina. A blood clot can also form and detach, then going to butcher a coronary artery is myocardial or cerebral artery and is the stroke or renal artery is insufficient kidney.</p>

<p><strong>The symptoms of these accidents are well known</strong> (or should be because of the vital urgency):</p>

<p>What are the signs of angina?
Stroke or Heart Attack? Warning symptoms differ!</p>

<p>Overall, all symptoms suggestive of cardiovascular disease involving excess cholesterol are:</p>

<ul>
<li>Calves pain;</li>
<li>Chest pain with tightness;</li>
<li>Nausea, dizziness;</li>
<li>Fever, headache;</li>
<li>Shortness of breath, palpitations;</li>
<li>Feeling cold extremities;</li>
<li>Loss of strength in the face, arms, legs, especially on one side;</li>
<li>Slurred speech;</li>
<li>Blurred vision;</li>
<li>Etc..</li>
</ul>


<h2>So when do calibrate their cholesterol?</h2>

<blockquote><p><strong>The cholesterol assay based on a simple fasting blood test</strong> (after 12 hours without food and drink intake).
We can measure total cholesterol, HDL-cholesterol (&ldquo;bad&rdquo;) and triglycerides, while LDL-cholesterol is calculated from previous values.</p></blockquote>

<p>It is recommended to calibrate their cholesterol once before the age of 30 to screen for familial hypercholesterolemia. Then the pace is every 5 years to 50 years and then every 3 years beyond because the arteries naturally harden with age. In case of diabetes, cholesterol is dose every year at least.</p>

<blockquote><p><strong>Thin also may have too much cholesterol!</strong>
If overweight and obesity increase the risk of having too much bad cholesterol due to an unbalanced diet, thin people can also suffer from high cholesterol and then it is usually a family phenomenon&hellip;</p></blockquote>

<p>In addition to age and diabetes, there are other risk factors that can lead to monitor your cholesterol more closely: family history of premature coronary heart disease, smoking, hypertension, overweight (or obese), waist excessive, etc&hellip;</p>

<p><strong>It is noteworthy that what characterizes excess cholesterol is precisely symptoms absence. This is why regular monitoring is required!</strong></p>

<p><strong>For more information</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Why do an assessment of blood lipids?</li>
<li>What is lipid?</li>
<li>Determination of total cholesterol: manual.</li>
<li>Why and how to HDL and LDL cholesterol balance?</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solar capsules (beta-carotene) to better tan?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/solar-capsules-beta-carotene-to-better-tan/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-15T09:17:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/solar-capsules-beta-carotene-to-better-tan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/solar-capsules-beta-carotene-to-better-tan/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="beta-carotene, solar capsules, discoloration of the skin" alt="Solar capsules (beta-carotene) to better tan?">Expected to prepare the skin for tanning, what is the actual effect of food supplements beta-carotene?
Do they tan, can you be more exposed to the sun and they protect cancer?
Focus on solar capsules.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Tanning and dietary supplements beta-carotene</h2>

<p><strong>Beta-carotene is a pigment that belongs to the family of carotenes.</strong>
It is found naturally in many plants very colorful, especially yellow-orange, like carrots, melons, peppers, apricots, as well as green leafy vegetables eg.</p>

<p><strong>Beta-carotene: an orange color of the skin</strong>
High doses of dietary supplements of beta-carotene (from 30 mg/day) or a very high consumption of foods rich in beta-carotene cause yellow/orange discoloration of the skin that doctors call &ldquo;carotenodermie&rdquo;. Such coloration is not hazardous to health and resolves when the amount of carotenoids absorbed decreases.</p>

<p><strong>An antioxidant against aging skin</strong>
Beta-carotene, also called provitamin A, is a precursor of vitamin A, which plays a role as an antioxidant, that is to say, it helps to fight against the excessive production of free radicals responsible for aging. Golden sun exposure are well known to accelerate the aging of the skin.</p>

<blockquote><p>For example, taking a dietary supplement beta-carotene (or adopt a diet rich in beta-carotene, and therefore rich in colorful fruits and vegetables) could accelerate the discoloration of the skin and therefore the tan, while protecting the skin from aging!</p></blockquote>

<p><strong>This is how many solar capsules are now available to enhance your tan, but their effectiveness in this area has not been formally demonstrated scientifically and without bias, as the duration of treatment and dosage to use.</strong></p>

<h2>Take solar capsules before going on vacation?</h2>

<p><strong>In the current state of knowledge, we can not recommend for or against solar capsules.</strong></p>

<blockquote><p>What is certain is that a cure of beta-carotene, even 15 days before exposure, during and after, does not relieve apply every two hours sunscreen with high protective index or n authorizes to expose longer or the hottest hours of the day.</p></blockquote>

<p>In other words, with or without beta-carotene, the main rules of prevention of skin cancer and accelerated skin aging are needed.</p>

<p>Finally, if you want to buy solar capsules should not exceed the manufacturer&rsquo;s recommended daily dose. Also note that these supplements are cons-indicated in children, pregnant or nursing women.</p>

<h2>Beta-carotene and cancer: protective effect or a negative effect?</h2>

<blockquote><p>These are: an excess of vitamin A can be toxic to the body, but this is not the case with beta-carotene, the vitamin A transformation is blocked as if the vitamin A status is already high. Overdosing seems so limited with beta-carotene.</p></blockquote>

<p><strong>For twenty years, studies consistently highlight the existence of a link between cancer prevention and beta-carotene</strong>: regular consumption, sometimes at high doses of beta-carotene would protect certain cancers.</p>

<p><strong>But, according to a study published in 2005 Inserm, this relationship is reversed in the case of smoking. Beta-carotene would be harmful.</strong>
Thus, smokers supplemented women see their risk of smoking-related cancers increase in proportion to the amount of beta-carotene consumed (20, 30, or 50 mg/day): lung cancer, gastrointestinal cancers, head and neck, thyroid, ovary, cervix, etc.. It is as if significant absorption of beta-carotene favored the formation of &ldquo;unusual cleavage products of carotenoids involved in the development of cancer&rdquo;. Note that this increase was observed both in smokers than in former smokers.
However, not all studies attest to this carcinogenic effect of beta-carotene dose in case of smoking. Thus, in 2012 the European Food Safety Authority (EFSA) concluded reassuringly to the lack of increase of lung cancer in heavy smokers to levels of beta-carotene supplementation &ldquo;reasonable&rdquo; (6 to 15 mg/day).</p>

<p><strong>So, do I take it or not solar capsules if I smoke?</strong>
To date, there is no reason to ban supplements beta-carotene for smokers, if consumed in reasonable amounts, ie less than 15 mg/day.
The best way to protect against cancer is to not smoke or stop!</p>

<p><strong>In summary:</strong></p>

<blockquote><p>If you want to prepare your skin to the sun and enhance your tan, you can of course make solar capsules, but no guarantee of effectiveness except to have a more colorful skin! By cons, apply the dose indicated on the instructions of dietary supplement and in any case, apply sunscreen to protect you from UV.</p></blockquote>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salt. A real danger to our health]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/salt-a-real-danger-to-our-health/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-13T23:38:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/salt-a-real-danger-to-our-health</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/salt-a-real-danger-to-our-health/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="salt, food, health" alt="Salt, a real danger to our health"><strong>Our diet is too rich in salt.</strong></p>

<p>Now the world specialists of hypertension and cardiovascular disease are unanimous: <strong>excess salt is detrimental to the overall population, regardless of age.</strong></p>

<p>Thus the reduction of salt is one of the leading objectives of national health nutrition.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>The dangers of salt</h2>

<p>A strong link has been established between excessive salt intake and health.</p>

<ul>
<li><p><strong>A diet high in salt is one of the risk factors for hypertension and cardiovascular disease.</strong>
In fact, there is a direct link between excess salt in the diet and high blood pressure because the genes that control blood pressure are also those that regulate salt reabsorption in the kidneys. But cardiovascular disease is the leading cause of death in our country.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Excess salt is also known to promote the gastric cancer.</strong></p></li>
<li><p><strong>Finally, too much salt increases the risk of osteoporosis.</strong>
Knowing that high salt levels in the blood increases calcium excretion in urine, after several years, this may result in a decrease in bone mineral density and increased osteoporosis.</p></li>
</ul>


<h2>The French consume too much salt</h2>

<p>According to the latest expertise of the National Agency for Food Safety (handles), the average salt consumption of French through food is 8.7 g/day in men and 6.7 g/day in women. At these intakes from food consumed, &ldquo;we must add 1 to 2 grams of salt per day, due to salting food and cooking water by the consumer himself&rdquo;.</p>

<p><strong>This is too much and too far from the recommendations of the WHO recommends not exceed 5 g of salt per day.</strong></p>

<p>So much so that health authorities have been forced to set interim target of 8 g per day maturity of 5 years, a reduction of 20% (6.5 g/day for women and children)!</p>

<h2>An imperative: reduce sodium intake in the diet</h2>

<p>Consumers generally know the risks associated with excess salt, but what they often do not know is that over 70% of the salt consumed comes from a group of 6 food:</p>

<ul>
<li>Bread and crackers.</li>
<li>The deli.</li>
<li>Soups.</li>
<li>Cheese.</li>
<li>The dishes.</li>
<li>Pizzas, quiches and savory pastries.</li>
</ul>


<p>To which must be added (because of their high consumption in children):</p>

<ul>
<li>The pastries.</li>
<li>The cereal breakfast.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Solutions they get there?</h2>

<ul>
<li><p>Decrease the salt levels in foods and thus encourage industry to engage in a charter or regulatory changes.
Remember that salt is interesting as a preservative, flavor enhancer and has a assoiffant power (likely to drive up consumption of drinks&hellip;).</p></li>
<li><p>More information for consumers through the labeling of the salt content of industrial products.</p></li>
<li><p>Encourage French to limit their consumption of the most savory and salt additions in the preparation and during the meal.</p></li>
</ul>


<p><strong>On the right track</strong>
These three fields of action have already been more or less established, with the first results in a decrease between 1999 and 2007 of 5.2% of average salt intake in the general population and 20-30% in very heavy users (more than 12 g/day).</p>

<h2>Delete eating habits at risk</h2>

<p><strong>We can all individually control a good part of our sodium intake by eliminating our eating habits at risk:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li><p>No salt available on the table.</p></li>
<li><p>Ban systematic dusting: always taste before adding salt or salt.</p></li>
<li><p>Replace salt with other types of seasonings such as spices, herbs and cooking with garlic, onions, shallots.</p></li>
<li><p>Reduce the amount of salt added to the cooking water.</p></li>
<li><p>Replace crackers, peanuts and chips with vegetables and fruits: cherry tomatoes, radish, melon balls, celery or carrots soaked in yoghurt sauce, etc..</p></li>
<li><p>Avoid too rich mineral waters by comparing the sodium salt contents on the labels.</p></li>
<li><p>Limiting industrial products, often very rich in salt.</p></li>
<li><p>Limit the richest salt foods: meats (salami, prosciutto), broth (vegetable or meat), sauces and condiments, cheeses, pizzas and quiches, pastries, crackers, etc..</p></li>
<li><p>Do not accustom young children to eat too salty because eating habits are set in early childhood and it is difficult to change in adulthood.</p></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hysteria: what symptoms? Being hysterical]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/hysteria-what-symptoms-being-hysterical/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-12T17:05:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/hysteria-what-symptoms-being-hysterical</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/hysteria-what-symptoms-being-hysterical/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="hysteria, hysterical personality, hysterical conversion, hysterical somatization" alt="Hysteria: what symptoms? Being hysterical">Hysteria, this term is often used in common parlance usually means in this context quite different things.</p>

<p>You are hysterical sometimes means: &ldquo;You get mad for nothing&rdquo;, &ldquo;You really added&rdquo; or &ldquo;I do not understand your operation!&rdquo;</p>

<p>However, the term hysteria has a different meaning in psychiatric medicine that hysteria itself corresponds to the symptoms found in the foreground in a pathological personality type, hysterical personalities.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>How is a person suffering from hysteria?</h2>

<p>Specific attitudes of hysteria are being representing. When you see such a person, you feel that it is too: it seems to be in a movie, play a role; it dramatizes, dramatize, exaggerate, in add. It is in excess, talking loudly, quickly, occupies the ground, laughed too, makes great gestures, uses formulas disproportionate to what it says. Some TV presenters or some actors therefore logically hysterical personality.</p>

<p>Hysteria up to the mythomanie when the affected person really adds some too. It can go up lie, misrepresent reality. However hysteria does not always go to this extreme.</p>

<p>Another very common element in hysteria is seduction: human relationships are eroticized, we try to seduce you, in life in general, but also in the sexual realm. In humans, hysteria is often linked to philandering, a tendency to collect relationships. However, this seductive attitude is often associated with a poor sex, inhibited difficult. For hysteria is a facade that hides gaps.</p>

<h2>What are the thoughts related to hysteria?</h2>

<p>The hysterical behavior and therefore hysterical symptoms, are exposed because they are caused by inner thoughts. In other words, a person with hysterical tendencies thoughts explaining his behavior.</p>

<p>It may be varied cognition:</p>

<p>&ldquo;I must be the center of attention&rdquo;;
&ldquo;I need you to notice me&rdquo;;
&ldquo;I&rsquo;m afraid to be alone&rdquo;;
&ldquo;I need to charm, to please&rdquo;;
&ldquo;I do not want you see my weaknesses, my fears&rdquo;;
&ldquo;I need the others because I do not know just do it myself&rdquo;;
&ldquo;I want you to find me irresistible&rdquo;&hellip;</p>

<h2>The deep emotions of hysteria</h2>

<p>If signs of hysteria are related to thoughts, these thoughts are related, deeper emotions. These emotions are especially fears that seek to be erased by the hysterical behavior:</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m afraid you do not love me&hellip; So I&rsquo;m doing what I think suitable for you love me.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m afraid I do not exist&hellip; So I do everything for you notice me and feel me exist.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m afraid I can not do it myself&hellip; So I need to charm around me that are helping me.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m afraid to be unhappy face myself&hellip; So I&rsquo;m dizzy from others, so do not find me alone with myself.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m afraid that my weaknesses are noticed&hellip; Then I add, I boast, I invent, I overplayed to try to hide my limits.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Overall, the hysterical symptoms, fairly simple to spot, and sometimes annoying for the environment actually correspond to deep fears and significant gaps. Perhaps by being aware, we can all show more empathy for people working in this register.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to calibrate their cholesterol. Triglyceride and HDL-cholesterol]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-10T01:15:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="cholesterol, cholesterol tests" alt="When to calibrate their cholesterol, Triglyceride and HDL-cholesterol">Certain periods of life, habits and diseases should motivate them to calibrate their cholesterol.</p>

<p>Recall that cholesterol is accompanied at first no symptoms until the day cardiovascular complications occur (myocardial infarction, stroke)!</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>At what times of life should you calibrate their cholesterol?</h2>

<h3>A adolescence</h3>

<p>A first cholesterol test is recommended between 16 and 30 years. Some people are more at risk than others and our lifestyle plays an important role, explaining that high cholesterol can occur in childhood. But during this period of life, the &ldquo;bad cholesterol&rdquo; is gradually deposited on the arterial walls and turns into plaque at the end of adolescence. In addition, it is to the age of 18 that cholesterol binds permanently.</p>

<blockquote><p>In other words, if cholesterol is high in adolescence, it will be a lifetime.</p></blockquote>

<h3>From 45 years for men and 55 years for women</h3>

<p>From these ages, a cholesterol test is recommended every 3 years. Is that with advancing age, the risk of having too much cholesterol in the blood is increased.</p>

<blockquote><p>As is also the case for other cardiovascular risk factors (hypertension, physical inactivity, overweight&hellip;), it must be particularly vigilant.</p></blockquote>

<h3>At the time of menopause</h3>

<p>In women, a dosage once installed menopause is wise. Indeed, major hormonal changes that occur at this time of life can lead to a significant increase in cholesterol.</p>

<blockquote><p>Menopause is a key period to make a determination of its cholesterol.</p></blockquote>

<h2>What are the diseases that require close monitoring cholesterol?</h2>

<ul>
<li>A <strong>type 2 diabetes</strong> imposes a cholesterol test every year.</li>
<li><strong>Overweight or obesity promoting cholesterol</strong>, it is necessary to conduct regular dosages. This is also the case when the waist is high: greater than 88 cm for women and 102 cm for men.</li>
<li><strong>Some diseases such as chronic renal failure and untreated hypothyroidism cause high cholesterol</strong> and impose specific monitoring.</li>
<li>Finally, <strong>some drugs affect blood lipids</strong>. Talk to your doctor.</li>
</ul>


<h2>What are the habits that require regular cholesterol test?</h2>

<ul>
<li>Smoking (or stopped for less than 3 years), especially if combined with an oral contraceptive.</li>
<li>Inactivity.</li>
<li>A diet rich in meat, animal products and fats.</li>
</ul>


<h2>What dose do we exactly?</h2>

<p>The determination of total cholesterol in the blood is commonly prescribed as part of a screening or surveillance.</p>

<p>However, to get a clearer picture, it is necessary to make an assessment of lipid abnormalities, including:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>The Triglyceride and HDL- cholesterol</strong> (normal: From 0.35 to 0.75 g/l).</li>
<li><strong>On the LDL-cholesterol</strong> is calculated from the values ??of the previous (normal: 1 to 1.6 g/l).</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Products debilitating arthritis pain]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/products-debilitating-arthritis-pain/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-05T12:52:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/products-debilitating-arthritis-pain</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/products-debilitating-arthritis-pain/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="arthritis pain, arthritis, diet, hondroprotectors, dairy products" alt="Products debilitating arthritis pain">Arthritis &ndash; an inflammatory disease of the joint (or more joints), and among the main causes various infections diseases, injuries, nervous system disorders, allergy, metabolic disorders, vitamin deficiencies. The disease occurs quite often, and do not always get sick elderly people (although they are certainly more often).</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Arthritis &ndash; a set of measures, including medication, mud hirudotherapy, physiotherapy, and, alas, sometimes it comes to surgery. But the disease could have been avoided or at least significantly delay it, if in time, that is, from his youth to think about its prevention. And this, above all, the right diet. But never too late to start, the people who have been diagnosed with arthritis, it is recommended to stick to a certain diet &ndash; in conjunction with the main treatment this will substantially reduce joint pain and slow the progression of the disease.</p>

<h2>Fighting overweight</h2>

<p>There have arthritis your &ldquo;favorites&rdquo;, but rather &ldquo;darling&rdquo; &ndash; is obese women overstepped 50-year milestone. As a rule, most of these ladies are suffering from any disease of the joints &ndash; this arthritis and osteoarthritis and gout, etc. It is important to understand that the further progression of these diseases in a short time can lead to disability and, of course, very spoil the quality of life, and that is why it is now important in combination with other therapeutic measures to think about weight loss. This not only helps to improve the condition of the joints, but also contribute to the overall improvement of the body.</p>

<h2>Priority products</h2>

<p>Is not a secret that vegetarians are significantly less likely to suffer from diseases of the joints than avid meat-eaters. Besides diet, based fresh fruits and vegetables containing fiber, promote rapid weight loss.</p>

<p>For example, people suffering from arthritis, recommended in all kinds of cabbage. It contains sulforaphane &ndash; a substance which prevents the destruction of the cartilage tissue. In this sense, all the good cabbage varieties, but especially broccoli. Cabbage also contains a record number of vitamins, micro and macro, and therefore not only helps prevent joint pain, but also enhances the body&rsquo;s resistance to many diseases. And by the way, the constant use of cabbage effectively helps to cope with the problem of constipation, if any.</p>

<p>Summer must eat cherries. These berries contain a lot of antioxidants (anthocyanins), which due to their anti-inflammatory properties, act as an anesthetic. Arthritis, osteoarthritis and gout even able to retreat before the cherries.</p>

<p><strong>Collagen</strong> is essential for building bone and cartilage, muscles and ligaments. He is in aspic jelly or which are prepared on the basis of bone broth.</p>

<p><strong>Chondroprotectors</strong> &ndash; another substance which promotes the restoration of the cartilaginous tissue and enhances the production of synovial fluid. Pharmacopeia offers a variety of drugs for the treatment of arthritis, based on glucosamine and chondroitin them who belong to the group chondroprotectors. Contains a substance in food gelatin, so do not forget to prepare a more delicious dessert and low-cal like jelly.</p>

<p>It must be treated gently <strong>proteins</strong>, such as red meat is recommended to exclude completely, but that does not mean that you should go to the protein-free diet. Proteins are needed to build new tissue and to restore the cartilage that covers the articular surfaces of bones. &ldquo;Take&rdquo; protein from lean white meat, fish and vegetable of buckwheat and legumes (peas, beans, lentils). By the way, the protein is better absorbed if the meat is cooked for a couple of stewed or boiled. Contribute to the restoration of the joints and dairy products, particularly useful dairy products &ndash; yogurt, fermented baked milk, cottage cheese.</p>

<p>One of the causes of joint diseases is metabolic disorders, so patients with arthritis need fats. It should be fats of vegetable origin, also allowed a small amount of butter.</p>

<p>Body needs B vitamins &ndash; they play an important role in the proper metabolism. A lack of these vitamins in addition to arthritis can appear many other diseases, is caused by impaired metabolism.</p>

<p>Vitamin D &ndash; is another important vitamin, its deficiency leads to excessive deposition of calcium in the articular cartilage to reduce its elasticity. Result &ndash; the cartilage is gradually destroyed. Compensate for the deficiency of this vitamin helps the fish oil &ndash; it requires not only children but also adults.</p>

<p>Drink a lot! Water &ndash; the basis of any diet in the treatment of arthritis. Dehydration is extremely harmful for our joints, and, as they say, do not lead to sin, it is understood that dehydration occurs in the joints long before a person starts to feel thirsty. But the fluid can not be abused &ndash; excess fluid leads to edema, and this disrupts the blood supply and food joints. So drink plenty of fluids, but be careful to avoid edema.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your legs get restless? This is the restless legs]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/your-legs-get-restless-this-is-the-restless-legs/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-01T16:14:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/your-legs-get-restless-this-is-the-restless-legs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/your-legs-get-restless-this-is-the-restless-legs/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="legs, restless legs, sleep, impatience, disease" alt="Your legs get restless? This is the restless legs">The restless legs syndrome is not known.
<strong>It appears at the two legs of impatience, temporarily relieved by movement.</strong><!-- more --></p>

<h2>Restless: twice as many women as men</h2>

<p>The restless legs also called &ldquo;impatience&rdquo; is due to an abnormality of the neurotransmitters dopamine (unlike Parkinson&rsquo;s disease, there is no neuronal death). It affects twice as many women than men, especially after age 50, and there is often a family history. This syndrome also occurs more often during pregnancy and after menopause without really knowing why, although a role of hormones is suspected.</p>

<blockquote><p>The impatience manifested by discomfort in both legs with the urge to move the legs, causing an almost immediate relief but short.</p></blockquote>

<p>This very unpleasant feeling has the characteristic to occur exclusively at rest, sitting or lying down, preferably in the evening and in the early part of the night.
<strong>This results in great difficulty in falling asleep, making restless legs the second leading cause of sleep disorders after sleep apnea syndrome.</strong></p>

<p>In 80% of cases, patients also suffer from automatic and periodic limb movements. The incidence of disorders varies greatly, ranging from several days to a few times a year by seizures.</p>

<p><em>Note that the restless legs seems to correlate with the occurrence of hypertension, diabetes and obesity.</em></p>

<h2>Restless Legs: strong repercussions in everyday life</h2>

<p>One can easily imagine the dramatic social and professional repercussions, due to insomnia and exhaustion, abnormal movements and the immediate need to move, making it impossible entertainment, transport or sitting at the hairdresser.</p>

<p>The medical check passes first by looking for an iron deficiency, which improves the correction disorders. Then the treatment is based on the administration of dopamine at lower than those used in Parkinson&rsquo;s disease doses.</p>

<blockquote><p>In conclusion, it should be noted that the restless legs syndrome exists and treated.
And if you suffer from sleep disorders, do not forget about your impatience to your doctor!</p></blockquote>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Factors of hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/factors-of-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-15T00:03:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/factors-of-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/factors-of-hemorrhoids/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="factors of hemorrhoids, causes of hemorrhoids, hemorrhoid treatment, proctology, Venapro" alt="Factors of Hemorrhoids">Hemorrhoids &ndash; an inflammatory disease that may affect the pathological expansion of hemorrhoidal veins and the formation of knots. According to medical statistics, hemorrhoids often occurs in people older than 45 years.</p>

<p>The exact cause of hemorrhoids is still not established. The main possible causes of the disease, modern medicine treats vascular pathology (dysfunction between the blood flow through the arteries and the flow of blood through the cavernous veins) and disruption of the muscular system, retaining hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Factors of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Promote the development of hemorrhoids are many factors among which are:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>Genetic predisposition</strong>. Some people venous network in the anus has a very dense plexus, which complicates the flow of blood through the vessels. In case of violation of vascular permeability develops blood stagnation that contributes to the inflammatory process.</li>
<li><strong>Pregnancy and childbirth</strong>. During pregnancy the uterus increases in size, which leads to a displacement of the movable upward while the rectum is pressed against the pelvis. Thus, the clamped venous blood vessels, which leads to an overflow of the cavernous bodies.</li>
<li><strong>Physical inactivity</strong>. Sedentary lifestyle contributes to the development of venous insufficiency, in particular to the development of stagnation in the pelvic organs. Reduce the chance of developing hemorrhoids is possible if regularly moderate exercise.</li>
<li><strong>Failure to comply with the rules of hygiene</strong>. When excessive hygiene anus, as well as the use of low-quality toilet paper mucosa irritated anus, thereby increasing the probability of acute hemorrhoids.</li>
<li><strong>Bad habits</strong>. Smoking worsens the condition of vessels, including hemorrhoidal veins. Also, smoking increases the severity of bleeding. As for alcoholic beverages, the alcohol helps dilate blood vessels, which in turn leads to stagnation of blood in the hemorrhoids.</li>
<li><strong>Malnutrition</strong>. Excessive consumption of hot and spicy food, as well as lack of fiber is a significant negative factor in the development of inflammatory processes in the rectum.</li>
<li><strong>Chronic constipation</strong>. Disturbances of feces leads to frequent constipation. Solid stool, lingering in the intestines, put pressure on the choroid plexus of the rectum, thereby helping to expand the hemorrhoidal veins. Also promotes the development of hemorrhoids during defecation habit to push.</li>
<li><strong>Hypothermia</strong>. Hypothermia leads to circulatory problems that can cause the development of inflammation in the rectal area. In particular, avoid hypothermia lower body (not sit on a cold surface, dress appropriately to weather conditions).</li>
<li><strong>Physical activity</strong>. Excessive exercise (weightlifting, bodybuilding, etc.) is likely to disrupt the tone of the muscular apparatus of the anus. Muscle weakness contributes anus prolapsed hemorrhoid. Furthermore, physical overload cause delay of blood in the veins, which increases the likelihood of developing hemorrhoids.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Hemorrhoid Treatment</h2>

<p>Any disease is always easier to prevent than to cure. At elimination of negative factors likely to develop hemorrhoids is minimal. Even hereditary predisposition to hemorrhoids may not materialize if lead a healthy lifestyle and eat right.</p>

<p>If the hemorrhoids are still developed, it is necessary as soon as possible to begin treatment. Depending on severity of the disease may be used as a conservative and surgical treatment.</p>

<p>Medication hemorrhoids includes use of anti- inflammatory, analgesic and hemostatic (if bleeding) drugs.</p>

<p>The most effective use of local products in the form of rectal suppositories. One such drug is Venapro. This combination drug, which includes an anti-inflammatory bufexamac, wound healing agent and bismuth subgallate anesthetic lidocaine component.</p>

<p>Venapro hemorrhoids is useful for a 1-2 stages, as well as diseases such as proctologic anal fissure, proctitis, anal eczema and other.</p>

<p>Available <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7" onclick="banner = ban.venapro">Venapro</span> in rectal suppositories, which makes it very convenient to use. The likelihood of side effects from the drug is extremely low.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[He does not like hemorrhoids?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/he-does-not-like-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-02T23:05:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/he-does-not-like-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/he-does-not-like-hemorrhoids/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="aggravation, contraindication factor, hypothermia, lack of exercise, physical activity, dietary fiber" alt="He does not like hemorrhoids?">Follow the advice of doctors and avoid the negative factors contributing to aggravate hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Why do I get hemorrhoids?</h2>

<p>Doctors say that lately hemorrhoids much &ldquo;younger&rdquo;. Most likely, the reason for that are the negative factors contributing to the development of the disease with which modern man often encountered. These factors include:</p>

<ul>
<li>pregnancy and childbirth;</li>
<li>heredity;</li>
<li>sedentary lifestyle;</li>
<li>unhealthy diet;</li>
<li>poor hygiene;</li>
<li>hypothermia;</li>
<li>chronic gastrointestinal disorder;</li>
<li>excessive exercise.</li>
</ul>


<p>The combination of these factors leads to the development of pathological enlargement of hemorrhoidal veins and implementation of disease. At the first symptoms should immediately contact a doctor, mainly because hemorrhoids characterized by chronic course with periodic exacerbations. In order to reduce the appearance of the disease and minimize the likelihood of an exacerbation, the patient must be aware of what not to do with hemorrhoids. Especially effective prevention of hemorrhoids is the first stage of the disease when the disease symptoms have not yet pronounced.</p>

<h2>Contraindications for hemorrhoids</h2>

<p><strong>Food contraindications</strong></p>

<p>When hemorrhoids diet is very important. As a preventive measure, doctors recommend eating foods containing large amounts of fiber. Such food will reduce the number of exacerbations and the severity of hemorrhoids. When varicose veins hemorrhoids may want to limit the consumption of these foods and dishes:</p>

<ul>
<li>fried foods;</li>
<li>hot and spicy dishes, irritating;</li>
<li>semolina;</li>
<li>mashed potatoes;</li>
<li>eggs;</li>
<li>jelly;</li>
<li>alcohol;</li>
<li>black tea, coffee.</li>
</ul>


<p><strong>Hypodynamy</strong></p>

<p>Sedentary lifestyle contributes to stagnation in the pelvic organs, which only aggravates the disease. At risk are people who have to be for a long time without moving (office workers, drivers). Try as much as possible to do a little workout. On the way to and from work, try to walk more. And best of all to engage in moderate exercise regularly. Jogging, swimming, walking trails and many other kinds of physical activity will only benefit.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bleeding internal hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/bleeding-internal-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-30T07:07:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/bleeding-internal-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/bleeding-internal-hemorrhoids/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Bleeding internal hemorrhoids" alt="Bleeding internal hemorrhoids"> <strong>Hemorrhoids.</strong> One of the main symptoms of this disease is the hemorrhoidal bleeding.</p>

<p>Literature data of recent years have pointed out that the cause of hemorrhoids is a violation of the outflow of blood from the venules of the cavernous bodies, which are located in the wall of the rectum (the largest cluster of notes on 3-7-11 hours on the dial) and is a substrate haemorrhoid. <!-- more -->Therefore, if the wall of the cavernous bodies, which is filled with blood directly from the arterial bed is damaged, the stands out of scarlet, oxygen saturation arterial blood.</p>

<p>Bleeding at internal hemorrhoids characterized in that the blood volume, wherein is of a few drops to 100-200 ml per day and with frequent hemorrhage causes the development of anemia. In some cases, hemorrhage may be inkjet and pulsating.</p>

<p><strong>Diagnosis.</strong> Under gentle disclosure of the edges of the anus hemorrhoids are defined as swollen formations bluish color, soft-elastic consistency, covered with a mucous membrane. Necessarily carry out the finger, mirroring studies and sigmoidoscopy. Soft hemorrhoids are rarely detected by digital examination, but this study is an important method for the differential diagnosis. When the mirror examination may reveal the bleeding internal hemorrhoids.</p>

<p><strong>Treatment.</strong> We must remember that the causes of intestinal bleeding may be tumors (benign and malignant) of rectum and colon. Only after exclusion of these diseases should begin to targeted <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7" onclick="banner = ban.venapro">treatment of hemorrhoidal bleeding</span>.</p>

<p>In chronic hemorrhoids, which manifests itself only bleeding internal hemorrhoids without a loss of knots, in the absence of common anorectal thrombosis recommends a hemostatic therapy with Venapro. 10 percent calcium chloride, 5 percent solution of aminocaproic acid as well as with the use of adrenaline suppositories by recipe.</p>

<p>In the absence of contraindications is possible to use an injection of sclerosing agents.</p>

<p>Contraindications to this kind of treatment are diseases of the prostate and hypertension, in which if there is no severe anemia, such  bleeding is as would damping. At presence of infectious diseases, inflammatory changes in the walls of the anal canal and rectal mucosa injection of sclerosing agents is contraindicated. Relative contraindications for sclerotherapy are loss of internal hemorrhoids and frequent exacerbation of chronic hemorrhoids, because the presence of these complications are indications for surgical treatment.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
