<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-12-02T00:01:59+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homemade masks for oily hair. Proper care and cleaning oily hair]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/homemade-masks-for-oily-hair-proper-care-and-cleaning-oily-hair/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-30T14:33:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/homemade-masks-for-oily-hair-proper-care-and-cleaning-oily-hair</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/causes-of-greasy-hair/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Causes of greasy hair, oily hair wash, homemade mask for oily hair" alt="Homemade masks for oily hair. Proper care and cleaning oily hair"> Greasy hair requires frequent washing. Oily hair often lead women to despair and cause a lot of inconvenience to them that quickly gryazneyut and by the end of the day look greasy and stale, even if they are washed in the morning. But experts urge not to get upset and argue that care for them is much easier than in the dry, which, moreover, are often brittle and weakened. In addition, oily hair, thanks to the high fat content, have a huge advantage over the dry, because they, like oily skin, thanks to the natural lubrication, well protected from adverse external influences.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Causes of oily hair</h2>

<p>The main reason is the high fat content is that the sebaceous glands work too active and produce more sebum than necessary. Increased sebum secretion is often caused by genetics, but could be evidence of violations of the endocrine system.</p>

<p>In addition, increase the separation of fat intake of antibiotics, poor nutrition, extreme temperatures, severe stress and improper care. Experts believe that the right care for oily hair will avoid many of the problems and ensure that they always look nice and neat.</p>

<h2>Wash oily hair</h2>

<p>A very important question is the frequency of washing. And if you have recently called for beauticians do not wash my hair 1-2 times a week, so as not to stimulate increased zhirootdelenie, now come to the conclusion that it is much more harmful to walk with excessively oily hair. If you do not wash your hair for a long time, the upper protective layer of the scalp are beginning to proliferate microscopic fungi and yeasts that cause itching, dandruff, acne on his head and a variety of inflammatory processes. In addition, the hair follicles become clogged with fat and sebaceous ducts harden, causing the hair to stop growing, thin and hard fall.</p>

<p>Therefore, wash oily hair should be implemented as necessary, at least every day. Water for washing should not be too hot, as hot water activates the sebaceous glands. Before washing, you need to carefully comb hair &ndash; it will partially remove dirt, dandruff and protect themselves from tangling. Shampoo need not be applied directly to the hair, because in this case it is not evenly distributed.</p>

<p>It is best to dilute a small amount of shampoo to wash with water and the resulting solution, or to put it first in the palm of your hand. Lather oily hair better twice, distributing shampoo soft circular motions and without scratching the skin nails.</p>

<p>It is important to thoroughly rinse the hair after washing, because of the remnants of shampoo they are faster and have gryazneyut adhesive and matte appearance. After washing, do not immediately need to comb your hair, they need to dry out a bit. Try to use a hair dryer only when absolutely necessary, because the temperature changes are bad for oily skin and stimulate the strengthening zhirootdeleniya.</p>

<h2>Shampoo for oily hair</h2>

<p>Shampoo for oily hair should be selected very carefully, studying the composition indicated on the label. A well-chosen shampoo helps to restore proper operation of the sebaceous glands and remove the irritation and the use of the wrong shampoo will only worsen the situation. Choose a shampoo transparent natural colors &ndash; white or off-white, creamy shampoos because the bright colors often contain poisonous unnecessary and harmful dyes.</p>

<p>The most effective are the shampoos with herbal extracts &ndash; nettle, chamomile, sage, mother and stepmother, and also contain algae, vitamins A, K, C, and zinc. In the presence of dandruff shampoos choose from zinc, sulfur and tar. Do not buy shampoos, if they contain silicone, because they are heavier hair and make them even fatter.</p>

<p>Great popularity in recent years become dry shampoos that are especially useful on business trips, travel and the absence of hot water and time. These shampoos are available in powder form and are applied by spray. After 5-10 minutes, when the powder to soak up all the grease and dirt, his combed comb.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Depression, anxiety and fear - not a sentence, all curable]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/depression-anxiety-and-fear-not-a-sentence-all-curable/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-30T14:31:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/depression-anxiety-and-fear-not-a-sentence-all-curable</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/mood/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Mood, vitality, there is no meaning in life" alt="Depression, anxiety and fear - not a sentence, all curable"> Depression is treated successfully with antidepressants. The problem of depression and other psycho-emotional disorders in this age of high speed is very urgent.</p>

<p>According to the WHO, the scale and speed of the spread of this disease are devastating, on the heels of such a &ldquo;popular&rdquo; diseases such as stroke, heart attack and diabetes. And the age of patients getting younger &ndash; if earlier depression affecting people after 40 years, but now the problem is widespread and adolescence.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>According to the same WHO, now every fourth &ndash; fifth of the Earth suffers what &ndash; or mental disorders, and by 2020 it is expected that depression will be the first in the world in disease.</p>

<p>However, do not confuse the real, medical depression with the usual blues and just a bad mood, because, at the household level depression &ndash; is sadness, grief and anguish. If you have just the blues, then there are many ways to cheer yourself and force of will to withdraw from this state.</p>

<p>Many people are faced with the phenomenon of temporary loss of mood and vitality, and everyone finds themselves out of this situation, what &ndash; something out. Who &ndash; is beginning to go hard in the gym who &ndash; that finds relief in the church, some with just dipped his head into some interesting job or hobby, alternate setting or go to rest. But if, unfortunately, you caught a real depression, then just your efforts will, unfortunately, will not be enough.</p>

<p>Depression, according to the definition in Wikipedia &ndash; is a mental disorder that is characterized by constantly depressed mood, loss of ability to experience pleasure, low self-esteem, and the complete loss of interest in life, and to that previously happy. The fact is that depression and mood decline is easily explained on a chemical level, and due to lack of production of the hormone serotonin in the body.</p>

<p>The role of this hormone in the human body is impressive &ndash; he is responsible for the process of cognitive activity, locomotor activity and muscle tone. But most importantly, it creates in us a sense of lifting mood and happiness, and so it is called the hormone of happiness. Normal levels of serotonin gives a person self-control, emotional and stress.</p>

<p>Some researchers have found that people who are dominant in society, have high levels of serotonin. People with a low level of serotonin, on the contrary, self-control, emotional stress and so reduced that the slightest pretexts are stressful, and as a result, depressed.</p>

<p>Very often people who are depressed, not knowing what was happening to them and trying to dull the emotional pain and anxiety begin to take alcohol or psychotropic substances, and this signing his own death warrant, because with the help of drugs and alcohol can only be purchased chronic alcoholism or drug addiction,  In this case, the craving for alcohol and drug abuse is secondary and serves the purpose of relieving anxiety and tension inherent in depression.</p>

<p>Moreover, the relatives of a person suffering from depression and alcohol secondary lapsed into alcoholism, of course, the best of intentions, are his &ldquo;encode&rdquo; to eliminate the pernicious craving for alcohol. But we must understand that &ldquo;coding&rdquo; refers to the psycho-terrorist methods and is based on an elementary intimidation sick that he could not lead a person to recovery, since no alcohol, no depression can not be cured in this way.</p>

<p>The big problem also lies in the fact that in our country are depressed people, especially young men, are often embarrassed to admit their psycho &ndash; emotional problems, ignore the problem and do not seek medical attention, thereby only exacerbating their condition.</p>

<p>Depression, as mentioned above, the only cure at will or not alcohol. This disease is treated with special drugs, which are called antidepressants, their effect on the regulation of the level of serotonin in the brain. There are so many antidepressants and use them to learn to successfully treat depression. Although long-term treatment and under mandatory supervision of a physician, but defeat disease is now possible once and for all.</p>

<p>Ashamed of their condition is not necessary, because it is the same disease as any other. Depression does not destroy the mind and human intelligence, it just does not allow him to live fully, and in a state of neglect often even leads to suicide.</p>

<p>Depression affects many of the greatest and brightest of today. British Prime Minister Winston Churchill struggled all his life with depression and called it &ldquo;the black dog that with me all my life.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Therefore, if you are suffering from depression and she does not go alone for a long time, do not worry, nothing bad has happened to you, just dropped us a much-needed level of the hormone serotonin. Entrust your problems doctor and competent therapist with the necessary medicines will return the joy in your life.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nail fungus. Fungal nail disease, symptoms and prevention]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nail-fungus-fungal-nail-disease-symptoms-and-prevention/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-30T14:29:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/nail-fungus-fungal-nail-disease-symptoms-and-prevention</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/nail-fungus/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Fungal nail disease, nail fungus" alt="Nail fungus. Fungal nail disease, symptoms and prevention"> Fungal nail disease and still require early treatment and prevention. Fungal nail disease and stop its rapid growth concern dermatologists around the world. According to their estimates, is suffering from a quarter of the world&rsquo;s population, especially in large cities with high population density, and this figure continues to grow.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Causes and Symptoms of fungal infections of nails and feet</h2>

<p>Ways of getting a lot of fungus in the body, you can catch anywhere, but most often it is on the beach, in the bath, in the pool, the sauna or the shoes of people infected.</p>

<p>Nail Fungus transmitted not only from person to person, but also from animals to humans, and from the external environment. Complicating the situation is that there is a great variety of mushrooms, more than 1.5 million of them are pathogenic to humans about 500 species.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, fungal infections do not produce immunity, and a person can be infected by the same form of the fungus many times. Fungi remarkably tenacious, as evidenced by the scientists conducted an unusual experiment &ndash; they put the shoes sick fungus man in a locker, and when 20 years later got her out of there, the spores of the fungus were fully viable. Therefore a crucial role in the fight against fungi plays prevention of fungal nail diseases and personal hygiene.</p>

<p>Mushrooms particularly active subject in humidity, heat and poor ventilation, and excessive use of soaps and detergents do not give that effect, which we expect hard observing hygiene. The fact that the surface of our skin has a protective, so-called lipid layer, the finest film of fat that they live in our &ldquo;native&rdquo; beneficial bacteria designed to protect us from the adverse effects of the environment.</p>

<p>Doctors do not recommend to wash with soap and water often, as when washing wool we literally rip off off this protective film, and a variety of micro-organisms, bacteria and fungi literally stick to our body without resistance, is not completely restore the natural cover, which takes about</p>

<p>An interesting scientific fact &ndash; in the 30-ies of the last century, during the establishment of the Soviet regime, the Chukchi, Evenki and other northern nations have become hard to teach hygiene, wash with soap making. The result was so unexpected that at first the doctors just shrugged and could not understand why Aboriginal started such a colossal death.</p>

<p>As it turned out later, soap destroying the protective layer of fat covering their skin and they were completely defenseless against the invasion of microorganisms. By the way, the researchers argue that it is for this same reason, and we often get sick after a bath, and not from the fact that hypothermia is commonly thought. Nature, as we know, did not know soap, the use of detergents &ndash; is a recent invention of European civilization. If you do not want to kill a cat or dog, do not wash them with soap or shampoo, because the animal can not live long in such a &ldquo;sterile&rdquo;.</p>

<p>If it affects the human fungal disease, first, as a rule, there are cracks between the toes and on the soles, and then passes the infection on your nails. It is believed that the fungus uncured stop sooner or later turns into a nail fungus from which escape is not so easy. Man begins to disturb the symptoms of fungal nail diseases &ndash; itching, discomfort and bad breath. Nail changes color becomes dull, opaque, crumbles, deformed, thickened. If the disease is not treated in time, the nail may collapse completely, and the fungus will eventually hit the nails on the hands.</p>

<p>If you do not fight the infection, the fungus begins to &ldquo;walk&rdquo; around the body, releasing toxins that affects the lymphatic and circulatory systems, reduces immunity and causes multiple allergies, sometimes even able to hit the brain. Man gets tired quickly, feel malaise, nausea, frequent colds.</p>

<h2>Prevention of fungal nail diseases</h2>

<p>Nail fungal disease is considered to be the surrender of immunity, so it is often susceptible to it people with weakened or immature immune, that is, children and the elderly. Considered a risk factor for various scratches, abrasions and other skin damage through which the fungus is easier to penetrate into the body, which are the gateway for incoming infections.</p>

<p>If you notice the first signs of fungal nail disease, such as discoloration of the nail, its transparency, thickening of the nail plate, an inflammation of the skin around the nail, as well as itching and redness between the toes, it is necessary without delay to see a doctor &ndash; dermatologist and deliver  The fungus is now successfully treated thanks to the arsenal of physicians in a large range of antifungal drugs. Most importantly, time to start treatment and prevent total capture of infection in your body.</p>

<p>If the affected area is small, it is often possible to cope with the fungus by local treatment. If the process of infection went away, then the treatment will be more time consuming, but, in any case, it should bring to an end, as the untreated fungus necessarily continue its destructive work. In the treatment of a family member, all others should also be examined, as most at risk of infection.</p>

<p>Better prevention of fungal infections of nails and feet &ndash; a thorough safety precautions to prevent re-infection. If you have been in a public bath and not too sure of its sterility, the best means of prevention is the treatment of foot boric alcohol or vinegar diluted as 1 tablespoon per cup of water, the media is detrimental to the fungus. Do not wear someone else&rsquo;s shoes, dry the feet, all the scratches and damage immediately treated with iodine or green paint.</p>

<p>When buying shoes, choose a spacious, comfortable, preferably made of natural materials and vented, because, as mentioned above, the fungus loves moist environment without air. Their shoes and do not forget to air regularly and periodically wipe the inside with a solution of vinegar, which kills germs, while leaving no odor.</p>

<p>If you nail fungal diseases is very important to strengthen your own immune system, destroyed the invasion of fungal infection. So, get the overall strengthening and healing the body &ndash; drink plenty of water, eat only healthy food with the required amount of vitamins and minerals, do not overeat, sometimes it is better to starve. And certainly normalize intestinal function, go in uncomplicated physical exercise, get enough sleep and maximize protect yourself from the stress.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meals centenarians. Secrets of longevity]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/meals-centenarians-secrets-of-longevity/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-28T23:12:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/meals-centenarians-secrets-of-longevity</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/food-centenarians/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Food centenarians, longevity secrets" alt="Meals centenarians. Secrets of longevity"> Secrets of centenarians &ndash; in their diet. The greatest Greek physician Hippocrates and teacher, whose name is in our perception is inextricably linked with the famous Hippocratic Oath, rightly considered the &ldquo;father of medicine&rdquo;, claimed that any human disease is due to a breach of food habits and lifestyle.</p>

<p>It belongs to Hippocrates famous phrase: &ldquo;We are what we eat&rdquo;, thus emphasizing the most important role nutrition for human life and health.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Without exception, all people want to live a long time, but have to stay healthy, vigorous, firm in the mind and memory. Scientists around the world are trying to find the answer to the secrets of longevity, carefully study this phenomenon, trying to understand why so few people manage to live so long without the disease, although genetically the human capacity for approximately 150 years of life.</p>

<h2>Power centenarians</h2>

<p>Despite the huge number of hypotheses about the secrets of health and longevity, as well as the fact that all the various centenarians living conditions &ndash; climatic, geographical, social, and views of all scientists in agreement that the power of centenarians is very closely linked with longevity and plays it  For all their differences and peculiarities, long-lived of all regions of the Earth have very similar features and rules for the use of food.</p>

<p>Slightly paraphrasing the famous line of Hippocrates, you can add that person &ndash; it&rsquo;s not only what he eats, but also the fact that he was drinking. All the world&rsquo;s centenarians drink only pure, natural spring water, which is the most important secret of longevity, since the human body is 75% water and therefore it is very important what kind of water it makes its internal reserves. On the crucial role of water in human life, norms of consumption and correct drinking regime for health read the article on our website.</p>

<p>Secrets of centenarians is pretty simple, like all brilliant. Centenarians world eat only those foods that grow in their climate zone without using anything to eat imported and exotic. It is so right that we should consider whether we need, such as bananas, which, undoubtedly, are a storehouse of vitamins, but only if they break and then eat.</p>

<p>However, as is known, bananas have not grow, they rip green, immature and thus are coated with wax and other harmful chemical compounds for prolonged preservation and transportation. So I ask, we need such fruits is not it better to eat an apple? The same question arises about the imported strawberries and watermelons have no taste, no smell, no good. Is not it better to wait for the season to gorge and plenty of delicious and healthy fruits and vegetables that grow in our area?</p>

<p>All centenarians eat very little of the world, never overeat and get up from the table without a sense of satiety. They are no excess weight and obesity, which are known to not add health and longevity. About the dangers of overeating and benefits of short breaks from eating to read this article.</p>

<p>Food in the diet dominated by long-lived low-fat and low-fat, which is very useful for keeping in perfect condition of blood vessels and the prevention of hypertension. The use of low-calorie food that has high biological activity, has long been experimentally proved by many scientists. Well known scientific experiment conducted on rats &ndash; in a subgroup of animals that reduced caloric intake by a quarter, life expectancy increased by 32%. However, where calorie reduced by 50%, the rats lived twice as long.</p>

<p>Food centenarians consume only fresh, it keeps the most of the vitamins and nutrients of food. Naturally, they reject the canned food and other unhealthy foods. No fast food, reheating and yesterday&rsquo;s food out of the fridge, all the half-eaten give cattle.</p>

<p>By the way, according to some studies, this indispensable in the modern kitchen thing as a microwave, just destroys the products have passed the microwave treatment, vitamins, minerals and nutrients. Therefore, whenever possible, should follow the example of centenarians &ndash; cook gruel and then eat it, not a three-day warm up in the microwave soup, which does not have anything useful. Especially do not recommend to warm up food in the microwave for small children.</p>

<p>Power centenarians virtually includes entrees and rich broth and meat on their menu is mainly present in cooked form. On the table there is always a lot of different herbs that help to keep the gut flora in perfect condition. In centenarians Abkhazia and Azerbaijan on the composition of intestinal microflora in general identical to the flora of healthy children, which is achieved by regular consumption of the national dairy products, which are known to be very useful for proper digestion.</p>

<p>An important secret of longevity is also made in the absence of sugar in their diet in its purest form, as well as a variety of jams, chocolates and other sweets today that can trigger the development of diabetes. Sugar they receive in the form of glucose, which is necessary for the body to quickly replenish energy deficit by eating honey, raisins and a variety of sweet fruit. Fruits and vegetables make up a large portion of all food centenarians.</p>

<p>Chinese gerontologists are absolutely sure that the formula found longevity and looks like this &ndash; very low calorie diet, with a minimal amount of fat and animal protein and lots of vegetables and fruits.</p>

<p>As far as this is true, time will tell, but do for yourself useful conclusions and adopt some simple secrets of centenarians in the diet, we just have to. Having started eating right, as do the long-lived all over the world, we will stop gaining weight, get sick, we are in great shape and, therefore, will live longer.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Periodontal disease and bleeding gums]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/periodontal-disease-and-bleeding-gums/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-28T23:10:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/periodontal-disease-and-bleeding-gums</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/periodontal-disease/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Periodontal disease, bleeding gums, periodontal" alt="Periodontal disease and bleeding gums"> Successful treatment of periodontal disease depends on timely access to a doctor. Bleeding gums is the most common symptom of periodontal disease &ndash; a complex of tissues surrounding and holding the teeth in the jaw bone. Despite the fact that by Parodont also include bone around the teeth and muscle ligaments that hold the teeth in the jaw bones, most people are faced with the problem of gum &ndash; regular or occasional bleeding, swelling and inflammation.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Many people mistakenly believe trifling periodontal disease and do not require emergency treatment of symptomatic &ndash; with &ldquo;harmless&rdquo; bleeding gums simply rinse their mouth herbs and do not go to the doctor. However, engaging in self-treatment, they cause serious damage to your health.</p>

<p>Fact that gingivitis (initial stage of periodontitis), the main symptom is bleeding gums, quite successfully (nearly 100%) is treatable if it initiated when the first symptoms.</p>

<p>If the disease takes the form of running, then there is a risk of losing teeth even at a young age. According to the WHO, 80% of children under the age of 10 years, there are already early signs of gingivitis, which is associated with significant physiological stress of the periodontal tissues in a growing body when cutting, shaping and growth of teeth.</p>

<p>For older people, because they have periodontitis tooth loss occurs in 95% of cases. However, there is good news &ndash; if only a few decades ago with the disease periodontitis keep the teeth was considered virtually impossible, the modern development of zubosohranyayuschih technology to successfully stop the destructive process.</p>

<h2>What is periodontal disease and periodontal disease &ndash; what&rsquo;s the difference between them</h2>

<p>Periodontal disease is a relatively rare disease (it accounts for only about 3 &ndash; 4% of the cases of periodontal problems), while periodontitis is &ldquo;honorable&rdquo; second among all dental disease (caries immediately after), and is present to varying degrees in nearly 95.</p>

<h2>Periodontal disease causes and symptoms</h2>

<p>Periodontal disease &ndash; is a non-inflammatory disease of periodontal tissues, which are due to internal disturbances in the body, leading to malnutrition and periodontal tissue perfusion and, as a consequence, to atrophy of the alveolar bone (bone edges of the hole tooth).</p>

<p>As a result of atrophic processes in periodontitis occur sclerotic changes in the bone tissue, reduced interdental septum, and the gums gradually become thinner and the like &ldquo;settle down&rdquo;, resulting in the effect of &ldquo;wedge-shaped teeth&rdquo; with bare roots. In the future, increased sensitivity to chemical and thermal stimuli, changing the color and the enamel is destroyed. Subsequently, as a result of running and complete atrophy, the teeth become loose and fall out much.</p>

<p>Local factors, in particular the impact of micro-organisms essential role in the development of the disease do not play, but serve only unfavorable factor aggravating.</p>

<h2>Periodontal disease symptoms and the stage</h2>

<p>Periodontitis, in contrast to periodontal disease, is an inflammatory nature and manifests the destruction of the connection between the tooth, gum and surrounding tissues, the formation of deep periodontal pockets and the gradual deformation and destruction of the bone hole tooth.</p>

<p>Because periodontal disease most often develops slowly and gradually over the years does not cause discomfort in the early stages it is quite difficult to diagnose. However, it should be noted that there are cases sufficient and rapid development of the disease.</p>

<h2>Step periodontitis</h2>

<p>First, the easy, harmless and effectively treatable stage of periodontal disease (gingivitis) is accompanied by a slight redness, inflammation and bleeding gums, bad breath and the formation of shallow periodontal pockets.</p>

<p>While moderate adds the following symptoms &ndash; a small tooth mobility, the emergence of cracks and gaps between the teeth, on education-and subgingival stones, difficulty in chewing food, deepening periodontal pockets (up to 5 mm) with a small selection of them.</p>

<p>In severe teeth start to hurt badly, offset, in part, loose and fall out, and deepened periodontal pockets and from their cavities are frequent and copious purulent discharge with an unpleasant odor.</p>

<p>Causes periodontal disease are diverse and the main of them are traditionally considered to be a lack of oral hygiene, however, all is not as easy as it might seem. Indeed, the microbes that live in the mouth and form plaque (stones), can affect the periodontal tissues, they cause inflammation and lead to loosening and loss of teeth. Therefore, periodic professional scaling is necessary, but, unfortunately, the lack of means of prevention.</p>

<p>Equally important role in the development of pathology plays the uneven load on the teeth, malocclusion uncorrected, errors prosthetics and jaw injuries. For example, periodontal disease often develops if removed 6th teeth and dentures soon not installed or improperly formed contact between the upper and lower jaws. Adverse effect might wear braces, microtrauma while cutting the thread, the habit of chewing on one side, leading to an overload of a separate part of the jaw, use as toothpicks metal objects, the effect on enamel acid and alkali.</p>

<p>It is important that the seals were installed correctly &ndash; do not protrude over the edge of the tooth, and at the same time, a close fit to it. If the seal is not tight fits, the germs and infections can easily penetrate to the root and destroy it, but if the seal hangs, it prevents the removal of plaque quality, and as a consequence, inflammation of the gum tissue. In case of improper prosthetic disease process develops locally, ie, only in problem areas. In such cases we say about the local gingivitis or periodontitis local.</p>

<p>In addition, the trigger for the development of the disease often appear overall negative factors for the entire body &ndash; lowered immunity, salivary gland diseases, endocrine diseases and malnutrition. In this case, the pathological process is developing in the area of ​​the teeth and is of a generalized (universal) the nature &ndash; of a generalized gingivitis or periodontitis.</p>

<h2>Periodontitis treatment</h2>

<p>Treatment of periodontal disease in the early stages, as mentioned, has a very good prognosis, so it is very important at the first warning signs, consult a dentist. First of all, you should alert the occurrence of bleeding when brushing your teeth and chewing hard food.</p>

<p>First, try replacing your toothbrush at a softer and more use toothpaste and mouthwash with the addition of healing, restorative and antiseptic natural components. If this does not lead to the desired result, you should immediately seek medical attention &ndash; periodontist, as the bleeding can not be ignored.</p>

<p>In the first phase treatment is limited, as a rule, professional cleaning and removal of plaque and use of folk remedies for periodontal disease &ndash; applications of aloe leaves and rinse with infusions and decoctions of medicinal herbs (chamomile, oak bark, sage, plantain). Traditional medicine with bleeding gums are also advised to rub them with sea salt, honey &ndash; Mix 20 g of honey with 5 &ndash; 10 g salt and rub the teeth and gums every day, not leading to injury.</p>

<p>In addition, the presence of periodontal pockets doctor offers them washing with antiseptic solutions &ndash; a process that helps reduce inflammation and swelling of the gums and reduce bleeding. If the teeth lose their stability, showed a temporary or permanent splinting especially strong ribbons &ndash; first on the tooth surfaces make the groove depth of about 0.5 mm, and then placed her in the tape and cover the filling material.</p>

<p>To gain stability, and widely used surgical techniques, in particular patchwork technique, transplantation of bone and soft tissues and artificial guided bone regeneration. Flap operation applies to the case where the gingival pocket too deep (greater than 5 mm) to reduce its depth. To do this, a small incision is made in the gum area and cleared of stones baring at the root. Then align the affected contour of bone and sutured incision.</p>

<p>Transplantation of soft tissue (taken from the sky) is applied at the tooth roots and bared for cosmetic purposes, and bone transplants (of their own bone or synthetic) used in significant destruction of the bone tissue for retaining the tooth, and for regeneration of new bone tissue.</p>

<h3>Treatment of periodontal disease</h3>

<p>Despite the fact that an effective treatment of periodontal disease is currently no exist as physiotherapy and surgical modern technology to recover gums and relieve itching, pain, hypersensitivity and other unpleasant symptoms.</p>

<p>Physical therapy aimed at improving blood circulation and regeneration processes in the periodontium. These include massage gums darsonvalization, vakuumoterapiya, flyuktuorizatsiya, gingival shower, UHF and magnetic-laser therapy. A good massage for the gums and the best prevention of periodontal disease is the chewing of solid plant foods. Abuse of soft refining food leads to exhaustion and bone atrophy, and with regular chewing solid foods, especially raw vegetables and fruit, on the contrary, there is a training vessel gums and natural cleansing of plaque.</p>

<p>Of the surgical treatment of periodontal disease using surgery to remove the periodontal pockets, removal of microabscesses and festering gums, bone grafting, removal of infected overgrown soft tissue closure of exposed roots, raised descended gums. One promising area of ​​treatment of periodontal disease is the use of cellular technologies to stimulate the recovery of their own bone. Similar operations are underway in Moscow.</p>

<h2>Prevention of periodontal disease</h2>

<p>For the prevention of periodontal disease should be serious about the state of their teeth:</p>

<ul>
<li>1 at least once a year to visit the dentist for a professional oral hygiene;</li>
<li>Brushing teeth 2 times a day, and possibly after every meal;</li>
<li>Remove it after eating the remains of the interdental spaces with dental floss;</li>
<li>To choose a toothbrush with rounded and not too coarse bristles;</li>
<li>Eat right. For periodontal health in the menu should be physiologically required amount of protein, carbohydrates, fats, vitamins and trace elements. Do not abuse the sweets and eat more fresh organic fruits and vegetables.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colon cleansing with salt water]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/colon-cleansing-with-salt-water/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-28T23:09:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/colon-cleansing-with-salt-water</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/colon-cleansing-salt-water/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Colon cleansing salt water, salt water purification intestine" alt="Colon Cleansing with salt water"> Clear the bowel salt water heals the whole body. Use a regular intestinal cleansing of toxins, toxins and poisons produced because of malnutrition, bad environment and stress, has long been no one in doubt because &ldquo;dirty gut&rdquo; is a favorable environment for the growth of pathogenic spoilage bacteria, which are gradually.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>As a result, in the body there is a lot of issues:</p>

<ul>
<li>There is a deficiency of vitamins and minerals that are synthesized by the beneficial bacteria;</li>
<li>Poisons are absorbed through unprotected rectal wall and the liver, which leads to disruption of the structure and the formation of gall stones in the gallbladder;</li>
<li>Suffers excretory system, causing the skin appears abrasions, acne, inflammation and signs of early aging;</li>
<li>Toxins negative effect on the blood vessels, causing them to spasm, increased blood pressure (hypertension symptoms) and the development of heart attacks and strokes;</li>
<li>Toxins and poisons can be absorbed from the intercellular space in the cell itself, destroying it at the genetic level, and contributing to malignant degeneration.</li>
</ul>


<p>The main features of slagging intestine when it is time to take action &ndash; drowsiness, headache, lethargy, furred tongue plaque, bad breath, heaviness in the abdomen, rumbling and bloating, skin rash, constipation, inflammation of the mucous membranes in the mouth, plaque on teeth  As a rule, people are not too young or not quite leading a healthy lifestyle, there is always more of the signs.</p>

<p>For regular colon cleansing should be a priority for every person who wants to maintain their health and protect against disease.</p>

<h2>Clear the bowel salt water</h2>

<p>The most effective and complete way of cleansing the body is to clean the intestines with salt water, used in the exercises of yoga for centuries. This unique technique is called Shank-Prakshalanoy and allows you to completely clear the gastro-intestinal tract, which can not in any way other than complete starvation.</p>

<p>All other methods, unfortunately, give the illusion of a complete cleaning, because the traditional enemas, and Colon are valid only in the large department. There are cases where people who thought that they clean the intestines after a colon hydrotherapy sessions, when the Shank-Prakshalany surprised to discover in their stool cherry stones, eaten many months ago.</p>

<p>The fact that the digestive tract towards the stomach to the anus extends a large number of food and sphincter valve which is opened and closed, helping to promote it. Methods Shank-Prakshalany except bowel cleansing with salt water, including performing specific exercises that relax the muscles of the valves. Because of this salty water flows freely into the rectum and acts like a lubricant there, softening the stool and freeing it from the traffic jams.</p>

<h2>Contraindications and frequency of execution</h2>

<p>Colon Cleansing salt water by the method of Shank-Prakshalany contraindicated for people with diseases of the stomach ulcer and acute lesions of the digestive tract &ndash; colitis, gastritis, pancreatitis, diarrhea, dysentery, tuberculosis, hemorrhoids and heightened bowel cancer. Also, do not carry it out during menstruation, at elevated temperature or blood pressure, heart attacks, any exacerbation of chronic illnesses and colds, when the body is too weak. Prohibits this method of treatment in pregnancy and immediately after the release of fasting (not earlier than one month).</p>

<p>Carry out the procedure Shank-Prakshalany can be as necessary as a preventive four times a year when the seasons change. For those suffering from chronic constipation, it may be the best means of &ldquo;re-education&rdquo; of the intestine and used in place of enemas &ndash; first two times a week, and then, to the extent of purification, once every two weeks. For best results, it is desirable to clean prepare in advance, that is, relax, moisturize and warm your body. To do this week try to refrain from fatty, fried, spicy and meat dishes every day, take a warm bath every morning and drink fresh juices vegetables &ndash; carrot, apple, beet, cucumber.</p>

<h2>Method bowel cleansing salt water</h2>

<p>Method bowel cleansing salt water is the following &ndash; you need to dissolve 1 tablespoon sea ​​salt in a liter of warm water and drink 1 glass, alternating between drinking a glass of water with the performance of special moves at a fast pace to help relax the sphincter. So it is necessary to repeat 6 times (a glass of water &ndash; exercises) until consumed 6 cups.</p>

<p>Stand with your feet shoulder width apart, arms at the castle over the head with his hands up, breathing free. Slow slopes alternately right and left by 8 times in each direction. These movements open the pylorus, what would the water could get out of it into the duodenum.</p>

<p><strong>Exercise number 2 &ldquo;Circular motion&rdquo;</strong></p>

<p>Pull the right arm forward, press the left chest. Thrusting his right hand, turn right only the upper part of the body. Then the other side. Perform 8 times.</p>

<p>Take the prone position, with emphasis on the elbows, feet shoulder width 40 cm Hold your breath, raise your hands and turn to the right, trying to see his own heel. Return to the starting position and relax. Repeat on the other side. Perform 8 times.</p>

<p><strong>Exercise number 4 &ldquo;Squatting&rdquo;</strong></p>

<p>Squat down so that the distance between the feet was about 30 cm and the heel located on the outside of the thighs, and not under the buttocks. Lower the left knee to the floor, hands on knees. By hand tilt the right foot to the left, tilting the body slightly forward. In this case, try to press down on the right foot stomach. The same is repeated at the left side, 8 times in each direction. This exercise helps to move water into the rectum.</p>

<p>Once the cup 6 is consumed and 6 complexes made should appear urge to defecate. If they are not within 5 mauled again, repeat the full range of motion at first and go to the toilet. If you still do not get emptied, which is unlikely, take a small enema with plain water without salt.</p>

<p>After the first empty again to drink a glass of water, do exercises and go to the bathroom. This cycle must be repeated up until the water comes out clean. The number of repeated treatments depends on individual pollution intestines, but usually requires no more than 10-14 glasses. After the end of the cleansing drink 3 glasses of plain water and pushing the root of the tongue, try to induce vomiting in order to fully clean the stomach and turn off the mechanism of evacuation. If you do not, then within a few hours of time you want to go to the toilet.</p>

<p>Sometimes, after a few glasses of salt water drunk nausea and abdominal fullness, feeling that the water does not pass into the intestine. This indicates that it is not opened the first sphincter. In this case, perform a series of exercises 2-3. Once the nausea will pass, then pass into the stomach and can be opened further to continue the procedure under the scheme.</p>

<p>If you feel that the gas formed in the gut tube and hinders the process of draining, push down on the belly with his hands, make a stand on the blades (birch) and do the set of all four exercises.</p>

<h2>Food and drink after bowel cleansing with salt water</h2>

<p>After the full completion of cleaning rest for half an hour, then be sure to eat, no later than an hour after the last discharge (this is important because you can not keep the stomach empty after salt treatment over an hour). Drink before a meal can not be, despite appeared thirsty, because you support this evacuation, and will continue to go to the toilet.</p>

<p>The first recommended food &ndash; rice cooked in water with butter (about 40 grams), wheat, oats or pasta with grated hard cheese. In the next days you can not consume milk, yogurt, white cheese, fresh vegetables and fruits, acidic foods and alcohol. The bread can be eaten after the second meal, at the end of day return to a normal diet, but meat.</p>

<p>The first bowel movements appear about 24-36 hours after treatment, they are golden-yellow in color and odor, as in infants. The positive effect of cleansing occur at some time in the form of fresh breath, improve the complexion and pure whites of the eyes. In addition, following this procedure, many people get rid of allergies and get excellent absorption of nutrients, resulting in one acquires ideal weight &ndash; thin rid of unhealthy thinness, and those who are overweight, lose weight.</p>

<p>People who intend to seriously address their rehabilitation and purification, may carry Shank-Prakshalanu every month, as it helps to rejuvenate, strengthen immunity, well-being and increased energy?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hemorrhoids - Causes]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoids-causes/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-24T20:14:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoids-causes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/causes-of-hemorrhoids/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Causes of hemorrhoids" alt="Hemorrhoids - Causes, Symptoms, stages and modern methods of treatment"> Modern methods of hemorrhoid treatment eliminates the need for surgery. Hemorrhoids called the veins of the rectum, resulting in the formation hemorrhoids that cause severe pain (especially in the act of defecation), bleed, fall out and cause a lot of people suffering physical and social problems.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Unfortunately, hemorrhoids have traditionally been considered &lsquo;shameful&rsquo; intimate problem and therefore postponed the visit to the doctor, as a rule, to the last, when the disease has already started and is accompanied by a strong unbearable bolyu.Po to the proctologist, about 70% of people experience these or other symptoms</p>

<h2>Causes of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Causes of hemorrhoids are quite diverse &ndash; an impetus to the development of the disease can provide both genetic factors (congenital anomalies of venous walls) and the error in the diet, unhealthy lifestyle, chronic internal diseases and pregnancy.</p>

<p><strong>Among the main causes of the disease doctors are the following:</strong></p>

<p>Long-term sedentary work leads to stagnation of blood in the pelvic organs. Therefore, the risk of disease has traditionally include all workers of &ldquo;sedentary&rdquo; jobs &ndash; drivers, accountants, operators, programmers, and the like</p>

<p>A sedentary lifestyle also contributes to the development of hemorrhoids, as due to lack of physical activity, and there is blood stasis is formed venous insufficiency.</p>

<p>Finding feet long and considerable physical load is not less harmful than hypodynamy as delay provokes blood in the veins and increase the pressure therein, resulting in venous wall gradually loses its elasticity. This process is most susceptible to teachers, dancers, hair stylists, as well as loaders and lifters.</p>

<p>Chronic constipation, according to the doctors, are the most common cause of hemorrhoids. As a result of constipation bowel movement feces inside difficult, it accumulates in the lower parts of it and pinched the vein, thus significantly impairing blood flow. In addition, further increase intra-abdominal pressure attempts suffering severe constipation in the act of defecation.</p>

<p>Alcohol and spicy food. Hot spices contribute to a strong flow of blood to the rectum and irritate the delicate lining of her. Alcohol provokes an excessive expansion of blood vessels and blood stagnation in the formation and inflammation of hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>Different tumors and inflammation in the pelvis often causes the development of hemorrhoids. These include gynecological problems (fibroids, uterine fibroids), inflammation of the prostate, liver cirrhosis, cancer of the rectum, as well as fistulas, ulcers and fissures.</p>

<p>Pregnancy and childbirth. During pregnancy, the growing uterus displaces all the organs of the pelvis up and the rectum, on the contrary, pressed down to the pelvic bone, squeezing blood vessels and helping to expand the veins and the formation of hemorrhoids. In the process of childbirth situation is further aggravated by the strong attempts mothers.</p>

<h2>Internal and external hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Hemorrhoids is divided into inner and outer, depending on where the hemorrhoids are located outside or inside.</p>

<p>When an internal hemorrhoid nodes are located in the lumen of the rectum. Outside the acute stage they are not visible to the eye and are determined only by special equipment. In the initial stage of internal hemorrhoids person usually has no idea of ​​developing the disease, while internal hemorrhoids do not begin to emerge in the act of defecating outside.</p>

<p>For external hemorrhoids nodes are outside around the anus, where they can be easily detected during normal feeling, even in the primary, painless stage. In practice, quite often (about 50% of cases) occurs combined hemorrhoids, which combines features of external and internal types.</p>

<h2>Symptoms and stages of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>The first symptoms of hemorrhoids are usually quite low, so they do not pay too much attention. However, as the disease progresses, all the unpleasant and painful sensations are enhanced.</p>

<p>First, the disease manifests itself only a feeling of heaviness or a sensation of a foreign body in the anus &ndash; this is due to swelling of the internal tissues of the anal canal.</p>

<p>After that arise in the anus itching and burning &ndash; a consequence of increasing the hemorrhoids, which is accompanied by minor blood and mucus secretions and causes irritation of the skin around the anus.</p>

<p>Then there are regular bleeding during discharge (of varying intensity). If at this stage to start emergency treatment hemorrhoids begin to precipitate and severe pain is constant, not only during defecation, but also in a sitting position and walking.</p>

<p>Proctologists distinguish 4 stages of hemorrhoids, depending on how much enlarged nodes, and how developed the degenerative process in the tissues muscle.</p>

<p>The first stage &ndash; increasing hemorrhoids, there is itching, burning, foreign body sensation in the anus, there are slight discharge of blood at the time of discharge. Because these symptoms are not permanent and occur only occasionally, the vast number of patients at this stage of hemorrhoids do not go to the doctor, the disease moves to the next stage.</p>

<p>The second stage &ndash; during bowel movements begin to &ldquo;creep&rdquo; nodules on toilet paper appearing regularly drop of blood. At this stage the nodes themselves are hiding back after bowel movements or a short period of time.</p>

<p>The third step &ndash; dropping nodes patient has to reduce a hand into the rectum to achieve more &ndash; less comfortable state. At this stage, the disease is already advanced, progressive and requires immediate medical attention, as the nodules begin to fall, not only during defecation, but also with any increase in intra-abdominal pressure (coughing, sneezing, lifting weights and even with little physical load).</p>

<p>The fourth stage &ndash; hemorrhoids will not reduce a fall or immediately after the reduction, look like bunch of grapes, very inflamed and painful. At this stage, very frequent bleeding, and pain in the anus is so strong that it is impossible to even touch the toilet paper. Intense frequent bleeding lead to anemia (low hemoglobin in the blood), which further worsens the patient&rsquo;s well-being.</p>

<p>In addition, the constant loss of hemorrhoids anal sphincter tone is reduced, and this may be total or partial incontinence of gas and liquid stool, which is a huge additional psychological problem for patients.</p>

<h2>Hemorrhoid Treatment at present</h2>

<p>Hemorrhoid Treatment in modern conditions completely depends on the stage of the disease &ndash; the sooner you start treatment, the better and faster will be the end result.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, the fourth stage of the disease, and, in some cases, with the third, no surgery do not work, so see your doctor as soon as possible and do not diagnose yourself by yourself. Self-treatment of hemorrhoids is dangerous because its symptoms such as itching, pain, bleeding and mucus, characteristic of many other diseases, including cancer.</p>

<p>According to medical statistics, in Europe, colorectal cancer ranks second among all diseases after lung cancer. This is due primarily to the fact that patients often go to the doctor too late, allowing you to develop many of the pathological processes and letting them start. There are cases where people have their own long-term cure hemorrhoids local Foot and micro enema, and as a result are hospitalized with terminal cancer of the colon.</p>

<p>If a proctologist after a comprehensive survey put you diagnose hemorrhoids, take responsibility for his recommendations, because the time to initiation of treatment will help in most cases, to avoid surgery and cure hemorrhoids without pain and complications. Under current conditions, only 5 -10% of cases of hemorrhoids require surgical intervention, in other successfully conducted minimally invasive non-surgical treatment methods.</p>

<p>In the first stage of hemorrhoids can be successfully treated with folk remedies, flebotropnyh drugs, various ointments, suppositories and preventive measures (special diet, therapeutic exercise, and the normalization of the bowel). If the disease is accompanied by hemorrhoidal bleeding, to eliminate it on the first and second stages of the disease is effective method of sclerotherapy.</p>

<p>After a few treatments of sclerotherapy improved tone of the anal canal, swelling and inflammation subside, the pain disappears. The procedure is as follows &ndash; a hemorrhoid or under the mucous membrane next to him is a special sklerotiruyuschim injection drug. Under the influence of drugs node is compacted, reduced in size and eventually atrophies (waived).</p>

<p>On the second and third stages of the patient may be asked to latekstnoe ligation sites &ndash; the newest popular method of treating hemorrhoids proctology in the world, which is a low-invasive, painless and performed on an outpatient basis. The essence of it is this &ndash; with the help of special devices on the hemorrhoid puts special latekstnoe ring that pinches the leg assembly and blocks blood flow in it. About a week and there is no manipulation of the node is expelled with the faeces.</p>

<p>Even if you have stage four of hemorrhoids, do not despair, modern proctology is not standing still and painful surgery hemorrhoidectomy with long-term disability benefits for a long time in the past. Instead, surgeons have successfully used the latest technology called &ldquo;dezarterizatsiya hemorrhoids through suture ligation.&rdquo; Dezarterizatsiya made, usually under local anesthesia in a day hospital, lasts no more than 30 &ndash; 40 minutes and a few hours after surgery, the patient may be allowed to go home.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The human papilloma virus - diagnosis]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/the-human-papilloma-virus-diagnosis/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-24T20:13:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/the-human-papilloma-virus-diagnosis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/human-papillomavirus-prevention/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Human papillomavirus prevention" alt="The human papilloma virus - diagnosis, treatment and prevention"> Treatment of warts and warts laser can get rid of them forever. The human papilloma virus (HPV), or human papillomavirus, is a very common infectious viral disease that is transmitted from person to person, or sexual contact &ndash; through everyday.</p>

<p>According to medical statistics, it infected more than 50% of the population, especially vulnerable to his people with a weak immune system.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>What is the human papilloma virus</h2>

<p>The human papilloma virus &ndash; is the common name of a large group of viruses that includes more than 100 varieties.  ).</p>

<p>Doctors say that 75% of the adult population are healthy carriers of HPV, as many of his views of children are infected even in children&rsquo;s groups. However, before clinical manifestations, that is, warts, papillomas and warts, comes not always. In addition, the vast majority of infected children and young people (mostly under 25) appeared papillomas and warts go away on their own.</p>

<p>Fact that papilloma &ndash; virus, which does not penetrate deeply into the body and blood, it resides exclusively in the basal layer of the upper skin. Therefore, if an infected person&rsquo;s immune system is strong and powerful, he will banish HPV and HPV go away without treatment. If you have contracted the virus in adulthood and his expulsion did not happen for 1 &ndash; 3 years, you become a chronic carrier of it. In this case, with the papilloma &ndash; virus, most likely, you will have to put up with all my life, since drugs, completely killing it, scientists have not yet invented.</p>

<p>The incubation period of HPV infection usually lasts for several months, but in some cases may be increased up to several years. There are cases when HPV lives in the body for many years, sometimes from birth, not giving themselves known and seen for the first time in old age, under the influence of any adverse factors that triggered the depression of immunity.</p>

<p>Therefore, it is safe to say that, as in case of other viral and fungal infections (herpes, thrush), the appearance of papillomas and warts indicates a decline in immunity and only begins when the body&rsquo;s defenses weakened to such an extent that they are unable to  According to recent reports, even the formation of calluses on his feet through a type of papillomavirus.</p>

<p>Activation of HPV, in which the disease becomes invisible to the clinical stage, contribute to frequent change of sexual partners, urogenital infections (gerpevirus, chlamydia, ureomikoplazmoz, mycoplasmosis), immunodeficiency, hypothermia, severe stress, depression, alcohol abuse and smoking.</p>

<h2>Is it dangerous to papillomavirus</h2>

<p>When asked how dangerous papillomas and warts, doctors answer is that it depends only on the degree of tumorigenicity of the virus. There are viruses nizkoonkogennye (6, 11, 42, 43, 44), medium oncogenicity (31, 33, 35, 51, 52, 58) and a high degree of tumorigenicity (16, 18, 45, 56). Sometimes the same person can have multiple types of viruses at the same time.</p>

<p>Current laboratory methods for diagnosis of HPV, the most informative and sensitive of which is a PCR (polymerase chain reaction), allow to precisely determine the type of virus and its danger, that is, whether it is to oncogenic types.</p>

<p>Different types of virus in the human body often behave differently. It is known that the human papilloma virus type 2 is a non-tumorigenic, affects mainly the skin (skin papilloma virus) and causes warts and moles hanging on different parts of the body. The most frequent HPV in the neck, armpits, eyelids, under the breasts in women, but they can settle down and to the mucous membranes of the nose, throat, mouth, vocal cords, bladder, intestines and stomach.</p>

<p>Viruses 6 and 11 types are characterized by a low risk of carcinogenicity and provoke the development of papillomas of the mucous membranes of the genitals called genital genital warts or genital warts. Women warts often located on the labia, the cervix, the vagina, perineal urethra and anus. In men, they tend to focus on the head and body of the penis, sometimes in the urethra, which provokes a difficulty urinating, spraying urine and change in shape of the jet.</p>

<p>The most unfavorable for carcinogenicity are HPV types 16 and 18, often found in women with cervical cancer and in men with cancer lesions of the penis. Women who have found these types of HPV, for the prevention of cancer process, it is recommended mandatory vaccination.</p>

<h2>Diagnosis and treatment of warts and warts</h2>

<p>Treatment of HPV performed only in cases where there are any clinical manifestations &ndash; HPV or genital warts as well as their appearance indicates the activation of HPV. Completely remove the virus from the body, unfortunately, can not, can only be possible to suppress the activity of the viral infection and translate it into a &ldquo;sleep&rdquo; state, preventing relapse and reoccurrence of tumors.</p>

<p>Treatment of HPV infection consists of two stages &ndash; first performed the complete removal of papillomas (warts), and then held restorative therapy, aimed at strengthening the immune system and preventing relapse (receipt of antiviral drugs, vitamins, immunostimulants).</p>

<p>Now remove warts is carried out in many clinics modern and effective ways &ndash; by using a laser beam of liquid nitrogen (cryotherapy), by electrocoagulation (affecting papilloma electric current of high frequency) and radio waves. The most common methods of laser removal and removal of warts with nitrogen.</p>

<p>Laser removal of warts on the neck, eyelids, under the breasts, face and any other part of the body is made in a few minutes. The advantages of laser destruction include the fact that during the removal of warts laser they disappear forever, as the virus is killed by the heat of the laser beam. After the procedure in place papilloma dry crust is formed, under which there is healing. After 10 &ndash; 14 days it automatically disappears, while the skin is not different in color from the surrounding tissue.</p>

<p>Remove warts with liquid nitrogen is carried out, on the contrary, due to very low temperatures (&ndash; 196 C), with removable fabric from freezing completely destroyed and subsequently falls off, the skin underneath it loses its sensitivity and becomes white. Advantages of this method &ndash; after cryoablation procedure is left scars, does not require anesthesia, the wound heals quickly.</p>

<p>Remove Warts on the genitals or in the perineum, especially when a large area of ​​destruction, large-scale tumors or lesions of the anal canal, often requires general anesthesia. The main condition &ndash; all warts should be removed in a single session, to prevent the possibility of re-infection. After removal of warts patient assigned intramuscular injection analgesics for 5 &ndash; 6 days, and antiviral creams and ointments.</p>

<h2>Prevention of HPV infection</h2>

<p>In recent years, many people, especially young people, a very lightly to infections, sexually transmitted, trusting, if necessary, by means of powerful antibiotics. However, it is a dangerous delusion, because the viruses, including human papillomavirus, is not amenable to antibiotics. In addition, they are very unpredictable and difficult to establish.</p>

<p>By the cunning of HPV include the fact that the use of condoms during sex is not sufficiently reliable means of protection against papilloma infection, as well as from genital herpes because the ground is enough to infect the skin and mucous membranes. Therefore, prevention of HPV is becoming of major importance, especially for women.</p>

<p>If men, for the most part, after the infection are asymptomatic carriers of most types of HPV, the infection for women can have much more serious consequences &ndash; in 95% of women with cervical cancer and HPV diagnosed. That is why every woman should at least 1 time per year to visit the gynecologist and take a swab from the cervix to detect changes in the state of epithelial cells in the early stages.</p>

<p>This test, called «pap-smear» (PAP test), according to doctors, will significantly reduce the morbidity and mortality of women from cervical cancer in developed countries. In addition, infected women should do regular cervical colposcopy (examination of the state of the mucous membranes and tissues under a microscope), and if necessary, cytology suspicious areas.</p>

<p>According to the scientists, all of which appeared Hanging moles, warts and other growths should be removed prophylactically, without waiting for their rebirth in the disease. For example, if time does not make the removal of genital warts, they are self-propagating away from the area of ​​primary education, and to create all the new centers. In severe cases, the warts may coalesce with each other, getting kind of cauliflower, break away during intercourse, bleeding and even interfere with walking.</p>

<p>Since papilloma virus infection tends to recur after removal of tumors is necessary to carry out the mandatory control of cure and implement a set of measures that increase the activity of immune system and overall resistance to viruses and infections. To do this, you need to give up bad habits (smoking, alcohol), do not use without urgent need antibiotics, eat healthy, exercise regularly, walking in the fresh air and possibly to protect themselves from the stress.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-cellulite massage at home - cups]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/anti-cellulite-massage-at-home-cups/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-24T20:11:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/anti-cellulite-massage-at-home-cups</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/cellulite-massage-at-home/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Anti-cellulite massage at home" alt="Anti-cellulite massage at home - cups, honey, brush"> Anti-cellulite massage at home helps to keep the skin in pristine condition. Anti-cellulite massage at home is the most affordable and effective means of dealing with cellulite. Because it can significantly improve the condition of the &ldquo;problem&rdquo; areas, increase circulation of blood and lymph in the subcutaneous fat layer and accelerate the elimination of toxins, toxins and metabolic products from the intercellular space.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>The principles and techniques of anti-cellulite self-massage</h2>

<p>The basic principles of anti-cellulite self-massage is quite simple &ndash; having mastered them, you can always maintain your skin in perfect condition, without resorting to expensive beauty salons.</p>

<p>Cellulite self-massage should be carried out energetic, but lightly. Common misconception of many women is that, ostensibly, to use as much physical strength. If you overdo and you will be too hard to knead and squeeze the skin, you will make a reverse effect &ndash; the deterioration of the situation and the weakening of lymph flow. There are cases where the use of unnecessary force due to the effect of cellulite noticeably intensified.</p>

<p>To avoid compromising the lymph flow is prohibited to massage in the groin, thigh dimples, inner upper thighs and the area around the pubic area.</p>

<p>The massage should be required from the bottom up.</p>

<p>For best results, before a session of self-massage, heat the good body with exercise or a warm shower. Hands should also not be cold &ndash; warm them by rubbing your palms against each other.</p>

<p>In order to achieve rapid results cellulite self-massage is desirable to carry out daily, ideally twice a day &ndash; morning and evening for 15-30 minutes. The first tangible results in the fight against cellulite, with due diligence, typically appear after 1-2 months.</p>

<h2>Key anti-cellulite self-massage techniques of hand</h2>

<p>In the exercise of self-massage hand-applied 3 main reception &ndash; rubbing, squeezing and pat.</p>

<p>Grinding &ndash; is carried out in a circular motion (clockwise) of the entire surface of the palm. In the thighs rubbing should be done in a circular motion, and on his feet &ndash; from the bottom up.</p>

<p>Pressing &ndash; at this reception to grab with both hands as much as possible the skin and knead &ldquo;the dough&rdquo;, while avoiding compression of the skin. Pushing effectively improves the tone flabby muscles.</p>

<p>Pat &ndash; the most effective massage techniques, carried out or the whole hand, or knuckles, clenched in a fist. In this case, applied a series of rhythmic strokes of varying intensity. Pat can be done to rhythmic music, producing them in time.</p>

<p>The most popular win these types of anti-cellulite massage as domestic cups, honey, and self-massage with a brush.</p>

<h2>Brush-cellulite massage</h2>

<p>Cellulite massage brush, according to the beauticians, the best way to recover at home blood and lymph circulation. It is held by a special massage brush with a handle, which can be purchased in a pharmacy or a department funds for the care of the body.</p>

<p>The skin must be dry, without the use of oils and creams, not to injure the skin. Brush technique of self-massage is circular motions (clockwise) for each zone massaged enough for about 40 &ndash; 60 movements. Movements should be moderate, but the skin at the same time should get red in the face considerably. The feeling of warmth and redness typically lasts for an hour.</p>

<p>When selecting the brush, give preference to natural thick stubble. If the brush is new and with the rough nap before applying pour over it several times with boiling water and mash the pile to make it less prickly. Remember that after the massage you should not have any bruises, scratches and tingling.</p>

<p>Beginning self-massage brush, divide it into zones necessarily rising from the bottom up. The best option &ndash; consistently handle first calf, then the hips and buttocks. The standard course of treatments &ndash; 30 &ndash; 40 daily sessions. Never use a hand-held anti-cellulite massage for skin diseases, varicose and heart disease.</p>

<p>Once a week, instead of the brush is useful self-massage to treat the cellulite areas of sea salt and freshly ground coffee. To do this, take a warm-up shower and rub in a circular motion with salt coffee or problem areas. After the procedure, put on body cellulite cream.</p>

<h2>Cupping cellulite massage</h2>

<p>Antitsellyuitny Cupping massage, thanks to the action of vacuum, well softens thick subcutaneous fat, so it is very effective for the correction of the beautiful contours of the body. In addition, it is quite effective in the fight against stretch marks (striae), and reduces swelling problem areas.</p>

<p>For the canned anti-cellulite massage using special soft cans sold in pharmacies. Just click on the jar, attach to the body and release it &ndash; work the principle of suction cups, and it would be easy to drive on the skin.</p>

<p>To Bank slid easily through the body, the skin is oiled with anti-effect. These oils can be purchased at a pharmacy or make your own. The basis of a 50 ml linseed oil or olive oil and added to it the choice of essential oils. Here are a few options for adding essential oils to the base:</p>

<p>5 ml of essential oils of orange, grapefruit and anise;
2 ml of oil red pepper and 5 ml of tea tree oil;
5 ml of essential oil of tangerine, lemon and dill;
3 ml of essential oils of fennel, juniper, lemon, cypress and tea tree;
3 ml of essential oils of lemon, mandarin, cypress, and 5 ml of vetiver oil.</p>

<p>Before canned massage, take a warm shower or do gymnastics, so that the body and the muscles are warmed up. Then apply the skin oil, and rub hands well &ndash; you need to slide the bank only on the body, not in your hand.</p>

<p>Bank needs to keep pressing her fingers on the sides and ensure that the skin is pulled into no more than 1.5 centimeters. If you overdo it, and the pressure in the bank would be excessive, move it through the body becomes hard. After the first few sessions may be small bruises, that&rsquo;s fine, as long as the body is not used to the procedures. If the bruises keep appearing and then, then chances are you are doing something wrong.</p>

<p>In addition, you can massage do not have to experience the pain and discomfort. If you experience any pain, do not have to endure &ndash; loosen the grip banks as cellulite affected areas should not be exposed to excessive squeezing.</p>

<p>Move the bank should be very smooth and continuous, circular movements should be directed strictly clockwise. Finish with every massage movement toward the venous outflow, with the tightness of its banks to rearrange and only then continue the session.</p>

<p>In order for the body to gradually got used to the loads, increases gradually during procedures &ndash; ranging from 2-3 minutes, increasing to 5 &ndash; 15 minutes for each problem area. Cup massage is a potent tool, so it is recommended not to do it more often than once every 2 &ndash; 3 days, standard course usually consists of 10-12 procedures. After a full course must be sure to take a break of 10-15 days, and only then, if desired, repeat.</p>

<p>Wonderful effect is a combination of canned massage with brush and antitsellyuitnymi wraps (acetic, mud, using algae and others). Procedures for self-massage brush and cans perfectly complement each other, as frolement well with the brush massage strengthens the capillaries and blood vessels, and the impact of self-massage cupping-glass vacuum at adjusts the flow of blood and lymph tissue.</p>

<p>As can massage should be done once every 2 to 3 days, and brushing every day, in the days when both procedures are coming, try to separate them in time to survive the interval between 4 &ndash; 6 hours, but not later than 20.00.</p>

<p>Contraindication to the cupping-glass vacuum cellulite massage is an inflammatory disease of the skin, malignant and benign tumors, large birthmarks in the area of ​​massaging, tuberculosis, poor blood clotting, thrombosis, thrombophlebitis and varicose veins in the area of ​​massaging.</p>

<h2>Honey cellulite massage</h2>

<p>Honey-cellulite massage &ndash; a unique and extremely effective way to fight cellulite, known since ancient Tibet. The content in honey is almost half of the periodic table provides power not only the skin but also the muscles, many internal organs and tissues. In addition, the unique effect of honey on your skin and the entire body is that it absorbs into itself all the toxins and wastes, literally sucking them through the pores of the skin.</p>

<p>For the massage, you can use only 100% pure honey, free of impurities and not exposed to significant heat treatment. It is advisable to buy it, or at a friend&rsquo;s beekeepers, or from a very trusted brands that exclude the possibility of forgery. Candied honey is not heated directly, or in the microwave, allowed only warm (not hot) water bath.</p>

<p>Before the honey massage is recommended to warm up the skin slightly, spending for 3 &ndash; 5 minutes of easy kneading. Then the honey slowly rubbed into the skin of a heated until it begins to thicken, making the massage movements impossible. After this tactic is changing &ndash; at first hand in turn tightly close to the body, and then pull up sharply. Such otlepleniya continue as long as the skin turns red, and honey does not darken and should not go gray flakes. This typically requires from 8 to 15 minutes.</p>

<p>Formed from the remnants of honey flakes removed using a hot compress and move to the massing of the other parts of the body. After the completion of the massage to shower thoroughly, since the waste honey, absorbed harmful substances are extremely toxic. After you cross the bridge, apply a moisturizer to the skin.</p>

<p>As you can see, honey massage technique is fairly simple, but, unfortunately, very painful. And, if you were not hurt, then massage simply failed. Helpful Hint &ndash; with the massaged areas necessary first remove hairs that massage does not become a real torture.</p>

<p>In the first session, if you can not endure the pain, not allowed to conduct massaging his palm and fingertips, until the skin becomes less sensitive. Moreover, during the initial procedures otleplenie hands can carry out more gently subsequently making them more sharp. No additional slaps and pressure on the skin to produce not need.</p>

<p>The most effective is a course of anti-cellulite massage honey from 12 &ndash; 15 procedures in a day. It is contraindicated only for allergies to honey and weak, located close to the skin surface vessels.</p>

<p>Since cellulite is a problem that the years do not pay attention to solving it is necessary to approach the complex &ndash; than the recommended massage techniques, it is necessary to eliminate the causes of cellulite, give up bad habits, as well as to normalize their diet and lifestyle.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cleaning vessels folk remedies]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/cleaning-vessels-folk-remedies/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-22T23:19:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/cleaning-vessels-folk-remedies</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/cleaning-vessels-folk-remedies/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Cleaning vessels folk remedies, cleaning vessels from cholesterol" alt="After cleaning the vessels are headaches and pressure"> Cleaning of vessels and keeping them in good condition is the key to health and longevity, because healthy blood vessels &ndash; is a guarantee of the normal state of circulatory and cardiovascular system and the prevention of atherosclerosis, hypertension, heart attacks and strokes.</p>

<p>As you know, with age wear vessels &ndash; they gradually thicken, lose their elasticity and become brittle, and their walls are jagged and rough.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>They eventually deposited layer of salt, fat lime, cholesterol, preventing blood flow and form plaques.</p>

<p>Intrigue atherosclerosis is that at first it goes unnoticed and does not provide any clinical symptoms, so such terrible its complications such as heart attack or stroke may suddenly strike is considered quite healthy person. Only by narrowing the blood vessels of more than 50% of the characteristic symptoms begin to appear atherosclerotic lesions.</p>

<p>Here are the main features of the &ldquo;bad&rdquo; blood vessels, which is necessary to pay close attention to and which indicate the need to do their cleaning and consolidation:</p>

<p>If it affects the blood vessels of the brain &ndash; the deterioration of memory and concentration, headaches, dizziness, decreased vision and hearing, loss of performance.</p>

<p>If it affects the blood vessels of the heart &ndash; shortness of breath, angina.</p>

<p>Atherosclerosis extremities &ndash; cramps in the legs, chill the extremities, muscle pain when walking, skin blanching legs.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it possible to remove moles?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/is-it-possible-to-remove-moles/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-22T23:17:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/is-it-possible-to-remove-moles</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/remove-moles/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Is it possible to remove moles" alt="What is the mole, and whether they can be removed"> A large number of moles &ndash; a sign of longevity. Moles or nevi are medically, have each person and are small, light brown spots are usually no more than the size of a pea.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>The cause of birthmarks</h2>

<p>Most often, they are located on the body, at least on the mucous membranes of the eye or retina. A child is born without a birthmark, nevus first begin to appear at the age of 1-2 years, with the first tan, and usually unobtrusive and small in number. The most active moles appear at puberty and during pregnancy, aided hormonal changes the body.</p>

<p>The cause of birthmarks is not fully understood, but the emergence of new nevi always mean that at this point in the top layer of skin has accumulated melanin &ndash; the pigment that gives the skin a dark color.</p>

<p>One of the reasons for the appearance of moles, especially the large number of them, scientists believe a long exposure to the sun, most often nevi appear on exposed skin &ndash; face, shoulders and arms. They are more prone to the appearance of people with blue eyes and red hair, white skin and freckles, and the important role of genetic factors.</p>

<p>Despite the fact that nevi are benign tumors, they must be treated very carefully, in any case, do not hurt and do not burn home remedies in case of accidental damage. The fact that nevi, unfortunately, can sometimes degenerate into malignant melanoma &ndash; the most common form of skin cancer. Therefore, any change in a mole, whether it is color, size, tenderness or bleeding, should alert you and ask advice from a dermatologist.</p>

<p>Despite the fact that the owners of a large number of nevi are more at risk of getting melanoma of the skin, for which there is good news &ndash; the researchers found that such people have a much slower the biological aging of cells. A slower aging, as well known, is a sign of longevity and reduces the severity of various age-related diseases such as osteoporosis, cardiovascular diseases and many other.</p>

<h2>Is it possible to remove moles</h2>

<p>On the question of whether to remove moles, physicians respond positively, if necessary, for example in traumatic injuries or qualitative changes nevus.  Especially susceptible to this birthmark, located on the palms, soles, scalp and neck, as well as those who are touched constantly clothes and accessories, injured when shaving and brushing. Any injury &ndash; is an occasion to visit a specialist to check the nature of the emerging changes.</p>

<p>Special attention pay attention to the size, color and shape of moles. If they do not grow or shrink in size, so are inactive and are not dangerous. If some of them are starting to grow strongly, rises above the level of the skin becomes uneven color (random mix of black, brown, gray and pink), has wrong jagged edges, cracks or asymmetric, then you need to seek immediate medical attention if necessary.</p>

<p>The main causes of malignant transformation of nevi doctors call trauma and exposure to the sun. With the very people with fair skin and a large number of moles (more than 50), especially if they include large (6 mm in diameter), it is necessary to limit the residence time in the open sun. They are not in any way be &ldquo;burn&rdquo; in the sun, because the sun burns occur during the development of malignant melanoma.</p>

<p>Is strictly forbidden to seal the birthmark before going in the sun, because the greenhouse effect may also contribute to its rebirth. Best of all these people in the shadows, as even sun creams are not able to fully protect nevi from harmful UV rays. To prevent dehydration of the skin and body, you need to drink every day for at least two liters of plain water.</p>

<p>Do not remove moles in beauty salons and at home grandmother&rsquo;s recipes. Modern medicine has at its disposal a reliable and safe methods of removal of nevi &ndash; a laser, microwave, and elektroizlucheniya using liquid nitrogen. Only careful and respect for one&rsquo;s skin can protect you from any serious problems.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Therapeutic exercise for patients with diabetes]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/therapeutic-exercise-for-patients-with-diabetes/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:49:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/therapeutic-exercise-for-patients-with-diabetes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/exercise-therapy-for-patients-with-diabetes/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Exercise therapy for patients with diabetes" alt="Therapeutic exercise for patients with diabetes"> Exercise therapy for patients with diabetes helps to offset the disease. Exercise therapy (physical therapy) for patients with diabetes, along with other essential elements of treatment (insulin therapy, medication drugs, diet and self-control), plays a critical role in the compensation of the disease and has a beneficial effect on the patient, helping to maintain good health and performance.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>The role of physical therapy for patients with diabetes</h2>

<p>The violation of protein and fat metabolism in the body accumulates toxins and it is poisoning products of incomplete combustion of fats. In addition, disturbance of lipid metabolism leads to the fact that blood fat filled, it increases bad cholesterol, thereby repeatedly increased risk of atherosclerosis and other cardiovascular diseases.</p>

<p>Exercise therapy is shown not only in all types of diabetes (except for depleted due to untreated or poorly the treatment of diabetes patients), but also when prediabetnom condition. Modern research shows that, if we strictly adhere to the prescribed diet, exercise and give up bad habits &ndash; overeating, smoking and alcohol, then go into pre-diabetes mellitus can be avoided.</p>

<p>According to currently available data, the most common occurrence and development of diabetes contributes to overeating. That is why a person full-bodied and with disturbances in metabolism, need to understand that once in a painful exchange process will involve carbohydrate metabolism, inevitably develop diabetes.</p>

<p>In connection with this, people with excess body weight, being at risk of diabetes, must periodically tested for the presence of sugar in the blood and urine, to detect the first time the symptoms of the disease and to begin treatment. In addition to weight loss, you should pay attention to the following common symptoms of incipient diabetes &ndash; long nezazhivlenie wounds, abrasions resistant to treatment, itching, bleeding gums, loosening of teeth, impotence.</p>

<h2>Features of physical therapy for patients with diabetes</h2>

<p>The main objectives of physical therapy for patients with diabetes:</p>

<p>Improving cardiovascular and respiratory systems;
Improving patients&#8217; health;
Reducing hyperglycaemia in non-insulin (type 2 diabetes) and the potentiation of insulin in patients with insulin-dependent (type 1 diabetes);
Opposition to the development of micro-and macrovascular.</p>

<p>In diabetes, insulin deficiency addition, broken oxidative processes in the muscle due to which they can not utilize glucose. At the same physical stress oxidative enzyme activity is significantly enhanced in the blood are increased alkaline reserves, thereby increasing the uptake and consumption of glucose by muscles, decreases hyperglycemia and increased tolerance of the organism in carbohydrates. In addition, exercise in combination with insulin increase the therapeutic effect of insulin, strengthen the nervous and cardiovascular system of the patient, increase the body&rsquo;s resistance and prevent the development of atherosclerosis.</p>

<p>The distinctive feature of LFC in diabetes is that the recommended exercises should be performed in a moderate (Slower) rate, as well as muscular effort. In the anaerobic organism not occur and oxidation processes that contribute to the increase of glucose by muscles.</p>

<p>Classes begin physiotherapy is recommended to elementary exercises for the muscles of the legs, arms and torso with no encumbrances, combining with breathing exercises.  In addition to physical therapy, are useful dosed walking, rowing, cycling, swimming pool, skiing, gardening, light physical work.</p>

<p>When doing physical therapy you need to carefully monitor their well-being &ndash; if after playing the feeling of weakness or fatigue, the load must be reduced. If training were to shake hands, there was a strong feeling of hunger and weakness, you need to eat 1 to 2 pieces of sugar and immediately stop training. Resuming workout just a day after the disappearance of the symptoms of hypoglycemia, while reducing the dosage. Patients with diabetes who are on insulin therapy, in the days of long and intense physical activities recommended to reduce the dose of insulin (after consultation with the attending physician).</p>

<p>LFC need to conduct studies in a well-ventilated room or outdoors, breathing in this case should be free and rhythmic, through your nose and exhale longer inspiratory time. Physical exercise is necessary to alternate the different muscle groups and perform with a large amplitude in the joints.</p>

<p>Repeat each exercise should be 5-6 times in the future, to the extent of fitness, you can enhance the load by reducing breaks, increasing the rate and number of repetitions. Age is not a barrier to practice physical therapy, monitoring the patient&rsquo;s state of health is the only changes and hyperglycemia and weight.</p>

<p>Since the blood sugar level rises patient after a night&rsquo;s sleep, (which partly explains quiet sleep) are most useful gymnastics, and light walking exercise in the morning, as they not only lower blood glucose, but also promote the release of insulin in a more  But, if possible, try to exercise and in the evening (for 1.5 &ndash; 2 hours before bedtime) to secure an equivalent exercise for the day.</p>

<h2>Complex physiotherapy for patients with diabetes</h2>

<p>Starting position &ndash; the main counter. Set aside the leg back, put your hands up &ndash; inhale, return to the initial position &ndash; Exhale. Repeat 4-5 times.</p>

<p>Within 2-4 minutes walk alternately with high lifting hips, with the movements of the arms up and to the side, with the attacks. Breathe freely.</p>

<p>Stand up straight, hands behind head, elbows pinch the face. On the 1-2 dissolve in hand, inhale. On the 3-4 return to the starting position, tilt your head forward, exhale.</p>

<p>Feet shoulder width apart. Spread your arms out to the side, turn the body all the way to the left, the right hand should be in front of the chest. Then turn to the full right (left arm in front of chest, right assigned to the side). Lean forward to the left leg, pulling the sock right hand. Repeat on the other hand.</p>

<p>Starting position &ndash; arms out, legs apart. Make 3 springy lean to the left (right leg bent, left arm behind his back, right arm is raised up).</p>

<p>Mahi legs, pulling his hands in front summarized hands.</p>

<p>Starting position &ndash; the main counter. Lean forward, trying to get his hands floor without bending your legs. Then fall to focus on her knees, feet alternately move back please stop lying. Without bending your arms and legs and moving them from place, lift the hips higher by tilting forward, lower your head between hands. Lower the pelvis, taking the emphasis lying. Then alternate movement of the feet take forward the emphasis on his knees, lift your pelvis up, straighten your legs and arms.</p>

<p>Emphasis sitting, fingers pull back. Cave in to stop lying behind. Without moving your heels and hands with room, sit down to the heels of the bent leg, then without removing your hands from the floor, straighten your legs and put them apart. Connect and bend your legs and then straighten (without moving from the place of the heel), and return to starting position. Repeat 6-8 times.</p>

<p>Lie on your back, bend your arms at chest (forearms parallel to the one above the other). Lift them up, without straightening and does not disconnect (inhalation) and lower into place (exhale).</p>

<p>Lie on your stomach, hands under shoulders. Arms out to the sides (palms down on the floor), bend your back, and then straighten them and cave in, off the floor straight legs and hands, his head laid back. Hold this position for a few seconds, re-dissolve and bring feet back to its original position.</p>

<p>Lie on your back, raise your legs vertically. At the 1 &ndash; 2 dilute and bring your feet on the 3-4 bend and straighten. Repeat 4-6 times, not holding my breath.</p>

<p>Starting position &ndash; the main counter. Lift your arms to the shoulders (inspiration), and then relaxed &ldquo;drop&rdquo; them, head down, shoulders rounded off with.</p>

<p>Perform a peaceful walk for 2 minutes.</p>

<p>At the end of lessons useful to take a cool shower, bath or sponging, as well as water treatment activate the oxidative processes in the body. Start to cool off with a towel soaked in water at room temperature (not below), gradually lowering the temperature of water by one degree in a few days. Motion for a rubdown should be directed from the periphery to the heart.</p>

<p>Despite the fact that diabetes is a life-long illness, with good self-control and respect for all the doctor&rsquo;s appointments, diabetics can keep working and socially useful life on a par with healthy and live to a ripe old age.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Therapeutic exercises in spinal osteochondrosis]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/therapeutic-exercises-in-spinal-osteochondrosis/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:48:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/therapeutic-exercises-in-spinal-osteochondrosis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/physical-therapy-in-spinal-osteochondrosis/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Physical therapy in spinal osteochondrosis" alt="Therapeutic exercises in spinal osteochondrosis"> Physical therapy reduces stress on the joints and helps the deposition of salts. Many people who have the first symptoms of joint disease &ndash; the crunch and clicks, believe that they have a &ldquo;simple&rdquo; salt deposits &ndash; a trifle, which is observed in almost all and therefore do not require treatment. However, the deposition of salt, as it is popularly called low back pain, the disease is not as harmless as it may seem at first glance.</p>

<p>The fact that the starting salt deposited only at inappropriate salt metabolism in the body. A healthy body can absorb salts only as much as is necessary for normal functioning, and the excess output.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>If you violate a salt exchange surpluses are deposited in various parts of the body, causing certain diseases, often low back pain, gout, kidney stones and gall stones.</p>

<p>For osteochondrosis deferrable salt are often formed in sharp spikes that compress the nerves and cause severe pain with movement, causing a person is suffering, can not turn his head, torso, and the robot has to move, protecting yourself from the pain. In addition, osteochondrosis of the cervical spine may be accompanied by severe headaches, and in the period of acute lumbar degenerative disc disease and sciatica people and is completely bedridden.</p>

<p>Due to the fact that the joints begin to undergo similar changes already 20 years old, everyone should regularly engage in the prevention of salt deposits, which includes the cleaning of joints, proper diet (read the article diet for gout, osteochondrosis and salt deposits in the joints), and clear the joints folk remedies, such as using rice or bay leaf, carried out in order to prevent a year and gives a good effect. Therapeutic diet should be organized to remove excess weight, which is an additional burden on joints and provide the body with all the necessary vitamins and trace elements, especially calcium for strong bones and cartilage.</p>

<h2>Physical therapy in spinal osteochondrosis</h2>

<p>Gymnastics spinal osteochondrosis plays a major role, as well strengthens and tones the muscles of the back. With weak muscles of the body burden is &ldquo;hanging&rdquo; on one spine, flattening and deforming discs. If the muscles of the back and loins are well fortified, as they would create an additional corset and take on the weight of the body.</p>

<p>In addition, therapeutic exercises in spinal osteochondrosis helps get rid of extra salt, because if you exercise the bone and muscle tissue using them to compensate for the physiological loss. Finally, regular active movements, with which physiotherapy is the deposition of salts, gradually, as it were &ldquo;polished&rdquo; salt spikes, making them less sharp and painful.</p>

<p>Physical therapy will be effective only if it is done regularly, every day for 10-15 minutes. The following is a universal set of exercises that will suit everyone. We need to start small, gradually complicating every move &ndash; increasing the number of repetitions, strength and amplitude of slopes and turns. To enhance the effect of the exercises you can use a stick, holding her elbows behind his back. The first four are preparatory exercises complex and prepare the cardiovascular system to the load, and four of the latter, on the contrary, contribute to bringing the body to a calm state after a workout.</p>

<h2>Versatile set of exercises with osteochondrosis</h2>

<h3>Preparatory exercises</h3>

<p>Raise your hands, stretch up (breath), and then lower down, returning to the starting position (exhale).</p>

<p>Grasp the support and rise from heel to toe.</p>

<p>Stand with your feet shoulder width apart, hands on his belt. Move the arms back, reducing the maximum blade (inhalation). Bring elbows to the first starting position and then forward as far as you can (exhale).</p>

<p>Tread on the spot, raising his knees.</p>

<p>Stand erect with your feet shoulder width apart. The maximum stretch up, raising his hands (breath), then lean forward (exhale).</p>

<h3>Arms down at your sides</h3>

<p>Stand erect. Turn around in different directions, arms relaxed at the same time and how would overwhelm the body.</p>

<p>Circular rotation to the right and left lower part of the body.</p>

<p>The circular rotation of hands alternately in different directions.</p>

<p>Stand erect, hands on waist, feet shoulder width apart. Take your right hand back, looking at her (inspiration), go back (exhalation). Similarly, perform the other hand.</p>

<p>Standing upright or sitting in a chair doing Reclining head turns to the right, left, back and forth, then a circular motion.</p>

<p>Sit on a chair and slowly slide your feet on the floor back and forth alternately.</p>

<p>Stand up straight, stretch up with your hands (inhalation), scroll down (exhale).</p>

<p>By the universal set of exercises with osteochondrosis can be added to the selection of specific additional exercises for the cervical, thoracic or lumbar spine, as well as for large joints most affected by the deposition of salts &ndash; shoulder, hip, and knee.</p>

<h3>Exercises for the cervical spine</h3>

<p>Starting position &ndash; lying on his stomach, head turned to the side. Lift up on the hands, throwing his head back (inspiration), go back (exhale).</p>

<p>Tilt your head back, touching the back. Draw your shoulders vertically.</p>

<p>Tilt your head forward and touching his chest, chin slide up and down, simulating the movement of birds to clean the feathers.</p>

<h3>Exercises to help relieve the chest department</h3>

<p>Sit in a chair, hands behind his head rewound (inhalation), cave as possible back, shoulders touching the chair back (exhale).</p>

<p>Get on all fours, cave in the back, keep your head straight, stay in this position for a few seconds, then return to starting position.</p>

<p>Exercise &ldquo;Boat&rdquo;. Lie on your stomach, arms along the body. Cave in &ldquo;boat&rdquo;, taking his head and legs as high as possible off the floor.</p>

<h3>Exercise for the lumbar spine</h3>

<p>Lie on your back, press down bent knees as close to your chest.</p>

<p>Lying on his stomach, rest on the floor bent arms. Straightening your arms, push-ups on the floor, keeping the legs.</p>

<p>Get on your knees, resting his hands on the floor straight. Maximum Flex the back up, then return to starting position.</p>

<p>Stand with your feet shoulder width apart. Lean down, trying to get the floor with his hands. Then stand up straight, raise your arms above your head cave in and make the most.</p>

<p>Exercise &ldquo;cat&rdquo; perfectly relieves tension from the back. Get on all fours, leaning on his knees and hands. Arms and back should be straight, do not tilt your head, look forward. Tilt your head back down and forecasting arc up like a cat, stay in this position for 10 seconds, then go back and relax.</p>

<p>It is also useful to hang out at every opportunity on the bar for 1-2 minutes.</p>

<h3>Exercises for the shoulder joints</h3>

<p>Sit on a chair, put his hands on his belt and spread to the sides. Slowly lift your shoulders up to the stop and gently lowered down slightly pulling down.</p>

<p>Sit on a chair, a push to the back, hands on his waist, elbows divorced. Follow the movement of the shoulders gently back and forth.</p>

<p>In the same starting position alternately follow the circular movement of the shoulders.</p>

<p>Sit on a chair and slide as far back as the patient&rsquo;s hand, healthy, grabbed her wrist and pull toward your buttocks until the pain. Stay in this position for 10 seconds and strain the patient&rsquo;s hand. Then relax and try to move it a few more inches to the onset of pain. Repeat 3-5 times.</p>

<p>Get a hands behind his back and locked in a castle. Then pull in different directions, as if trying to break the lock. Alternately, drag them to the right and to the left, not disengaging.</p>

<p>Stand erect, flattened behind the castle as his hands slowly allot up and back, trying to take as much as possible, but without sharp pain. In this case, the patient remains passive hand.</p>

<h3>Exercises for the hip joints</h3>

<p>Lie on your side with your right leg at the knee and remove the floor in front of him. Then do the same with the other hand.</p>

<p>Lie on your stomach. Bend your right leg, pull it to the side and push the knee to the floor, as if crawling &ldquo;on their bellies.&rdquo; Then do the same with the left hand.</p>

<p>Lying on his stomach, focusing on the bent arm. Then straighten your arms and sit on your heels.</p>

<p>Sit on the floor cross-legged with his legs crossed. Swing your body back and forth.</p>

<h3>Exercises for the knee</h3>

<p>Movement &ldquo;Bicycle&rdquo;. Lying on his back, legs mimic the movement while riding a bike, do not touch the floor.</p>

<p>Lie on your stomach. Without lifting your hips off the floor, bend your legs alternately, trying to touch their buttocks. If there are no sharp pains, you can perform up to 50 times.</p>

<p>Lying on your stomach, bend your leg at the knee at 90 degrees with respect to the body and hold a few seconds. Follow by turns both feet until you get tired (you can up to 50 times).</p>

<p>Sitting on the floor and holding exactly back, dangling his feet at a moderate speed. This exercise is useful to carry out during the day for a lot of times.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Herpes simplex virus types I and II]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/herpes-simplex-virus-types-i-and-ii/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:47:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/herpes-simplex-virus-types-i-and-ii</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/herpes-virus-type/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Herpes virus type" alt="Herpes simplex virus types I and II. Prevention of herpes"> A good immune system &ndash; the best prevention of herpes. At the household level, people used to think that herpes &ndash; an ordinary &ldquo;cold&rdquo; or &ldquo;fever on the lips,&rdquo; but it is actually not so simple. Herpes (from the Greek herpes &ndash; creeping) &ndash; a viral disease that affects the mucous membranes and the skin of a person.</p>

<p>It has been known to mankind for a long time and was described by Hippocrates, who gave him the name because of the &ldquo;creeping&rdquo; nature of the spread of the disease. Among the huge number of viral diseases herpes is a leader because, according to the scientists, latent, that is hidden, &ldquo;sleeping&rdquo; form, it affects about 90% of the entire population of the planet.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>There are about 100 species gerpevirusa, but only eight of these are able to cause diseases in humans, the most common herpes first and second type.</p>

<h2>Herpes virus type</h2>

<p>Herpes virus (HSV-1) is passed as influenza, via droplets &ndash; coughing, sneezing and by contact with the skin or mucous membranes of an infected person. The people he called the &ldquo;common cold on the lips,&rdquo; because, though striking the whole body, outwardly manifested mainly on the lips and nose wings.</p>

<p>The first time it enters the body of the first type of herpes virus does not manifest itself clinically, people do not even realize that he is infected. Before the acute phase of the illness is called the incubation period lasting from 2 to 14 days, during which the virus is actively propagated and implemented.</p>

<p>When the virus starts to become more active on the lips appear very painful blisters with fluid, severe itching, burning, swelling, often increased body temperature and increased lymph nodes. Then the bubbles begin to burst, sores scab, which is also very painful and can last up to 10 days. After healing of wounds virus again &ldquo;hiding&rdquo; in the body and is waiting for a chance for recurrence, the timing of which can not be predicted.</p>

<p>Infection with the first type initially occurs most often between the ages of 3-4 years, and the children of the first years of life almost never get sick herpes because they have immunity from the mother, and by 5 years of age, as a rule, already have in your body  Antibodies to genital virus most often appear in adolescence, around 15 years, initially infection penetrates not only through sexual organs, but also through the mucous membranes of the mouth and skin.</p>

<p>Earlier traditionally believed that the first type of virus affects the upper part of the body &ndash; the face, mouth, eyes and lips, and the second type of virus &ndash; the lower half of the body, usually the genitals. But, now, this division is purely conditional, since there are cases genital lesions gerpevirusom first type.</p>

<h2>Herpes second type</h2>

<p>Second type of herpes virus (HSV-2), more commonly called genital because, unlike the first type, it affects mainly genital mucosa. Transmitted mainly through sex, but also there may be cases of infection through saliva, oral-genital contact. Less common infection through casual through linen and personal care products, as well as through medical procedures such as blood transfusions and organ transplants.</p>

<p>If it affects the human genital herpes incubation period ranging from 1 to 10 days, then comes the acute phase, characterized by fever, malaise, weakness and increased inguinal lymph nodes, which is extremely painful. On the genitals appear painful blisters, itching and pain. Primary genital gerpevirus can last a very long time to heal 3-5 weeks.</p>

<p>A particularly dangerous genital gerpevirus for pregnant women, because the child becomes infected it either in the womb or during childbirth when passing through an infected birth canal.  They are very common neurological disorders, blindness and death. In this regard, it is vital for women planning pregnancy, tested for the presence of viral infections to its occurrence, and if necessary undergo treatment.</p>

<p>Someone gets sick herpes every few years, and someone every few weeks, often the virus affects the same areas. And, if the first type of herpes manifests itself quite rare, mostly not more than three times a year, the second type of herpes recurrences gives every couple of months, and sometimes several times a month, delivering huge human physiological, moral and social issues. According to studies, one in two women suffering from genital gerpevirusom, lonely and Neustroev in his personal life, which often leads to depression and a variety of neuropsychiatric disorders.</p>

<h2>Prevention of herpes</h2>

<p>Despite the enormous prevalence of herpes, most people are passive carriers of it and only 20% of people observed symptoms. Scientists have found that the whole family gerpevirusov is our constant companion throughout life &ndash; to introduce into the body one day, they&rsquo;ll never leave. And only on the condition of the immune system depends on how the virus will behave in the body &ndash; whether it will just live quietly, without letting themselves known, or will regularly remind yourself endless recurrence.</p>

<p>From the primary contact virus gets into the bloodstream and lymph nodes, and future behavior is entirely dependent on the state of the human immune system. When good immunity develops local, or local form of herpes. If, however, reduced immunity, the virus penetrates further into the body, affecting such important organs such as the liver, kidney, spleen, adrenal glands.</p>

<p>The virus accumulates in the cells and in response to various trigger factors will periodically cause permanent relapses. It is promoted by exposure to cold, chronic fatigue, poor diet, excessive exercise, stress, alcohol, antibiotics.</p>

<p>Since the medicine of today has in its arsenal of medicines that allow to completely heal cold sores, it becomes clear that in the first place there is the problem of prevention of infections and the overall strengthening of the immune system. Protect against genital herpes, in contrast to the first type of herpes that is transmissible through airborne droplets, it is possible, respecting the rules of personal hygiene: Do not use someone else&rsquo;s lipstick, do not smoke a cigarette for two, drink, and eat only with their dishes, use a condom and do not in any way engage in oral sex if your partner has gerpevirusa blisters on the lips.</p>

<p>In order to prevent the insidious virus of the herpes host in your body and spoil your life, will make every effort to maximize strengthen your immune system and viruses then no you are not afraid. To do this, use the entire arsenal of tools for healthy living &ndash; nutrition with the presence of all necessary for the body of vitamins and minerals, the correct drinking regime, moderate exercise, healthy sleep, as well as smoking cessation and alcohol.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vegetative - vascular dystonia (VVD)]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/vegetative-vascular-dystonia-vvd/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:46:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/vegetative-vascular-dystonia-vvd</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/vegetative-dystonia/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Vegetative-vascular dystonia" alt="Vegetative-vascular dystonia (VVD) Causes, types and treatment"> Vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia (VVD), and neuro-circulatory dysfunction &ndash; the pathological state of the autonomic nervous system, which results in insufficient supply of oxygen to tissues and organs. According to doctors, with one or other signs of VSD face about 80% of people of all ages.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Vegetative &ndash; dystonia symptoms and signs</h2>

<p>Vegetative (autonomic) nervous system located in the brain and spinal cord, is an essential part of the human body &ndash; it is fully coordinate the activities of all internal organs, blood vessels and glands of internal secretion and provides them to adapt with changes in the external environment.</p>

<p>In particular, the autonomic nervous system regulates blood pressure, heartbeat, body temperature, and composition of extracellular fluid volume, blood flow, metabolic rate, thirst, hunger and satiety, sweat gland function, kidney function, muscle tone internal organs, circadian (daily</p>

<p>For dystonia, which is a consequence of a breach of vascular tone, characterized by the following symptoms:</p>

<p>Neuropsychiatric &ndash; weakness, lethargy, fatigue, low efficiency, dizziness, headaches, sleep disorders, fainting, decreased sexual activity, and panic attacks;
Thermoregulatory action for breach of sweating and thermoregulation &ndash; spontaneous fever, excessive sweating, fever, flushing, or, on the contrary, sensitivity to cold extremities;
Spider &ndash; the instability of the arterial and venous pressure;
Cardiology &ndash; disruption of the heart, frequent heart contractions and pain in the heart;
Breathing (respiratory) &ndash; shortness of breath, chest tightness and a feeling of lack of air;
Dyspeptic &ndash; a disorder of the stomach &ndash; intestinal tract (constipation, diarrhea), voiding dysfunction and gallbladder dyskinesia.</p>

<h2>Vegetative &ndash; dystonia types and causes</h2>

<p>Despite the fact that the uniform classification of the IRR does not exist, the following types are divided vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia:</p>

<p>The nature of the disease:</p>

<ul>
<li>Permanent form &ndash; occurs without abrupt jumps in the patient&rsquo;s condition;</li>
<li>Paroxysmal or paroxysmal &ndash; manifested in the form of attacks (or panic attacks crises), in the intervals between attacks manifestations of the disease are almost invisible;</li>
<li>Mixed ESP (permanently-paroxysmal) &ndash; combines the features of a permanent and paroxysmal forms;</li>
<li>Latent, or hidden form &ndash; in this type of VSD disease may not manifest themselves for quite a long time, until the trigger factors (stress, illness, fatigue).</li>
</ul>


<p>Depending on violations of cardio &ndash; vascular system:</p>

<ul>
<li>Hypertensive type or vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia of hypertensive type. Accompanied by a significant rise in blood pressure (145/90 &ndash; 175/95 mm Hg. c.), sometimes with heart palpitations, sudden excitement, fever, symptoms of a panic attack, and, the pressure can be increased not only in times of emotional stress, but also in a state of complete rest;</li>
<li>Hypertensive type or vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia hypotonic type. In this case, the blood pressure is substantially lower than normal and reaches 100/50 and even up to 90/45 mm Hg. Art. and is accompanied by lethargy, weakness, shortness of breath, nausea, sweating, fatigue patient, sometimes fainting;</li>
<li>Normotensive or heart (cardiac) does not depend on the type of blood pressure and heart disorders defined by the (slow heart rate, or, conversely, rapid, feelings fade and disruptions of the heart), as well as pain in the chest area;</li>
<li>Mixed type of VSD combines multiple symptoms and signs typical for any type.</li>
</ul>


<p>Depending on the cause of vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia, the following types of VSD: genetic, infectious &ndash; allergic, traumatic, psychogenic (as a reaction to stress or traumatic situations), and arose as a result of excessive emotional or physical stress.</p>

<h2>Vegetative &ndash; dystonia treatment and prevention</h2>

<p>From the timely and correct diagnosis of VSD depends largely on the success of further treatment. If you have frequent attacks of headache, weakness, dizziness, fatigue, insomnia, unfounded anxiety, fear, jumps in blood pressure and heart rate, &ldquo;lump&rdquo; in the throat, shortness of breath, pain in the heart and stomach, as well as grow cold and numb limbs &ndash;</p>

<p>Do not listen to bad advice of friends and acquaintances in an &ldquo;ESP is not a disease and will pass without treatment.&rdquo; Doctors claim that untreated dystonia is very dangerous because it can be complicated by panic attacks and other serious disorders that occur on the wrong team, the autonomic nervous system and debilitating nervous system.</p>

<p>When panic attacks (Sympathoadrenal crisis) a person starts suddenly (often in a public place) to shake, choke and breaking into a cold sweat. At the same time, he has a wild fear of death, heart pounding jumps and pressure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ankylosing spondylitis]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/ankylosing-spondylitis/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:45:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/ankylosing-spondylitis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/ankylosing-spondylitis/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Ankylosing spondylitis" alt="Ankylosing spondylitis: causes, symptoms, diagnosis"> Modern methods of treatment of ankylosing spondylitis help stop the inflammation of the joints. Ankylosing spondylitis, or ankylosing spondylitis (ankylosing spondylitis) &ndash; a chronic inflammatory disease of the spine and joints, accompanied by pain, stiffness and deformity and progressive ossification of the joints, including the formation of irreversible changes in them and complete immobility.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Ankylosing spondylitis causes</h2>

<p>Causes of ankylosing spondylitis is not thoroughly understood, but it is known that people who are carriers of the gene HLA-B27, a genetic predisposition to the disease Ankylosing Spondylitis Disease (BB).</p>

<p>The immune system of such people &ldquo;mistakenly&rdquo; believes tissue of the joints and ligaments, and alien attacks them, causing inflammation and damage.</p>

<p>However, even in the presence of this gene, ill ankylosing spondylitis is not all that is a mystery and the subject of further research for doctors &ndash; Rheumatology. Additional factors that may trigger the development of the disease are considered to change the immune status of the &ndash; for colds, colds, viral and infectious &ndash; allergic diseases and injuries of the pelvis and spine.</p>

<p>In addition, the latest research scientists have shown that ankylosing spondylitis is a psychosomatic illness and because, more than a third of cases the first symptoms began to appear after heavy and prolonged stress.</p>

<h2>Diagnosis and distinctive symptoms of ankylosing spondylitis</h2>

<p>Because some of the symptoms of ankylosing spondylitis is very similar to the symptoms of degenerative disc disease in the early stages of these diseases are often confused, as ankylosing spondylitis often starts as a normal low back pain &ndash; pain in the lower back and painful back muscle strain.</p>

<p>Therefore, for correct diagnosis and start early treatment, it is important to identify the disease early in its development, to prevent the complete immobilization of the spine and associated threatening complications. The most dangerous complication of ankylosing spondylitis include:</p>

<p>Amyloidosis &ndash; degeneration of the kidneys, leading to kidney failure;
Defeat heart and aorta, leading to shortness of breath and chest pain provoking and disruption of the heart;
Tuberculosis and other diseases of the lung, derived from &ndash; the decrease in the mobility of the chest;
Uveitis &ndash; inflammation of the choroid, leading to blurred vision, eye pain and sensitivity to light;</p>

<p>Among the primary symptoms of ankylosing spondylitis is the most characteristic periodic pain (in 75% of cases). But if osteochondrosis pain is permanent and increases when moving, then in ankylosing spondylitis is different &ndash; the pain is much worse at night and several subside during the day, after the start of active movements.</p>

<p>If osteochondrosis person can lean on at least one side, or turn to the right &ndash; to the left, then the movement of ankylosing spondylitis usually fails in all directions. In addition, the most frequent symptom of ankylosing spondylitis is swelling and tenderness of the joints, as well as the characteristic change of posture, posture called the &ldquo;petitioner&rdquo;.</p>

<p>In the formation of an asylum patient poses a gradual straightening of the normal curvature of the spine &ndash; the back is straight and flat. A little later freezes thoracic, there is a strong slouch, and the legs when walking instinctively bend at the knees. Over time, spinal stiffness reaches such a degree that the person begins to move as if he rather inflexible spine stick.</p>

<p>Properly diagnose disease helps the spine x-ray in which an experienced physician may notice the early signs of changes of bones and joints, magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) and a blood test for C-reactive protein, erythrocyte sedimentation rate (ESR), and the presence of the antigen HLA-B27. ESR parameter greater than 30 mm/h and the presence of HLA-B27 antigen confirm the validity of the diagnosis of ankylosing spondylitis.</p>

<h2>Ankylosing spondylitis treatment</h2>

<p>As the basis of therapy in the treatment of ankylosing spondylitis patients assigned to longer courses (from 1 year to 5 years) of non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs, which help to significantly slow down the progression of the disease, as well as anti-rheumatic drugs, corticosteroids, and necrosis factor blockers. Sometimes, in particularly severe cases, shows the assignment of immunosuppressive drugs.</p>

<p>In addition, it is important to sanitize all the centers of chronic infections in the body and carry out strengthening therapy &ndash; it is well to prevent cases of relapse. As an alternative treatment successfully used acupuncture, reflexology, magnet, pchelolechenie, hirudotherapy, physiotherapy and massage.</p>

<p>Girudoterapiya (leech therapy) has a good anti-inflammatory, analgesic and anti-bacterial effect, as contained in the saliva of leeches enzymes (hirudin, Eglin, destabilaza) soften and make more plastic stiff spine, relieve inflammation and tissue damage of the joints and ligaments, and normalize blood flow.</p>

<p>In addition, leech therapy has a beneficial effect on the entire body &ndash; by improving the blood circulation and better blood oxygen saturation, dissolve blood clots, normal metabolism, improved sleep, appetite and mood, and increases immunity.</p>

<h2>Physiotherapy</h2>

<p>Exercise therapy for ankylosing spondylitis is very important, as regular exercise and exercise increase blood flow in the joints, help maintain flexibility of the spine and lower extremities, stop the progression of the disease and prevent disability.</p>

<p>However, you should remember that exercise should be a feasible and gentle, so as not to lead to poor health. So, absolutely contraindicated in patients with BB running, jumping, shaking in the transport and hypothermia. On the contrary, it is very useful to calm walking (up to 3 &ndash; 5 kilometers), including skiing on flat terrain. Swimming in ponds and pools allowed at water temperatures below 23 &ndash; 22 degrees, and leave recommended in areas with warm and dry climate.</p>

<p>If you have a long time to be in the same position, it is necessary to change the position of each hour of the body. During the day, preferably several times to lie on a hard bed without a pillow when lying on stomach with legs straight. If this position is not straighten up, you can put a small pillow under her stomach.</p>

<p>Therapeutic exercises should be mandatory daily procedure, even if you do not feel well and have no hope of restoring spinal mobility. The fact that, due to splices and joints chest stiffness deteriorates ventilation, which may lead to pneumonia, pulmonary fibrosis and other diseases. Therefore, in order to prevent serious complications, the patient is required breathing exercises (daily, 3-4 times a day, inflate a balloon) and regular walks in the fresh air.</p>

<h2>Complex physiotherapy in ankylosing spondylitis</h2>

<p>Initial position (and. etc.) &ndash; sitting on a chair.
Turns head to the right and to the left, half circles and head tilts his ear to the shoulder.
Hands on waist, shoulder blades are brought together, back straight &ndash; chin stretch ahead.
Hands separated the sides, fingers clenched in a fist &ndash; chin hug the neck and connect the blades.</p>

<p>Starting position &ndash; lying on his back
Raise your head and stretch your chin to her stomach.
Hands pull at your sides, legs join together &ndash; relying on the heel, neck and hands, lift the hips as high as possible and forecasting.
Rewound Hands behind your head, legs together, feet on yourself &ndash; lift the body by 45 degrees, a little linger in this position, and slowly lower to the starting position.
Lift straightened legs and work out them alternately in different directions circular motion.
Bend your legs, arms behind his head rewound &ndash; lift the pelvis, cave in and slowly lower.</p>

<p>Starting position &ndash; lying on its side
Both the knee to the chest, move and try to reach out to their forehead. Then straighten your legs and cave in back.
Follow alternately mahi straight leg forward &ndash; back and leg lifts straight up.
Fold the leg at the knee and follow the circular motion of the hip.</p>

<p>However, it is worth noting that the set of physical exercises can not be yourself, it must be paired with your doctor, who will take into account the individual characteristics of the course of ankylosing spondylitis and the general condition of the body.</p>

<h2>Massage, diet and prevention of complications</h2>

<p>Massage in ankylosing spondylitis, used in conjunction with physical therapy, good pain relief and muscle fatigue, strengthens the muscular system, normalizes skin tone and helps to preserve the ability of the vertebral motor.</p>

<p>However, massage is just beyond the acute phase should be easy and gentle, with no hard techniques (cutting, effleurage) and carried out by a qualified technician. The total duration of the massage treatments should not exceed 25 minutes, after the course of treatment (20 &ndash; 25 sessions) needed a break for 3 &ndash; 4 weeks.</p>

<p>Nutrition in ankylosing spondylitis, as with any other chronic inflammatory disease must be balanced, but not excessive, so as not to lead to obesity. Caloric intake should closely match the physiological needs of the body and exercise patient as overweight creates a dangerous extra strain on the joints of the spine and lower extremities.</p>

<p>In the menu there should be enough protein foods, especially fish and low-fat dairy products, salads with fresh vegetables with the addition of unrefined sunflower or corn oil, fruits and herbs. Ordinary table salt substitute on the marine containing many useful trace elements. Nutritionists advise instead of salt to add to ready-made meals seaweed powder, which contains all necessary for the normal functioning of the bones and cartilage of trace elements.</p>

<p>In addition, the diet should be excluded sharp, smoked, fried and salty foods, alcohol and refined foods, preferring healthy homemade food &ndash; whole grain porridge, stewed and pureed vegetables and soups. Doctors say if you stick to eating right, just get treatment and begin to actively engage in physical therapy, the inflammation in the joints can significantly slow down and you will be able to lead a full life.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Total bilirubin in the blood]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/total-bilirubin-in-the-blood/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:43:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/total-bilirubin-in-the-blood</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-lower-bilirubin/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Direct bilirubin, indirect bilirubin, elevated bilirubin, how to lower bilirubin" alt="Total bilirubin in the blood, direct, indirect"> Increased bilirubin &ndash; a source of dangerous intoxication of the brain. Bilirubin &ndash; the pigment saturated yellow-brown color, is produced in many organs and tissues and is the end product of the breakdown of hemoglobin and other proteins heme-containing in the cells of the liver, bone marrow and spleen.</p>

<p>The physiological role of bilirubin is not completely understood, but according to recent research, it is necessary not only for the disposal of hemoglobin, as previously thought, but is also a powerful natural antioxidant that gives great promise for the discovery of new treatments for cancer, cardiology and many other diseases.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Bilirubin direct, indirect and total</h2>

<p>In the human body bilirubin is present in two forms &ndash; direct (related) and indirect (Free). Total bilirubin in its pure form does not exist, and is defined as the sum of direct and indirect, and, normally, direct bilirubin should be 75% of the total. Every day, the body is made of about 250 &ndash; 350 mg of bilirubin, wherein, about 80% erythrocytes formed during decomposition (1 gram of hemoglobin &ndash; about 36 grams bilirubin).</p>

<p>It is known that human blood is a rapidly renewing connective tissue composed of plasma cells and uniform elements: erythrocytes (provide tissues with oxygen), white blood cells (responsible for the immune system and fight infections) and platelets (responsible for blood clotting).</p>

<p>The erythrocytes, or red blood cells &ndash; the most numerous of the blood cells. They live in an average of about 120 days, after which decompose, releasing the hemoglobin contained in them. Hemoglobin, after complex chemical reactions, originally converted into a free or indirect bilirubin is insoluble in water and is extremely poisonous. It is concentrated in the liver by gripping it from the blood of liver cells.</p>

<p>Unconjugated bilirubin in the liver as a &ldquo;neutralized&rdquo; &ndash; under the influence of special enzymes, it connects to the glucuronide and get involved. Due to the effect of glucuronic acid, direct bilirubin, in contrast to indirect becomes soluble and less toxic &ndash; easily soluble in bile, it falls along with it in the intestine and then removed from the body naturally with faeces, giving it a brown color.</p>

<h2>Increased bilirubin in the blood causes and symptoms</h2>

<p>In the normal metabolism of bilirubin in the blood gets very little direct bilirubin. However, under pathological failure, it can significantly increase the concentration in blood (hyperbilirubinemia) and urine (bilirubinuria) penetrating into the surrounding tissue and causing yellowing of the skin, sclera eyes and mucous membranes. In addition, frequent signs of the disease &ndash; nausea, weakness, vomiting, bitter belching, heaviness in the right upper quadrant, bleached almost white feces, urine, beer color and itchy skin.</p>

<p>Primary cause of bilirubin metabolism:</p>

<p>Diseases of the blood in which there is a sharp increase in the number of non-viable red blood cells (anemia), the immune aggression toward normal red blood cells (hemolytic disease of the newborn rhesus &ndash; conflict with the child&rsquo;s mother), and exposure to toxic chemicals and blood cells.</p>

<p>Liver disease (viral, bacterial, autoimmune, toxic and drug hepatitis, jaundice), striking or destroy liver cells. When severe jaundice yellowing not only the skin and the sclera eyes, but also saliva, sweat, tears, breast milk, and all the internal organs.</p>

<p>Violation of the free passage of bile on biliary pathways &ndash; gallstones, gallbladder dyskinesia, pakreatit, the presence of tumors, scars or enlarged lymph nodes in close proximity to bile ways.</p>

<p>Poisoning by alcohol, chemicals and medicines.
A lack of vitamin B12.
Hereditary lack of liver enzyme &ndash; Gilbert&rsquo;s syndrome.
Physiological neonatal jaundice.</p>

<h2>Normal bilirubin in children and adults</h2>

<p>Determining the level of bilirubin in the blood is an important tool for the diagnosis of many diseases, especially of the liver, biliary tract and the hematopoietic system, and is one of the key indicators of the biochemical analysis of blood. Refferentnye values ​​of normal levels of total, direct and indirect bilirubin levels for adults and children are shown in the table below</p>

<h3>In adults and children older than 1 month</h3>

<p>Birth 51-60 mmol/l, with 2 days to the end of the first week may increase to 256 mmol/l by indirect (preterm and 170 pmol/l).</p>

<p>3 By the end of the week approaches the indicator for vzroslyhNepryamoydo 15.4 mmol/l (75% of the total) in the peak period of not less than 90% of the obschegoPryamoydo 5.1 mmol/l (25% of the total) in the peak period of not more than 10%.</p>

<h2>Physiological neonatal jaundice</h2>

<p>Increased bilirubin in neonates is not a disease and in most cases takes place independently and does not require treatment. This phenomenon is called physiologic jaundice (jaundice) in infants and children is associated with the adaptation of the organism to changing environmental conditions.</p>

<p>Fact that blood first days of life of children comprises a so-called fetal hemoglobin (formed in utero) which differs in composition from adult human hemoglobin and is active replacement for the first month of life.</p>

<p>Due to the fact that the replacement of a significant amount of released hemoglobin degradation products of erythrocytes, and the liver and biliary system infant has not yet fully operational, approximately 3 &ndash; 4 days of age his skin and mucous membranes may be colored yellow. Afraid of this state do not have to &ndash; as soon as the enzyme system of the child is fully working, skin color changes to pale &ndash; pink, this is usually a 7 &ndash; 8 day of life.</p>

<p>A slightly longer and expression can occur in rhesus jaundice &ndash; conflict (Rh negative mother and an infant positive) or in the presence of mothers in the first group of blood, and the child&rsquo;s second (sometimes third). At the same time children become overly drowsy and need to wake up for feedings.</p>

<p>To reduce the toxicity effects of high levels of bilirubin and accelerate its excretion in feces and urine, modern medicine is widely used method of light therapy (phototherapy). Infant is placed under a special lamp, close your eyes and cover the bandage, if possible, on both sides. Typically, after the 4 &ndash; day fotolecheniya, jaundice symptoms completely disappear.</p>

<p>The positive effect of the treatment has zheltushki breastfeeding and earlier attachment baby to the breast &ndash; it promotes more rapid discharge of meconium and reduces the likelihood of complications. In more severe cases, with severe jaundice may require donor blood transfusion, allowing the nervous system and save a child&rsquo;s life from the toxic effects.</p>

<h2>How to lower bilirubin?</h2>

<p>To reduce the bilirubin in the blood, it is first necessary to establish the root cause of its increase. Otherwise, it will continue to rise since hyperbilirubinemia is not a separate disease but a symptom of a disease.</p>

<p>In particular, if the fault stagnation of bile, sufficient to remove the obstacle, for example, remove the stone in the gall bladder or a course of treatment with drugs that improve bile secretion. In viral hepatitis need antiviral treatment, hemolytic anemia &ndash; a means to warn increased breakdown of red blood cells. If the reason is due to intoxication of the body, will help welcome the adsorbents bind toxic substances and getaprotektorov, which serve to protect the liver.</p>

<p>In addition, to reduce the rate of the enzyme in blood, it is necessary to unload the liver and gallbladder, changing his diet toward healthy diet. From the menu to exclude acute, smoked and fried foods, carbonated drinks, alcohol, strong tea, sweets. Choose more fresh, boiled and baked foods, especially vegetables &ndash; this will help to eliminate the causes of constipation, restore useful microflora and provide quick removal of toxins from the intestines.</p>

<p>In order not to disturb the functioning of the digestive tract, eat often, but little by little, do not overeat and avoid long breaks between meals. In addition, during the acute banned starvation diets for weight loss, showing compliance with therapeutic diet for gallstones.</p>

<p>For the correct diagnosis needs to know how to properly prepare for the tests. Blood is drawn from a vein in the morning on an empty stomach is not recommended to eat and drink coffee (caffeine reduces bilirubin levels) for 8 hours before the procedure, otherwise the results may be unreliable.</p>

<p>In previous blood donation day give up fatty foods (not to overload the liver) and from excessive exercise, provoking pain in the right upper quadrant. To obtain accurate figures, sometimes requires the prior cancellation (within 2 weeks), certain drugs, in particular vitamin C and anti-epileptic drugs.</p>

<p>If the research is carried out correctly and showed enzyme levels significantly below normal, it also should be alerted. Causes of low bilirubin insufficiently studied, because, more often than not, people are suffering from high enzyme content, not low. However, according to some medical studies, a direct link between between its reduced level of disease and coronary heart disease, that is, the risk of heart attack and stroke is much lower at high bilirubin than at low.</p>

<p>Finally, we note that high levels of bilirubin requires careful and rigorous, as it is highly toxic to the central nervous system and causes a variety of ailments &ndash; persistent headaches, fatigue, slowing of heart rate (bradycardia). Therefore, the best way to avoid poisoning the brain and body &ndash; at the first symptoms to seek medical attention.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banana diet for 3 days and 7 days]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet-for-3-days-and-7-days/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:41:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet-for-3-days-and-7-days</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/banana-diet/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="banana diet, banana and milk, cottage cheese-banana, kefir-banana" alt="Banana diet for 3 days and 7 days. Menus, reviews, results"> Banana Diet &ndash; minus 5-6 pounds per week. Banana Diet is one of the most popular short-term mono-diet of fruit, allow a few days without much trouble to get rid of extra pounds. An estimated nutritionists, 3 days prior to the banana diet lost 3 &ndash; pounds overweight, and this week &ndash; about 5 &ndash; 6 pounds.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Banana Diet Reviews and contraindications</h2>

<p>Reviews of the banana diet for both patients and physicians, the most positive. The fact that by means of bananas can not only &ldquo;eat&rdquo; and satisfying lose weight, but also greatly improve the condition of the gastro &ndash; intestinal tract, cardio &ndash; vascular system and blood circulation.</p>

<p>From &ndash; due to the high content of potassium in the pulp of banana (360 mg per 100 g product), magnesium (27 mg), and fiber, this miracle &ndash; the fruit greatly improves the water &ndash; salt metabolism in the body, good displays excess fluid (edema), toxins, toxins, excess glucose and bad cholesterol and stimulates the smooth operation of the intestine.</p>

<p>Because bananas almost do not cause allergic reactions, are an excellent source of energy and the supplier of many essential vitamins and minerals, they are often included as complementary foods into the diet of infants, pregnant women and nursing mothers. Assign them as well as dietary and impaired postoperative patients, the elderly and athletes.</p>

<p>In addition, bananas are useful for depression (from &ndash; for the content of pleasure hormone serotonin), chronic fatigue syndrome, hypertension, intestinal problems (constipation, diarrhea), gastritis, reduced hemoglobin, diseases of the bladder and biliary tract, arthritis, heartburn.</p>

<p>Banana days, in contrast to other severe handling fruit monodiets days (cucumber, apple, carrot), due to the presence of large amounts of natural fruit sugars (fructose, glucose, sucrose) are less hungry and promote more rapid and prolonged saturation.</p>

<p>Do not stick to the banana diet for people with individual intolerance to bananas, as well as in diseases of thrombophlebitis and varicose veins. The fact that bananas are a group of products, thickening the blood, so they should be avoided when varicose veins and circulatory disorders of blood vessels. List of products, blood thinners and advice on therapeutic nutrition to varicose veins, read the article on our website.</p>

<p>In diabetes of both types of banana diet is not contraindicated, but because of the high sugar content, it must be agreed upon with the attending physician to correctly calculate individual daily amount of carbohydrates (bread units BU) and eliminate sudden increases in blood glucose levels. Detailed treatment recommendations for patients with diabetes first and second types are described in the articles about diets for diabetics.</p>

<h2>Features choice of fruit for the banana diet</h2>

<p>Pick the fruit for banana mono-diet is of great importance. Slimming perfect ripe &ldquo;fruit&rdquo; Bananas &ndash; rich yellow color, soft, thin-skinned and of medium length. If you bought a slightly unripe fruit, do not rush to use them, first wrap in plastic paper and leave for a few days in a dark place to ripen.</p>

<p>Do not buy so-called &ldquo;feed&rdquo; bananas &ndash; long, green and thick rind and dried, which is several times high-calorie fresh. Before use, the fruit must be thoroughly clean not only on the skin, but also on the white threads, leaving only the pulp of a ripe.</p>

<h3>Strong banana diet for 3 days</h3>

<p>Banana diet for 3 days, often referred to as a banana &ndash; milk diet is the easiest and one banana a strict diet. Daily menu milk &ndash; banana diet consists of 3 &ndash; bananas and 3 &ndash; cup of skim milk or yogurt (1%).</p>

<p>Divide the specified amount of food for 5 &ndash; 6 portions and eat at regular intervals throughout the day &ndash; split meals to avoid the appearance of a strong sense of hunger. Fruits and dairy products can be used as separate from each other, and as a banana yogurt or neck &ndash; whip banana yogurt or milk using a blender.</p>

<p>Additionally, throughout the day as possible drink plain water and herbal teas without sugar, it promotes better bowel cleansing and normalization of the gastro &ndash; intestinal tract. The last meal plan no later than 3 hours before bedtime.</p>

<h3>Banana Diet 7 days</h3>

<p>The seven-day option is not as strict as three days, and does not limit the amount of fruit consumed &ndash; are allowed to eat per day to 1.5 kg of peeled ripe bananas. However, slimming process in this embodiment is quite effective for night out on average about 1 kilogram of body weight.</p>

<p>As soon as you feel hungry, Eat one fruit at once. If it is a very &ldquo;hungry&rdquo;, as a source of complete protein can be added to the menu 1 boiled egg. From drinks are allowed in unlimited quantities of water and herbal tea without sugar, consumption of dairy products with the exception.</p>

<h3>Curd &ndash; banana diet</h3>

<p>Curd &ndash; banana slimming option for up to 4 days, involves alternation of banana and cheese fasting days and makes it quite effectively reduce weight, up to 3 &ndash; 4 pounds. Since cheese is quite a varied and useful product, banana &ndash; curd alternation transferred easily and is therefore very popular with losing weight.</p>

<p>The first and third days &ndash; cheese:</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; 120 g low-fat cottage cheese (up to 5% fat), fruit;
Lunch &ndash; 120 g cottage cheese, vegetable salad without oil;
Dinner &ndash; 120 grams cottage cheese, grapefruit.</p>

<p>The second and fourth days &ndash; banana:</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; banana, 120 g low-fat yogurt or cottage cheese;
Lunch &ndash; 2 banana, 1 boiled egg;
Dinner &ndash; 200 grams of cooked lean meat, 1 &ndash; 2 bananas.</p>

<h2>Exit after the banana diet tips and advice</h2>

<p>Longer than the recommended 3 &ndash; 7 days to comply with the banana mono-diet is not recommended. First, despite the usefulness of the product, banana slimming, like any other mono-diet is not completely balanced and can cause serious injury.</p>

<p>A in &ndash; Second, our body is designed wisely and in a few days can adapt to any conditions and, if necessary, the power-saving mode. Therefore, for more than the recommended terms of losing weight is not only harmful but also impractical because the weight will fall either very slow or it hard to stand still &ndash; nutritionists effect of this phenomenon is called a &ldquo;plateau&rdquo; (described in more detail in the diet roller coaster diet and Ladder).</p>

<p>Exit after kefir &ndash; the banana diet, as well as following any diet, despite the achieved effect, must be smooth and gradual &ndash; is necessary in order to permanently fix the result. Within a week, gently insert the usual foods and observe moderation &ndash; if you start to eat off of hungry days, the weight comes back very quickly.</p>

<p>If losing weight on bananas was comfortable for you, start to practice weekly unloading banana days &ndash; this will easily support the weight without the stress and shocks. To the menu was not too severe, it offers a variety of delicious and hearty recipes.</p>

<p>Banana &ndash; fruit salad &ndash; cut slices of banana and add the slices of apple, pear or peach. The second option salad &ndash; add walnuts and lettuce.</p>

<p>Oatmeal with banana &ndash; Boil water for oatmeal, add back milk and finely chopped banana slices.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[American diet for weight loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/american-diet-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:39:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/american-diet-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/diet-roller-coaster-diet-dinner-minus/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Diet roller coaster, diet dinner minus" alt="American diet for weight loss. Roller coaster and minus the dinner diets"> Diet Rollercoaster allows you to securely lose weight by speeding up metabolism.</p>

<p>Diet roller coaster developed by American nutritionist Martin Cathan more than 30 years ago and in that time has gained wide popularity. It is one of the most effective ways to reduce weight and allows the presence of physical activity, reduce up to 7 pounds in a week.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>The essence of the diet roller coaster</h2>

<p>There is a simple explanation. The fact is that our body is able to quickly adjust and adapt to any diet. To do this, it is enough to just a few days, after which it includes saving mode (power saving), so the metabolism (metabolism) slows down and stops weight plummeted.</p>

<p>Dr. Martin Katan take into account this feature, and developed the technique in such a way as to literally &ldquo;confuse&rdquo; the body, preventing it &ldquo;remember&rdquo; the amount of calories consumed and not allowing to adapt to the new regime.</p>

<p>Recommended them daily caloric intake ranges up &ndash; down, from minimum to maximum, which gave the name of a popular diet roller coaster ride. Through this approach to nutrition he managed to lose about 30 pounds of dead weight and to help numerous people lose weight.</p>

<h2>Diet Rollercoaster menu</h2>

<p>Follow the diet roller coaster is simple, you have to do only the willpower to break away and not to follow through, and meticulous counting calories. Product Composition, unlike most other programs weight reduction is not critical. That is, you can eat all you want, above all, to keep within the recommended number of calories.</p>

<p>The most severe and difficult from a psychological point of view, are the first three days, which are allowed to eat only 600 calories. These days will be very hungry all the time and will want to eat, but you have to strictly follow your plan and understand that it will be easier. To do this, try to choose the daily caloric not chocolates, biscuits and light carbohydrate and low-calorie vegetables, fruits, low-fat dairy products and cereals on the water.</p>

<p>Since these products are made up of fiber and slowly digestible carbohydrates, they provide a feeling of satiety for a long time and do not give a break to &ldquo;Jordania&rdquo;. In addition, fiber helps avoid the inevitable with insufficient food constipation, thoroughly clean the intestines and populate it useful microflora.</p>

<p>Do not forget about the copious drinking regimen, drink plenty of simple and non-carbonated mineral water and herbal tea (without sugar). This will not only enhance the cleansing process in the intestine, but also help to avoid excessive hunger. Because we all know that people often confuse hunger with a feeling of thirst. Sometimes it is enough to drink a glass of water, and there is no longer want to.</p>

<p>Thus, the scheme of alternation calories, designed for 3 weeks:</p>

<p>The first &ndash; the third day &ndash; 600 calories;
Fourth &ndash; the seventh day &ndash; 900 calories;
The eighth &ndash; the fourteenth day &ndash; 1200 calories;
The fifteenth &ndash; seventeenth day &ndash; 600 calories;
Eighteen &ndash; twenty-one days &ndash; 900 kcal.</p>

<p>Daily menu, as already mentioned, can be anything from any of the products, dishes and combinations. But to you it was easier to navigate, give an approximate daily food intake by 600, 900 and 1200 kcal. You can take it as a basis and change the components in its sole discretion, according to the energy value of foods (see table on the caloric content of products and labels) and the individual taste preferences.</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; unsweetened tea, a small piece of rye bread;
Lunch &ndash; 100 grams of boiled beef and cooked rice, a salad of radish and cucumber without oil;
Dinner &ndash; 1 boiled egg and a glass of low-fat yogurt.</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; black tea (you can add 1 liter. sugar) with rye crackers, apple green;
Dinner &ndash; boiled or steamed fish, pasta and vegetable salad (100 g). Tea (sugar content not exceeding 1 tsp);
Dinner &ndash; 1 boiled egg, 100 grams of cottage cheese (low-fat), and a small banana.</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; 200 grams of oatmeal (on the water and no oil), tea (sugar 1 tsp) with rye croutons;
Dinner &ndash; boiled chicken (200 g), buckwheat porridge with a small piece of butter (100 g);
Dinner &ndash; Assorted fruit salad of apples, grapes, bananas, pineapple.</p>

<p>During the day, between meals, snacks are permitted &ndash; 1 cup low-fat yogurt, a small banana.</p>

<p>After a full course of 21 days, you can gradually return to your normal diet. According to Dr. Katana, during this period can not reliably &ldquo;confuse&rdquo; the body, so the result is stored for a long period of time and will have to repeat the whole cycle will not soon.</p>

<p>It should be noted that to observe the &ldquo;roller coaster&rdquo; only healthy people, the beauty and harmony should not be achieved at the expense of health. Slimming prohibited under the scheme &ldquo;600-900-1200&rdquo; with the gastro &ndash; intestinal tract, pregnant women, nursing mothers, as well as any chronic illnesses. Even if you feel perfectly healthy, losing weight before check with your doctor.</p>

<p>Despite the fact that physical exercise can significantly, by almost 2-fold, to enhance the effect of the diet (with exercise you can lose up to 10 pounds, without them &ndash; to 6 pounds), heavy physical exertion banned because they can lead to a sharp deterioration  It is useful to practice yoga, walking, pilates, aerobics and leisurely cycling. To distract from the food, walk a little more in the fresh air and get enough sleep, at least 8 &ndash; 9 hours a day.</p>

<h2>American diet &ldquo;Dinner minus&rdquo;</h2>

<p>The American Diet Dinner minus does not promise weight loss in 3 days, but it is very comfortable to compliance and requires meticulous counting calories eaten each piece as a roller coaster. In addition, during the follow-up system, &ldquo;dinner minus&rdquo;, the body produces the correct and healthy eating habits &ndash; consume a major amount of fat in the first half of the day, when the active hormones are responsible for their split.</p>

<p>It is based on the familiar childhood postulates that at night there are harmful and need to be fed in accordance with the well-known saying &ldquo;Eat breakfast yourself, share dinner with a friend, a dinner give to the enemy.&rdquo; That is, the authors offer a methodology completely forget about this concept as dinner and after 17 hours is recommended to drink only ordinary water.</p>

<p>Thus, the basic principles of the diet minus dinner:</p>

<ul>
<li>Copious drinking regime &ndash; drink at least 2 liters of water daily;</li>
<li>Last meal be carried out not later than 17 hours;</li>
<li>Decrease in the consumption of animal fat diet, replacing them with vegetable. Just keep in mind that fats can not be completely ruled out, suitable for all common sense;</li>
<li>Choose a menu for only quality products without trans fats, dyes, preservatives, emulsifiers, preferring fast food nutrition healthy homemade food.</li>
</ul>


<p>Composing your diet, avoid distortions in any direction. If you strongly want something sweet, do not deny yourself &ndash; eat a small piece of dessert in the first half of the day. Do not focus only on choosing low-calorie foods, pay more attention to their usefulness and naturalness. Remember, the beauty and harmony can only give a healthy body, provided a balance of everything necessary for the normal functioning &ndash; proteins, fats, carbohydrates, vitamins and trace elements.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surgical treatment of hemorrhoids: the cost of surgery to remove nodes]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/surgical-treatment-of-hemorrhoids-the-cost-of-surgery-to-remove-nodes/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:22:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/surgical-treatment-of-hemorrhoids-the-cost-of-surgery-to-remove-nodes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoids-surgery-cost/14.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="hemorrhoids surgery cost" alt="Surgical treatment of hemorrhoids: the cost of surgery to remove nodes"> If a man appeared for the first time in the life of hemorrhoids, he usually tries to take all measures to get rid of the unpleasant symptoms. If the patient in time refers to the proctologist, complaining of discomfort during bowel movements, itching, cracking or bleeding from hemorrhoids, you can quickly get rid of the early stages. However, the disease often becomes extremely sleazy. Almost all patients go to the doctor already after conservative treatment of hemorrhoids is no longer effective. In this case, the doctor carefully examines the patient and determines the future strategy of the treatment of the disease. Often, the final stage of this process is the surgical treatment of hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>If doctors detect external hemorrhoids requiring mechanical removal, to begin the patient is usually prescribed minimally invasive techniques that do not require surgical intervention. However, they are not suitable for all patients, so a large percentage of people suffering from hemorrhoids, gets on the operating table.</p>

<p>Do I need surgery if you have hemorrhoids? As mentioned above, the doctors try to minimize the chances of radical treatments. If there is a chance to eliminate the disease conservative or non-surgical method, the doctor uses all techniques that can have an effect. Most often, the operation shall be appointed, if a person is present hemorrhoids grade 3 complications. If the disease is the first or second step, the patient may help non-surgical hemorrhoid sclerotherapy.</p>

<h2>How do the surgery and what to choose?</h2>

<p>Today in medicine there are two main types of surgery to remove hemorrhoids. First &ndash; this is a hemorrhoidectomy for Milligan-Morgan. Second &ndash; gemorroidopeksiya by Longo. Longo operation differs from the operation of Milligan-Morgan. With this procedure, the hosts themselves are not deleted, but removes part of the rectum. By removing a portion of mucosal blood flow is disturbed nodes, whereupon they atrophy. The intervention on the Milligan-Morgan exterior and interior nodes are excised and then sewn sutures.</p>

<p>How much surgery? Data close to the end of the article. On the appropriateness of the procedure you can tell your doctor. As for the criteria for the appointment of each of the types of intervention, they can be represented as a simple table.</p>

<h2>Do I need to prepare?</h2>

<p>Preparation for surgery is performed in both cases. Both types of procedures performed in a hospital, so patients necessarily prepared for anesthesia and the surgery in advance. Hemorrhoidectomy and operation Longo require prior hospitalization. As for anesthesia, then the operation can Longo local anesthesia, although most often it is performed under general intravenous anesthesia. Hemorrhoidectomy for Milligan-Morgan performed only under intravenous anesthesia. Also, the patient can make epidural anesthesia. Local anesthesia is hardly found. Preparing for Surgery Hemorrhoids usually are not too durable, but you can not avoid this step.</p>

<h2>How long is the surgery?</h2>

<p>Another criterion &ndash; the duration of the procedure. The operation to Milligan-Morgan takes about half an hour, and the operation Longo lasts no more than twenty minutes. Tolerated both procedures are equally good, but after the surgery the patient requires medical supervision. Treatment after surgery includes preventive tools for toning the veins.</p>

<h2>Stay in a hospital</h2>

<p>After the surgery, the patient remains Longo in hospital under observation for 2-3 days. When hemorrhoidectomy hospital stay may increase up to a week. Deserve special attention, patients who develop complications of thrombosed hemorrhoids: surgery in this case should only start after the relief of the inflammatory process. Do not put the patient on the operating table during an exacerbation. It should be noted that the cost of surgery to remove hemorrhoids almost never include the cost of hospital stays. If you are being treated at a private clinic, check in advance how much are the day following hospital treatment.</p>

<h2>Terms of rehabilitation</h2>

<p>In contrast to the non-invasive techniques, after which the patient can go to work the next day, after surgical treatment of hemorrhoids patient must comply with bed rest to a week. Temporary disability after intervention by Milligan-Morgan can reach months, and after the operation is issued weekly Longo hospital.</p>

<h2>Pain</h2>

<p>How to be a painful operation? This question is asked all the patients who were prescribed surgical excision or removal of nodes of the rectal mucosa. According to experts, in operation Longo pain is negligible. In the case of the operation for Milligan-Morgan pain observed in the postoperative period in almost all patients. This procedure is a significant drawback, however, this does not diminish its effectiveness. While the patient is in the hospital, doctors removed the pain with the help of powerful analgesics. Absolutely painless surgical removal of hemorrhoids does not exist. The only option &ndash; a minimally invasive procedure. With their help, you will get a low-cost and rapid treatment of hemorrhoids &ndash; the prices of these procedures are low. However, many advanced cases surgery is the only curative treatment of the disease.</p>

<p>It should be noted also that the operation Longo is assigned only when an internal hemorrhoid. If you are running outside or combined hemorrhoids, then applied to eliminate the disease hemorrhoidectomy by Milligan-Morgan.</p>

<h2>Contra</h2>

<p>Advantage Longo operation is that it is practically no contraindications. It is quite easy to carry, even if the patient is suffering from a serious illness. With this method it is possible to eliminate even postpartum hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>As for the Milligan-Morgan, then to her, there are a range of contraindications. Among them are the following:</p>

<ul>
<li>HIV;</li>
<li>Crohn&rsquo;s Disease;</li>
<li>Pregnancy and lactation</li>
<li>Cancer;</li>
<li>The aggravation of chronic diseases;</li>
<li>Acute inflammation in the body.</li>
</ul>


<h2>How much is hemorrhoid surgery?</h2>

<p>Both methods require a certain investment, but the Milligan-Morgan different low cost, unlike the method Longo, since the latter requires expensive equipment surgeons.</p>

<p>The average price for an operation to remove hemorrhoids is:</p>

<ul>
<li>The method of Longo &ndash; the cost of surgery is about $ 1,200;</li>
<li>The method of Milligan-Morgan &ndash; 650 &ndash; $ 800</li>
</ul>


<h2>Complications</h2>

<p>As with any surgical procedure, surgery to treat hemorrhoids can be followed by subsequent complications. The most common complications</p>

<ul>
<li>Bleeding</li>
<li>Rectal and vaginal fistula</li>
<li>An infectious infestation of the affected tissues</li>
<li>An inflammatory process</li>
</ul>


<p>Doctors tend to avoid complications, and for which there is a post-operative hospital.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
