<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-01-08T20:15:09+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Belly Massage for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/belly-massage-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-08T11:18:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/belly-massage-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/belly-massage-for-weight-loss/img.jpg" title="WBelly massage for weight loss" alt="belly massage for weight loss at home"><strong>Massage</strong> - a method that has long been in service with the conventional medicine. It is approved by the Ministry of Health, and is used to treat a huge number of diseases. Of course, as an auxiliary method of therapy. Massage is used in virtually all areas of medicine. He is firmly entrenched in our lives, and probably in the world there is not one person who would never lay on a massage table.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>The effectiveness of massage</h2>

<p>The effectiveness of massage has long been proved. It can help you improve the condition of the patient, regardless of the disease, which he suffers. However, the inability of the placebo-controlled studies leaves some doubt as to the mechanism of its effects. Which factor plays the most important role: the psychological or physiological? What makes a person feel relieved: relaxation and faith in the healing power of massage or mechanical effect on the soft tissues of the body?</p>

<p>This question remains open for the time being. We are interested in, whether it is possible with the help of abdominal massage to lose at least a few kilograms? Agree, it would be great: no need to starve, no strain, just lie down on the table, belly up, and wait for someone skilled hands make short work of your fat. Is it possible? Let&rsquo;s deal.</p>

<p>All the effects of the massage can be divided into psychological and physiological. The first is certainly very useful, but are unlikely to have a specific and predictable effect on the weight of your body. Therefore, it makes no sense to consider them, go directly to the physiological. We will not engage in speculation, use a pseudo-data, for example, on energy currents - too. That&rsquo;s the impact on the human body has a significantly abdominal massage:</p>

<ul>
<li>Warms the skin due to emitted as a result of mechanical friction heat;</li>
<li>Stimulates the microcirculation of the skin by heating;</li>
<li>It stimulates the flow of lymph and venous blood due to mechanical compression of blood vessels;</li>
<li>Relaxes the muscles by mechanical action on them, as well as enhance blood flow.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Belly massage and weight loss</h2>

<p>Which of these mechanisms, in your opinion, can contribute to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>? Let&rsquo;s look at them all in turn.</p>

<p>Obviously, warm skin of the abdomen can not dissolve fat. It does not melt like wax, so the effect of massage is unlikely to reduce the weight of your body. Judge for yourself if the increase in skin temperature contribute to weight loss, for the acquisition of a slim figure you would rather stick a couple of yellow cards in the stomach, or heat it with an ordinary table lamp. From the sea, everything is back to not only rested, but also slim, because the fat left on the beach not only the stomach, but also from the entire body.</p>

<p>The skin temperature increases by touching hand massage, so the blood vessels dilate to give away excess heat. This is one of the mechanisms of thermoregulation, protects the body from overheating. Due to dilation of small blood vessels nutrition improves soft tissues, primarily the skin. Does this mean that fat belly will start to leave? No, otherwise all alcoholics with red faces would not wear belly in his hands, and would look more slender birch. Medicines from the group of proofreaders microcirculation, led by pentoxifylline, have themselves become popular drugs for weight loss.</p>

<p>This effect helps to eliminate stagnant lymph and venous blood. Thus, the massage display allows the liquid that has accumulated in the soft tissues. Perhaps it is this feature made people consider massage as a regular method of losing weight. <strong><em>Firstly</em></strong>, with the fluid leaves the body weight, that causes a person to believe that massage helped him to break down fat. <strong><em>Second</em></strong>, visually stomach becomes more flat. This is due to improvement of the skin and removal of liquid. <strong><em>Third</em></strong>, the possible reduction in waist circumference, again, due to the removal of edema.</p>

<p>At the young age of these effects may not occur at all, or to be mild, but after 40 years, when the body breaks down the balance of hormones, a change in metabolism, fluid accumulates more actively. Accordingly, massage is more effective way to reduce body weight. Of course, the effect of massage is very useful for the figure. But make no mistake, the fat remains in place, leaving only water.</p>

<p>Surprisingly, making the opposite action, a lot of people waiting to get on the output a result. Shaking the press, they are straining the abdominal muscles, hoping to lose weight. Visiting massage people relax the same muscle groups, waiting for an identical effect - weight loss. So what still needs to be done with the muscles? Perhaps, after all, cut, and as often as possible. If muscle relaxation accompanied by weight loss, people have lost weight during the holidays. To enhance the effect, he tried to muscle relaxants and antispasmodics - drugs that reduce muscle tone.</p>

<p>Lose weight with the help of belly massage can be in only one case: if you are doing it yourself. And preferably more than once per day. Massage takes away a lot of strength and energy, so you&rsquo;ll save calories, and with them - the extra weight. But lying on the table and making the masseur knead your stomach, you just get rid of the money that paid for his services. Of excess weight - is unlikely.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Should You Run? Benefits and Harms of Running]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/why-should-you-run-benefits-and-harms-of-running/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-08T11:05:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/why-should-you-run-benefits-and-harms-of-running</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/why-should-you-run-benefits-and-harms-of-running/img.jpg" title="Why should you run? Benefits and harms of running" alt="benefits and harms of running">Nowadays, an active and healthy lifestyle is often associated with running. That this exercise has the most popular, and throughout the world. Those who are older will remember the American trend of the 90s, according to which everyone had to run. Everyone is used to talk about the benefits of running, but no one really thinks about its pros and cons. All are accustomed to consider running a useful exercise, but the question is: why? - no answer. We will try to carry out a detailed analysis.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>First of all, it should be noted the current situation - a large part of the population leads a sedentary lifestyle, that they have observed an increased risk of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/vascular-disease/" title="cardiovascular disease">cardiovascular disease</a>. The argument at the time forced thousands of Americans to get out into the fresh air and to carry out various marathons. Even then began to celebrate the negative consequences of the long run. Look at the Champions marathon, do they look healthy people? Not at all. And it is a professional, not to mention the amateurs that morning wearing a pair of sneakers, running headlong, piously believing in <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> and the benefits of such action.</p>

<p>It was at that time running for the analysis came from many foreign sports institutions. It was found that the most rational way to engage in such aerobics is not more than thirty minutes 4-5 times a week. Less time will not produce the desired effect, as the fat storage will remain untouched, as the metabolic rate. At the same time, longer running session, the body perceives as <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a>, and not a positive one. The adrenal glands begin to secrete hormones in the emergency mode. Of course, the human body is designed for such loads, but your body can not withstand such conditions for a long time.</p>

<p>Speaking on the merits, it is one of the best basic exercises that makes working all the muscles of the body. All limbs are not fixed and do not have support, which in turn loads the muscles excellent stabilizers. But perhaps the biggest advantage of ease of implementation can be considered. Running is suitable for both beginners and advanced fitness.</p>

<p><strong>The general scheme of the positive factors of running is as follows:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Improvement of the cardiovascular system;</li>
<li>Saturation of oxygen (also leads to lipolysis);</li>
<li>Burning of a large number of calories;</li>
<li>Destruction of fat storage (with slow running and interval);</li>
<li>Strengthening the musculoskeletal system;</li>
<li>An increase in heat production, thereby burn fat.</li>
</ul>


<p>Among all the aerobic exercise jogging can &quot;boast&quot; the highest risk of injury. An illiterate training can quite undermine health. It is important to moderate the amount of load, a good rest, and regular exercise. Observance of these three factors in most cases will prevent overtraining and injuries.</p>

<p>It should be noted that when running load on all joints and bones of the person is increased 5-8 times - especially in obese second and third type. Any excess weight puts a ban on small jogging. Your feet are simply not ready for such a huge load. Mindlessly running can completely erase the patellar tendon, and the sport will have to forget. In addition to this common injury is a sprain or a dislocation of the ankle joint. As a rule, this is due to incorrect posture while running. Posture plays a key role, both in daily life and in sports. In terms of its lack of load balance collapses.</p>

<p>The saddest thing for us - women, is the fact that we are exposed to greater risk of injury than men. Nature endowed us a wider pelvis in order to fit it all the organs. As a result, changing the angle of the femur, whereby the knee joint when running gets practically doubled load.</p>

<p>Of course, running has lots of advantages. It is an indispensable exercise for both professionals and amateurs. In addition, it can be used for cardio sessions (intervals or slow), and for the development of strength endurance (short track speed). However, in the meantime, if you have a high percentage of body fat, you need to use this exercise with caution. We encourage you to quick step, since such a motion is not necessary to perform semi-jumping, and as a consequence there is no short-term use of one leg for support. This load sparing joints and bones, ie - It is more acceptable.</p>

<p>In general, feel free to use running, but do not forget to adjust it for yourself. Women tend to be employed in running and cardio training to maintain the overall tone, using a slow tempo or intervals.</p>

<p>It is imperative that the correct heating, ie - Warm-up. Perform stretching all muscle groups. Take this aspect of 5-10 minutes. Next, you need to warm up the muscles of the neck separately, as they are the most vulnerable spot on the body. Many girls while running quite actively rotate the head, eventually received various injuries. Follow the circular movements of the head and side bends. This will cause the blood to go to the scalene muscles, causing the neck to temporarily become stronger.</p>

<p>Running should start slowly, even if you use intervals. You need to provide the muscle gradually increasing the load. Even a car can not dart off in fifth gear. Everything happens in a timely manner. The same can be attributed to the person during the run. Quick Step is gradually transformed into a slow run, after 2-3 minutes the pace increases, etc. up to the level you require.</p>

<p>With regard to the position of the body, the torso should be slightly tilted forward. Back and head should be kept in line. Always follow the arching of the spine, the back should not be circular. The width of the steps depends on your individual characteristics, so that there is no general recommendations. During the run look only forward. Falling Down view discourages and does not allow to keep your back straight.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ginger for Weight Loss. Useful Properties of Ginger]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/ginger-for-weight-loss-useful-properties-of-ginger/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-08T08:58:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/ginger-for-weight-loss-useful-properties-of-ginger</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/ginger-for-weight-loss-useful-properties-of-ginger/img.jpg" title="Ginger for weight loss. Useful properties of ginger" alt="ginger for weight loss, eat ginger, how to prepare ginger for weight loss"><strong>Ginger</strong> - a tropical plant, it is not found in the wild and cultivated, and this requires certain climatic conditions.</p>

<p>Ginger has long been known and used as a spice. However, rich chemical composition makes it possible to use it for medicinal purposes. In folk medicine, ginger is used for the prevention and treatment of many diseases.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>The composition of ginger</h2>

<p>The chemical composition of ginger more than four connections. Therefore, its taste and aroma of the originals, and biological properties of the manifold.</p>

<p>Key elements are part of ginger:</p>

<ul>
<li>Fatty acids - caprylic, linoleic acid, oleic acid;</li>
<li>Vitamin C, B1, B2, fat-soluble vitamin A;</li>
<li>Salts of magnesium, silicon, phosphorus, iron, calcium, sodium, potassium, zinc and germanium;</li>
<li>Asparagine, which is part of many proteins;</li>
<li>Gingerol, which gives the hot taste of ginger, improves intestinal motility, reduces nausea</li>
<li>Antihistamines (<a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/allergology/allergy.html" title="allergy">allergy</a>) of the substance;</li>
<li>Essential <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids/" title="amino acids">amino acids</a> - lysine, phenylalanine, threonine, tryptophan, methionine. Essential amino acids are important for normal metabolism, including for the exchange of fat, so the ginger root is used in <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> diets.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Action ginger on the body</h2>

<ul>
<li>Normalizes metabolism;</li>
<li>Improves <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a>, stimulates the production of gastric juice;</li>
<li>It has a choleretic effect;</li>
<li>It improves digestion of proteins;</li>
<li>Activates the splitting and removing fat from the body;</li>
<li>Stimulates the thyroid hormones that are important in metabolism;</li>
<li>Enhances the antitoxic function of the liver;</li>
<li>Diuretic effect (peel ginger root);</li>
<li>Mild laxative effect, which is also important for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="slimming">slimming</a>, especially in patients suffering from <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/constipation.html" title="constipation">constipation</a>;</li>
<li>Displays and neutralizes the toxins and bad digested products of digestion. Ginger cleanses the body from all kinds of toxins: alcohol, food, chemical and radiation.</li>
</ul>


<p>Thus, the main purpose of ginger - stimulate the digestive process and neutralize dietary toxins.</p>

<p>Due to the fact that the use of ginger in food accelerates the metabolism, it is widely used as a means for weight loss in violation of lipid metabolism. By drinking ginger reduces body fat in the abdominal area.</p>

<p>In addition, it has anti-inflammatory, antibacterial, antifungal properties and is used in the fight against diseases of the upper respiratory tract and the common cold in the autumn-winter period.</p>

<p>Being a good immunomodulator, ginger is used for the prevention of many diseases.</p>

<h2>Ginger slimming</h2>

<p>It is noticed that ginger tea - the best way to fight <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>.</p>

<p>You will find many recipes and tea-based beverages ginger root. They differ in the number of ginger per liter of water and, accordingly, the concentration of the solution. Drink too pungent taste, can cause discomfort in the stomach, so you need to choose the most suitable for you in taste.</p>

<h3>Several applications of ginger to lose weight</h3>

<p>It should take 1-2 tablespoons fresh ginger, grated on a fine grater, 2 liters of boiling water and infuse for about 2 hours. The drink is cooled add 60 ml of lemon juice and honey (if desired). Drink need to drink during the day. If you have never used the ginger and do not know the body&rsquo;s reaction to it, then start to drink half a glass and drink limit to 1 liter. Thereafter, the dosage is increased up to the glass, and the amount of consumed beverage ginger to 2 liters per day. Take a drink should be 30 minutes. before meals.</p>

<p>A similar drink can be prepared and insist in a thermos and take hot, which is very nice in the winter season. Lemon and honey are added immediately before use.</p>

<p>To enhance the metabolic process and therefore increase the effect of weight reduction is recommended to use a combination of ginger and garlic for cooking beverage. Take 1 tablespoon grated ginger and finely chopped garlic 2 liters of warm water. Infuse, strain and take to eating 0.5 cups. Precautions should be taken to persons suffering from <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/gastritis.html" title="gastritis">gastritis</a> or <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/diagnosis-of-peptic-ulcer-disease.html" title="peptic ulcer">peptic ulcer</a>. Burning drink can irritate and cause <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/heartburn.html" title="heartburn">heartburn</a> and aggravation of the disease.</p>

<p>Ginger to lose weight can be taken as a part of herbal teas. Such additives can serve as a sheet of strawberries and cranberries, which have a diuretic effect. Mint and Melissa help reduce appetite, and orange and lemon drink in combination with ginger root accelerate metabolism. At 0.5 liters of boiling water take 0.5 tablespoons of minced ginger, 1 tablespoon of peppermint leaves and a pinch of cardamom. Currently 30 min., Filter and enter into the drink freshly squeezed lemon juice and orange 60 ml. Before use, you can add honey to your liking. As is known, cardamom helps the good work of the intestine, diuretic.</p>

<p>In addition, ginger to lose weight should be added fresh to salads, first and second courses. The food is better absorbed with ginger and takes a sharp, spicy flavor. Ginger promotes better digestion of proteins, so is used as a seasoning for meat and fish. Of course, the effect will be greater if ginger not passed the heat treatment. Good results are marked weight loss, if you replace one meal a low-calorie salad of celery and ginger.</p>

<p>If you are well tolerated and did not appear ginger pain in the stomach, you can just chew fresh ginger root during the day between meals.</p>

<p>Thus, if the ginger all year round will be present at your table, and you use it regularly, throughout the year, you can lose up to 10 kg of excess weight. Of course, this must also comply with the general recommendations for dieters. One ginger you this will not help.</p>

<p>Before the start of the regular use of ginger in food need to be aware of contraindications to its use. <strong>These are</strong>:</p>

<ul>
<li>Gastric ulcer and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/peptic-ulcer-of-the-stomach-and-duodenum.html" title="duodenal ulcer">duodenal ulcer</a>;</li>
<li>Diverticula of the esophagus and intestines;</li>
<li>Stones in the kidneys and the bladder;</li>
<li>Nonspecific <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/ulcerative-colitis.html" title="ulcerative colitis">ulcerative colitis</a>;</li>
<li>Pregnancy and lactation.</li>
</ul>


<p>There are some caveats with the combined use of ginger and certain medications. So, welcome ginger reduces the effect of nitrates and calcium channel blockers, prescribed for coronary <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/cardiology/heart-disease.html" title="heart disease">heart disease</a>. In this connection, it may cause <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/pain-in-the-chest.html" title="chest pain">chest pain</a>, despite taking medication. For the same reasons, should be used with caution in <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/cardiology/hypertension.html" title="hypertension">hypertension</a> ginger, in the case of the appointment of calcium channel blockers and beta-adrenergic blockers for the treatment of the underlying disease.</p>

<p>Ginger enhances the effect of anticoagulants (anticoagulants), and because he has the ability to reduce blood clotting, there is a risk of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/injuries-and-accidents/bleeding.html" title="bleeding">bleeding</a> when taken with anticoagulants.</p>

<p>In case of overdose of ginger possible side effects - nausea, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/diarrhea.html" title="diarrhea">diarrhea</a>, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/vomiting.html" title="vomiting">vomiting</a>, allergic reactions. If there is at least one of the side effects is an urgent need to stop the use of spices.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing a Anti Stretch Marks Cream After Giving Birth]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-06T11:50:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/img.jpg" width="250" title="Choosing a cream for stretch marks after giving birth" alt="anti stretch mark cream, stretch marks, choose, pregnancy, childbirth, anti stretch cream">Congratulations! You became my mother and one of the most difficult stage of your life - pregnancy - over. Unfortunately, stretch marks on the body remained. We advise you not to delay and as soon as possible to remove them.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Of course, now difficult times - in the hands of your newborn, you&rsquo;re tired, exhausted, and now need to find the time and energy to fight stretch marks.</p>

<p>Not all that bad. In fact, all it did not take much of your time. In general, you should not take this as a &quot;war&quot; against stretch marks. The procedures can be used as the rare moments of relaxation when you are busy only themselves. This is a great opportunity to catch your breath in the hectic first few months after <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/childbirth.html" title="childbirth">childbirth</a>.</p>

<p>Well, if during <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a> you have followed our advice and engaged in the prevention of stretch marks. But even if they could not avoid, get rid of them after delivery possible.</p>

<p>Of course, the list of steps for the elimination of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/best-stretch-marks-creams-for-pregnant-women-how-to-choose-a-popular-brand/" title="stretch marks">stretch marks</a> is not limited by the choice of the best anti stretch mark cream. But in other ways to get rid of them you can find in other sections of the site! Now we will focus on how to choose the right cream for stretch marks after giving birth.</p>

<h2>How to choose a best anti stretch marks creams</h2>

<p>Let us examine what requirements need regulations for stretch marks which you intend to use after pregnancy. There is enough pitfalls.</p>

<p>Firstly, if you are breast-feeding a baby, and stretch marks have appeared in this area, the cream should be safe for a newborn. And it must be harmless both in body contact and do not cause allergies in children who drink milk mom.</p>

<p>For the same reason, most likely, will not work with a strong and cream (or) a pungent odor. Therefore, selecting the best anti stretch mark cream, first find out whether it is hypoallergenic and does not have a strong flavor.</p>

<p>Best of all, even without purchasing the anti stretch mark creams, to hold the sample. Find a store where there is the presence of probes. Well if they give out for free, but in a pinch, and you can buy. Much offensive would happen if you chose an expensive means of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/allergology/allergy.html" title="allergy">allergy</a>. Spread the anti stretch mark cream on the skin site. If during the day is no allergic reaction has not appeared - that this cream is safe for you.</p>

<p>The next item - the cream should be suitable for the time of use. There are anti stretch mark creams that can be used immediately after birth. And there are those that are recommended to apply to the skin a few months after birth. Note that. Mix funds. Start with one that is safe to use immediately after birth and go on a more serious money later. Of course it would be better if the cream will be the same make and brand.</p>

<p>Choose a cream for a specific type of stretch marks. If you have any stretch marks on thighs, do not try to eliminate them with a cream designed to combat stretch marks on the abdomen. Pay attention to the fact against any problem areas focused cream.</p>

<p>If you have stretch marks in several places, each zone may need your vehicle. In this case, too, it is desirable to use products of one brand.</p>

<h2>Deciphering the composition cream</h2>

<p>And now try to understand the composition of selected tools and understand the role played by each of the components. And that should be present in a good anti stretch marks creams.</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>Retinol.</strong> This ingredient has to be in each of the anti stretch marks cream after giving birth. It is responsible for the regeneration and constant hydration of your skin.</li>
<li><strong>Collagen and elastin.</strong> Protein molecules directly responsible for the elasticity of the skin and its renewal. That decrease in their development as a result of hormonal changes and often leads to stretch marks.</li>
<li><strong>Jojoba oil and Shea.</strong> These two components significantly improves blood circulation in the skin. They can be found in almost any means of best anti stretch marks or cellulite cream.</li>
<li><strong>Essential oils.</strong> Various different oils for the skin, but they improve the total weight of the metabolism in the skin and increase the elasticity.</li>
<li><strong>Vitamins and <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids/" title="amino acids">amino acids</a>.</strong> Prerequisites that feed the skin and promote the rapid regeneration.</li>
</ul>


<p>List of different means of stretching with reviews, features description, composition and other important data can be found in the section Means against stretch marks.</p>

<h2>How to use a anti stretch marks cream</h2>

<p>A few tips on proper use of anti stretch mark cream.</p>

<p>Firstly, the cream should be applied to clean and dry skin. If you take a shower or bath, before it should be carefully wipe. In general, the adoption of water treatments (eg, contrast shower) before applying the best anti stretch mark creams after giving birth, if not necessary, it is desirable.</p>

<p>Typically, the cream is applied twice a day - morning and evening. The second time the application is best to plan before you go to bed.</p>

<p>Third, just before rubbing, the skin is better &quot;warm&quot; light massage. This promotes better wicking agent components and increases their efficacy.</p>

<p>The cream is applied in a circular massage until completely absorbed.</p>

<h2>Additional ways to deal with stretch marks</h2>

<p>As we wrote above, other ways of dealing with stretch marks after giving birth you can find in the relevant sections of the site. Yet, briefly enumerate what other steps to take if you seriously want to get rid of stretch marks after pregnancy.</p>

<p>Massage areas with stretch marks. This procedure is best done using a chosen using the tips in this article means.</p>

<p>Contrast showers and swimming. This practice is great affect on the skin. It helps strengthen blood circulation in the subcutaneous tissue and make the skin more elastic.</p>

<p>Physical exercises. One of the main ways to get rid of stretch marks. Exercising helps your muscles to keep the skin toned and helps to regenerate tissue in it.</p>

<p>The use of essential oils as a massage, and special baths. We have a special article on the application of essential oils pregnant. It must be remembered that this method has contraindications.</p>

<p>To consume the necessary amount of water. Often, problems with the skin and the appearance of stretch marks due to the low water content in the body. The skin becomes more fragile and prone to damage. And most importantly - the water out of the body and subcutaneous tissue hazardous substances.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fitness During Menstruation]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/fitness-during-menstruation/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-06T11:10:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/fitness-during-menstruation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/fitness-during-menstruation/fitness-during-menstruation.jpg" title="fitness, sports, training, yoga during menstruation" alt="Fitness during menstruation">On this point there are different opinions. Most people do not accept the &quot;intermediate&quot; options are the supporters of a categorical &quot;no&quot; or &quot;yes&quot;. The first show that during <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="menstruation">menstruation</a> sports is clearly prohibited, because &quot;these days, even on the physical education free&quot;, while the latter argue that the first - a &quot;freeloader&quot; who are too sorry for yourself and make excuses for their laziness. Ostensibly, they simply do not want to once again rise to the sofa and go to the gym or to the stadium&hellip; <!--more-->In general, the two positions are not supported by any reasonable arguments and certainties - the emotions and own assumptions. Well, we look at how really things, and whether monthly about the &quot;hang&quot; of workouts.</p>

<h2>What is menstruation?</h2>

<p>Menstruation - a rejection of the uterine mucosa, which occurs under the influence of hormones. The presence of menstruation - is one of the main signs of &quot;consistency&quot; of the female body.</p>

<p>Each month the uterus prepares for the possible implantation of the embryo, in other words, to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a>. Therefore, it is the mucous membrane (endometrium) grows gradually, becoming more &quot;thick&quot;, it increases the number of vessels. This is necessary in order to ensure that the embryo expected a decent supply of nutrients.</p>

<p>About a week after ovulation (egg release from the ovaries), which accounts for about 10-14 day cycle, the state of the mucous optimal for the development of the ovum. It is 5-6 mm layer of well-perfused epithelial cells.</p>

<p>If pregnancy does not occur, the endometrium thickens. In the end, it becomes a cell so much that the uterine vessels simply lose their ability to feed. Therefore mucous is rejected; The &quot;bursting&quot; vessels, and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/injuries-and-accidents/bleeding.html" title="bleeding">bleeding</a> occurs. Actually, this is menstruation.</p>

<p>Description of the process looks pretty grim and unpleasant, but the first day of the monthly body again &quot;taken up the old&quot; and again starts optimistically preparing for a possible pregnancy. Run active processes of regeneration (recovery), and monthly stop.</p>

<p>All cyclic changes run hormones at the beginning of the cycle (about 2 weeks from the first day of menstruation) in the body increases the content of estrogen in the second half increased levels of progesterone. The fact that all this means - below.</p>

<h2>What happens in the body during menstruation and how it is reflected in the athletic achievements?</h2>

<p>So, during menstruation a woman&rsquo;s body is going through a fairly large-scale changes, which is accompanied by changes in health and response to exercise.</p>

<p><strong><em>Hormonal storm.</em></strong> High blood levels of progesterone is replaced by increase of estrogen levels. Progesterone causes accumulation of fluid in the body, it improves the extensibility of tissue. However, against the background of its high content of muscle relaxation occurs, thereby reducing the physical strength and endurance. For this reason, in the first 1-2 days monthly until little estrogen and progesterone much sprinting and power load perceived by women worse than usual. But stretching exercises, on the contrary, a better work out.</p>

<p>3-4 day weakness caused by hormonal storm reduced. Estrogens are growing, and they are - a kind of hormones, anabolic steroids.</p>

<p><strong><em>Blood loss.</em></strong> Almost all Internet resources assert that during menstruation is a loss of blood, so the woman is reduced hemoglobin levels, which means that tissues receive less oxygen. On this basis, some advise to give up loads or doing gymnastics on the type of &quot;two imbedded - three cotton&quot;.</p>

<p>However, this is not entirely correct. First, the female body is genetically adapted to blood loss. If you&rsquo;ve ever been on blood collection points, then we saw that among donors to faint after giving blood fall mostly men. Second, the blood loss is not as great as it seems. On average, it is 80-100 ml for all time periods. For the body is almost invisible, and hemoglobin almost not reflected.</p>

<p>Another thing, if a woman or heavy menstruation, especially violations of the cycle in which the menstrual period is prolonged. There really need to spare yourself. But in other cases, if the load is well tolerated, it is not a necessity.</p>

<p><strong><em>Bad feeling.</em></strong> Someone feels absolutely adequate at any day of the cycle, but for someone periods become almost a tragedy. Hormonal changes, certain features of the body and the presence of so-called oligomenorrhea (painful menstruation) can provide an unforgettable woman &quot;critical days&quot;.</p>

<p>Some of the girls during the time of menstruation (stronger in the early days) complain of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/neurology/headache.html" title="headache">headaches</a>, nausea, bad mood, severe pain in the abdomen, weakness, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/neurology/dizziness.html" title="dizziness">dizziness</a>. Is all this a contraindication to physical exercise? Of course, yes. If you feel unwell training for the benefit will not go and will only torment.</p>

<p>We hope that the content of the previous section, you realize that there is no single answer, to determine the sports activities during menstruation should be individually.</p>

<p>A woman can not carry the load, or need to schedule them gently if they are accompanied by <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/abdominal-pain.html" title="abdominal pain">abdominal pain</a> and general poor health.</p>

<p>In other cases, you can engage in moderate-intensity workouts, nothing terrible will happen. Professional athletes are never asked to release them from employment and competition if they have the &quot;wrong&quot; days. And nothing&hellip;</p>

<p>Another important point. Many online resources contain information that during menstruation can not practice the exercises on the abs, as it can increase bleeding and abdominal discomfort. If in your case, they are accompanied by &quot;side effects&quot;, they are really better to take time off.</p>

<p>But we would advise you to exercise more to fear on the buttocks and thighs. The fact that the rear of the hip muscles are indirectly connected with the ligaments of the fallopian tubes. Therefore, active walking, running, leads the feet back, deep squat tube tightened and that &quot;disturbs&quot; the uterus and can cause the appearance of spastic abdominal pain and increased bleeding.</p>

<p>Let&rsquo;s hope this post has helped you answer the question: &quot;Can I play sports during menstruation?&quot; Adequately plan the schedule of sports activities, listen to their feelings during and after workouts, choose the &quot;right&quot; exercise, and menstruation does not prevent you keep yourself in the form and lead an active life.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[For What Needed Amino Acids?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-06T10:55:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/for-what-needed-amino-acids/img.jpg" title="For what needed amino acids?" alt="amino acids, how to make amino acids, amino acids for weight loss, essential amino acids, amino acids for muscle growth, what are amino acids">Amino acids - are chemical compounds that comprise proteins. When the human digestive tract gets protein foods, using special enzymes, it is split into amino acids. Only then it can be assimilated. Small-sized molecules penetrate the amino acids from the intestine into the blood, and then the body can use them for their own purposes.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Amino acids perform many important functions in the body. They can be divided into plastic and energy. Plastic functions are built from amino acids of the protein molecules that make up all the tissues of our body. Because amino acids are not only bodies, but also biologically active substances: enzymes, certain hormones, neurotransmitters. The energy function is the splitting of the amino acids in order to release energy.</p>

<p>To maintain human life he needed only 20 species of amino acids, although they exist in nature much more. They are divided into three groups:</p>

<ul>
<li>Interchangeable - can be synthesized in the body from chemical compounds having a non-protein origin;</li>
<li>Conditionally replaceable - are synthesized in a limited number;</li>
<li>Essential - are not synthesized in the body.</li>
</ul>


<p>Man receives daily amino acids from food. Most of them are found in meat, fish, eggs, milk and other animal products. The richest vegetable source of protein is soy and other legumes, but they contain less essential amino acids.</p>

<h2>What are amino acids common man?</h2>

<p>Everyone needs amino acids. None of these chemical compounds, we can not synthesize protein. If the amino acids are no longer come from the outside, the body begins to break down its own tissues and organs, to compensate for their deficits. The absence of even one essential amino acid in the human diet leads to severe disease.</p>

<p>The source of these materials were previously only foods. Today amino acids produced by many pharmaceutical companies as supplements or drugs. Some of them are designed for the treatment of certain diseases, others are used by athletes to build muscle. With the purpose of treatment of amino acids into the reception - this is an expensive and inefficient pleasure.</p>

<p>There are many medications on the basis of amino acids, which are used for parenteral nutrition patients. If a person can not eat food alone, he poured the amino acid solutions intravenously. Often because of these drugs the doctors save patient lives, as in the period of severe illness when the body&rsquo;s plastic processes are active, the body needs protein more than usual.</p>

<h2>What are amino acids during training?</h2>

<p>Most athletes who are engaged in bodybuilding, taking protein powders. They use it as an additional source of protein to build muscle mass quickly. Alternatively the protein amino acid solutions are applied. Pharmaceutical companies argue that they are more effective than the protein obtained from food as well as familiar to most athletes protein powders.</p>

<p>True or not? Most companies that produce amino acids for athletes, convince us of the veracity of this information. But their interest is obvious: the amino acids of the protein are much more expensive, so bring more income from sales. For the successful promotion of the product on the market was invented so-called &quot;protein window&quot; or &quot;protein corridor&quot;.</p>

<p>&quot;Protein box&quot; - a period of time after the workout, which is considered optimal for protein <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a>. It is 40-50 minutes. During this period the athlete should learn the most protein to gain muscle growth. If the late bodybuilder, muscles will grow more slowly. But the protein from foods like protein powders, slowly digested, so the athlete has only one chance to catch up to the closing &quot;window of protein&quot;. To do this, take the amino acid solution.</p>

<p>Unlike the protein, amino acids absorbed from the intestine immediately without pretreatment with proteolytic enzymes. Their concentration in the blood rises sharply after 15-20 minutes after taking the supplements. Thus, a person has time to deliver the amino acids in muscle, while &quot;protein window&quot; remains open.</p>

<p>It is quite logical to study the benefits of amino acids in protein loved athletes. Very often in the specialized literature for bodybuilders can find information about the &quot;protein window&quot;. But studies have shown that intake of protein and amino acids provides identical results athletes during training. &quot;Protein window&quot; hardly exists, although the myth about him still wanders from book to book, stimulating the sale of free amino acids.</p>

<p>BCAA - three amino acids, most commonly used in the training. These include isoleucine, valine and leucine. It is these amino acids are part of the majority of sports supplements for bodybuilders. The main effects of BCAA:</p>

<ul>
<li>The accelerated build-up of muscle mass;</li>
<li>Increasing strength athlete;</li>
<li>Reduction of body fat mass.</li>
</ul>


<p>There is no doubt the benefits of BCAA bodybuilder. With them he will reach sports results. They are rapidly absorbed and have high bioavailability, are easy to use. But the lack of supplements based on amino acids BCAA is the price. They are expensive, but a similar result can be obtained by an athlete using whey protein.</p>

<p>Amino BCAA available in different dosage forms. There capsules and solutions, but less likely to take the supplement in powder form. It is recognized that the powder is less convenient to use: it is poorly soluble in the liquid and has a bitter taste. Ready amino acid solutions are tastier, more convenient to use and transport, but are more expensive.</p>

<p>Take BCAA recommended 1 teaspoon (4-5 grams), from 1 to 3 times a day. Amino acids are allowed to be combined with any other sports nutrition. Of course, it makes no sense to take them together with protein, since these additives have the same mechanism of action, although some people do it to save money.</p>

<p>Amino acids - are chemical substances, of which built all the proteins in our body. A person must receive them regularly with food to stay healthy. Athletes who are building up the muscles need additional source of amino acids. Especially important for them leucine, valine, isoleucine, which are abbreviated as BCAA. Supplements containing amino acids, convenient to use and easily digested. However, they are expensive, so as a source of amino acids most athletes use a cheaper but equally effective protein powder.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Lose Weight at Home?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-05T08:48:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/img.jpg" title="rapid weight loss, how to lose weight fast at home, rope, exercise for weight loss and press" alt="How to lose weight at home?">It&rsquo;s not a secret that proper healthy diet is essential for maintaining the health and control their weight. To overcome the overweight should be, above all, to overcome their bad eating habits, such as overeating, eating before going to sleep, irregular eating, eating unhealthy foods. Remember that the stomach - a hollow muscular organ that easily expands as binge eating, and later - in the normal diet in order to achieve a sense of saturation required to eat large amounts of food, because the stomach is already &quot;accustomed&quot; to be stretched. Consumption while healthy but high-calorie foods in quantities exceeding the energy intake necessary for you daily energy requirement, a sedentary lifestyle, low physical activity also contribute to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>. Therefore, to maintain a slim figure of the ideal need to eat regularly and properly balanced, and exercise more.</p>

<!--more-->


<p><strong>Willpower and mood of success</strong> - your first allies in the difficult task to lose weight. There should be a clear desire to get rid of the extra kilos. Do not give up until you shake the ill-fated arrow on the mechanical balance in the smaller side, or until crawl down the numbers on the display of electronic scales.</p>

<p><strong>Learn to say a firm &quot;no&quot; to temptation</strong> and fast food, but, unfortunately, bad nutrition. Before you succumb to the temptation to buy a pizza, sugary sodas, delicious fries, a double burger with cheese or soft flour cakes, bathed in chocolate - think about the number of calories that are contained in them and imagine how they will be stored in the fat folds of your limp body.</p>

<p>Eat <strong>more foods with dietary fiber</strong>. They give food volume contribute to the rapid filling of the stomach and thus less food will cause a feeling of fullness in the brain. In addition, dietary fiber contribute to the removal of toxic products of metabolism from the gut, serve as a substrate for the intestinal flora, stool form, in part serve as prevention of unpleasant intestinal conditions like <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/constipation.html" title="constipation">constipation</a> and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/diarrhea.html" title="diarrhea">diarrhea</a>. Where to contain dietary fiber? Vegetables, fruits, bran, cereals, wholemeal bread. All of these products can and should be consumed in large quantities under the emergency measures for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> at home.</p>

<p>Wash consumed foods. <strong>Drink plenty of fluids</strong>, because the water speeds up metabolism and promotes breeding and disposal of harmful metabolic products in the urine, feces, evaporation through the surface of the skin (sweating) and lungs. Drinking water reduces hunger and helps <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a>. Remember that an adequate daily fluid intake is the key to the proper functioning of the internal organs of the human body, especially the liver.</p>

<p>Part of the daily routine should be a morning <strong>exercise, stretching, exercises with weights</strong>, and better training on a stationary bike or treadmill - on any simulator that you can install at home. It would be even better to regularly engage in gyms, make daily walks and engage in a variety of active sports.</p>

<p>Remember that any kind of mental pressure lead to the emergence of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a> and even <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/depression.html" title="depression">depression</a>. Stress, in turn, can lead to <strong>emotional overeating</strong>. So try not to be nervous, overexcited and do not take to heart the negative attitudes of other individuals. A good practice would be breathing exercises, such as, for example, deep breaths, different meditation technique, oriental health exercises. Do not forget about the rest. Remember that proper rest (not a computer screen) currently has therapeutic effects on the body. The same applies to bed. You must sleep at least 7 hours a day.</p>

<p>What else can be done at home for a successful weight loss? Remember that <strong>you need not only eat well, but also regularly</strong>. Eat 5 times a day in small portions, rather than 2-3 times larger. Perfect breakfast should be low calorie, low fat and high content of dietary fiber. For lunch, eat anything, the main thing that it was useful and tasty (do not forget to enjoy a healthy meal). Do not wait with dinner. The evening meal should be completed in 2-3 hours before bedtime. Do not forget that the number of calories consumed can be reduced by increasing the content of fruits and vegetables in the diet, but they also contain large amounts of vitamins and minerals.</p>

<p>So remember that your daily energy expenditure in the <strong>form of exercise</strong> must exceed the consumption of food in terms of kilocalories contained therein. Unfortunately, however, the intensity of modern life does not always give us the opportunity to be engaged enough in gyms, leisure or sports outside the home, so why do not we engage in more physical activity where we spend about half of my life - that is the house? But in any case, do not take physical exercise as a burden his duties enthusiastically approach to employment, involve family members, including your favorite TV channel or the necessary music. And finally, here are 9 public exercises which you can do at home without having to buy special equipment or equipment:</p>

<ul>
<li><em>Walks around the house (walking):</em> This is the best kind of exercise, you generally do not need to do this only functioning legs. However, if you live in a cramped home, or if the weather is really very good, you can take the opportunity to walking on the street. Necessarily involve your home for this event. Even banal raising and lowering the stairs leading to tone your muscles.</li>
<li><em>Jumping rope:</em> it is itself energy-intensive way of exercise and an occasion for pleasant childhood memories of girls.</li>
<li><em>Ups:</em> Although this type of exercise is given quite difficult, many people prefer push-ups, because they are well trained muscles in the arms and shoulders.</li>
<li><em>Lifting legs:</em> the perfect exercise to strengthen the muscles of the lower extremities and abdomen. For best results, you want to raise the straight legs, but if you feel that it is very difficult, it is possible to bend them a little.</li>
<li><em>Lift the body to the knees from a prone position on the back:</em> This type of exercise is essential for abdominal exercise. Down with flabby abdominal wall with large accumulations of fat! Long live the &quot;cubes&quot;! Cheers &quot;cubes&quot;! By the way, &quot;blocks&quot; are formed by constrictions tendon rectus abdominis muscle, so you need to train this muscle. Just remember that the cubes can be seen when the fat content in the body is about 10% lower.</li>
<li><em>Sports running:</em> very good exercise to train the cardiovascular and respiratory systems, as well as to optimize the consumption of calories. Everyone can jogging or even brisk walking, while listening to the radio, music or just enjoying nature. The only thing you need - a couple of good shoes, and, of course, a strong belief in getting rid of unnecessary kilograms.</li>
<li><em>Squat:</em> have a striking impact on glutes and leg muscles. Even better would be if you crouch not alone, but in company with two charming brunette - dumbbells and Rosa Clara.</li>
<li><em>Weightlifting:</em> if you are a girl and did not want to spend money to buy glamorous dumbbell, you can start to lift weights that are easy to get at home - a laptop man, iron, grown fat cat, two-liter bottle of Coca-Cola (stop, people dumping kilograms, there should be no sugary sodas in the fridge) and large capacity air-conditioned for the washing machine (it is convenient to do just to lift).</li>
<li><em>Dance:</em> yes, dance - it is also an interesting exercise. They increase the speed of your metabolism and give a sense of overall satisfaction.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gone Month After Weight Loss. How to Restore the Month Following the Diet?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-05T08:35:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/menstruation-after-weight-loss/img.jpg" title="title" alt="alt">This problem is very common among girls, too much carried away by losing weight. Heavy training in the gym, wasting the minimum calorie diet, unbalanced power - all this, acting together, can disrupt the hormonal balance of the female body and lead to amenorrhea - the cessation of menstruation. Their absence is a sign of serious damage to health and can cause other, more terrible consequences. So, if the problem you have encountered, you should take as soon as possible for its decision.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The normal termination of a woman&rsquo;s menstruation should occur only in 45-55 years, when she, because of age, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/menopause.html" title="menopause">menopause</a>. In younger years cycle disorders are a symptom of a more or less serious violations.</p>

<p>Some girls are easy enough to react to the fact that <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/body-wraps-for-weight-loss-belly/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> after they begin the long delays or even complete absence of menstruation. This is probably due to all the well-known myth, if sportswomen month did not happen. However, in reality, only to suffer a similar professional athletes, usually engaged in power sports, and often taking specific means to improve their physical condition, such as steroids. At the same time, they make a conscious choice between sports achievements and his health - in favor of the first, as you may have guessed.</p>

<p>You do not engage in professional sports, but just decided to lose a few pounds, so you should not be like this. Maybe for you, even absence of menstruation seems convenient, but keep in mind that it is able to do a lot of damage to health.</p>

<p>If you are a long time did not receive a sufficient amount of food nutrients, it could contribute to the emergence of anemia, disturbance of the production of sex hormones, changes in metabolism, resulting in a disruption of the normal functioning of the ovaries. At first it is fixable, but then atrophy and other changes in the reproductive system are becoming more stable and may even be irreversible.</p>

<p>Significantly it is not proved, but experts believe that, given the long absence of menstruation due to weight loss, women may develop complications. Moreover, their appearance is possible even if the cycle is still possible to recover. In particular, the likelihood of complications include dishormonal disorders: dysfunctional uterine <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/injuries-and-accidents/bleeding.html" title="bleeding">bleeding</a>, the development of hormone-dependent benign tumors, polycystic ovaries, and cysts. Ultimately, in particularly serious cases, this can lead to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/infertility.html" title="infertility">infertility</a>.</p>

<p>The key point for safe weight loss - it is a slow or moderate speed weight loss. If you are struggling to the results &quot;minus 30 kg per month&quot;, and ready for this fast and torturing your body unbearable load it one way or another will have an effect: someone - a stomach ulcer, someone - violations of the cycle.</p>

<p>The second rule, which will save you from the problems of women&rsquo;s health - is striving for a balanced diet, even against the background diet. In particular, you even in small amounts, but should eat fat-containing animal products, because it is based on <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a>, which you are so afraid, are built molecule hormones. This does not mean that you can not use a mono-diet, or fat-free diet, simply by practice over several days rather than months in a row.</p>

<h2>What should I do to restore menstruation?</h2>

<p>Take action, and fast. Of course, the emergence of amenorrhea on the background of weight loss does not require as much emergency treatment to the doctor, as a traumatic brain injury, or other medical emergency, but to think you should not spend more than a week.</p>

<p>It is desirable to bring to the solution of the problem of a specialist. If you do not understand, which is why it&rsquo;s happened, he will explain the reason for cessation of menstruation, to recommend changes in diet and prescribe drugs for the treatment. It will be hormonal. Do not be afraid of what you prescribe them because now they are needed. Artificial hormones entering the body, will lead to the cyclic operation of the reproductive organs and quickly restore cycle. In a few months you will be able to give them up.</p>

<p>You can also simultaneously - not as a basis, in the form of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/aids.html" title="aids">aids</a>! - To use national treatment. As the herbs that have a positive impact on women&rsquo;s health are known upland uterus, lovage, chamomile, parsley. Their decoctions and infusions is also possible to use if you do not have contraindications to herbal medicine, in particular <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/allergology/allergy.html" title="allergy">allergy</a> to grass.</p>

<p>So, if on the background of intensive weight loss you have gone monthly, restore them as soon as possible. Doing this is through a combination of good nutrition, medication, prescribed by a physician, and, if desired, the use of aids. Even if you have not yet reached their ultimate goal in losing weight, you better time to interrupt this process and pay attention to their health. Let this situation will give you some lessons and will help you understand that you can not scoff at his body with impunity. Hopefully, you will restore your health, and in the future, you will not be so foolish to strive for weight loss.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Stretch Marks Creams for Pregnant Women, How to Choose a Popular Brand]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/best-stretch-marks-creams-for-pregnant-women-how-to-choose-a-popular-brand/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-05T07:37:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/best-stretch-marks-creams-for-pregnant-women-how-to-choose-a-popular-brand</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/best-stretch-marks-creams-for-pregnant-women-how-to-choose-a-popular-brand/img.jpg" title="best stretch mark cream" alt="Best stretch marks creams for pregnant women, how to choose a popular brand">During childbearing in women on hormone levels occur huge change. That&rsquo;s when most women appear stretch marks or striae. For the prevention or reduction of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/" title="symptoms">symptoms</a>, there are special funds. However, during <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a> the body&rsquo;s response to this kind of money may not be predictable. Therefore, best stretch marks cream for pregnant women should be not only effective, but do not pose a threat to the health of women and baby.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Almost every woman during pregnancy ponder over the question of the prevention of stretch marks, because in this period, in the body there is a substantial restructuring. In addition to hormonal factors on the occurrence of stretch marks is largely influenced by genetic predisposition. Even if you have good genetics, neglected preventive measures is still not worth it. The whole point is that so if there were striae, eliminate them would be virtually impossible. In addition, they can not be tan, and many regarded as a skin defect. To prevent the appearance of stretch marks during pregnancy, or at least reduce the risk of their occurrence, there are various creams with special moisturizing ingredients and nutrients.</p>

<p>As part of an best cream for stretch marks should be present retinol, it is an excellent moisturizer the epidermis, thus does not penetrate into the deeper layers of the skin. Good moisturizers are also aloe vera, chitosan and hyaluronic acid. Very well, if any of these components contained in the best cream for stretch marks. In addition, the composition should comprise a good cream vitamins C, E and A, amino acid, collagen, minerals, wheat germ extract, seaweed, protein hydrolysates, various oils (shi, jojoba). There are also special means of stretching (creams and gels) with healing effects. Usually in their composition contains components such as cocoa butter, avocado, grape seed, rose hips, wheat germ, soya. Such funds have an intensive moisturizing and softening effect, increases the elasticity of the skin (which prevents it from hyperextension), contribute to improving cell regeneration and have a pronounced drainage effect that prevents swelling.</p>

<p>The main rule when using these creams during pregnancy - is regularity, because even the best stretch mark cream in the world will not give results if you use it on occasion. Nutritious and moisturizing ingredients should come to the skin on a daily basis, only in this case, the skin did not lose its elasticity and beauty. To prevent stretch marks is not a chance occurrence, it is important to start to use special means already the third month of pregnancy, it is possible before, and this should be done twice a day after showering. Best stretch marks cream should be well absorbed. When choosing a cream you need to carefully examine the label as part of the means should not be any fragrance. Apply the product to be massaged on the problem areas (ie areas where stretch marks occur most often: breasts, thighs, abdomen, buttocks).</p>

<p>It should be noted that not all best creams for stretch marks are identical, they are classified depending on the destination. For example, for the prevention of stretch marks on the abdomen and chest should be used for a variety of creams. To avoid the appearance of unsightly red or white stripes on the abdomen is necessary to use creams, as part of which there are special vegetable oils, natural ingredients, vegetable protein. The funds for the breast are composed only hypoallergenic ingredients, as the skin in the area of the breast is particularly sensitive. Usually on the package means indicates to some areas of the body, it is most suitable. Such funds now in the cosmetic market represented a lot, with different price category. Regardless of grade and cost, it is important that the composition means have been included only natural ingredients. This is necessary in order to eliminate any chance of getting harmful substances to the fetus. Usually, on the box itself, or jar (tube) indicate whether you can use this tool during the gestation of the baby. If such a mark is not recommended to give preference to other means, it is better not to risk it.</p>

<p>If for some reason you missed the boat, and stretch marks appear, you should consult with your doctor about this. You may need to do some procedure, the doctor will advise you the best cream for stretch marks after pregnancy. The effect of such funds aimed at intensive skin nourishment and stimulating its regenerative functions. In this case, it is important not to leave it to chance, since the stretch without proper attention in time become more pronounced. It should be borne in mind that such funds must be suitable for use during breast-feeding the baby (if any).</p>

<p>We should also note that almost all best creams for stretch marks should be used for a further three to four months after giving birth, because in this period the skin returns to its original state (compressed), and it needs vitamins and various enzymes that are responsible for skin elasticity and firmness. These substances are present in best creams for stretch marks.</p>

<p>Nowadays there is an incredible number of brands and companies engaged in the production of cosmetics for pregnant against stretch marks. The funds differ in texture, smell, color, so every expectant mom will find its own version. Among the means that are popular, it may be noted best rated stretch mark creams brands Vichy, Lierac, Avent, Sanosan, Revitol.</p>

<h2>Rules for the choice of a best stretch marks cream</h2>

<p>These funds (usually a mark &quot;Maternity&quot;) are advised to purchase only in pharmacies and specialized stores, so you will reduce the risk of buying counterfeit goods to a minimum.</p>

<p>Special effects have best stretch mark creams containing emollients (jojoba or shea butter), components, improves circulation, of vitamins, amino acids, collagen, which in combination restore skin tissue, making it smooth.</p>

<p><strong>Best cream for stretch marks should be</strong> unobtrusive smell, or even the most good and high-quality cream will bring you a lot of inconvenience and discomfort.</p>

<p>Choose only hypoallergenic cosmetic products. If possible, it is better first to buy a sampler and a skin test for the presence of allergic reactions. If you have friends who enjoy a similar tool, you can take them and do a test for skin sensitivity to the product.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Body Wraps for Weight Loss Belly]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/body-wraps-for-weight-loss-belly/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-04T17:36:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/body-wraps-for-weight-loss-belly</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/body-wraps-for-weight-loss-belly/body-wraps-for-weight-loss-belly.jpg" title="Body wraps for weight loss belly" alt="Body wraps for weight loss belly">How should look like your belly so you can feel free to wear tight shirts and short tops? Some girls like sports press - absolutely flat stomach with a hint of &quot;cubes&quot;. Others prefer a more feminine option - a combination of a thin waist with a faint soft roundness below the navel; just so perfect tummy looks at the owners figure &quot;hourglass&quot;, and not just in this case, it looks perfectly piercing. Unfortunately, for many people neither one nor the other is not available, and they do not even know how to actually look like their waist, because it is hidden under the more or less visible fat layer. How to lose weight? Some are used for different types of wraps. In this article we will describe some of the most popular body wraps for weight loss belly and talk about their performance.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Vinegar wraps</h2>

<p><strong>As they are made.</strong> Dining room (ie diluted) vinegar moistened cloth, the size suitable for the desired part of the body. Fabric slightly drained, is wrapped in 1-2 layers (depending on the thickness of material) around the waist and leave all approximately 30-40 minutes. On top of the fabric should not be any clothes you need to vinegar is evaporated. After the procedure, the skin is rinsed with water.</p>

<p><strong>Expected effect.</strong> During evaporation means the skin surface to which it is applied, it is cooled; on the same principle based vinegar rubdown in patients with <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/fever.html" title="fever">fever</a>. At the same time, low body temperature contributes to the fact that the body begins to waste energy on heating, spending reserves of calories available.</p>

<p>Comparing these two well-known fact, supporters of vinegar wraps claim if such procedures cause the burning of fat in the body is applied to the vinegar. In addition, it is assumed, if the vitamins, minerals and acids that means a positive effect on the skin and can even reduce the size and depth of stretch marks. Whatever it said, the experts?</p>

<p><strong>The real effect of the procedure.</strong> Unfortunately, the effectiveness of vinegar wraps is greatly exaggerated, their real effect - almost zero. Why? Firstly, during their cooling of the skin is not so much that the body began to actively warmed. Secondly, under the local effect of low temperature energy is drawn not from the area, which is cooled and from the general reserves of fat, that is, there is not a local, and the total weight loss. Third, as a part of vinegar is only dilute acetic acid, other &quot;acids, vitamins and minerals&quot; it there, so that on stretching means will not act.</p>

<p><strong>Conclusion.</strong> Vinegar wraps useless for slimming the abdomen.</p>

<h2>Cold wraps</h2>

<p><strong>As they are made.</strong> For the procedure, you will need two layers of fabric and crushed ice. Pieces of ice should be evenly distributed between the layers of matter and wrap it around your waist. Of course, it is not easy, since the pieces may be shifted and fall out, so they are sometimes used instead of ice water. In this case, as heating the tissue, ie, every 2-3 minutes, remove the cloth, re-soak in water, drained and then wrapped around the waist. The procedure lasts about 30 minutes.</p>

<p><strong>Expected effect.</strong> It uses the same principle as that of acetic wrappings: It is assumed that the cooling body will promote local lipolysis.</p>

<p><strong>The real effect of the procedure.</strong> As already mentioned, the local impacts of low temperature does not contribute to the breakdown of fat in the area of &#8203;&#8203;exposure to the cold. Nevertheless, these wraps are more effective than acetic acid. <strong><em>Firstly</em></strong>, they are used for lower temperatures, and thus the body is still in its warm spends a certain amount of calories. <strong><em>Second</em></strong>, the strong cooling effect on the blood vessels, which increases the drainage of fluid from the problem area and therefore contributes to a small extent visual thinning waist, although quite insignificant and brief.</p>

<p><strong>Conclusion.</strong> Cold wraps are ineffective for weight loss abdomen, but can be used in combination with other treatments aimed at weight reduction.</p>

<h2>Coffee wrap</h2>

<p><strong>As they are made.</strong> From natural ground coffee prepared paste by mixing it with water. The mixture was applied to the waist region, is wrapped on top of it 3-4 times with cling film. Then the abdomen is additionally wrap and lie down for an hour under a warm blanket.</p>

<p><strong>Expected effect.</strong> Coffee is known as an aid to weight loss. It is believed that during the wrapping caffeine penetrates beneath the skin and causes the breakdown of fat in the coating.</p>

<p><strong>The real effect of the procedure.</strong> Alas, even the best components and organic coffee does not penetrate into the subcutaneous fat layer. So its &quot;toning, firming and stimulating&quot; effect can be felt only in respect of the nervous system and for receiving the coffee inside, and not in relation to fat when external use. The only positive effect of wrap is the local application of heat, which dilates blood vessels, improves microcirculation and promotes drainage of fluid in the tissues. All of this does not lead to weight loss, but a little better effect appropriate measures aimed at fighting fat.</p>

<p><strong>Conclusion.</strong> Coffee wraps can be used only against the background of exercise of massage and dieting. With their independent use of weight loss will not happen.</p>

<p>For the effects on the stomach area, and recommended other kinds of wraps: honey (we wrote about it in one of my previous posts), mustard, clay, etc. We do not see much point to describe in detail each of them: in any case, their effect will be largely determined by the application of heat or cold, but not unique influence selected for their active ingredient.</p>

<p><strong>Even the most effective options for existing wraps will help you not just go and get rid of excess fat on the abdomen; the most that you can expect from them - a drainage action, against which will create the appearance of weight loss.</strong> The real effect you watch only when specifically will undertake to improve the figure and will no longer rely on the fact that lose weight, lying under a blanket in plastic wrap.</p>

<p>Study at home or join a gym if you can not discipline themselves; reduce caloric intake or consult a dietitian to recommend you a diet; do massage and wraps the problem area, or make an appropriate cosmetic procedures. The main thing - do it all the time, long and complex. If you really want to achieve, and to see his waist in perfect condition, you will not stop what it will take up to several months of effort, and that it will be accompanied to your constraints and the need to carry physical activity and possibly material costs.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Reduce the Acidity of the Stomach?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-04T17:20:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach.jpg" title="How to reduce the acidity of the stomach?" alt="How to reduce the acidity of the stomach">Even healthy people a few times a year are faced with situations where they suddenly starts to bother nausea, heaviness in the abdomen or stomach pain. The reasons for this may be many - from the use of poor-quality food to the side effects from taking aspirin. In some cases, listed complaints arising from the increased acidity of gastric juice, which can contribute to the development of some diseases in the first place, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/gastritis.html" title="gastritis">gastritis</a> and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/diagnosis-of-peptic-ulcer-disease.html" title="peptic ulcer">peptic ulcer</a> disease. So if you think you have such a breach, you should pay more attention to their own health.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Currently, in various diseases of the stomach is quite rarely do the analysis on acidity, because it has been proven that the prospects of treatment depend on this factor only to a small extent (a much more significant role played by the nature of the disease, its severity, and others.). And if the person has no serious pathologies and considers himself generally healthy, such a diagnostic procedure the more meaningless - and, moreover, very unpleasant. However, it should be remembered that increased acidity in the body can create an environment in which to easily develop disease processes; In addition, it brings a man some discomfort. So what to do to prove its existence?</p>

<p>Just listen to yourself, and your <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/" title="symptoms">symptoms</a> you may use a fairly high probability to determine if there is a violation of you or not. If you are concerned about the &quot;acidic&quot; belching, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/heartburn.html" title="heartburn">heartburn</a>, pain in the upper abdomen (especially after eating foods that enhance the secretion of gastric juice), then it is possible that you have increased the acidity. Your guess is finally confirmed when you experiment with food and other methods to reduce it, and they will give results. So what to do to help themselves?</p>

<p>It can be said, the cornerstone of your efforts - without the normal power supply to solve the problem fail. The first thing is to give up all the foods and beverages that contribute to enhanced secretion of digestive juices. When acidity organism too responsive to food stimuli, whereby the stomach is filled with &quot;excess&quot; of hydrochloric acid, which irritates its wall.</p>

<p>Now, remember, <strong>you should not eat (especially on an empty stomach and/or in large quantities), the following products:</strong> coffee, chocolate, soft drinks, sour berries and fruit (currants, some varieties of apples), citrus, undiluted fruit juice, spices, canned food, meats, hearty soups and broths, pickles, fried foods. It contains so-called extractive substances, which greatly increase secretion. Also, do not get involved in a very cold food and drinks.</p>

<p>Instead of all this is to increase the content in the diet of boiled, baked and stewed vegetables and meat, milk and dairy products, sweet fruit. Lower acidity and protect the stomach wall against possible damage to help jelly, mucous soups and soups, porridge. If you suffer from symptoms of hyperacidity, do not recommend to stick to strict diets to lose weight: eat small portions you need, but fractionally, from 4 to 6 times a day. Fasting is also strictly contraindicated.</p>

<p>Do not forget that food should moderate amounts include fats, animal and especially plant to help recover the mucosa and create on it a thin protective film. Although, of course, it is important not to overdo it: a piece of fatty mutton will your stomach into complete confusion and provoke hypersecretion of hydrochloric acid, which will cause you to regret his shortsightedness.</p>

<p><strong>Bad habits and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a>: how they affect the acidity?</strong></p>

<p>Bad! And you probably heard about it is great. It is no secret that the lady&rsquo;s finger greater among those who are often nervous - hence, the stress increases the acidity of gastric juice. In addition, the experience contribute to disruption of the activity of certain hormones local action and reduce the blood supply to the mucosa. Also, a state of nervous tension inhibits the work of the cells that produce the protective mucus and bicarbonate, which in the normal digestive enzymes do not dissolve the stomach itself.</p>

<p>Smoking and alcohol also significantly impaired digestion, so it is better to give them. It is believed that a cigarette after a meal is not so much effect on gastric secretion as smoked on an empty stomach, but with frequent smoking effect of nicotine becomes a constant that does not relieve us from the consequences.</p>

<p><strong>Folk remedies for reducing the acidity</strong></p>

<p>There are many variations of recipes that supposedly help solve problems associated with acidity. But the really significant action you can expect only on the rice or oat broth that protect the stomach from acid, and even recommended by doctors as a therapeutic agent for patients with gastritis or ulcer.</p>

<p>To reliably reduce gastric acidity, should be performed at any one, but all these suggestions. Controlling diet and avoiding bad habits and stress, you are literally within 2-3 weeks will achieve a result. If this does not happen, and you will still be something to disturb refer to a gastroenterologist: <strong>persistent symptoms can talk about already developed the disease, which will make you friends not only with the &quot;right&quot; food, but also with medications that reduce the acidity.</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Soybeans: Benefits and Harms, Doctor Review]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-04T15:52:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review.jpg" title="Black soybeans: benefits and harms, doctor review" alt="Black soybeans">Black soybean - a product that is used in traditional Chinese medicine. It is considered a source of balance. Therapeutic effects: replenishes blood levels, nourishing yin, expels wind, strengthens weakened, normalizes the activity of the channels of stomach and spleen. In Russia, black soybeans also find healing, but its effect is usually described using different terminology, more understandable to our man.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Black soybean useful in exactly the same extent that and soy white or yellow. This is a common legume has a high protein content and insoluble dietary fiber. There is hardly any sense to use it as a medicine. Black soybean much more suitable for use in food. Nevertheless, she decided to attribute the following useful properties:</p>

<ul>
<li>Normalizes nervous activity;</li>
<li>Cures cancer (probably not in the world of plants, which it does not cure, according to admirers of traditional medicine);</li>
<li>To protect people from the harmful effects of the environment;</li>
<li>Reduces the level of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a> in the blood;</li>
<li>Promotes weight loss.</li>
</ul>


<p>All these inventions. This can be read on virtually any product of plant origin. Perhaps black soy and healthy if its systematic use in food, but cancer or diabetes, it is certainly not cures.</p>

<p>Black soybean contains no toxic compounds for the organism. The damage is only possible with overeating or the presence of diseases of the digestive system. Disadvantages of the product:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>High calorie</strong> - do not pass at a weight problem;</li>
<li><strong>High fiber content</strong> - possible bloating, changes in the frequency and stool consistency;</li>
<li><strong>Small size, dense texture, slippery edge</strong> - a man with a deficit of intelligence can strangle if Bob gets into the respiratory tract.</li>
</ul>


<p>People with normal mental development and good health black soybeans can not hurt anything. Eat without fear for their health.</p>

<p>On the Internet a lot of popularity gained supplement for weight loss called &quot;black soybeans&quot;. The advertisement says that it is delivered directly from Japan. It is not clear why they are doing, because it is a good idea in Russia is growing.</p>

<p>At sells website reported that the secret of longevity of the Japanese, finally revealed! It turns out the high life expectancy - a consequence of regular consumption of black soya.</p>

<p>Take supplements you offer for the following purposes:</p>

<p><strong>1. Weight Loss.</strong> The main purpose of black soya. Weight reduction is due to increasing the activity of fat cells. Those allegedly begin to burn fat, regardless of the amount of food consumed by you, including, if you have no physical activity. In addition, thanks to soy protein, according to advertising, the muscles grow without any training.
<strong>2. Improvement by saturating the body with useful substances.</strong> The site Product asserts that certain vitamins, minerals and amino acids are contained only in black soybeans. Nowhere in nature, they are no more. I wonder what kind of minerals are? If you would like Mendeleev heard, he probably would have got out of the coffin to burn his table of chemical elements.
<strong>3. Rejuvenation.</strong> It is due to dietary fiber (which, incidentally, are in any plant food). The body is rejuvenated as a result of lightning elimination of toxins under the influence of black soy from Japan. After that, according to the suppliers of goods, there is a surge of energy forces in the cell, and you feel much better.</p>

<p>Due to what effect this wonder-drug that reduces weight and rejuvenate the body? If you believe the official site, as part contains the following components:</p>

<p><strong>Proteins.</strong> Present in any food products. They are a source of calories. Promote weight loss, but only if used in place of fatty and sugary foods, not in addition to it.</p>

<p><strong>Vitamins A and E.</strong> So these vitamins, which are found nowhere else in nature, except for black soy! Or is there? Yes, still there. Vitamin A is full in carrots and other yellow vegetables, and vitamin E in abundance found in vegetable oils. Both components are useful for health, weight loss but not in any way contribute.</p>

<p><strong>B vitamins</strong> are present in many other foods. Good for your health, but they do not lose weight and look younger.</p>

<p><strong>Alimentary fiber.</strong> In fact contribute to weight loss. But only if the abundance of dietary fiber in the diet causes decrease in consumption of other foods. By themselves, they do not burn fat.</p>

<p><strong>Amino acids.</strong> This protein structural components, so that in fact when transferring the composition manufacturer repeats the same material twice. As mentioned above, from the proteins do not lose weight if they are a supplement, not a substitute for the usual ration.</p>

<p><strong>Trace elements.</strong> What kind of minerals are in the black soybeans - the manufacturer is not recognized. Given that nowhere in other products do not, in general, these micronutrients to mankind is not known, to evaluate their real impact on the shape and health is very difficult.</p>

<p>Black soybean are sold as a concentrate. You will receive a jar of powder. It must be diluted in a glass of water and drink before each meal, three times a den.Takoe use of black soya will help in weight loss, as it will reduce appetite.</p>

<p>Of course, this will not happen because of the presence of this plant amazing fat-burning properties. Hunger subsides as the day before the meal in the stomach will be less space. As a result, you eat less. If this happens regularly for at least several months, you will eventually be able to normalize the figures.</p>

<p>Black soybeans - is one of hundreds or thousands of useless goods for figure and health that is actively circulating on the Internet. It pacifiers in a beautiful package. They are sold on the colorfully decorated sites and skillfully advertised, but because demand. Nevertheless, the man who would be able to lose weight and rejuvenate with the help of black soybean, the world does not know.</p>

<p>This product is recommended to buy the people:</p>

<ul>
<li>The rich - who do not consider $ 40 money, worthy of attention;</li>
<li>Curious - who are used to check for yourself;</li>
<li>Stupid - who believed in a bright, but not the most convincing and reasoned advertising;</li>
<li>Desperate - who wants nothing to do with his own figure and wants to clear his conscience, allegedly fighting <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a> even with the help of useless supplements.</li>
</ul>


<p>The rest of the people recommended to use other methods of weight loss. There are supplements better. However, keep in mind that without the support of the diet and increase physical activity, no medication is not going to work.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protein for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-04T11:05:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/protein-for-weight-loss/protein-for-weight-loss.jpg" title="Protein for weight loss" alt="weight loss protein">Protein - one of the three main energy substrates required to sustain the human body. Along with carbohydrates and fats, they form the basis of our food. In the intestine, the proteins are broken down into amino acids, which are released into the bloodstream, and can then be consumed as a &quot;fuel&quot;. But if fat and especially carbohydrates energy function is the main, the proteins are spent mainly on the construction of the cells in our body.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Surely you notice that most of today&rsquo;s diets restricted in the first place, the consumption of fats and carbohydrates, while the basis of the diet are just proteins. What is the reason? Obviously, nutritionists believe proteins are less harmful to the figures, so a person is allowed to use them in large quantities. But the splitting of proteins produce as much energy as carbohydrates. That is, their calorie content comparable. What is the secret properties of dietary protein foods?</p>

<p>Secret 1. As already mentioned, only a small portion of protein is used to meet the energy needs of the body. The rest are going to build new cells, enzymes, antibodies, hormones.</p>

<p>Secret 2. Squirrels rarely turn into fat, as this is a complex and energy-intensive process, which, moreover, takes place in two stages. In the process of gluconeogenesis from amino acids derived glucose, which can then be used for the synthesis of triglycerides (fats). Normally, our body is not economical decided on such irrational action.</p>

<p>Secret 3. The process of protein breakdown in the intestines requires large amounts of energy. For example, to 1000 kcal of protein, the body has to expend about 300 calories. To remove the same amount of energy from carbohydrates consumed only 70 kcal.</p>

<p>All protein products, in fact, are dietary. But not only this is the reason for the wide use of proteins in nutrition programs aimed at weight reduction. If the shortage of fats and carbohydrates is only good figure, the lack of protein in the body can turn around serious health problems.</p>

<ol>
<li>It reduces the body&rsquo;s defenses, increased incidence of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/" title="infectious diseases">infectious diseases</a>. Proteins are essential for the maintenance of both cellular and humoral immunity same. Antibodies complement system, interferon, lysozyme, immunoglobulins, leukocytes - to produce all the necessary elements of the immune system proteins.</li>
<li>hormonal imbalance, deterioration of the skin, fatigue, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/depression.html" title="depression">depression</a>, decreased libido, and even cessation of menstruation - can also be caused by protein deficiency.</li>
<li>If there is insufficient protein the body tries to get them from domestic sources, breaking down the body&rsquo;s own tissue. First in the course are the skeletal muscles. Therefore, in the absence of a sufficient amount of food proteins, at some point, muscle mass begins to decline rapidly.</li>
<li>When the amount of albumin in the blood is reduced, the swelling begin to form. The reason for this decrease in oncotic (exerted proteins) plasma pressure. The liquid passes easily from the vessels into the interstitial (intercellular) space, which results in swelling of the soft tissues.</li>
<li>Protein is needed for generation of platelets and clotting factors. Therefore, protein deficiency increases the risk of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/injuries-and-accidents/bleeding.html" title="bleeding">bleeding</a>.</li>
</ol>


<p>The protein does not burn fat, but it promotes weight loss when used instead of fats and carbohydrates. As one of the three main sources of energy, in fact, this nutrient has the lowest calorie. So most popular diets are based on reducing the intake of carbohydrates and fats that are harmful to the figure. Proteins thus, are generally not limited.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protein Diet. Sample Menu Protein Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-04T05:15:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet.jpg" title="Protein diet. Sample menu protein diet" alt="Protein diet">The most common protein diet try to choose those who are engaged in fitness, or who can not give up meat and fish, but calmly dispenses with flour and sweet.</p>

<p>The basic idea of protein diets is that we create a shortage of carbohydrates in the body, are considered the main source of energy for the organism. As a result, the metabolism starts to rebuild, and the body will consume fat.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The bulk of the protein diet involves almost complete rejection of carbohydrate foods, and consumption of products containing large amounts of protein.</p>

<p>The diet protein diet usually includes meat and fish, eggs, cottage cheese, yogurt and low-fat cheeses.</p>

<p>Sometimes, for example, egg diet, the diet can include citrus fruits (grapefruit, oranges, and the like), which are positioned as a source of vitamins.</p>

<p>The main disadvantage of all protein diets - it is unbalanced diet.</p>

<h2>We can not exclude carbohydrates completely!</h2>

<p>For weight loss on the protein diet is usually used following recommendations may be included on the menu only lean chicken, fish, egg whites and low-fat cottage cheese (it is desirable to have 4 meals, at a time that the output of 25-30 g of protein) and a drink sugar and other products should be deleted (except Citrus).</p>

<p>This menu can not be considered a balanced&hellip; In most cases the authors of these methods is recommended to keep a diet for 2 weeks, ostensibly for &quot;changes in metabolism&quot;. In practice, the rejection of carbohydrates is harmful to the body. The complete absence of ontaining carbohydrates foods in the diet and an excess of junk food can cause ketosis (increased content of ketone bodies in the tissues of the body).</p>

<p>Ketosis is a kind of unmistakable indication that the process of lipolysis. Reach ketosis state - the main goal of many low-carb diets.</p>

<p>Typically ketosis appears when the amount of carbohydrates is less than 100 grams per day. In some people, ketosis occurs only with reducing carbohydrates to 40 g per day.</p>

<p>To determine the presence of ketone bodies can use the urine test.</p>

<p>Some authors protein diets claim that the complete rejection of carbohydrates - a necessary condition for weight loss, because ketosis state body draws its energy mainly from the fat reserves.</p>

<p>It is believed that the ketogenic diet is very harmful and even dangerous for your health. Indeed, the ketogenic diet can be dangerous, it all depends on the individual person&rsquo;s health status.</p>

<p><strong>However, current research tells us this:</strong></p>

<p><em>&quot;A diet rich in protein products should not be carbohydrate-free. That, as far as we lose weight, largely depends on the daily caloric intake and what we consume carbohydrates during the day and at what time (in the morning or late afternoon), how much protein per 1 kg of body weight comes from food&quot;.</em></p>

<p><strong>If you are not ready to compete in fitness or bodybuilding, so what&rsquo;s the point to exhaust yourself? To reduce the percentage of body fat, you can go for less severe measures, albeit the result will be noticeable not so fast.</strong></p>

<p>Carbohydrates - a major supplier of food for the nervous system.</p>

<p>If they are missing, the following <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/" title="symptoms">symptoms</a>: fatigue, loss of efficiency, reduction of attention, irritability.</p>

<p>Eat 4-6 times a day, the first meal - 20-30 minutes after the lift, the last reception for 2-3 hours before bedtime. Each meal should consist of a portion of protein (20-30 g) and other low-calorie foods. Till one o&rsquo;clock permitted to 1-2 servings of complex carbohydrates. This 8-10 tablespoons of buckwheat or oatmeal. Or the same amount of boiled brown (brown) rice. ontaining carbohydrates from other products on time, weight loss will need to be abandoned. After 13 hours of the day should be protein products will have only non-starchy vegetables: cucumbers, tomatoes, cabbage, zucchini, etc. Fruit is consumed sparingly and preferably in the morning. Allowed 2 unsweetened apple or 1 grapefruit. Drink at least two liters of plain water a day.</p>

<p>Take vitamins after breakfast (can be sports, such as: Opti-Vites or Daily Formula).</p>

<p>Limit fats permitted to 40 g per day.</p>

<h2>How to make the correct protein diet?</h2>

<p>During a diet to lose weight you need to eat one of these foods at each meal:</p>

<ul>
<li>150-200 g skinless chicken breast;</li>
<li>150-200 g lean fish (flounder, cod, pollock, tuna);</li>
<li>100 g turkey, beef or veal;</li>
<li>150-200 g fat-free yogurt.</li>
</ul>


<p>These protein products must be consumed in an amount which indicated above.</p>

<p>Also you can include in your diet: 1-2 servings of whey protein per day.</p>

<p>200-250 ml (1 cup) of skim milk or plain water, one scoop (30 grams of protein).</p>

<p>1 serving of protein shake - this one meal. Very handy if you do not have time to prepare write.</p>

<p>It is recommended to drink in the morning, after 1.5 hours after exercise (if you want to lose weight), and (or) at night.</p>

<p>Choose whey isolate firms: Dymatize or Syntrax.</p>

<h2>Menu protein diet</h2>

<p>We offer you a rough menu for women who exercise regularly (3-5 times a week) and perform cardio + work in the gym.</p>

<p><em>The first meal (breakfast)</em>: 4-5 tablespoons of oatmeal with cinnamon, 6 egg whites with spinach, apple half. Unsweetened tea or coffee.</p>

<p><em>The second meal (lunch)</em>: 150 grams of cooked breast, served with 4-5 tablespoons of cooked brown rice.</p>

<p><em>The third meal (a dinner)</em>: 150 g of tuna and a salad of non-starchy vegetables, season with olive oil (1 tablespoon).</p>

<p><em>The fourth meal (afternoon snack)</em>: 200 g fat-free cottage cheese with vegetable salad (you can add lemon juice).</p>

<p><em>Fifth meal (evening meal)</em>: 150 g of fish with steamed green beans, protein shake or a cup of yogurt.</p>

<p><strong>Protein diet</strong> can help lose weight, and virtually all its effectiveness is increased by an order if you do weights and cardio in the gym.</p>

<p>It should be noted that during the period of weight loss and the use of refined foods alcohol is not allowed.</p>

<p>To prevent disruptions once a week (for example, every Sunday) you can eat a small portion of your favorite product.</p>

<p><strong>Protein diet: -70 kg for 60 months</strong></p>

<p>Before you start the protein diet, you should consult with your doctor!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Appetite Before Menstruation. Why Before Menstruation I Want to Eat a Lot?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/appetite-before-menstruation-why-before-menstruation-i-want-to-eat-a-lot/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-03T18:02:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/appetite-before-menstruation-why-before-menstruation-i-want-to-eat-a-lot</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/appetite-before-menstruation-why-before-menstruation-i-want-to-eat-a-lot/appetite-before-menstruation-why-before-menstruation-i-want-to-eat-a-lot.jpg" title="Appetite before menstruation" alt="Appetite before menstruation. Why before menstruation I want to eat a lot">What would you no longer want to eat - yogurt, a chocolate bar or a hamburger? At any other time, you will be thinking, but if at the moment your new cycle is nearing completion, the answer is obvious: &quot;All and more!&quot;. Among other <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/" title="symptoms">symptoms</a> of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/premenstrual-syndrome.html" title="premenstrual syndrome">premenstrual syndrome</a>, sometimes women overcomes increased appetite, due to which all the household food reserves are disappearing at a high rate and must be constantly replenished. What is happening and how to deal with it?</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>A brief excursion into the female physiology</h2>

<p>Some girls have every reason to be jealous of men with hormonal virtually flat. In the weak half of humanity it is not so: in women occur every 28-32 days cyclical changes, and during each cycle, they have a certain time can be observed patterns change in health. To make it easier to understand the causes of their increased appetite, to remind you of some of the physiological characteristics of your body.</p>

<p>The menstrual cycle is divided into two approximately equal length phases. The first phase in the body gradually increases the level of hormones, estrogen (estradiol, estriol, estrone). This promotes the maturation of the egg; during this phase the woman feels great, different optimal performance and on what does not complain.</p>

<p>At the peak of the concentration of estrogen ovulation - out egg from the ovary into the fallopian tube where it is ready to be fertilized. From that moment so much estrogen the body is already unnecessary: &#8203;&#8203;their level is gradually reduced, but increasing performance of the hormone progesterone. It prepares the body for a possible <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a>, and creates the conditions to safely settled alleged embryo in the uterus.</p>

<p>All anything, but with the growth of the level of this hormone often start various &quot;tricks&quot; to health. Irritability, lethargy, drowsiness, edema, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/acne.html" title="acne">acne</a> and, of course, a great desire always something to chew&hellip; And how progesterone affects your appetite?</p>

<h2>Mechanisms of appearance of increased appetite</h2>

<p>There are several common explanations for increase appetite during the premenstrual period.</p>

<p>Someone says that estrogen somehow affect the selection into the body of the hormone of happiness, serotonin. Once the second phase of the cycle the estrogen level decreases, it means that the body does not have enough of this &quot;happiness&quot; that makes women look for his other sources, for example, chocolate&hellip;</p>

<p>This is too simplistic an explanation. Firstly, hormones - not only to affect serotonin, and secondly, it promotes the synthesis of not only chocolate but also milk, bananas and other products. Third, before menstruation women pulls not only sweet but also in meat, bakery, etc.</p>

<p>There is still a belief that shortly before the onset of menstruation activates the metabolism, which leads to increased consumption of nutrient and calorie needs increase. This is not so: the metabolic processes are most active when a lot of estrogen in the body (the first phase of the cycle, if you remember the previous section). And with the prevalence of the metabolism of progesterone, on the contrary, a few slowed down.</p>

<p>Other statement does is from the category of &quot;popular&quot;, is that a woman&rsquo;s body prepares for the &quot;cleansing&quot; in the form of monthly, so the pre-stored nutrients to restore torn away the endometrium and blood volume replacement. This is not true! So what&rsquo;s the deal?</p>

<p>But the fact that a woman&rsquo;s body each month naive &quot;hopes&quot; that she finally will assume the obligations imposed on it by nature, and decides to become a mother. So he is not preparing for cleansing, but rather for pregnancy. Under the influence of certain hormones changing composition of the activity of some brain structures (limbic system, reticular formation, hypothalamus). Among other things, the activation of the hunger center; also observed increased secretion of the glands of the digestive tract and other metamorphoses.</p>

<p>In general, the specific reason for your hunger there; blame him - the complex interaction of hormones that influence the changes of the central nervous system, digestive tract and other organs. Act on all this is impossible&hellip; And mediated cause increased appetite is a weakness, irritability and general malaise before menstruation, against which you want to console himself tasty.</p>

<h2>All you are experiencing increased appetite before menstruation?</h2>

<p>As you obviously already knew in their observations, not all women respond to hormonal surges desire to cry, aggression towards others or the desire to absorb the entire contents of the refrigerator. Most just live a normal life, without feeling any particular signs of the end of the cycle.</p>

<p>There are those who have known premenstrual syndrome is not accompanied by increased appetite, but on the contrary, it proceeds with an aversion to food, nausea and even <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/vomiting.html" title="vomiting">vomiting</a>. All individually. So, if you regularly eats before menstruation, do not consider yourself the most miserable creature in the world: Believe me, there are far more options unpleasant condition known as PMS.</p>

<p>You may have noticed on offer, write a few lines above: that the changes in the body that lead to increased feelings of hunger, do not depend on the will of a woman and are not controlled. This is true; You can not make your ovaries change operation&hellip; But no, you can, there is one way.</p>

<p>According to the research, hormonal contraceptives can reduce or eliminate the symptoms of premenstrual syndrome, including increased appetite and. Against the background of hormonal balance is more equalized, and it allows women to feel better.</p>

<p>Other ways to fight hunger are ineffective; We have to rely only on his will and not the means that somehow it will reduce. It is recommended to comply with a reasonable diet, eat more fruits, whole grains, vegetables, chocolate and flour to replace the dried fruit and other more benign figures for sweets. All this will help to eat less, but will only because you themselves will control myself. Another good idea helps something to occupy themselves: loads before menstruation work, school, or anything else, and it will make you think less about hunger.</p>

<p>And in general, why you are so worried about increased appetite? Practice shows that the food eaten during this period, usually fully consumed by the body and does not cause the actual weight gain, unless your condition is not close to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/bulimia.html" title="bulimia">bulimia</a>. Try to get on the scales after a couple of days after the month - and you most likely will not see any changes. So it is not worth much to blame themselves and experience; just try to limit the amount eaten, and your monthly &quot;attacks&quot; will not affect the figure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Activated Charcoal Slimming. Is It Possible to Lose Weight With the Help of Activated Charcoal]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/activated-charcoal-slimming-is-it-possible-to-lose-weight-with-the-help-of-activated-charcoal/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-03T16:58:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/activated-charcoal-slimming-is-it-possible-to-lose-weight-with-the-help-of-activated-charcoal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/activated-charcoal-slimming-is-it-possible-to-lose-weight-with-the-help-of-activated-charcoal/activated-charcoal-slimming-is-it-possible-to-lose-weight-with-the-help-of-activated-charcoal.jpg" title="Activated charcoal slimming" alt="Activated charcoal slimming. Is it possible to lose weight with the help of activated charcoal?">Activated carbon - is the most popular sorbent. Use it to quickly remove toxins that are caught in the intestines from food. Activated carbon is present in every home medicine cabinet. It is cheap, but it is as effective as most expensive sorbents. Activated carbon is made to use in the case of food poisoning. But it is also used to reduce weight.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Losing weight with the help of activated carbon</h2>

<p>To count people who are trying to lose weight with the help of activated charcoal? On the Internet you can find the following explanation of the mechanism of drug action:</p>

<ul>
<li>It displays the body of toxins, so there is a strengthening of metabolism and accelerate fat digestion;</li>
<li>Adsorb on the surface fat, so if you take the activated carbon during the meal, the calories are not absorbed by the body;</li>
<li>Coal is useful when dieting because removes harmful metabolites are formed during digestion of fat;</li>
<li>Activated carbon removes from the bowel gases so belly becomes smaller;</li>
<li>It can be taken before meals with a view to filling the stomach and loss of appetite.</li>
</ul>


<p>In fact, lose weight with the help of activated carbon you are unlikely to succeed. He is really good on the surface adsorbs substances, some of which have a toxic effect on the body. Only one gram of activated carbon has an area of 500 square meters, so it is able to attach many chemical compounds that might adversely affect the health.</p>

<p>But people, weight loss is recommended for activated carbon are mistaken about the causes of weight gain. In fact, stout man not because of his poison some mythical toxins. He is gaining weight because they consume a lot of food. However, activated carbon is not out of the body fats and carbohydrates. Therefore, it does not help a person to reduce body weight.</p>

<h2>The inclusion of activated carbon in diet</h2>

<p>Some diets are designed for weight loss, intended to include in the diet of activated carbon. This is surprising, given that he is neither a food product or a blocker of calories or dietary fibers that could fill your stomach without increasing the energy value of food. As a rule, the activated charcoal is recommended to take 1 tablet per 10 kg of weight, before a meal or during a meal.</p>

<p>It is believed that taking activated charcoal before meals reduces appetite. We will not argue with that statement. Perhaps eating 7-8 tablets of coal, you really feel that the stomach is something there. There is a small chance that you will be able, even in such a way to reduce appetite. That&rsquo;s just for the oppression of hunger before a meal, there are safer methods - tablespoon of bran plus a glass of water.</p>

<p>If you need to fill your stomach with something before you eat, what to use for this activated carbon? After all, it takes from your stomach trace elements, vitamins and other nutrients. Taking coal once, no health problems will not arise. Even after a week of regular use of the drug in the food you are likely to experience the side effects.</p>

<p>But after a month or more on their appearance is quite real. It may develop goiter, diarrhea, deficiency in certain vitamins or minerals. Activated charcoal, if you plan to use it during a weight loss diet, will have to take a long time.</p>

<p>To tidy up your figure, people usually spend at least a few months. But this is not the drug that you can take a long time, so it is better to refuse from all. Especially since the activated carbon did not reduce appetite.</p>

<h2>Diet with activated carbon for weight loss</h2>

<p>The Internet is widespread three-day diet with activated charcoal. It severely limits the diet, and it is a prerequisite for the reception of sorbents. Diet menu with activated carbon as follows:</p>

<ul>
<li>first day - for breakfast and dinner, you can drink a cup of yogurt;</li>
<li>second day - three times you eat apples, but not more than 0.5 kg per meal;</li>
<li>third day - three times per day, you can eat a small portion of vegetable salad.</li>
</ul>


<p>Half an hour before each meal you need to take a few tablets of activated charcoal. The authors of the diet believe that it is due to the presence of sorbent in the human diet will lose weight. In their view, a three-day fast is only a subsidiary factor that contributes to weight loss.</p>

<p>In fact, if you prolong this diet for a week or two, you can use all sorts of drugs. All of them are supposed to promote weight loss. And if you add an aerobic workout, the activated carbon becomes even more effective. Fat begins to melt before our eyes.</p>

<h2>Activated carbon - the use of slimming</h2>

<p>There is also another way to use charcoal for weight loss. Some sources say that it can bind fats and remove them from the gastrointestinal tract unchanged. Not being exposed to enzymes that are not split into fatty acids, triglycerides are not assimilated. Therefore, a person consumes fewer calories, even without changing the diet. And all you need to do - to take a few tablets of activated charcoal during a meal.</p>

<p>In fact, if the activated carbon and prevents absorption of fat, it is only to a minor extent. Attach and remove them from the body is not able to accurately sorbent. But it can bind bile acids, which are essential for normal digestion.</p>

<p>Theoretically, this is a very slight extent would promote weight loss. But in practice this is hardly possible. Most likely, the activated carbon does not block the absorption of fat and promotes weight loss. We have several arguments in support of this view:</p>

<ol>
<li>Coal does not bind bile acids so intensively to create their deficit.</li>
<li>There is no evidence of violation of digestion of fatty foods after taking charcoal. Meanwhile, it is one of the oldest drugs. He long ago studied the length and breadth.</li>
<li>Upon receipt of the coal in the patient there is no side effects that are common to all blockers calories (frequent and loose stools, abdominal pain, flatulence, fat in the stool).</li>
</ol>


<h2>Activated carbon for purification of toxins</h2>

<p>In our bodies there is no slag. No man in the world who would see with their own eyes. Traditional healers, advocating the need to get rid of toxins, can not even clearly explain what they are. What are the chemical compounds they contain? Which toxins have consistency? What effect do they have on the body? In the end, what they look like? It would be interesting to see the slag at least in the photo.</p>

<p>It argued that cleansing the body from them, you can lose weight. And activated carbon is actively promoting this process. Just a few days the person using it can get rid of toxins, and then the weight will start to fall by itself. It is not necessary to believe in such nonsense. You can not get rid of toxins because they are not. And if they were, the cleansing of the body does not affect the weight of your body.</p>

<p>Another thing - the use of activated charcoal during a low-calorie diet. For example, if you have limited diet or exercise, your body fat is gradually broken down. If you have been for several years suffered from overweight, toxins begin to really get into the blood. They can accumulate in the fatty tissue, while losing weight is released, breaking the state of human health.</p>

<p>In this case, administration of activated charcoal improve health. Many toxins excreted from the body through the intestines. Activated charcoal helps to neutralize it, and thereby prevents reabsorption of toxic substances into the blood system. But this does not mean that the sorbent will lose weight faster.</p>

<p>Instead, intoxication is usually accompanied by weight loss. The man who was poisoned, decreased appetite, and his body spends a lot of energy to fight the toxins circulating in the blood. But do not be afraid of intoxication due to weight loss, because:</p>

<ul>
<li>toxins in the fat tissue is not so much, unless of course you&rsquo;re not a young man worked in the chemical industry;</li>
<li>lipolysis rates are quite low - stand out toxins gradually and healthy body copes with them, even without the aid of activated carbon.</li>
</ul>


<p>Activated charcoal should be used only in case of poisoning. Moreover, even in these cases it must be combined with laxatives, because sorbent may irreversibly bind toxins. Activated carbon is also successfully used for the treatment of flatulence. But reducing the amount of gas in the stomach, the drug is not able to reduce your belly. It has a large size is not due to the gases and because the subcutaneous fat. And the amount of activated carbon has no effect.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cellulite. Causes, Symptoms, Treatments]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/cellulite-causes-symptoms-treatments/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-03T15:43:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/cellulite-causes-symptoms-treatments</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/cellulite-causes-symptoms-treatments/cellulite-causes-symptoms-treatments.jpg" title="Cellulite" alt="Cellulite. Causes, symptoms, treatments"><strong>Cellulite</strong> in medicine refers to inflammation of subcutaneous fat.</p>

<p>But really popular word &quot;cellulite&quot; was when he began to communicate with the perennial problem, which is so concerned about the people who want to have a beautiful body. Known to most people <strong>cellulite - it changed the appearance of skin with subcutaneous fat</strong>. Cellulite usually occur on the thighs, buttocks and stomach, at least - in the armpits, chest, upper arms.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Cellulite - is not a disease, but an <strong>esthetic problem, which is inherent in the female constitution</strong>. He varying severity occurs in about 80% of women aged over 20 years. A common misconception - is that cellulite is only complete. Most characteristic changes occur in women of normal weight and even located on the lower limit of normal body mass index.</p>

<h2>The mechanism of formation of cellulite</h2>

<p>Under the influence of certain factors (heredity, diet, hormonal factors, physical inactivity, the deterioration of the microcirculation and others.) In the fat cells increases the deposition of fat and reducing its metabolic degradation. As a result, fat cells subcutaneous tissue <strong>uneven increase in size</strong>. Strong long connective partitions between them tightened and pressed into the part of the fat cells, and on the sides of the strands of fat portions protrude more, leading to even more uneven skin surface.</p>

<h2>Causes and risk factors of cellulite</h2>

<p><strong>Overweight</strong> - an increase in body fat in itself leads to increased levels of estrogen in the blood, which exacerbates the appearance of cellulite.</p>

<p><strong>Hormones</strong>: growth of fat cells is dependent on the level of the female hormone <em>estrogen</em>, so women with a higher concentration of estrogen in the blood more prone to the risk of the appearance of cellulite. This again indicates that the light level of cellulite it is almost normal, but its <strong>first manifestations should be a signal to work on yourself</strong>. In the case of predisposition to cellulite you need to keep yourself in good shape, so as not to aggravate the appearance of cellulite.</p>

<p><strong>Use of hormonal contraceptives</strong> - an artificial change in the blood levels of sex hormones also affects the rate of growth of fat cells.</p>

<p><strong>Poor circulation and lack of exercise</strong> - are interrelated. Circulatory disturbance occurs when a long stay in one position, low muscle tone and lack of physical activity, wearing tight underwear, stockings, a long walk in high heels.</p>

<p><strong>Heredity</strong> - often cellulite occurs in those who have a genetic predisposition to develop it. So if someone in your immediate family has any degree of cellulite, you need to start it early prevention. The best prevention of cellulite - proper nutrition and physical activity.</p>

<h2>The symptoms of cellulitis</h2>

<p>The skin is covered with small pits and often reminiscent of orange peel. Cellulite is different depending on the severity. In mild cases it is visible only when the skin is trapped in the fold. In more severe cases, it gives the skin an uneven appearance with dimples and pits. Symptoms of cellulite worsens with age as the skin loses its elasticity.</p>

<p>Cellulite is not a serious medical problem, and compulsory treatment is <strong>not necessary</strong>. Although if you believe in complete aesthetic disaster on your thighs or buttocks, you can seek help from a doctor or dermatologist plastic surgeon. The skilled artisan will prompt the most effective ways to solve the problem and give an approximate forecast of the results of different methods of treatment for you.</p>

<h2>Cellulite Treatment</h2>

<p>Many advertised ways to combat cellulite - creams, massage devices - promise significant results. But, unfortunately, most of these methods are &quot;not fulfill&quot; promises. The most effective methods to combat cellulite:</p>

<ul>
<li><p><strong>Weight loss</strong> - a healthy diet and regular exercise - at the moment it is the <strong>most effective and safe way</strong> to treat cellulite. Strengthening the muscles of the legs, buttocks, arms, abdominals and obliques, and getting rid of extra kilos can significantly improve the landscape and appearance of the skin. Do not expect immediate results from these methods, and the more you can not throw a healthy lifestyle, a week later if you did not notice the changes. On strengthening the muscles it takes time more than one week. In addition, cellulite is sometimes tends to diminish some time after returning to a normal weight. Although the results are usually still visible after a few weeks of starting treatment. In addition, proper low-calorie food coupled with exercise - it is the only method that does <strong>not threaten your health and life, and just goes in his favor</strong>.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Operation with a laser</strong> - is currently considered the most promising surgical method. There are several methods of laser treatment. One method involves a combination of tissue massage, radiofrequency exposure to fatty tissue and infrared radiation. Another method is to deliver into the subcutaneous tissue diode laser energy. The third technique uses high-frequency effects on the deep and superficial layers of the subcutaneous tissue. All varieties of laser treatment to produce results post treatment. The result, however, unstable, and the average remains about 6 months. Laser treatment is considered minimally invasive (causing minimum damage to the tissues of the body) and produces a purposeful destruction of fat cells with accompanying skin tightening.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Liposuction</strong> - the name of the operation for a long time at the hearing. During surgery, the surgeon places through small incisions under the skin of a narrow tube through which oil is pumped out and destroyed. But liposuction does not eliminate cellulite, because it comes from the superficial layers of the subcutaneous tissue and fat is removed from the deeper layers. Therefore, liposuction can sometimes even worsen the appearance of cellulite.</p></li>
</ul>


<p><strong>Local treatment - cream with a variety of active extracts, massage</strong>. The most successful proven extracts of grapefruit. Although the effect of it is very different and poorly defined. Also, according to recent studies, creams containing 0.3% retinol shown to be effective against cellulite after 6 months of use. But these resources, however, and massage can be used only as an adjunct to a healthy diet and physical activity.</p>

<p>Remember that surgical treatments always carry a certain risk (reaction to anesthesia, extensive tissue damage), so before you use them, it is better to try the safest way: strengthening of muscles and weight loss. If you once will acquire the habit of a healthy and active lifestyle, it will bring you in addition to the disappearance or reduction of cellulite and many other useful &quot;bonus&quot;. So try to choose the most convenient method to combat cellulite.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strength Training for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/strength-training-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-02T14:16:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/strength-training-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/strength-training-for-weight-loss/strength-training-for-weight-loss.jpg" title="Strength training for weight loss" alt="Strength training for weight loss">How to lose weight? The first thing that comes to mind for most people - you need to go on a diet and running every day. But not only cardio training, such as jogging or swimming, contribute to weight loss. One of the methods to reduce body fat - it is strength training. It is to lose weight used by both men and women. It is advisable to work out in the gym, where there are all necessary: &#8203;&#8203;shells, trainers, coaches, moral support and competent advice. But at home to lose weight using weight training is also possible, although the results will be worse.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>The mechanism of action of strength training</h2>

<p>Strength training affects the body fat mass by means of several mechanisms:</p>

<ol>
<li><em>Energy consumption during the workout</em>. Rising iron or doing other exercise, you expend calories. Spend an extra 400-500 calories per day, you will lose weight faster.</li>
<li><em>Accelerate metabolism</em>. Surely you&rsquo;ve noticed that even after 1-2 hours after exercise, you still feel like you are out of the heat. This is a consequence of accelerated metabolism. Increased heat indicates an increased calorie consumption per unit time. That is, even in a state of rest after returning from the gym, you lose weight.</li>
<li><em>Build muscle</em>. Regular classes are usually weightlifting increases muscle mass man. The higher it is, the greater will be the average daily calorie consumption.</li>
</ol>


<p>We should not suppose that only one sport can give yourself a great figure. If your body a lot of fat, in addition to strength training diet is necessary. Classes burn an average of 500 kcal per day in addition to the primary energy consumption. At the same time with the diet can be reduced energy input into the body to 1000 kcal per day and more.</p>

<p>The diet is more effective for weight loss than weight training. But these methods of weight loss can not be opposed to each other. You will achieve maximum results, combining them. Combining sport, proper nutrition, supplementation, adjusting lifestyle, you will lose weight more quickly, and this process will become more natural.</p>

<p>Men are much more likely to engage in weight training than women. This is quite a natural phenomenon, because the stronger sex to have a good figure, should have developed musculature. At the same time big biceps women scare men rather than attract, so the girls better to lose weight with the help of kardionagruzok.</p>

<p>Strength training for men may include:</p>

<ul>
<li>Training with a barbell: bench press, deadlift, wide grip pull-up to his chest, curl with reverse grip barbell bench press standing because of the head;</li>
<li>Training with dumbbells: lunges, squats, curl with dumbbells standing on a bench, dumbbells swings to the side lying, divorce dumbbells;</li>
<li>Exercises using own weight: twisting, pulling on the bar, push-ups, sit-ups.</li>
</ul>


<p>It is advisable to go to the gym and worked under the guidance of coach as weight training require specific knowledge and skills. They help to achieve higher sports results while avoiding overtraining, injury and loss of motivation. Although the house is also possible to lose weight and be sure to purchase this post with a bench and dumbbells.</p>

<p>Women can also be used for weight loss weight training. It should be remembered that too much muscle hypertrophy, especially in the back and arms, will not make the figure more beautiful. Therefore, exercise must be carried out primarily at strengthening the muscles of the legs, buttocks, abdomen, chest.</p>

<p>Women weight training can achieve the following results:</p>

<ul>
<li>Make the legs more slender;</li>
<li>Become more confident, get rid of complexes.</li>
</ul>


<p>For successful weight loss is recommended for women to alternate weight training and cardio training. Catching weightlifting, girls can not build muscle as well as men. This prevents both hormones, and differences in the structure of the muscle fibers. Women have less endurance-they are not able to exercise for one to burn as many calories as men.</p>

<p>Optimum training schedule for weight loss:</p>

<ul>
<li>1-2 times a week - trip to the gym and doing exercises with dumbbells and barbell;</li>
<li>2-3 times a week - cardio training (bike, running, skating);</li>
<li>Every day - walking 30 minutes or more.</li>
</ul>


<p>Be aware of the need for dieting. Training usually increase the appetite, so you have to control your diet conscious.</p>

<p>Strength training may be used as a method of weight loss. It allows you to spend a lot of energy during exercise, temporarily speeds up the metabolism, it helps to build muscle mass. As a method of weight loss, strength training are more suited to men than to women, because the beauty of their figures is largely dependent on the amount of muscle. In addition, they have more stamina for regular and sustained exercise. Women desirable to combine strength training with cardio: running, training on a stationary bike, swimming, skating, aerobics.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corrective Underwear Abdomen and Waist]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/corrective-underwear-abdomen-and-waist/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-02T13:58:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/corrective-underwear-abdomen-and-waist</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/corrective-underwear-abdomen-and-waist/corrective-underwear-abdomen-and-waist.jpg" title="Corrective underwear abdomen and waist" alt="Corrective underwear abdomen and waist">Corrective underwear - is clothing for women, which hides figure flaws. More often than not buy it because of the extra weight. Corrective underwear hides fat folds, reduce the number of waist circumference, to give a figure more slender look. Some manufacturers of such clothing argue that it promotes weight loss or getting rid of cellulite, which is not true.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Linen can be of different types, depending on the problem area, where it will be used.</p>

<p>To improve the appearance of the abdomen is the best choice corsets, kombidressy, shorts with a high waist.</p>

<p>The main mechanism of action of corrective underwear abdomen and waist - is concealing folds of fat and improve body contours. Some unscrupulous manufacturers also indicate in the advertisement that the clothes by nanotechnology or massage promotes weight loss and improvement of women. It is not true.</p>

<p>Benefits of using corrective underwear, compared with the actual weight loss:</p>

<ul>
<li>Immediate effect - it does not need to wait for weeks or months;</li>
<li>You can quickly improve the figure before the holiday, corporate, date or an important business meeting.</li>
</ul>


<p>The disadvantages of using corrective underwear:</p>

<ul>
<li>There is no improvement of health;</li>
<li>There is no significant change in body contours - the effect is very moderate;</li>
<li>Uncomfortable to wear - underwear compresses the body.</li>
</ul>


<p>The correct choice of corrective underwear - this is very important as picking the wrong size, you can not improve, but on the contrary, visually impair the figure. Apart from the size, you should pay attention to:</p>

<ul>
<li>Fabric - Linen has slimming properties, and it should not lose elasticity after a few days of use;</li>
<li>An inner layer - underwear should be comfortable to wear, not to provoke sweating, do not rub the skin;</li>
<li>The thickness of the fabric - do not buy the warm summer corrective underwear;</li>
<li>The degree of tightening - if necessary, buy rigid correction underwear corset with black inserts and a silicone impregnation;</li>
<li>Absence of seams, which can be seen under clothing.</li>
</ul>


<p>Note that corrective underwear vendors often provide unreasonable promises about the results of its use. In particular, it is often argued that visually you reduce 2 sizes. That&rsquo;s not true, this effect is not possible. Reducing waist circumference will be minimal. The main purpose of corrective underwear - it is smoothing the contours of the body, rather than contraction.</p>

<p>It is not necessary to wear a corrective underwear abdomen and waist during pregnancy, damaged or rash on the skin at the site of the alleged contact with the tissue. It should not be too zealous in the use of such clothing. No need to wear it for too long and too often - it can negatively affect the skin condition. Exerting pressure on the body, corrective underwear thereby impairs blood circulation and may eventually worsen the appearance of cellulite.</p>

<p>Corrective underwear is designed to improve the appearance of women. It hides the fat folds, smoothing the contours of the body. This significant reduction in waist circumference does not occur. Shaping lingerie gives a temporary result. It can not be an alternative to weight loss and is not conducive to it. The clothes should be taken only in size. If it is less or more than you need, you can worsen rather than improve the appearance of the figure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tea Weight Loss Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/tea-weight-loss-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-02T09:53:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/tea-weight-loss-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/tea-weight-loss-diet/tea-weight-loss-diet.jpg" title="Tea weight loss diet" alt="Tea weight loss diet">Tea diet - it is a method of losing weight by drinking tea for several days. It is presented in different versions, and almost all of them are designed for rapid weight loss due to the complete failure of the food or the strong reduction of caloric intake. Estimated fat burning effect is achieved both through the restrictions in food, and because of the beneficial effects of tea on the figure.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The essence of the most popular tea diet is only one use of tea for 3 days. There are many versions of this diet where the drink is chosen black or green, used with or without sugar, restricted or permitted in any quantity.</p>

<p>There are varieties of tea diets designed for a longer period - 7 or 14 days, and some embodiments include, in addition to the use of beverage foodstuffs. But the most common is still a tea diet for 3 days. Its rules:</p>

<ul>
<li>The day you can drink six cups of tea;</li>
<li>Black tea should be taken - in which case an additional fat-burning effect is provided by the presence of caffeine in it;</li>
<li>Relies on a cup of tea spoon of sugar.</li>
</ul>


<p>This diet is too short to be able to talk about significant weight loss. Maybe it can help you get rid of 0.5 kg of fat per 3 days, but better results can hardly count. Although the scale, you will see more impressive numbers, in fact pitches due to a greater extent the devastation of the intestine, for you for three days without eating, although there continue to visit the toilet.</p>

<p>Positive aspects of the tea diet:</p>

<ol>
<li>Quick results. Tea diet can be used in cases where the 3 days you will visit an important event where you want to look a little better than it really is. Due to the devastation you have multiple bowel reduced belly, which will get into smaller clothes. But keep in mind that after the return of the form of diet, because the intestine is filled again.</li>
<li>With respect to good tolerability when compared to other diets generally do not provide meals. Lack of strong hunger is provided on one side of caffeine contained in tea leaves, on the other - sugar. It comes in small portions at regular intervals, thereby allowing time to time to reduce hunger by increasing the level of glucose in the blood.</li>
<li>A small duration. Tea diet is harmful to health. Well, it only lasts for 3 days. Perhaps, during this time you will not have time to earn gastritis and disrupt your metabolism.</li>
</ol>


<p>There is a diet in which the tea is used in conjunction with milk. It is believed that it itself has fat burning properties and impact positively on the figure even without dieting. But this is nothing more than rumors - milk tea has the same effect on weight, such as milk and tea, drunk alone.</p>

<p>Recipe tea with milk to the diet is very simple: take the tea leaves, place in a teapot, but does not fill with water as you usually do, and boiled milk.</p>

<p>There are plenty of diets based on the consumption of tea with milk. They mainly involve the reception throughout the day 1.5 liters of the drink without eating food. The difference lies in the duration. Sometimes diet offered to observe three days, sometimes - 5 or 7 days.</p>

<p>Some advise once a week to arrange a fasting day on milk and tea, and this option is the most preferred. It is not harmful to health, reduces the total number of calories consumed per week, and most importantly - constantly promotes weight loss and long-term, if you practice these regularly fasting days.</p>

<p>Most tea diets are stupid, harmful and ineffective. They come only to those who are on his body only 1-2 kg of excess weight. In this way, they can be quickly reset, and this is really hungry enough for only 3-4 days. All other tea diet, including the use of milk is not recommended because:</p>

<ul>
<li>The effect of these weak and temporary;</li>
<li>Such diets harmful to health;</li>
<li>A number of consecutive days, hungry and poorly tolerated at all discourage the human desire for further weight loss.</li>
</ul>


<p>Thus, from the tea diet can get more harm than good. Moreover, not only for health but also for the figure, because the diet with poor tolerability undermine motivation.</p>

<p>However, the above does not apply to schemes slimming day using the tea with sugar or milk. Fasting days on this drink once a week to help control weight. In combination with other measures aimed at reducing body weight, they contribute to the full normalization of the figure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
