<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-11-10T19:27:17+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 7 conditions for victory over hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/top-7-conditions-for-victory-over-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-10T19:22:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/top-7-conditions-for-victory-over-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/top-hemorrhoid-treatment/3.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Top hemorrhoid treatment" alt="Top 7 conditions for victory over hemorrhoids"> Medical experts from the Office of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), the United States, called the 7 rules that will help prevent and cure hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Do not read in the bathroom. The study showed that 35% of Americans take with them into the toilet Ipad.
Use the special napkins during a visit to the toilet or wet toilet paper. This protects the sore from too much stimulation sites. Avoid paper and napkins with an aromatic fragrance and alcohol.
Be aware of hygiene: take a warm bath and then take care of the dryness of the anus to avoid friction sensitive tissues.
Go to the toilet every time when you feel the urge to defecate. Delay chair helps increase pressure on the weakened veins, ie, worsening of hemorrhoids.
Avoid constipation: Drink plenty of water, eat foods rich in fiber.
Move more. Activity helps to reduce the pressure on the veins, as well as get rid of the excess weight that contributes to hemorrhoids.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to treat hemorrhoids at home?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-treat-hemorrhoids-at-home/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-10T18:57:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-treat-hemorrhoids-at-home</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/home-cure-for-hemorrhoids/2.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Home cure for hemorrhoids" alt="How to treat hemorrhoids at home?"> For home cure for hemorrhoids treatment include the use of warm baths, medicinal herbal preparations, ointments, creams and suppositories. So how to treat hemorrhoids at home?</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Sitz baths</h2>

<p>Warm water relaxes the sphincter muscles, it can also help soothe the pain associated with hemorrhoids speaking.</p>

<p><strong>Usage:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Fill the tub to the third warm water.</li>
<li>Do not add anything to the water.</li>
<li>Sit in the bath for 15 minutes.</li>
<li>Repeat the procedure several times a day.</li>
</ul>


<p>When the hemorrhoid pain, hip bath &ndash; it&rsquo;s the best and easiest way to get quick relief.</p>

<h2>Using petrolatum or zinc oxide</h2>

<p>Studies have shown that petroleum jelly and/or zinc oxide works best for hemorrhoids than any other expensive creams. To reduce the pain and swelling of hemorrhoids, you can use both tools at the same time.</p>

<p><strong>Usage:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>After cleaning the skin of the anal region, apply a small amount of petroleum jelly or zinc oxide deposited on a cotton swab to the swollen places.</li>
</ul>


<p>Another popular recipe. In order to &ldquo;get rid&rdquo; of hemorrhoids enough to buy at the pharmacy vial zinc ointment, put a little more in the plastic cover and then add five drops of tincture of peppermint and as much butter. Components mixed for several hours and put in the freezer. After a while you need to get the mixture from the refrigerator and cut into slices, in the form of suppositories to be inserted into the anal canal at night. For the treatment usually lasts 2-4 caps.</p>

<ul>
<li>Keep the swollen area clean and dry. Do not use scented toilet paper, soap or gel for the body, containing chemicals clinically proven that they are harmful to irritated skin.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Herbal home cure for hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>The most frequent cause of hemorrhoids is a low fiber content, resulting in constipation, whereby chair hardens, and it is difficult to pass through the large intestine. Psyllium, or psyllium seeds, are high in fiber, which essentially helps make stools soft, and easily passable. Psyllium seeds help prevent hemorrhoids and also to make bowel movements less painful. Those interested in how to treat hemorrhoids at home, it is recommended that the seed husks have become a part of your daily diet. Plantain seeds can be easily found in most pharmacies.</p>

<p><strong>Usage:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Start taking a teaspoon of psyllium with a glass of water in the morning as part of your breakfast for a week.</li>
<li>During the second week, add another glass of seeds to your dinner.</li>
<li>Slowly and carefully enter the third glass of the third week, and make the adoption of psyllium three times a day, your longstanding habit.</li>
<li>When you have begun to take psyllium seed at 3 times a day, you do not need to take any &ndash; or other add-ons. Make sure that you drink plenty of water when taking psyllium or any other type of fiber because fiber softens the stool by absorbing water. It is recommended to drink 50 grams of water per kilogram of your body weight in a day.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Avoid sweat and strain</h3>

<p>Do not try to make a bowel movement, if you do not feel like doing it. And do not spend a lot of time on the toilet than is required for a bowel movement without straining. Once your intestines freed sufficiently, and do not exert yourself.</p>

<h3>Try different positions</h3>

<p>It has been suggested that squatting in the toilet during a bowel movement is a more natural position than sitting on the toilet. Some people believe that maintaining feet on a small foot, and stretching the knees toward the chest, good help for those interested in how to treat hemorrhoids at home.</p>

<h3>Heed the call of nature</h3>

<p>On the other hand, do not wait too long.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How long to cure hemorrhoids?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-long-to-cure-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-10T18:49:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-long-to-cure-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-long-to-cure-hemorrhoids/1.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="How long do hemorrhoids last" alt="How long to cure hemorrhoids?"> Many of the people in connection with their professional activities or old age are sedentary throughout the day. That&rsquo;s just the body that is not beneficial. The most annoying thing that can undermine your health in this case, it is hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>After the hemorrhoid formation raises the question: how long do hemorrhoids last? As is the case with any other illness, duration of treatment depends on the stage of the disease and the method by which you will be treated. In no case did not begin treatment on their own. Only a doctor can determine the extent of the disease and will take just a decision about treatment. Hemorrhoids tend to move in the acute form, without any warning, even if you initially tried to treat the most simple form of it.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>In the early stages it is possible to shoot down the pain and itching. In this case, the ice will latch to the anal area or compress the warm water. After defecation is best for 15 minutes to apply a warm bath. But do not overdo it with the temperature as excessively warm water can cause burns to the anal area. A few days is to stay at home and keep bed rest. It is recommended to sleep belly down, placing a pillow under your hips. During defecation should not strain the anus.</p>

<p>How long do hemorrhoids last, if he does not retreat? In the following steps should refer to the drugs that the doctor prescribed. Here each drug in accordance with its capabilities involves different durations of treatment. It may be medications that will reduce the outflow of blood and clots (hemorrhoidal formations), in addition to that, they will function as pain relief. Various creams and ointments should be applied to the anal area with a massage at the same time. Massage also performed with the introduction of candles into the anus for hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>Advanced stages of hemorrhoids are treated with surgery. Such methods resort after medication has no effect. External hemorrhoids are removed only if they are too large scale. The most popular surgical procedure with the appearance of internal hemorrhoids. After removal of the clot will take some time to adapt and overcome the pain in the anal area. It is necessary to strictly follow the diet, not eating spicy and fatty foods, and alcohol.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homeopatic treatment of diseases. Hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/homeopatic-treatment-of-diseases-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-10T17:57:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/homeopatic-treatment-of-diseases-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/homeopathic-remedies-for-hemorrhoids/index.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Homeopathic remedies for hemorrhoids" alt="Homeopatic treatment of diseases. Hemorrhoids"> Hemorrhoid is an inflammation of veins in the rectum, where they expand, so that nodes are formed.</p>

<p>Those at risk for the disease hemorrhoids include obese people, lovers of spicy foods and alcohol, people who are on duty have little move and sit constantly, constantly bearing the weight people (such as housewives), pregnant and nursing mothers, as well as suffering from constipation several distinct stages of the disease.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Stages of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>In the first stage of development and the severity of patients experience itching in the rectum, frequent constipation. Stronger feelings are after weight lifting, spicy food and drinking alcohol.</p>

<p>The second stage is characterized by the appearance of bleeding hemorrhoids fall out, the pain is getting stronger and more.</p>

<p>Sign of the next stage of hemorrhoids &ndash; hemorrhoids do not reduce a, resulting in an thrombosis or necrosis of the veins of the rectum.</p>

<h2>Symptoms of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>The first striking symptom of hemorrhoids &ndash; is bleeding during each act of defecation. Also, patients notice a prolapsed hemorrhoid, a burning sensation and pain in the anus, feeling the presence of a foreign object into the anus and the severity of the groin.</p>

<p>Immediately, we note that emit sharp and chronic hemorrhoids. In acute discomfort of the disease is stronger and brighter, whereas in chronic long can not be felt and gain strength only in certain periods of life. Among the symptoms of acute hemorrhoids also present perianal swelling.</p>

<p>Next, hemorrhoids noted mucus from the anus, and finally, pain hemorrhoids.</p>

<h2>Hemorrhoid treatment drugs classical medicine</h2>

<p>As with any other disease, hemorrhoids are much easier to treat in the early stages. It was in the early periods of the disease can take advantage of non-surgical treatments. When hemorrhoids are very important the correct way of life that takes into account both traditional medicine and homeopathy.</p>

<h2>Lifestyle hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>The first and most important thing for hemorrhoids &ndash; to begin to move more, will be useful not too heavy physical activities, including swimming. From large loads should be avoided, as with alcohol and spicy food.</p>

<p>Do not forget about hygiene. Need to take a shower after each act of defecation on the toilet paper it is desirable to give up.</p>

<p>Diet plays a huge role in the treatment of hemorrhoids. As mentioned above, you need to stop eating bad foods in the diet and increase the number of fruits and vegetables.</p>

<h2>Treatment of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Proper treatment of hemorrhoids in classical medicine depends on what stage of development is a disease. For example, in the early stages to achieve the result by using the drug, but the drugs are aimed primarily at reducing the discomfort, rather than knocking causes disease. They decrease pain, improve blood flow and reduce inflammation. There are local medications such as ointments and candles, and there are those that are taken orally, such as tablets and injections.</p>

<p>As soon as a thrombosis, as indicated by increased pain and discomfort in the anal area, ointments prescribed blood-thinning. The point of this is to not allow the blood to clot. In the case of very heavy bleeding from hemorrhoids begin receiving hemostatic drugs.</p>

<p>Also recommended medications that strengthen the walls of veins, in particular often used Venapro.</p>

<h3>The treatment of hemorrhoids without surgery</h3>

<p>We should also say about treatments for hemorrhoids without surgery, which, like medication, are good only at the initial stages. Today, sclerotherapy is used (in hemorrhoids introduced special substances to fill the lumen and wall adhesion), infrared coagulation (blocking the blood supply to the hemorrhoidal nodes), proximal ligation (ligation of the arteries) and ligation (ligation latex rings). The latter procedure is good even in the third stage of hemorrhoids.</p>

<h3>Surgery for hemorrhoids</h3>

<p>If the disease has gone too far and the application of the methods described above will not give proper result, it is necessary to resort to surgery. Unlike conventional medicine, homeopathic remedies can cure hemorrhoids without surgery, even at the last stage of its development.</p>

<h3>Hemorrhoid Treatment drugs homeopathy</h3>

<p>Many homeopathic remedies for hemorrhoids have been used successfully in the treatment. Tell you about the most common ones.
If the disease worsened, that is passed into the last stage, it should be administered Atsidum muriatikum or hydrochloric acid in the sixth, twelfth and thirtieth dilution.
If hemorrhoids are accompanied by itching and burning, it will help Venapro or capsicum in the third, sixth and twelfth dilution.</p>

<p>When the disease is characterized by a sense of gravity, then appoint Sokotrina aloe or aloes in the third decimal, third and sixth dilution.</p>

<p>When hemorrhoids, accompanied by bleeding, or helps Hamamelis Virginika hamamelis virginiana third decimal, third and sixth dilution, as well as ointments and oils.</p>

<p>In general, the following are recommended for hemorrhoids homeopathic remedies:  Venapro drug combines these medications well.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hemorrhoid home treatment]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoid-home-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T23:36:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoid-home-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When we say the word &ldquo;hemorrhoid&rdquo;, many are experiencing negative, sometimes reaching up to phobias, feelings. However, this disease is not so bad, especially in the early stages. It occurs due to poor nutrition, physical inactivity and sedentary lifestyle. It may be provoke a heredity.</p>

<p>In order to answer the question of how to treat hemorrhoids, you need to give it a clear definition. Hemorrhoids are vascular cavernous body. These are formed in the rectum (in the lower part). Nodes can be internal or external. Simultaneously, at the patient may be present both species, in this case will help only complex treatment.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Characteristically reluctance of a large number of patients to see a doctor in the early stages of this disease. They do not ask how to cure hemorrhoids and how to pick a remedy for hemorrhoids, even experiencing pain and discomfort. However, the need to go to a specialist as soon as possible. It is better to hemorrhoid home treatment, than to resort to complex surgery, which in some cases does not bring the proper favor and alleviate suffering.</p>

<p><strong>In the U.S., 80% of persons with hemorrhoids, the doctor did not address</strong></p>

<p>There are four stages of this disease:</p>

<ol>
<li>The formation hemorrhoid nodes inside the rectum (internal hemorrhoids);</li>
<li>There is a loss of nodes of the rectum after a bowel movement, they themselves reduce a back;</li>
<li>The nodes do not reduce a own but it can still be done with your fingers;</li>
<li>Impossible to reduce fallen nodes (external hemorrhoids).</li>
</ol>


<p>Effective hemorrhoid home treatment is possible only on the first and second stages. On the third and fourth often have to resort to surgery.</p>

<p>In spite of the obvious symptoms of many ill in no hurry to seek medical help. They will not go to the doctor, as a result, they develop hemorrhoids third and fourth stage. For some reason, some people think hemorrhoids are something shameful. They hide their illness from others. This trend is not exclusive to the United States, but also in many European countries. However it is better to learn from experts how to treat hemorrhoids, rather than later hospital treatment needed or, worse, in the outpatient and dispensary observation.</p>

<p>Today, a large amount of useful information on how to cure hemorrhoids, can also find on the Internet. In a network there are enough sites on which there is information about the problem of the disease, the mechanisms of its development, prevention methods and hemorrhoid home treatment.</p>

<h2>How to treat hemorrhoids. The main methods</h2>

<ol>
<li>Non-medical impact. Effective only in the early stages, is to change the lifestyle and diet, increasing physical activity.</li>
<li>Drug therapeutic impact.</li>
<li>Reducing the pressure in the anal canal (the means for doing so are drug «Venapro» and ointments such as Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Locoid etc.).</li>
<li>Non-surgical methods of influence.</li>
<li>Surgical treatment.</li>
</ol>


<p>In the early stages of the disease and as a prophylactic course after surgical treatment is <strong>very effective natural product «Venapro»</strong>.</p>

<p>Identify hemorrhoids simply by the following symptoms:
&ndash; Bleeding during bowel movements, blood in faeces.
&ndash; The occurrence of burning and itching in the anal area.
&ndash; Pain when sitting, walking, bowel movements.
&ndash; The emergence of a sense of gravity or presence of a foreign body in the rectum.
&ndash; Inflammation of hemorrhoid nodes. They be palpated, this gives rise to pain.
&ndash; Occurs loss of nodes of the rectum.</p>

<p>It should, as soon as possible, seek medical attention if these symptoms.</p>

<h2>Hemorrhoid home treatment. Traditional methods</h2>

<p>The use drug treatment is usually only gives a relief of symptoms of the disease in the third and fourth stages. To effectively deal with hemorrhoids, you need to use an integrated approach.</p>

<p>Modern medicine offers to hemorrhoid home treatment is not only tablets but also in other ways. In the early stages helps to get rid of the pain and reduce inflammation of the nodes special diet. Of the food exclude alcohol, spicy and fatty foods, condiments and spices. A diet enriched with plant-based diet high fiber content. Recommended for early hemorrhoids long walks, special exercises, including squats, press load, tilts, etc. It is necessary to make a thorough hygiene of the anus after defecation.</p>

<p>However, the disease exacerbation of those measures will not be enough. In the acute form of hemorrhoid home treatment will require the use of anal suppositories, ointments, and cold lotions. When it is impossible to stop the periodic occurrence of venous bleedings knots injected sclerosing solutions.</p>

<p>By resorting to surgery only in cases where there are prolonged and severe bleeding, constantly drop nodes, at a jamming. All the same any form of treatment is useless if you do not aimed at removing underlying causes of the disease. They only temporarily make easier the patient&rsquo;s condition, reduce pain and symptoms.</p>

<p>In the complex treatment of hemorrhoids is to include products «Venapro &ndash; Hemorrhoid formula». It is especially effective in the early stages of the disease.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hemorrhoids. Natural remedy for hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoids-natural-remedy-for-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T23:28:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoids-natural-remedy-for-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Along with balms, ointments and compresses, which can be used for hemorrhoids, there are tablets and capsules. You do not need a prescription to obtain them. You can order these products via the Internet, or buy them at your local health food store, or through distributors, that deal with Chinese medicinal substances.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Understand that surgery should not be the only opportunity. There are many safe and effective, organic and natural remedy for hemorrhoids, you should try, before you decide to go under the knife. If the Chinese can not suffer from hemorrhoids, why can not you too? Here I will describe those drugs with which I had to read, and the use of which, I quickly went to the amendment. By the treatment of hemorrhoids must be approached comprehensively. In these natural medicines, it is natural! Instead of synthetic, with which the market is oversaturated, contain active components that promote rapid healing of hemorrhoids wall units and. Let&rsquo;s get started!</p>

<p><strong>Hemorrhoid Quick Peace Tablet</strong>. This product is used for both internal and external hemorrhoids. Stops bleeding and pain, reduces swelling, as well as weakens the bowel movements. It contains: root ampelopsisa, Sophora flower, sumac, black beans and pig bile. Dosage &ndash; 4 pills 3 times a day.</p>

<p><strong>Notoginseng Hemorrhoids-Transforming Pill</strong>. This product also stops the bleeding and swelling of both types of hemorrhoids. Dosage &ndash; 3 grams, 2 to 3 times a day. It contains: Notoginseng, the imperative and groundsel.</p>

<p><strong>Venapro</strong> relieves the symptoms of hemorrhoids; contains ingredients vitamin E, zinc oxide, L-Argine, horse chestnut, oat straw, Plaintain, Cascara Sagrada, blueberries, mullein, cayenne pepper. Please note that Venapro is not only intended for temporary relief, and can be used to eliminate the causes of hemorrhoids.</p>

<p><strong>Avatrol</strong> educes the severity of symptoms, as well as a reduced risk of the disease returning. Contains: buckeye, arginine, oat straw, Cascara Sagrada, blueberries, butcher&rsquo;s broom, mullein, cayenne pepper, and zinc. Perfect for the relief of symptom.</p>

<p><strong>Hem-Relief</strong> natural product that helps reduce swelling and inflammation. Contains: horse chestnut leaves and roots of ginger.</p>

<p><strong>Hemorrease</strong> is a powerful anti-inflammatory agent, used to reduce the symptoms of hemorrhoids, with ingredients such as: White oak bark, butcher&rsquo;s broom, witch hazel, Pipa.</p>

<p>As you can see, most of these natural remedy for hemorrhoids are very popular ingredients that promote healing. The use of these drugs &ndash; one of the ways to deal with hemorrhoids. Typically, a doctor writes a prescription rather strong medications that have a number of side effects, because contain a synthetic material comprising.</p>

<p>All of these products, as you can see, assist in the elimination of the symptoms of hemorrhoids. Remember, only natural remedy are able to cure and eliminate the cause of hemorrhoids, be sure to read them. The fact that commonly prescribed doctors only, which is advantageous since get kickbacks from pharmacies as a percentage of sales. Should not be the subjects in this dirty business. Think how much money you&rsquo;ll save!</p>

<p>Remember, hemorrhoids can come back! In spite of all natural products, or recipes that you use, you need to make changes in your diet and lifestyle, if you want to get rid of him once and for all. Many have already done so, now it&rsquo;s your turn!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Herbal remedies for hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/herbal-remedies-for-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T23:24:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/herbal-remedies-for-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hemorrhoids &ndash; a common disease that affects more than half of the population. While hemorrhoids are not yet entered the stage when conservative methods do not work, need to focus on such a method of treatment to avoid injury.</p>

<p>Hemorrhoids can be internal and external. Internal hemorrhoids &ndash; is modified vessels, hemorrhoids, which are located inside the rectum and are not visible from the anus. External hemorrhoids – are nodes that fall out, you can find with your fingers, and their doctors see perfectly without any instruments.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>For the treatment of internal and external hemorrhoids is quite widely used tablet form, giving good results. Tablets from hemorrhoids often include natural ingredients that are safe for pregnant women and older people. In times of acute illness and cracks can be used painkillers for hemorrhoids. Consider the most famous and effective pill for hemorrhoids, as in the treatment of hemorrhoids tablets also have a major role.</p>

<p>Venapro – fitodrug, comes in tablet form and as a spray. The structure of this drug include herbal extracts, which strengthen the walls of blood vessels. Venapro stop bleeding, anti-inflammatory action. With these pills improves sensation during defecation &ndash; out voltage disappears itching and burning sensation in the anal area. Thus Venapro pills help the digestive process and the actual. The drug should be used within three weeks &ndash; then it will be the first results. Consistent effect can be achieved in about 3-6 months of reception these pills.</p>

<p>If hemorrhoids are fairly long and progressive, it requires preparation with a wide spectrum of action, which would get rid of the multiple symptoms of hemorrhoids immediately. It is a drug Pilex. Its components have anti-inflammatory, analgesic and hemostatic effect. As part of Pilex tablet natural herbal ingredients that have a beneficial effect on the vascular wall. Increasing the turgor of capillaries, respectively, and reduced the number of swollen.</p>

<p>Tablets with hemorrhoids have several indisputable advantages. First, they can be used anytime and anywhere. Secondly, the tablet is more convenient in terms of use. Often it happens that sitting at work there is a need to take a pill. After all, why would you go to the toilet every day, several times to lubricate the anus and remove itching. Therefore, blisters of pills are very comfortable &ndash; they are always on hand, can only take a pill in case of aggravation.</p>

<p>Tablets of hemorrhoids include not only chemical substances, but also useful natural components, by which healing is much faster and more efficient. Pill is easier to use for older single people who can not serve themselves qualitatively. However, it is important to remember that the tablets of the hemorrhoid doctor should prescribe that the data collected survey makes the choice to certain drugs. In any case, do not despair &ndash; among all the different products you can always find exactly the pill that will relieve you from hemorrhoids permanently.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consequences of birth: ruptures and hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/consequences-of-birth-ruptures-and-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T23:20:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/consequences-of-birth-ruptures-and-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Unfortunately, not all women after childbirth fine. There are some side effects to deal with that would not like anyone, but often still have to. Of course all of this vremennoya phenomenon, but it has to be properly experienced.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>The three most common problems are:</p>

<ul>
<li>Perineum dissection,</li>
<li>Ruptures soft tissue crotch,</li>
<li>Hemorrhoids.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Perineum dissection and ruptures</h2>

<p>It often happens that in the process of childbirth maternity make a neat incision or does it turn out breaks. At these places later stitches.</p>

<p>If you stitches, then you should know how to look after them:</p>

<ul>
<li>Joints must be kept clean and dry. Bowl gasket change, and even better throw a &ldquo;ventilation&rdquo;;</li>
<li>When taking a shower, watch the water would not fall into the vagina;</li>
<li>Outer seams are very well cleaned chamomile, calendula;</li>
<li>The first two months of getting out of bed very carefully and do not make any sudden movements;</li>
<li>If the outer seams &ndash; the first two weeks is not recommended to sit;</li>
<li>Does not in any way lift heavy;</li>
<li>Breastfeed better lying down;</li>
</ul>


<p>During the healing you can feel the pain slack, but if you suddenly become joint pain fester and worsen, immediately consult a gynecologist. If the scars are large and hard to soften the suit light massage with the infusion of herbs. Just do Kegel exercises, they will help restore elasticity of the skin.</p>

<h2>Hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Hemorrhoids &ndash; varicose veins in the form of a nodule in the anus. This problem can affect you during pregnancy and during labor, and after them. If you are faced with such a sensitive issue, do not despair. Of course, you need to see a doctor.</p>

<p>In addition to expert advice will help you:</p>

<ul>
<li>Take a warm bath with herbal infusions in a sitting position. However, it can be done only after the post-partum end up in isolation.</li>
<li>Apply directly to the trouble spot fitoled.</li>
<li>As well help herbal compresses.</li>
<li>Avoid constipation. Include in your diet: beets, baked apples, sea cabbage, cereals.</li>
<li>Avoid strenuous exercise.</li>
<li>Perform Kegel exercises.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get rid of hemorrhoids for good]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-get-rid-of-hemorrhoids-for-good/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T23:16:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-get-rid-of-hemorrhoids-for-good</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How to get rid of hemorrhoids at home, so do not bother hemorrhoids bumps and could sit comfortably. All patients with hemorrhoids like this, but not all in this endeavor. Hemorrhoids insidious disease and calls for a serious approach. The systematic application of the treatment and the combination of its different variants and persistence will help get rid of hemorrhoids for good.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>How to get rid of hemorrhoids at home for good</h2>

<p>When a sedentary job or lifestyle, diet does not promote healing. Here we have to solve each: what is more important &ndash; the health or human weakness.
Traditional medicine is armed with a lot of good recipes from hemorrhoids. They all help to eliminate the bleeding, reduce inflammation cones. Unfortunately, a family history of venous varicose vein walls and fine win easy, but you can.</p>

<h2>How to get rid of hemorrhoids for good, old-fashioned recipe:</h2>

<p>This is an old recipe to effectively treat hemorrhoids. To get rid of the disease must be made within 40 days without missing a single day, drink 1 tbsp 2 times a day for an hour before eating corn oil.</p>

<h2>How to get rid of hemorrhoids for good with a normal garlic:</h2>

<p>Get the great big clove of garlic, mash it in a frog, add a little boiling water and this fluid lubricate the anus outside and inside. Very much will burn, but for 2-3 hours you get rid of hemorrhoids for good.</p>

<p>After dinner, at eight o&#8217;clock in the evening, and can be a little early to take a pack of black pepper powder (20 g), pour into a glass and pour warm, room temperature water to the brim. Interfere with a teaspoon, until a homogeneous mass and drink all at once. You will burn in your mouth as if you ate the soup with pepper, and then, while you&rsquo;re watching TV &ndash; will be held.
But then nothing can neither eat nor drink. Go to bed in the morning, when you go to the toilet a lot, you will have to tweak the anus &ndash; is good, your hemorrhoids will disappear forever.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ice and cold water as an effective remedy for hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/ice-and-cold-water-as-an-effective-remedy-for-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T23:12:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/ice-and-cold-water-as-an-effective-remedy-for-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A fun way to treat hemorrhoids came to us from the Caucasus. Severe Highlanders got rid of the disease by means of which was always at hand &ndash; clean water. More precisely, no water, and ice &ndash; the perfect material for making candles.</p>

<p>The impact on hemorrhoids low temperatures is very effective.
Ice is able to stop the bleeding, to neutralize the pain, prevent further progression of the disease.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>The main thing in this process &ndash; accuracy; careless use of candles ice can cause serious damage to your intestines.</p>

<p>Therefore, in the manufacture of candles to observe the following rules:</p>

<ul>
<li>Candles are made as follows: rolled tube of paper, filled with water and placed in the freezer.</li>
<li>Once the water is completely frozen, the remains of a paper form with the scraping pieces of ice, and it becomes suitable for use.</li>
<li>Candles should be of small diameter to avoid excessive stretching of the walls of the anus. The procedure is the introduction of ice rods can not be called pleasant, so no need to exacerbate feelings.</li>
<li>Before the introduction of candles Break off the sharp tip and chamfer the place of breaking up. Otherwise you risk serious damage to the intestines sharp icicles.</li>
<li>Do not overdo the candle. The first procedure should last no longer than 25-30 seconds. Subsequently, their duration can be increased to one &ndash; one and a half minutes.</li>
</ul>


<p>Modern medicine also does not deny the use of ice and its effectiveness in the fight against hemorrhoids. To optimize the treatment of hemorrhoids with ice, developed a special instrument. It is a plastic tube filled with liquid to freeze. It melts more slowly than regular water, thus increasing the procedure. This contributes to the material of construction of the tube.</p>

<p>No need to touch the ice directly to the affected area to reduce discomfort and get rid of the risk colds.</p>

<p>Cold water can be used to alleviate pain and in the liquid state. Bath lasting 3-5 minutes (sitting in a basin) can be used in conjunction with almost any other folk remedies. In the water you can add a cube of potassium permanganate: this eliminates the risk of further irritation.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colonoscopy and hemorrhoids - effective diagnostic method]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/colonoscopy-and-hemorrhoids-effective-diagnostic-method/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T23:09:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/colonoscopy-and-hemorrhoids-effective-diagnostic-method</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Colonoscopy &ndash; an excellent diagnosis of hemorrhoids. To detect internal hemorrhoidal nodes enough rectoscopy (using proctoscope). Colonoscopy and hemorrhoids is performed to diagnose problems of the colon and the sigmoid colon, located above the rectum, which can not be examined rectoscope. But we should not forget that this procedure is carried out not only for diagnostic purposes. It allows you to make removal of polyps and stop excessive bleeding. Colonoscopy and hemorrhoids is usually carried out just when we need it urgently to stop the bleeding, cauterize varice. This procedure is performed to confirm the diagnosis, as well as in cases of suspected presence of other gastrointestinal diseases (ulcers, tumors, Crohn&rsquo;s disease, etc.).</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Colonoscopy helps proctologist make a visual assessment of the colon mucosa her. An additional advantage &ndash; the ability to perform therapeutic manipulation, up to the removal of tumors, recanalization of the sigmoid colon.
Extraction of foreign bodies. The device, which is made by examination &ndash; a colonoscope. The apparatus comprises a flexible probe of the LEDs. He &ldquo;knows&rdquo; how to take photos, guides you through the fence on the analysis of tissue (biopsy), remove growths of tissue. Image of the surface of the colon is displayed on the computer screen.</p>

<p>Colonoscopy &ndash; is one of the most important methods of diagnosis of sigmoid, colon and rectum. Doctors offering this procedure, based on the following symptoms:</p>

<p>Blood in the stool (typical symptoms of hemorrhoids, and many other diseases);
Difficulty in bowel movements (constipation);
State of intoxication (weakness, loss of appetite);
Diseases of rectum and colon in history, polyps;
Diarrhea;
Sharp loss of total body weight.</p>

<p>Procedure has no contraindications. Side effects in rare cases, a puncture of the bowel wall. The time of the diagnosis from an hour to one hour. If an outpatient colonoscopy, the patient waits in the hospital a couple of hours. In order to be able to in the event of fever, dizziness, abdominal pain, bleeding, consult a doctor immediately.</p>

<p>Patients over 50 years as a regular colonoscopy shows the annual survey. In the presence of family pathologies line the colon should begin to be surveyed before, without waiting for the first call from serious illness.
Assigning you to this procedure, the doctor decided to dispel the doubts he had accumulated, to confirm or reject the diagnosis. Medical error &ndash; the serious consequences for the body.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foods for hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/foods-for-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T22:51:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/foods-for-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If you want your life to be fulfilling and not different from that of healthy people, and you have such a disease, such as hemorrhoids, then you should choose the right nutrition. Poor nutrition with this diagnosis can aggravate and worsen the quality of life. To this did not happen, you need to radically restructure the principles of supply.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Meals should occur every 2-2.5 hours, the feed should have 6 times a day. Foods for hemorrhoids should be selected taking into account the course of the disease it is your.</p>

<p>Vegetables, fruits and cereals should be the basis of your diet. Of cereals should be consumed buckwheat, oats, barley. You can eat bread, but made from wheat flour. Such dish like pasta use is not prohibited, but the quantity should be limited, as well as potatoes. As for vegetables, there is a list of products is quite large. Cucumbers, squash, beets, carrots, cauliflower, broccoli &ndash; all this can be eaten both raw and cooked.</p>

<p>The list of fruits as well weighty enough. It includes apples, prunes, bananas, dried apricots, apricot. To meet organism dietary fiber in the diet should include a product as bran. Bran can be rye, oat or wheat. They need to eat at least 60 grams of adding oatmeal, or diluted with water to mushy state.</p>

<p>Foods for hemorrhoids include and meat. But you need to use it in boiled or steamed. The meat should be chosen not fat varieties.</p>

<p>A must in the diet of people with the disease is a product like vegetable oil. It stimulates colonic contractions. Required list also includes the use of water in an amount not less than 2-2.5 liters per day. If your weight is a little more than you need, the amount of water consumed should be increased. Fasting should drink every morning a glass of cool water to improve bowel movements.</p>

<p>Any dairy products will perfectly support the work of your intestines. If they are rich in bifidobacteria and lactobacilli, it will be well to maintain the balance of microflora. Not restricted juices and fruit drinks, but do not abuse them.</p>

<h2>What products can not be hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>If no proper nutrition can make it difficult for the disease. In order not to complicate your life, you should avoid products containing animal proteins. Do not abuse the fish, meat and eggs. It is necessary to give up alcohol. In order not to cause bloating, eliminate from your diet grapes, turnips, radish and brown bread. Refuse need from coffee and strong tea, so as not to cause constipation.</p>

<p>What products can not be haemorrhoids, depends on the extent and severity of the disease. Strongly sparing diet is also not recommended, as you can break the evacuation function of the intestine. Admission sweets just want to restrict. During an exacerbation shows besshlakovaya diet. It should take no more than 2 or 3 days. The protein omelette, boiled meat and broth, dried white rice porridge on the water intake will be of such a diet. In rice porridge allow the addition of a small piece of butter.</p>

<h2>Prohibited foods for hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>There is a list strictly forbidden foods for hemorrhoids. In order not to complicate the course of the disease, should be permanently give up eating certain foods. It is strictly forbidden to eat spicy, salty, pepper, fatty and fried. These products contribute to the expansion of the venous network of the cavernous tissue of the anal area, and violate local blood flow. It will be good if you&rsquo;re using steam method for processing of vegetables and meat, fish and poultry. By forbidden foods for hemorrhoids include any hard or soft carbonated drinks. Breakfast cereals, which contain large amounts of sugar, nutritionists forever excluded from the diet of patients with the disease.</p>

<p>Always remember that choosing the right diet for yourself, you should always consult with a physician. Selection of the diet should come from the specific features of the disease and the individual organism. Independently experiment is not necessary, as it can lead to complications of the disease and its intensification.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treating hemorrhoids at home. Care for hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/treating-hemorrhoids-at-home-care-for-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T22:39:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/treating-hemorrhoids-at-home-care-for-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hemorrhoid treatment at home mainly involves adherence of the day, healthy eating habits and procedures for the relief of symptoms of hemorrhoids, besides requires hemorrhoid care and proper medication.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>A few tips about the hemorrhoid care, which will help with hemorrhoids:</p>

<ul>
<li>Use care soaked with water after defecating white soft toilet paper or baby wipes.</li>
<li>Do not rub in the anal area. Remove what you need warm water in the shower or bidet.</li>
<li>Use baby shampoo to hemorrhoid care and anus that does not contain dyes and flavor.</li>
<li>When the first urge to empty bowels get the opportunity to do so.</li>
<li>Do not rush when defecating, let the body do its own thing.</li>
</ul>


<p>To quickly relieve the itching and pain of hemorrhoids take praperat Venapro. It consists of herbal ingredients necessary for the treatment of hemorrhoids, which makes it, in addition to high efficiency, safe and very convenient preparation (available as tablets and spray).</p>

<p>10 main rules preventing hemorrhoids:</p>

<ul>
<li>Save the stool soft. The best way to prevent and hemorrhoid care is a softening of the stool that they pass easily, thus decreasing pressure and voltage.</li>
<li>Allow the intestines empty itself as soon as possible after the urge to defecate. Relax, let it happen naturally.</li>
<li>Regular physical activity, including regular walking. Imagine you with each passing kilometer hemorrhoids removed from you for two. Admit it, it&rsquo;s worth it!</li>
<li>Follow a simple diet. Lots of water. Not greasy, spicy and salty. A lot of fiber, raw vegetables and fruits. Little ice cream, cheese, white bread.</li>
<li>Avoid constipation. If you have difficulty with the natural bowel movement &ndash; help it, take a laxative, such as Regulaks.</li>
<li>Do not read while sitting on the toilet.</li>
<li>Avoid lifting heavy objects.</li>
<li>During the day make frequent short walks.</li>
<li>Avoid holding your breath during a bowel movement.</li>
<li>Avoid prolonged use of laxatives &ndash; let laxative will be in your medicine cabinet for emergencies.
For the prevention and the care for hemorrhoids should also take Venapro.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
