<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2017-03-12T18:02:28+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Quickly and Properly Lose Weight by Summer]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-quickly-and-properly-lose-weight-by-summer/"/>
    <updated>2017-03-12T16:17:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-quickly-and-properly-lose-weight-by-summer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-quickly-and-properly-lose-weight-by-summer/img.jpg" alt="How to quickly and properly lose weight by summer">Very soon, there will come a season of short skirts, swimsuits and beach photos in social networks. In order to look good in these photos, you need to prepare your body in advance for the summer.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Schedule work front</h2>

<p>Do not expect a miracle. Training for a couple of weeks before the summer, no matter how intense they may be, will not bring any result - only disorders. You need to lose weight in a complex and in advance. And it&rsquo;s better not to start on Monday, but right now. Determine how much you need to lose by the summer - 5 kg, 10 or all 20. And starting from this, make your plan - yourself or with your personal trainer. We need to set ourselves tasks for each week and strive to fulfill them. To control the process of losing weight and provide additional motivation, you can take photos once a week in full growth.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<h2>Healthy food</h2>

<p>You can believe in fairy tales as much as you want, that there are miraculous ways to lose weight without diets, but this is not so. Proper <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-on-cellulose/" title="nutrition">nutrition</a> - in itself already a kind of diet for the body, which is used to chips, chocolates and fried potatoes with ketchup. Therefore, we must abandon the sweet, flour, roast and smoked in favor of products containing protein, as well as herbs, cereals, vegetables and fruits.</p>

<p>The golden rule of a <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/pineapple-diet/" title="healthy">healthy diet</a> is regularity. You need to clearly divide your diet for breakfast, lunch and dinner and give up snacks. If the appetite has greatly developed, you can eat an apple, carrots or just drink a glass of water or a cup of tea.</p>

<p>Also it is necessary to refuse fast food. Dishes cooked with their own hands are more useful, but this requires strength and time, which is not always enough. Instead of buying a cake in the store, it is worth trying a couple of times to cook it in your kitchen. Most likely, this process will seem too laborious for you, and the cake itself will not be so much wanted.</p>

<h2>Doing sports</h2>

<p>One correct diet is not enough. Physical loads will accelerate the process of losing weight and make you more enduring. The easiest option is to buy a subscription for a couple of months in the fitness center. The administrator will help you to create a convenient schedule. Two or three classes a week will be enough to throw off a few kilograms by the summer. In addition, fitness centers can be used not only on simulators. Choose any sport that is closer to you, for example, swimming or aerobics. Girls can sign up for yoga, body-ballet or another kind of dance, where you need to move a lot. If you want to not lose weight, and adjust your <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/" title="figure">figure</a>, it is best to hire a personal trainer who has drawn up a plan of classes and tells you how to eat.</p>

<p>If there is no possibility to go to group or individual lessons, you can go in for sports yourself. On the Internet there is a huge number of master classes from fitness trainers, which will show what exercises you need to perform to achieve your goal. Nobody canceled the old and effective way - morning runs in the park before work and banal exercises in the morning.</p>

<h2>Lead a healthy lifestyle</h2>

<p>A healthy lifestyle is not only about proper nutrition and exercise. To lose weight, you must abandon the frequent use of alcohol. Smoking also does not help losing weight. Ideal - completely get rid of this addiction, or at least significantly reduce the number of cigarettes smoked per day.</p>

<p>People are surrounded by a huge number of irritating factors, not contributing to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/watermelon-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>. It is better to try once again to avoid <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a>, at least for the sake of your figure. And, finally, you need to sleep enough to have a good mood and enough strength to exercise.</p>

<h2>Massages, baths and creams</h2>

<p>Many go to the masseurs, to the sauna or buy expensive cream in the hope of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="rapid weight loss">rapid weight loss</a> without any effort. All this is effective only in conjunction with proper nutrition and exercise. By themselves, these methods are useless and will not yield a significant result.</p>

<p>It is worth to be afraid of various &quot;teas&quot;  for losing weight. No matter how they are advertised in social networks, at best, such a tea will contain diuretics that will simply remove water from the body, at worst - narcotic drugs.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diet for the Skin]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-for-the-skin/"/>
    <updated>2017-02-25T18:50:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-for-the-skin</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/diet-for-the-skin/img.jpg" alt="Diet for the skin">
There are contraindications, consult your doctor.</p>

<p>Every woman wants to have a clean, beautiful, well-groomed, youthful skin. The youngest must be skin on the face, as her <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="every day">every day</a> see the surrounding. To be beautiful, a woman uses cosmetics and skin care products, but this is not always enough. To skin remains smooth and youthful, you need proper <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-on-cellulose/" title="nutrition">nutrition</a>.</p>

<!--more-->




<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Usually <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/" title="diet">diet</a> does not last long - a week, two weeks, a month, sometimes more. Still, any diet sooner or later ends. For beautiful skin one week or one month is not enough nutrition. Follow dietary recommendations you have for life.</p>

<p>Through nutrition, you can not stop the aging process of your skin. You still will be wrinkles, whatever you do. Nature is relentless, and with the passage of time it takes away from the <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet/" title="beauty">beauty</a> of women. But for sure you pay attention, that in 50 years, a woman looks like an old woman, while for the other, the same age as her, still invited on a date a man.</p>

<p>Someone facial skin aging earlier, and someone later. Diet - is one of the ways to keep the skin in good condition. You should consume enough of:</p>

<ol>
<li><p><strong>Vitamins</strong>. Have you ever noticed that the writing on the banks with vitamins pharmaceutical companies? Usually there can be read, that multivitamin preparation will improve the condition of your skin. However, the vitamins can be obtained not only from the cans. They are full of in food. Eat more vegetables, fruits. Regularly eat liver - it has accumulated a huge amount of vitamins.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Water</strong>. When the body lacks fluids, skin becomes dry, limp, ugly. It is necessary to drink water regularly. If your body is constantly in a state of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/dehydration.html" title="dehydration">dehydration</a>, the skin of your face will quickly become flabby and wrinkled.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>PUFAs</strong>. Polyunsaturated fatty acids should be present continuously in the diet. The use flaxseed oil and fish as their source.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Iron</strong>. Do not iron deficiency in the body. It is part of the protein hemoglobin, which carries oxygen. Naturally, the chronic oxygen <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/starvation.html" title="starvation">starvation</a> of the skin over time is not well reflected in your face. Iron is found in:</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Antioxidants</strong>. The substances that destroy free radicals, slow down skin aging. Therefore, your diet must be present in large quantities fruits contain antioxidants in abundance. Many of them also present in green tea.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>Women with problem skin constantly have to deal with the emerging pigmentation in the face, red spots, inflammatory elements. She sweats, gaining weight, and shows the black dots and white pimples. To face skin looked normal, you need to use cosmetics, do cosmetic procedures. But diet is also able to assist in the fight against skin problems.</p>

<p>The following products should be restricted:</p>

<ol>
<li><p><strong>Sweets</strong>. It is believed that the confectionery increase the likelihood of skin inflammatory elements. It is not known, however, these or not. But in any case, limit sweets will not be superfluous, since it is well reflected not only on the face, but also in the <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/" title="figure">figure</a>.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Water in the evening</strong>. Water is essential to the skin of the face lacked moisture. It should not dry. But excess water in the evening will cause swelling on the face in the morning. The more frequently in the morning you will suffer from edema, the faster you will have wrinkles. Therefore, from late teas should be abandoned.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Alcohol</strong>. Alcoholic drinks are harmful to all organs and systems. Of course, alcohol and harm the skin. If you do not believe me, look, it looks like the skin of women who abuse alcohol. 40 They are worse than some 60.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Coffee</strong>. On some sites, you can read that coffee appear on the skin pigmentation. Apparently, this assumption is due to the black beverage. It is unlikely that coffee you will have pigmentation on the face. But for problem skin drink it is harmful, because it enhances the separation of sebum.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Sol</strong>. From her appear edema. For this reason, if you have problem skin, better to limit the intake of salt. This does not mean that you should eat salted insufficiently dishes. Just give up salted fish, chips, cheese suluguni and other products containing salt in excessive quantities.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>There diet for cleaning intestines, kidneys, blood, or whole organism. Diet for cleansing the face too. Another thing is how effective it is? A woman who wants to clean the skin, it is recommended to use:</p>

<p>There are diets that have a duration of 3, 7 or 10 days, and the alleged need to make your skin cleaner. In fact, to purify it, it is not enough food. To do this, you need:</p>

<ul>
<li>treating the skin with special lotions;</li>
<li>visit a beautician and perform cleaning procedures.</li>
</ul>


<p>None of these products, you make eating the skin of your face clean. First of all, you should pay attention to skin care and lifestyle that you lead.</p>

<p>Oily skin - a real problem for women. It should not just wipe the face with a napkin, as a person immediately becomes unkempt appearance. For oily skin, constantly emerging inflammatory elements, and it can not please women. Unfortunately, this problem can not be solved with diet. The skin does not become less oily, if you limit the amount of fat in their diets.</p>

<p><em>You may want to reduce the consumption of the following products:</em></p>

<p>Theoretically, such a diet can make your skin a little less fatty. But in practice, no significant difference you will likely not see. Therefore, use cosmetics, drugs to reduce sebum production, regularly visit a beautician. The only way to significantly reduce the oiliness of the skin and the amount of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/acne.html" title="acne">acne</a> on the face.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glycemic Index Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/glycemic-index-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-19T13:23:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/glycemic-index-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/glycemic-index-diet/img.jpg" alt="glycemic index diet">The nutrition system based on controlling carbohydrates receipts called glycemic index diet: It allows you to quickly lose weight without causing harm to the body.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Diet with a low glycemic index foods: essence, the benefits and features</h2>

<p>The glycemic index (GI) - a measure of the speed of fission products to the further formation of the primary energy source - glucose.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>The higher the glycemic index of the product - the more rapidly digested and glucose is the formation of fatty deposits.</p>

<p>Talking about what is on the glycemic index diet, should take into consideration all its stages:</p>

<ul>
<li>In the first stage we have to eat foods with a low GI, and at that time is the most active fat burning. Duration - two weeks or more, until the desired result is achieved;</li>
<li>In the second stage glycemic index diet meals are resolved with an average GI to consolidate the results. Duration is also not less than 14 days;</li>
<li>The third stage is the output, and at this time permitted high GI foods, but in small quantities. The diet should be based on foods with middle- and low-index.</li>
</ul>


<p>What are the features of a diet with a low glycemic index:</p>

<ul>
<li>Its menu consists of a low-calorie foods, so weight loss is achieved due to the fact that the body produce more energy than it receives;</li>
<li>All simple carbohydrates are replaced by the complex.</li>
</ul>


<p>Advantages diet based on the glycemic index impressive of all dieters:</p>

<ul>
<li>Even in the first stage <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/starvation.html" title="starvation">starvation</a> practically impossible, since it is based on principles of nutrition;</li>
<li>This method helps to enhance metabolism, improves bowel and has a favorable effect on the functioning of internal organs, so it can be used all my life;</li>
<li>The nutrition system is suitable even for pregnant women and nursing mothers, as well as those who suffer from chronic or serious illnesses.</li>
</ul>


<p>Perhaps the only drawback is the fact that throughout the weight loss glycemic index diet foods will have to consult with the special GI table, but after some time to get accustomed to this.</p>

<h2>How much can you lose on a glycemic index diet</h2>

<p>It is worth noting that this method of weight loss is not fast, so for a month of its application can throw no more than 10 kg. This <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/" title="figure">figure</a> also depends on physical activity and energy intake - it should not be higher than 1700 kcal per day.</p>

<h2>Glycemic index diet for weight loss: compliance rules, menu, table, recipes</h2>

<p><em>Terms glycemic index diet for weight loss:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>It is best to give preference to products with low GI and high nutritional value, and not vice versa;</li>
<li>It is not recommended to use fried food: it is best to cook, bake or eat fresh salads;</li>
<li>Water increases the rate of excretion of excess fluids, but drink it in such volumes as often stated in other techniques, is not necessary.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Low glycemic index foods</h3>

<p><strong>Foods with a high glycemic index (GI of 70 and above)</strong></p>

<table width="100%">
    <thead>
        <tr>
            <th>Product</th>
            <th>GI</th>
        </tr>
    </thead>
    <tbody>
        <tr>
            <td>Beer</td>
            <td align="center">110</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Dates</td>
            <td align="center">103</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Glucose</td>
            <td align="center">100</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Modified starch</td>
            <td align="center">100</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Toast of white bread</td>
            <td align="center">100</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Swede</td>
            <td align="center">99</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Buns</td>
            <td align="center">95</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Baked potato</td>
            <td align="center">95</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fried potatoes</td>
            <td align="center">95</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Potato casserole</td>
            <td align="center">95</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Rice noodles</td>
            <td align="center">92</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Canned apricots</td>
            <td align="center">91</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Gluten-free white bread</td>
            <td align="center">90</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>White (glutinous) rice</td>
            <td align="center">90</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Carrots (boiled or stewed)</td>
            <td align="center">85</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Hamburger Buns</td>
            <td align="center">85</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cornflakes</td>
            <td align="center">85</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Free sugar popcorn</td>
            <td align="center">85</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Rice pudding with milk</td>
            <td align="center">85</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Mashed potatoes</td>
            <td align="center">83</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cracker</td>
            <td align="center">80</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Muesli with nuts and raisins</td>
            <td align="center">80</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sweet donut</td>
            <td align="center">76</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pumpkin</td>
            <td align="center">75</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Watermelon</td>
            <td align="center">75</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>French baguette</td>
            <td align="center">75</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Rice porridge with milk</td>
            <td align="center">75</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Lasagna (from soft wheat)</td>
            <td align="center">75</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Savoury waffles</td>
            <td align="center">75</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Millet</td>
            <td align="center">71</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Chocolate bar ("Mars", "Snickers", "Twix" and the like)</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Milk chocolate</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sweet drinks ("Coca-Cola", "Pepsi-Cola" and the like)</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Croissant</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Noodles of soft wheat</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pearl barley</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Potato chips</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Risotto with white rice</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Brown sugar</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>White sugar</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cuscus</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Munk</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
    </tbody>
</table>


<p><strong>Products with an average glycemic index (GI of 50 to 69)</strong></p>

<table width="100%">
    <thead>
        <tr>
            <th>Product</th>
            <th>GI</th>
        </tr>
    </thead>
    <tbody>
        <tr>
            <td>Wheat flour</td>
            <td align="center">69</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh pineapple</td>
            <td align="center">66</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Instant oatmeal</td>
            <td align="center">66</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Orange juice</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Jam</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Beetroot (boiled or stewed)</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Black yeast bread</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Jujube</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Muesli with sugar</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Canned pineapple</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Raisins</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Maple syrup</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Rye bread</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Potatoes cooked in their skins</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sorbet</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sweet potato</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Whole wheat bread</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Canned vegetables</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pasta with cheese</td>
            <td align="center">64</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Wheat sprouts</td>
            <td align="center">63</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pancakes from wheat flour</td>
            <td align="center">62</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pizza on thin wheat dough with tomato and cheese</td>
            <td align="center">61</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Banana</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Chestnut</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Ice cream (with sugar)</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Long-grain rice</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Lasagna</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Industrial mayonnaise</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Melon</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Oatmeal</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cocoa powder (sweetened)</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Papaya fresh</td>
            <td align="center">59</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Arab pita</td>
            <td align="center">57</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sweet corn, canned</td>
            <td align="center">57</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Grape juice (sugar free)</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Ketchup</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Mustard</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Spaghetti</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sushi</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Bulgur</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Canned peaches</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Shortbread</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Basmati rice</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cranberry juice (sugar free)</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Kiwi</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pineapple juice without sugar</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Lichee</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Mango</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Persimmon</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Brown crude rice</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Apple juice (without sugar)</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
    </tbody>
</table>


<p><strong>Foods with a low glycemic index (GI of 49 or less)</strong></p>

<table width="100%">
    <thead>
        <tr>
            <th>Product</th>
            <th>GI</th>
        </tr>
    </thead>
    <tbody>
        <tr>
            <td>Cranberries (fresh or frozen)</td>
            <td align="center">47</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Grapefruit juice (sugar free)</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Canned green peas</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Brown basmati rice</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Coconut</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Grapes</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Orange fresh</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>A toast of wholemeal bread</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Whole grain breakfast cereals (without sugar and honey)</td>
            <td align="center">43</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Buckwheat</td>
            <td align="center">40</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Dried figs</td>
            <td align="center">40</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pasta, cooked "al dente"</td>
            <td align="center">40</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Carrot juice (sugar free)</td>
            <td align="center">40</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Dried apricots</td>
            <td align="center">40</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Prunes</td>
            <td align="center">40</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Wild (black) rice</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Chick-pea</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
            </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh apple</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Meat and beans</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Dijon mustard</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Dried tomatoes</td>
            <td align="center">34</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh green peas</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Chinese noodles and vermicelli</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sesame</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh orange</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh plums</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh quince</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Soy sauce (without sugar)</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Low-fat yogurt</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Ice cream with fructose</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Beans</td>
            <td align="center">34</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh nectarines</td>
            <td align="center">34</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Garnet</td>
            <td align="center">34</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh peach</td>
            <td align="center">34</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Compote (without sugar)</td>
            <td align="center">34</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Tomato juice</td>
            <td align="center">33</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Yeast</td>
            <td align="center">31</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Soy milk</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh apricots</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Brown lentils</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh grapefruit</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Green bean</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Garlic</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh carrots</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh beets</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Jam (no sugar)</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>fresh Pear</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Tomatoes (fresh)</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cottage cheese low fat</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Yellow lentils</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Blueberries, cranberries, blueberries</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Dark chocolate (70% cocoa)</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Almond milk</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>  
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Milk (any fat content)</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Passionfruit</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh mandarin</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Blackberry</td>
            <td align="center">20</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cherry</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Green lentils</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Golden bean</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh raspberries</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Red currant</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Soy flour</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Strawberry, wild-strawberry</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pumpkin seeds</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Gooseberry</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Peanut butter (no sugar)</td>
            <td align="center">20</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Artichoke</td>
            <td align="center">20</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Eggplant</td>
            <td align="center">20</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Soy yogurt</td>
            <td align="center">20</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Almond</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Broccoli</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cabbages</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cashew</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Celery</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Bran</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Brussels sprouts</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cauliflower</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Chilli</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh cucumber</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Hazelnuts, pine nuts, pistachios, walnuts</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Asparagus</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Ginger</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Mushrooms</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Squash</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Onion</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pesto</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Leek</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Olives</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Peanut</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Salty and pickled cucumbers</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Rhubarb</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Tofu (bean curd)</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Soy</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Spinach</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Avocado</td>
            <td align="center">10</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Leaf salad</td>
            <td align="center">9</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Parsley, basil, vanilla, cinnamon, oregano</td>
            <td align="center">5</td>
        </tr>
    </tbody>
</table>


<h3>Low glycemic index diet: Menu</h3>

<p>You can use this example to the right to make your own menu:</p>

<ul>
<li>For breakfast we eat oatmeal with berries with the addition of a low GI, drink green tea;</li>
<li>After 2 hours, a snack dates;</li>
<li>Lunch soup with vegetable broth, eat a salad with sausage;</li>
<li>Afternoon snack citrus juice;</li>
<li>For dinner, leave vegetable salad.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Montignac Diet on Glycemic Index</h3>

<p>French Diet Montignac M. dietitian for weight loss is recommended to eat as follows:</p>

<ul>
<li>We have breakfast any fruits with a low GI, as we eat low-fat yogurt;</li>
<li>At lunch consume protein foods: cottage cheese, boiled eggs, yogurt, chicken;</li>
<li>Lunch grilled fish and salads of vegetables;</li>
<li>Afternoon snack with yogurt;</li>
<li>We have supper at the latest 19.00 boiled beans and meat.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Glycemic index diet recipes</h3>

<p><em>The recipe for stewed chicken with mushrooms:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Cut into pieces of chicken, onions shinkuem, spread all on a buttered pan;</li>
<li>Next, add the peeled and chopped mushrooms, salt and pepper, fry 5 minutes;</li>
<li>Add 100 ml of water, cover with lid and simmer for 15 minutes.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Recipe for vegetable salad:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Tear hands lettuce, sliced tomatoes, cucumbers and greens;</li>
<li>Mix all dressed with olive oil and mustard sauce.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Soup recipe:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Fill with water to 300 grams of lean meat, put the stew;</li>
<li>Chop and fry the onion, carrot, tomato and pepper;</li>
<li>Shred cabbage, cut into bars potatoes, spread them in a ready-made broth;</li>
<li>After 10 minutes, add to the pan roasting, parsley, bay leaf and spices;</li>
<li>Boil 5 minutes, then turn off.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Losing weight on a low-glycemic index foods: reviews, the results of losing weight</h2>

<p>Doctors in most cases favor food with a low glycemic index, but the duration of the first stage should not be more than three weeks. This is due to the fact that the human body still needs slow carbohydrates, which limits this technique.</p>

<p>As a result of diet on the basis of the glycemic index of the products can be substantially reduced weight as well as to stabilize and improve the metabolism of the bowels. In order to continue to not score dropped weight, you must eat at the table of products with an average GI, occasionally allowing himself to eat any food with a high GI, and further to do fasting days.</p>

<p>Out of glycemic index diet is happening even in the third stage, when the allowed foods high in GI, while eat only it is not recommended.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove Stretch Marks on Thighs&#58; Change Life for the Better]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-remove-stretch-marks-on-thighs-change-life-for-the-better/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-03T18:46:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-remove-stretch-marks-on-thighs-change-life-for-the-better</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-remove-stretch-marks-on-thighs-change-life-for-the-better/img1.jpg" alt="How to remove stretch marks on thighs">The reasons for the appearance of stretch marks on thighs a lot of pregnancy, hormonal changes the body during adolescence maturing, a sharp weight gain or weight loss. In addition to this disease it may be associated with a genetic predisposition commonplace. How to remove stretch marks on thighs, treatment and causes of the disease - everything is in the article proposed to your attention.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Main reasons for appearance of stretch marks</h2>

<p>Young girls are often scared of such manifestations, think these marks on the skin remain forever and will be very noticeable. But stretch marks that appear on thighs during adolescence is nothing but a small skin&rsquo;s ability to stretch, not in time behind the growth of the organism. Often, a similar phenomenon can be seen at the athletes lift weights. Thus, the main causes of stretch marks:</p>

<ul>
<li>Sudden changes in weight</li>
<li>Changes in hormonal balance: the skin loses its elasticity, thinning, stretch marks appear red (inner anguishes with bright color)</li>
<li>Genetic predisposition</li>
<li>Local blood circulation failures</li>
<li>The strong skin stretching at playing sports, weight lifting.</li>
</ul>


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Causes - it is clear, but it is always more concerned not why there are white stretch marks on thighs, and how to get rid of them. By the way, white stretch marks are often the result of excessive weight: at strong stretching skin overstrain. Blood vessels are emptied over time, changing the red color on white.</p>

<h3>How to remove stretch marks on thighs: simple and affordable ways</h3>

<p>Main remedy for stretch marks on thighs - is the maintenance of elasticity of the skin at any age. Subject to the fluid balance in the body, the use of proper diet and moderate exercising can never worry about stretch marks. But life is making, often <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="stretching occurs during pregnancy">stretching occurs during pregnancy</a>, and women who had gathered to become a mother, it is important to know how to remove stretch marks on thighs.</p>

<p>In the fight for a beautiful body approach absolutely every means, both homemade as well as medication. The problem of disposal should cover the full range of measures, from rubbing to change diet. Only some ointments and creams for stretch marks on thighs do not get rid of. It is important to understand that the poor condition of stretch marks, the more difficult and sometimes impossible to cope with them. However, regular use of the total volume of advice if you remove stretch marks completely, but would make them virtually invisible. There are many ways of treatment. It is necessary to be aware of some of them.</p>

<h4>Available recipes to get rid of stretch marks</h4>

<p>Learn how to remove stretch marks on thighs at home, it is easy, it is important to understand that it requires complete dedication and patience:</p>

<ol>
<li>Use plant extracts, mask and cream for stretch marks on thighs, essential oils, elastin and collagen to maintain balance and prevent stretch marks.</li>
<li>Home remedies - a natural scrubs (salt, caramel, coffee coarser, any stone fruits).</li>
<li>In addition, well help the oils: almond, olive, peach - they need to be rubbed into the already appeared striae and in places of possible manifestations.</li>
<li>Massage - the best and literally a healing agent. Simply stroking while rubbing oils, tougher rubbing or anticellulite massage - all options are suitable here. The main thing - do not be lazy and do it consistently.</li>
</ol>


<p>In addition to knowledge of how to remove stretch marks on thighs, we must also know how to avoid them. And here too there are tricks:</p>

<ul>
<li><p>Train yourself, your body and raise the tone of the skin. Never forget that the skin - this is the only clothes that can not be removed, ironed and darned. When applying the cream, pinch it to enhance absorbency, stroking and patting. Improve skin tone will douches (unless contraindicated). In addition, it is very nice, it is also harden the vessels, burn extra calories and add vitality throughout the body. After such a soul the whole body will be grateful to accept oils, creams and ointments.</p></li>
<li><p>Sport! It&rsquo;s not just life or health, in the case of prevention and the appearance of stretch marks - that&rsquo;s the beauty. Gradually, in small doses, with rest and plenty of approaches begin to engage in physical exercise. Jogging, brisk walking, swimming, skis or roller skates - it is quite easy, it does not take much time and will be an excellent way to deal with stretch marks on thighs.</p></li>
<li><p>Food. The main reason for the appearance of stretch marks is overweight. Review diet. Eat more healthy food with vitamins, minerals and easily digestible. But do not try to lose weight fast, it will not lead to anything good. Find your diet, a balanced diet and to choose the best products to help dietician.</p></li>
</ul>


<p>A healthy lifestyle, exercise, maintenance of skin tone and timely prevention - it is excellent. But even using all possible means, some women are unable to avoid the appearance of stretch marks, and even more to get rid of them. Do not worry. Even if there were stretching on the inner side of the thigh, can reduce their visibility to a minimum, so that they do not cause inconvenience. This is - by any forces of the fair sex.</p>

<p><em>Beauty salons offer a wide range of services for the removal of stretch marks, but the prices of these procedures are very high. But do not despair: the latest developments in the field of cosmetic products can solve the problem in a fairly short time and at home. Emulsions, creams, ointments can be selected in any price range from budget to exclusive brands. Their main action is aimed at improving the blood supply, causing and improves skin tone.</em></p>

<p><strong>Persistently and consistently going to the purpose, do not forget that the class should be regular!</strong> Mirror - here is your main judge in the fight against stretch marks. The slightest change you will see at once, but if extensions do not go to the end - that&rsquo;s no reason to give up. Smartness figure, radiant skin, confident look and optimism - that every woman seeks. And that is what you can get, doing all of the above recommendations.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Rid of Stretch Marks on Breasts and Return the Former Beauty of the Body]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-get-rid-of-stretch-marks-on-breasts-and-return-the-former-beauty-of-the-body/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-26T10:59:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-get-rid-of-stretch-marks-on-breasts-and-return-the-former-beauty-of-the-body</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-get-rid-of-stretch-marks-on-breasts-and-return-the-former-beauty-of-the-body/img.jpg" alt="How to get rid of stretch marks on breasts and return the former beauty of the body">How to get rid of stretch marks on breasts we describe here. All women want to have beautiful skin of the breast, which in fact is not surprising and fine. Most breast skin spoil streamers, which are the majority of women. In medicine, they are called striae, they appear due to the excessively sharp reduction or weight gain. Most <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="childbirth">stretch marks appear after childbirth</a> or nursing. Naturally, in such a situation, women are beginning to look for the most effective means, to once and for all get rid of stretch marks on his chest.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Despite the progress of modern medicine, to get rid of stretch marks on his chest stuffy today is almost impossible. But if you start to deal with them as soon as they appear on your skin, as they are painted in pink and have not yet become pale, then you will be a good result. With proper care, fresh stretch marks disappear forever from the life.</p>

<p>Today there are a lot of beauty, as well as drugs that help remove and prevent the appearance of stretch marks. It is the most effective means of oil, namely lemon, almond, flax, orange. You need to choose any of these oils and systematically rub it into the skin to get rid of stretch marks on his chest.</p>

<p>Below we will acquaint you with several methods of removing stretch marks, which help to quickly resolve the problem.</p>

<h2>Water treatments</h2>

<p>It is known that cold shower improves circulation and strengthens blood vessels, which in turn helps the skin to become more elastic so you do not have to worry about How to get rid of stretch marks on breasts. You must perform the procedure in a circular motion, starting from the right, for a few minutes. Carry out this procedure every day. It is not necessary to increase the duration of the procedure, since it is possible to chill the breast and cause a variety of inflammatory diseases and not to get rid of stretch marks on breasts.</p>

<p>Also get rid of stretch marks on breasts, you can wipe the chest with the help of small pieces of ice, this procedure gives a lifting effect that accelerates the elimination of stretch marks.</p>

<p>It helps as well and wiping with a wet towel. You need to soak a towel in normal water and then grind them to his chest. When you need to take the dry, warmed towel and dry breasts.</p>

<h2>Cosmetic procedures</h2>

<p>Wraps and masks also good help to get rid of stretch marks on breasts. They improve the skin and lead to normal metabolism.</p>

<p>Recipe mask: should be thoroughly mixed cheese and olive oil, add sour cream, honey, egg, and then apply the mixture on the chest. Keep this weight is necessary for twenty minutes and then gently rinse and apply a quality moisturizer.</p>

<h2>Massage</h2>

<p>Breast massage is one of the most important processes of care for your body and the way to get rid of stretch marks on his chest. Because it improves circulation, tightens muscles, improves lymph drainage. To eliminate stretch marks is the best Taoist and Manual massage.</p>

<p>Taoist massage to get rid of stretch marks is carried out as follows: take a breast in his hand and make a couple of rotational movement in the direction from the shoulder to the center, and then you need to embrace the breasts with his hands and make a couple of pressings on the exhale.</p>

<p>Manual massage is carried out in several stages. First, prepare the breasts using light circular movements, after the tips of his fingers begin to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/neurology/stroke.html" title="stroke">stroke</a> his chest in the direction of the nipple. Next you need to go to the main part of the massage, take a breast in his hand and a second hand work out easy blows on his hand. Then just keep breasts in his hands and produce oscillatory motion from the nipple to the shoulder. Complete massage should be light stroking. Of course, it is desirable to entrust the conduct of massage professionals as they make the procedure more qualitatively and pick methodology taking into account the individual characteristics of a person.</p>

<h2>Physical culture</h2>

<p>It is useful to combine all the above activities, physical exercise, as it will accelerate the receipt of the result aimed at is to get rid of stretch marks on breasts.</p>

<p>The best approach is swimming, but if such an opportunity you do not, just go a special course at the fitness center or perform exercises on their own. To go to the main part of the session you must first warm up the muscles of the body is good, it needs to do a couple of turns of the shoulders, head and make the slopes and so on. Now we go to the main exercise.</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>The first exercise</strong>. We must come face to the wall, lean on her hands and make ten pusher movements in the wall.</li>
<li><strong>The second exercise</strong>. Stand up straight, well-pressed hands to the body, and then try to connect their blades. You should do eight sets of ten seconds each.</li>
<li><strong>The third exercise</strong>. It is necessary to connect the front of the palm and try to squeeze them much, do it eight times in five seconds.</li>
<li><strong>The fourth exercise</strong>. You need to be back to the wall and make a hundred motions simulating swimming breaststroke.</li>
</ul>


<p>In the fight against stretch marks you need to remember that everyone has their genetics, and for this reason, exercise can not give you the desired result. If any method fails, then try another until you find your method.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diet on Cellulose]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-on-cellulose/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-14T13:19:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-on-cellulose</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/diet-on-cellulose/img.jpg" alt="Diet on cellulose">There are many effective diets for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/watermelon-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>. But people in the majority of cases they do not lose weight because they refuse to low-calorie food in just a few days after the decision on the fight against <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>. Blame - hunger, tormented man due to reduced caloric intake. To avoid it, and to increase the effectiveness of the diet, cellulose can be used. Let&rsquo;s talk about how it works, and what kind of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/model-diet/" title="weight-loss">weight-loss</a> schemes are applied to cellulose to date.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Perhaps you&rsquo;ve read online that cellulose reduces appetite, cleanses the body of toxins, normalizes metabolism, restores hormonal balance, metabolism. Most of this information - is not true. Cellulose fills the stomach, and this is its main function.</p>

<p>The real benefits of using cellulose in the diet to lose weight:</p>

<ul>
<li>prolongs the feeling of satiety;</li>
<li>It reduces the rate of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a> of carbohydrates.</li>
</ul>


<p>Cellulose does not burn fat. This is just a means of improving portability of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/low-calorie-diet.html" title="low-calorie diet">low-calorie diets</a>. You can reduce caloric intake, and thereby lose weight. Cellulose will reduce hunger and significantly reduce the probability of failure of the diet.</p>

<p>For any diet on cellulose itself, you will need cellulose. Where to get it? It is sold in pharmacies in the form of medicines or bioactive agents. Method of production - powders that are dosed spoons or pills. The last is more expensive but more convenient dosing, and, moreover, do not contain extra <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/" title="calories">calories</a>.</p>

<p>Cellulose is simple to manufacture, has a low cost, so it is produced by many companies.</p>

<p>Siberian cellulose can not be purchased at pharmacies, but can be purchased from the members of this network of the company or to order via the Internet. Please note that the price may vary significantly at different sites and by different retailer. But in any case, such a cellulose is cheaper than microcrystalline cellulose from the pharmacy.</p>

<p>There are many diets on the cellulose and yogurt. Some of them - short designed for 1-3 weeks. Others - long recommended for use over several years or even a lifetime. Let us discuss a few of these diets.</p>

<p><strong><em>Diet for a week.</em></strong> Within 7 days of the foundation of the diet of yogurt and cellulose. In total you need every day to drink 4 glasses of fermented milk beverage. It should add 2 tablespoons cellulose. Do not forget that the whole week you should drink plenty of water - preferably up to 2.5 liters per day. As a snack between meals, you are allowed to eat per day 200 g of raw vegetables or fruits.</p>

<p><strong><em>The diet for 3 weeks.</em></strong> In the morning you eat porridge without salt. At lunch - steamed vegetables and chicken breast. At dinner - only a cup of yogurt with cellulose. Also, one glass should drink 15 minutes before breakfast and dinner. Thus, all your daily diet consists of two meals and 3 glasses of yogurt with cellulose.</p>

<p><strong><em>Fasting days.</em></strong> The essence of the method of losing weight is by organizing weekly fasting days, during which time allowed for the day to drink a liter of yogurt. On the glass is necessary to put 1-2 tablespoons of cellulose.</p>

<p><strong><em>Long-term diet.</em></strong> One of the power supply circuit is recommended for long-term use. Diet is used as long as the weight reaches the desired values for you. Further it can be applied in the &ldquo;light&rdquo; mode to maintain body weight within acceptable limits. The essence of this diet is that the size of portions is reduced by half, and before every meal you take a cup of yogurt with 1-2 tablespoons of cellulose.</p>

<p>The power supply circuit, where the basis of the diet is protein foods and cellulose, is one of the variants of the <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="protein diet">protein diet</a>. Weight loss occurs to a greater extent by limiting carbohydrates less - because of the reduction of the total caloric intake. For this diet is not used in the pharmacy purchased cellulose - the organism gets her vegetables, fruits, mushrooms and other plant foods.</p>

<ol>
<li><p>Each meal should consist of foods that contain large amounts of cellulose and protein foods (meat, fish, milk, eggs, legumes, seafood).</p></li>
<li><p>Prohibited fatty and carbohydrate-rich foods (sweets, flour products, cereals, potatoes).</p></li>
</ol>


<p>Diet lasts up to a full normalization of weight. It has both advantages and disadvantages. Pluses diet on protein and cellulose:</p>

<ul>
<li>good tolerability - varied menu, tasty food, no hunger;</li>
<li>a gradual but steady weight loss effect.</li>
</ul>


<p>Lows in the diet cellulose and protein:</p>

<ul>
<li>harmful to health (it is better not to sit on such a diet with liver disease, kidney disease, endocrine abnormalities);</li>
<li>the need for specialized knowledge (need to have data on the chemical composition of food and products - to know how much they contain cellulose, protein, carbohydrate, cellulose);</li>
<li>high cost (protein food are more expensive cereals, pasta, potatoes).</li>
</ul>


<p>It should be borne in mind that the diet should be held in a total ban on the carbohydrate-rich foods, especially pastries. The slightest deviation from this rule leads to the complete ineffectiveness of diet.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Milk Diet for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/milk-diet-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-08T11:19:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/milk-diet-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/milk-diet-for-weight-loss/img.jpg" alt="Milk diet for weight loss">Everyone in their own way refers to different products. Someone like olives, some do not; someone loves caviar, and someone can not understand what&rsquo;s so special. So it is with milk: it has both fans and haters. However, in some form or other dairy products they consume almost everything and most people refer to it quite bearable. If you - among them, and want to lose a few extra kilos, you can get acquainted with several options dairy diet, which will be discussed in this post.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Thus, the basis of dietary food in this case is milk. And, as varieties of this product, there is quite a lot, and opinions diverge about the choice.</p>

<p>Most dieters claim that, once go on a diet, it is necessary to choose only low-fat product or a maximum of 0.5-1.5% milk, which contains only 39-47 <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/" title="calories">calories</a> per 100 ml. However, we advise you to seek the smallest <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/" title="figure">figures</a>, because in the process of normalization (bringing the milk to the desired fat content), it partially loses its valuable properties. The fact that the fat-soluble vitamins useful and other components partially extracted from it, together with the &quot;surplus&quot; fats. Moreover, milk fat is not as dangerous as &quot;normal&quot; animal, which is contained in fat and fat meat. Its main components are useful phospholipids rather than potentially threatening <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/cardiology/atherosclerosis.html" title="atherosclerosis">atherosclerosis</a> <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a>.</p>

<p>Thus, you can not pay so much attention to the choice of issues. Will suit you like milk with 1.5%, and the &quot;standard&quot;, with 2.5% fat content, which can be found in every store. Although, of course, if you do opt for the 6% of the product or liquid cream, it is unlikely to benefit figure.</p>

<p><strong>As milk diet effect on the body?</strong></p>

<p>This in itself has a low calorie milk and contains small amounts of protein required in the diet body. Actually, that&rsquo;s all, what are its advantages when it comes to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/watermelon-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>. Fat is not mobilized, a depressing effect on the appetite does not, on the blood sugar level is not affected. It&rsquo;s just a useful product small calorie, which can be used as a dietary. The effect of a diet is to ensure that the diet is severely limited energy value.</p>

<p>Itself milk diet, in whatever form it is employed, is rigid and is usually not perfectly balanced, so it is not recommended for a long time.</p>

<h2>Types of milk diet</h2>

<p>If we approach the issue of transfer of dairy diet with all the responsibility, you can find a dozen different versions of it, in which as the dominant power component acts milk. But the most commonly used are 3 types.</p>

<p>It is intended for use during the day (as the handling of the day), the most healthy people are allowed to use it for 3 days. On day <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="slimming">slimming</a> offered 1 liter of milk; moreover, it can drinking ordinary water and mineral. That is, in fact, mono-diet on milk is <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/starvation.html" title="starvation">starvation</a>.</p>

<p>During the day it takes about 500-700 g of weight, three days you can lose up to 2 kg. But, in any case, it requires the observance of the human ideal health, and sit on it longer than strictly prohibited.</p>

<p>By the choice of food it can be characterized as a protein, because during its compliance permitted only various embodiments of dairy products. You can drink milk, yogurt, fermented baked low-fat, low-fat cottage cheese has, diet cheese, unsweetened yogurt. Glazed cheese, ice cream, yoghurt, sweet, cream, sour cream - all this, of course, prohibited.</p>

<p>Ingestion performed 5-6 times per day total caloric intake calculated individually for women - not less than 1200 kcal, if it is supposed to adhere for 1 week, and not less than 1500 kcal, when it is planned to extend for 14 days.</p>

<p>Longer &quot;sitting&quot; on the expanded dairy diet is contraindicated, since such power marked a clear shortage of fats and carbohydrates, which can lead to adverse effects on the part of health. As for the results, then a week on it, you can lose about 2-3 kg.</p>

<p>From the listed options for the most useful and safe. It consists in the fact that, along with the milk (1-1.5 liters per day), a person is allowed to eat fresh fruits and vegetables, salads and boiled or baked vegetables. Excluded are only those plant foods that contain too much sugar and starch (corn, potatoes, grapes). Should be fed 4-6 times a day, calculated calorie in the same manner as the previous embodiment diet.</p>

<p>Since vegetables and fruits generally lower in calories than the milk-based products, the amount of power becomes greater, and diet quite easily tolerated. But more than 2 weeks of her stay is not necessary, you need to take a break for at least 10 days. And another recommendation: if you are planning a meal with the addition of fresh fruits and vegetables, do not drink milk immediately after use, it is better do it in an hour and a half. Due to the high acid content in vegetable products in such a combination may cause <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/diarrhea.html" title="diarrhea">diarrhea</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diet Aphrodite]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-07T14:41:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/diet-aphrodite/img.jpg" alt="Diet Aphrodite">In Greek mythology, Aphrodite - the goddess of love and <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet/" title="beauty">beauty</a>. Therefore its name is often referred to as a <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/watermelon-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> diet, as an integral feature of female attractiveness is a slim figure. Variants of Aphrodite, there are many diets. Most often, the so-called power scheme, which is based on the use of Mediterranean cuisine.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Menu Diet Aphrodite is strongly reminiscent of a Mediterranean menu. Eat only a useful and <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/pineapple-diet/" title="health">health</a>y food. Carbohydrates, which are the direct cause of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>, severely limit. The source of fats are fish, seafood, and vegetable oils, which are allowed to be added to vegetable salads.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<ol>
<li>The diet of many fish and seafood.</li>
<li>It is recommended to the regular inclusion of seaweed menu.</li>
<li>Shrimp - one of the basic diet products. They need to eat at least twice a week, and if it allows the thickness of the purse, then more often.</li>
<li>Chicken should be a priority meats.</li>
<li>Lactic acid products need to drink before bedtime.</li>
<li>Allowed to eat eggs, but it is recommended to separate the yolk - it has a lot of fat.</li>
<li>In many dishes is recommended to add the celery.</li>
<li>Fruits and juices can be drunk in unlimited quantities.</li>
<li>Sweets and flour products are excluded from the diet.</li>
<li>Cereals and bread can be eaten only in the morning.</li>
</ol>


<p>In this embodiment Aphrodite diet has no restrictions on duration, caloric intake, the number of meals. But to know the measure, of course, necessary. Despite the dominance of the diet of protein foods and vegetables, plump with overeating can even be on these products.</p>

<h2>Diet Aphrodite with goat cheese</h2>

<p>The Internet is widely distributed another version of Aphrodite&rsquo;s diet with goat cheese. She is short, only lasts three days and is designed for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="rapid weight loss">rapid weight loss</a>. Menu of such a diet is clearly laid out by day. Power - Four.</p>

<p><strong>The first day:</strong></p>

<ol>
<li>Goat cheese - 100g of bread - 50 g.</li>
<li>A glass of yogurt.</li>
<li>Soup, which consists of mushrooms, cucumber, goat cheese and olive oil.</li>
<li>Vegetables and Goat Cheese.</li>
</ol>


<p><strong>Second day:</strong></p>

<ol>
<li>Oatmeal and dried fruits.</li>
<li>A glass of yogurt and an apple.</li>
<li>Vegetables and shrimp.</li>
<li>Goat cheese and scrambled eggs with tomatoes.</li>
</ol>


<p><strong>Day Three:</strong></p>

<ol>
<li>Egg, cucumber, 100 g of goat cheese.</li>
<li>100 grams of cottage cheese, a piece of fruit.</li>
<li>Goat cheese with mushrooms.</li>
<li>Vegetables.</li>
</ol>


<p>With such a diet can really lose weight. However, to do it for three days is not possible, but it is not designed for a long life. Therefore, a diet of Aphrodite on the goat cheese is unlikely to radically change your figure.</p>

<h2>Greek diet Aphrodite</h2>

<p>Probably the most stupid diet should be considered as the Greek Aphrodite. It is designed for weight loss, but the diet based on - carbohydrates, while protein-containing foods is limited. Menu options Aphrodite Greek diet consists mainly of:</p>

<ul>
<li>vegetables;</li>
<li>cereals;</li>
<li>pasta;</li>
<li>fruits;</li>
<li>nuts and seeds;</li>
<li>dairy products;</li>
<li>of bread;</li>
<li>legumes;</li>
<li>olive oil;</li>
<li>wine.</li>
</ul>


<p>These foods should be consumed daily. An intermediate position is occupied by the food recommended to be put on the table, no more frequently than every other day:</p>

<ul>
<li>honey;</li>
<li>chocolate;</li>
<li>seafood;</li>
<li>a fish;</li>
<li>eggs.</li>
</ul>


<p>Finally, in the least favored by the creators of the meat of the Greek diet. Oil-rich generally prohibited. But chicken or veal to use as possible, but not more than three times a month. What thoughts <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/why-should-you-run-benefits-and-harms-of-running/" title="running">running</a> through my head of people who compose this diet, we do not know. But if you do not want to multiply the fat reserves on your stomach, it is better to give it up.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watermelon Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/watermelon-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-07T14:00:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/watermelon-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/watermelon-diet/img.jpg" alt="Watermelon diet"><strong>Watermelon diet</strong> is classified as mono-diet. Watermelon diet is considered to be tough enough, so do not comply with its longer deadline.</p>

<p><em>The average calorie daily diet of 1200-1350 kcal.</em></p>

<!--more-->


<p>It is important to understand that, despite the fact that many people love watermelons, after a few days you may experience pain in the digestive tract or kidneys. Watermelons have a strong diuretic effect, therefore, increases the load on the kidneys. In the first two days the weight is greatly reduced, but the main reason for that - the loss of excess water and salt deposits.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<h2>Menu watermelon diet for 3 days</h2>

<p>The main thing for this diet - a strict limit of watermelon consumption depending on the initial weight. For example, if you weigh 70 kg, then the day you can eat no more than 7 kg of watermelon. That is, 10 kg of 1 kg is allowed watermelon.</p>

<p>Nothing else is allowed to eat, but you can drink as much as you want. Allowed to drink water, and green tea in any amount. Alcohol should be excluded completely.</p>

<h2>Watermelon diet for 8-10 days</h2>

<p>The diet of this diet is not as hard as in the first case. It is allowed in addition to watermelon to eat at each meal 2 slices of rye bread. Follow the diet should be 8-10 days. Other products can not eat.</p>

<p>Not recommended to follow this diet for more than 10 days, but if it is right to go out of it, you can significantly improve your score. To do this, proteins were gradually introduced into the menu, fats and carbohydrates, but only gradually, not otherwise. Before going to bed for an additional 10 days to eat a few slices of watermelon, but not much. Do not have dinner after 20.00. If you eat right for another 10 days, you can lose weight by 2-3 kg, but not as rapidly as during a diet, but the result will be more stable.</p>

<p><strong>Pros watermelon diet:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>the main advantage - it is satiety. Each of us knows how to eat the heart of a ripe, juicy, red flesh and not &quot;die&quot; from overeating, because after half an hour, your body expels excess fluid, and you feel like a new person;</li>
<li>enough high efficiency, but it is worth noting that most <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/pineapple-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> with the help of watermelon diet - it is removing excess fluid from the body;</li>
<li>diet normalizes metabolism.</li>
</ul>


<p><strong>Cons watermelon diet:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>the first and most important negative - it is a contraindication to watermelon diet for kidney and urinary tract;</li>
<li>another minus - not a balanced diet. Just like any other mono-diet, it does not provide a complete diet, but rather poor in proteins and fats, which in varying degrees, the body needs.</li>
</ul>


<p>Whatever it was, watermelon lovers with healthy kidneys watermelon waiting for a few pleasant days for which you can reduce your weight.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Model Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/model-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-07T11:20:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/model-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/model-diet/img.jpg" alt="Model diet">Judging by the name, the model diet is intended for the purchase of model appearance. However, judging by its duration, it is unlikely to reach its goal. Model Diet is one of the short circuit power to lose weight. In one embodiment, it takes 3 days, in another - 7 days. Let&rsquo;s get acquainted with them.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Model diet for 3 days</h2>

<p>It is unlikely that the model used the diet, which will be discussed. Rather, they use a more healthy ways to lose weight under the supervision of doctors. But the title of this three-day supply circuit stuck. diet menu model for 3 days as follows:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>Breakfast</strong> - one boiled egg or boiled;</li>
<li><strong>Dinner</strong> - 300 g of raw vegetables, can be in the form of salad, 2 fruit, 100 g of fish steamed.</li>
</ul>


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Impossible to lose weight in 3 days at this menu. For such a short period of time at all you can not change the contours of the figure. Model diet limits caloric intake, but not so much that people lost weight. In addition, in the evening the candidates in the model are invited to taste the bread and butter, which violates several rules of diet.</p>

<p>Usually carbohydrates are consumed in the morning, so the body can use them up during the day. But the model diet allows you to eat an egg for breakfast only, half-day so people have to embarrass colleagues his rumbling stomach. In the evening, a candidate in the model would be a good idea to eat a light dinner consisting mainly of proteins and containing a minimum of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/" title="calories">calories</a>. But no, he eats a calorie sandwich with butter, consisting of fats and carbohydrates.</p>

<p>Perhaps, it is possible to lose a few kilos for a month on a model diet. But so long it withstand very difficult. Besides, it is designed only for 3 days. During this time, you will surely not be able to buy a model appearance.</p>

<p>But there is another version of the diet. It is a hard and probably reduces the weight even by removal of bowel contents. If you need to urgently improve the shape of your abdomen, you can use the following diet:</p>

<p><strong>Dinner (no later than 15 hours)</strong> - 100 grams of cottage cheese.</p>

<p>Diet is very difficult. It is harmful to health and brings only a temporary effect. Therefore it is better to pay attention to diet to lose weight at the expense of allowing the splitting of fat, rather than create the illusion of a flat stomach as a result of bowel emptying.</p>

<h2>Model diet for 7 days</h2>

<p>The seven-day model diet is more forgiving than both variants diet for 3 days. It involves three meals a day. Menu is very flexible. Low calorie diet, the amount of food is small. But the model diet for 7 days makes it possible to more or less normal breakfast, lunch and even dinner.</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>Breakfast</strong> - a small piece of boiled meat, two eggs, bread and butter, tea;</li>
<li><strong>Lunch</strong> - fish or meat (no more than 100 g), 2 fruit, 250-300 g of vegetable salad with green peas;</li>
<li><strong>Dinner</strong> - a salad of green vegetables (300 g), two slices of bread and butter.</li>
</ul>


<p>Throughout the diet should drink water. It is advisable before each meal consumed green tea - at least one glass at a time. Additional fluid can overcome hunger.</p>

<p>Let&rsquo;s have a diet rapid analysis. Obviously, the base diet - a protein-containing products and vegetables. One would assume that the diet allows you to lose weight by restricting carbohydrates. But one day a person eats three slices of bread with butter and two pieces of fruit, which, although they do not have a high-calorie, contain simple sugars. This limitation is not enough sugar to lose weight, even if the diet is observed for months.</p>

<p>However, it is likely that a person will be able to get rid of a small amount of fat due to the low calorie diet. Because dense foods on the menu only oil is present. But it is not enough - only a few grams. The relatively high nutritional value has bread. The rest of the food - it is vegetables, fruits, lean meat, eggs and fish. These products are considered useful for the figure.</p>

<p>Energy value of the daily diet is about 1000 kcal. Perhaps it will suffice to the amount of fat in your body has decreased by 0.5-1 kg. It is unlikely in the model diet for only 7 days you will be able to lose weight more. If you cut off a huge loaf of bread instead of a small piece, and inflict on him the oil layer two inches thick, you soon get better than that reduce weight.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pineapple Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/pineapple-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-06T16:38:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/pineapple-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/pineapple-diet/img.jpg" alt="Pineapple diet">Who among us does not like <strong>pineapples</strong>? This is perhaps one of those tropical delicacies, which like almost all children and adults. But few know that the sweet and juicy fruit contains only 56 calories. Tasty, useful and non-nutritive - that&rsquo;s great!</p>

<!--more-->


<p>In addition, the pineapple contains an enzyme that in common called <em>&quot;enzyme harmony&quot;</em>, and in science - <em>bromelain</em>. Magic enzyme enhances the action of gastric juice, due to this substance protein <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a> occurs much faster. Many have already try pineapple <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="slimming">slimming</a> teas, tablets containing bromelain, but the pineapple diet is much healthier and tastier.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<h2>Rules pineapple diet:</h2>

<ol>
<li>It is necessary to write down <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="every day">every day</a> at least 2 liters of fruit (or herbal) tea or water.</li>
<li>Observe the correct diet - eat at least four times a day in small portions.</li>
<li>Daily diet should consist of two breakfast, a hearty lunch and a light dinner.</li>
</ol>


<h2>Breakfasts pineapple diet</h2>

<p>The menu for the first two breakfasts for all days the same diet pineapple.</p>

<p>Using a mixer or a blender to make a puree of fresh pineapple, peeled beforehand. Add 2 teaspoons of oatmeal and 100 g of low-fat yogurt with no sugar. To sweeten slightly, add sugar substitute, but it is better without it. Tasty and nutritious light breakfast of 170 kcal ready.</p>

<p>Boil hard boiled egg and make a delicious sandwich of rye bread, spread with butter and salmon (not more than 20 grams). Very hearty and very tasty!</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - raw boiled rice, seasoned with curry.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - potatoes on the original recipe and cheese sauce.</p>

<p>One potato medium size weighing 100g boiled in their skins. Mix 50g of fat-free yogurt with a tablespoon of sour cream (10% fat) and a teaspoon of horseradish raw (grate). By potato with cottage cheese sauce add pineapple. Calories - only 275 kcal.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - fried chicken with pineapple, cut into slices.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - salad of shrimp and pineapple.</p>

<p>Boil 100g and clean shrimp, cut in half. Cut the pineapple into small pieces. Add finely chopped celery and a small cucumber, sliced rings. Add salt to taste, pepper, finely chopped dill. Season salad with low-fat mayonnaise. Calories - 285 calories.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - vegetable salad with garlic sauce.</p>

<p>Diced pineapple, half a red pepper and two small tomatoes and place in a deep dish. Dress the salad with 1 cloves of garlic sauce, mustard and a teaspoon of horseradish frayed. Sprinkle vegetable oil (home) and lemon juice. Calorie dishes - 225kkal.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - sliced pineapple, braised turkey and 2 small loaf of rye.</p>

<p>100g turkey breast (breast), cut into thin strips, fry for 7-10 minutes with the addition of vegetable oil (no more than a teaspoon), add 1 tablespoon of finely chopped onion. Pour a quarter cup of water, salt the, cover and simmer 10 minutes. Calories - 350 calories.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - salad with chicken, orange and pineapple.</p>

<p>Cut into julienne chicken, pre-fried on the grill. 100g pineapple and three slices of an orange cut into cubes. Stir vegetables, chicken and 2 tablespoons. spoons of green peas. Season with 2 tablespoons of fat-free mayonnaise, salt the, add red pepper. Energy value - 290 kcal.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - vegetable soup with celery, pineapple slices 100g.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - puff pastry stuffed with (100-150g). Stuffing <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="choose">choose</a> to taste.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - boiled rice with pineapple.</p>

<p>Boil 2 tablespoons of brown rice, diced pineapple, stir. If desired, add sweetener to taste. Calorie dishes - 245kkal.</p>

<p><strong>Pineapple diet</strong> can rightly be called the most delicious, varied and interesting. But, despite this, it is very effective. The only disadvantage of this diet - relatively expensive, but in principle, it&rsquo;s nothing compared with the possibility of so good and so fast to lose weight. Magic enzyme enhances the action of gastric juice, due to this substance protein digestion occurs much faster. Many have already try pineapple slimming teas, tablets containing bromelain, but the pineapple diet is much healthier and tastier.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banana Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-06T13:35:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/banana-diet-menu/img.jpg" alt="Banana diet">Bananas - a fruit that have a sufficiently high calorific value. Most people are aware of this and try to avoid them in the diet. However, there are power circuits, which involve the use of banana as the major product. Is it possible to lose weight on these fruits? Are there effective diets that reduce weight with the help of bananas? Let&rsquo;s analyze the three most common <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet-for-3-days-and-7-days/" title="banana diet">banana diet</a> and make conclusions.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Banana diet for 3 days</h2>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Lose weight for 3 days - the dream of every woman. As a rule, such a need arises at them before going to the beach this weekend, in case of sudden visits or New Year&rsquo;s Eve. The majority of women for some reason do not realize that it is impossible to lose weight in 3 days. Even in the case of complete <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/starvation.html" title="starvation">starvation</a> the body begins to vigorously break down subcutaneous fat only a few days after the rejection of food.</p>

<p>But the most common version of the banana diet offers <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> was 3 days. According to this method of fans to reduce weight, such a short period of time is sufficient to reduce their body weight by three kilograms. Banana essence diet on day 3 is as follows:</p>

<ul>
<li>there can be only bananas;</li>
<li>three times a day people should eat a banana and wash it down with a glass of milk;</li>
<li>milk should be lean;</li>
<li>at other times any food and beverages except water, are prohibited.</li>
</ul>


<p>It is unlikely to 3 days on a diet could achieve a significant improvement in the figures. But surely abide by it will not be too difficult. Bananas and milk enough nutrients to not feel wild hunger in the diet period. At the same time they do not contain a lot of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/" title="calories">calories</a>, so the banana-milk days people will spend more energy than it will receive from food.</p>

<p>Still, 3 kilograms of weight to lose can not be sure. Even given that bananas have a mild diuretic effect due to the content of potassium salts from your body will not leave as much fluid you to become significantly easier. Banana diet for 3 days only help relieve digestive system, giving it a breathing space. But for weight loss need much longer.</p>

<h2>Banana diet for 7 days</h2>

<p>Banana diet for 7 days provides a more solid results. On the Internet you can read that it can help a person will lose one kilogram of weight per day. That is, the end of the diet he folds 7 kilograms of fat. These results are possible even in the event of complete failure of the food. Nevertheless, we will introduce you with such an embodiment of the banana diet. Its essence is as follows:</p>

<ul>
<li>you can only eat bananas;</li>
<li>restricted their consumption of 1.5 kg per day;</li>
<li>you can drink only water and green tea - in any quantity;</li>
<li>you can eat in either mode, but the last meal - no later than 19 hours;</li>
<li>to avoid starvation, it is desirable not to eat at one time more than one banana;</li>
<li>if bananas are completely fed up, you can enter into the diet of two boiled eggs in a day.</li>
</ul>


<p>Bananas - not the best diet product. It is not clear what criteria guided the creators of this diet, choosing bananas as the sole source of nutrients. They are sweet, because they have a lot of sugar. Even far from nutrition person knows that the sweet recover and not lose weight. Bananas have a high glycemic index, consist mainly of carbohydrates and thin because they are not very convenient.</p>

<h2>Cottage cheese and banana diet</h2>

<p>Cottage cheese and banana diet lasts for six days. Three of them - the banana. Yet three days - cheese. Start with cottage cheese day. Check, respectively, have a banana. The diet is more varied diet, compared with the previous power schemes. cheesecake of the day menu looks like this:</p>

<ul>
<li>breakfast - 120 grams of low fat cottage cheese, a grapefruit;</li>
<li>lunch - 120 grams of low fat cottage cheese, a slice of melon;</li>
<li>dinner - again, 120 g of cottage cheese and grapefruit.</li>
</ul>


<p>Why cheese? It contains a lot of protein and little sugar. It has a low calorie, but nourishes by a viscous consistency, high-volume, slow progress on the gastrointestinal tract.</p>

<p>Why grapefruit? Rumor has it that it promotes weight loss. And although it is fiction, many believe in the fat burning properties of grapefruit.</p>

<p>Why melon? Her presence in the diet does not seem logical. In this fruit a lot of sugar, and it has a high glycemic index. Melon is harmful for the figure, and most diets for weight loss exclude it from the diet.</p>

<p>Banana days include the following menu:</p>

<ul>
<li>breakfast - a banana and a glass of milk;</li>
<li>lunch - banana and boiled egg;</li>
<li>dinner - 200 grams of banana and chicken.</li>
</ul>


<p>Eggs, milk and chicken contain a lot of protein. They are low in carbohydrates, so these dietary products can be called. And that&rsquo;s why in this scheme bananas - are not known. If they were replaced by other, less high-calorie fruit, the good of diet would be more. However, not much. Like other short-circuit power for weight loss, banana curd diet does not allow to achieve significant results in reducing weight.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The American Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/the-american-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-06T11:31:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/the-american-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/the-american-diet/img.jpg" alt="The American diet">This diet is considered one of the most famous systems of combating <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a> worldwide. Many Hollywood stars stick to this <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet/" title="diet">diet</a> to stay in shape. Today, I can feel like a star each.</p>

<!--more-->


<p><strong>There are several types of the American diet:</strong></p>

<p>This diet is designed for 7 days. The main feature of the diet - is the lack of hunger due to a well balanced diet.</p>

<p>If you have eaten a fatty meal, be sure to seize him several slices of pineapple or grapefruit.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Drink plenty of liquids - it helps to remove waste products and toxins from the body. Eat only until five o'clock in the evening. It is necessary to eat only foods that are really useful to humans. Not allowed salt, sugar, pepper, vinegar, oil, fat and alcohol.</p>

<h2>American diet menu:</h2>

<p><strong>Breakfast for all days of the same</strong> - coffee with milk but no sugar, 2 apple or an orange, a slice of bread or toast, boiled egg.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - 200g of boiled or fried fish, 100g celery with lemon juice, tea or coffee (without sugar or milk).</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 100 g cooked meat (chopped finely, add a little onion and 1 egg yolk), a slice of bread from wheat flour, one apple or a glass of low-fat milk.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - 200g stewed spinach, 150g of boiled or fried veal liver, 2 boiled potatoes, tea or coffee.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 200 grams of fat-free yogurt, a salad of tomatoes, beets, carrots, cabbage, seasoned with vegetable oil, a slice of bread or toast, a slice of lean ham, boiled egg.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - orange or grapefruit, tomato juice, 200g of low-fat fried meat, lettuce, coffee or tea.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 200 low-fat yogurt, 2 boiled eggs, 2 tomatoes, a slice of bread or toast, an apple or a pear.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - 200g of boiled or fried chicken, 150 g of cabbage, croutons and a piece of bread, coffee or tea.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 50 g low-fat cottage cheese, you can add a little green onion, bell pepper, egg yolk (raw); 6 radishes, toast or a slice of bread, 200g of low-fat milk.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - 250g grated carrots, 150g of cooked lean meat, 2 potatoes in their skins, toast, coffee or green tea.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 150 boiled beef with horseradish, apple, lettuce, 200g of low-fat milk.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 200 grams of cooked lean chicken, 100g of rice, 100g of lettuce leaves (chop and season with lemon juice), green apple, 200g of low-fat milk.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 200 grams of low-fat yogurt, 2 small chops, slice of bread, a green apple.</p>

<p><strong>The second option - a roller coaster:</strong></p>

<p>This diet is based on the principle of change in calorie daily diet. This makes it possible to achieve optimal results, because the body does not have time to tune in to a particular diet and constantly burns calories.</p>

<h2>The ration for the &ldquo;roller coaster&rdquo;:</h2>

<ul>
<li>The power supply system is designed for 3 weeks. Exclude from menu fatty food.</li>
<li>The first three days is necessary to consume 600 calories per day.</li>
<li>From the fourth to seventh day - 900 calories per day.</li>
<li>During the second week, the daily caloric diet is 1200 kcal.</li>
<li>The third is similar to the first week, that is, after 600 to 900 calories per day.</li>
</ul>


<p>This ration allows <strong>the american diet</strong> to lose 6-7 kg of excess weight, but for optimal results, it is best to combine this diet with exercise. If you play sports, the result can be more impressive - 8-9 kg in just one week.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nine-day Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-05T12:26:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/nine-day-diet/img.jpg" alt="Nine-day diet">Want to quickly bring your body in good shape before the long-awaited vacation? Nothing could be easier. Nine-day diet will help you deal with this problem in a few days.</p>

<p>And why is it always? All year flies by, but we did not have time to enroll in a gym, in the shaping or dance, we eat what we want, and grabs his head only when the time is almost gone. And as always in the holiday expectations we stand before the mirror and realize that all night snacks, salted potato chips and crisps, beer and cocktails are our figure does not help, but rather spoiled her beyond recognition. <!--more-->Looking in the mirror, we realize that with such a body to appear in a bikini on the beach - it&rsquo;s a crime. An urgent need to do something!</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
First of all you need to tune in to the fact that, following the right diet of this diet, you will lose weight in a day 0.5-1kg. This is certainly a serious <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a> to the body, so before starting the diet is better to consult a doctor. This diet is not suitable for those who have stomach ulcers, diseases of the cardiovascular system, or even the uncommon cold.</p>

<p>Next, you should understand that no diet compliance, a periodic &quot;jumping from diet&quot;, etc. It leads to the fact that all is well kilos gone back to his place, and maybe even &quot;friends&quot; with a lead. Began to lose weight - grow thin, you do not want to lose weight - do not sit on a diet. To fix the result, it is necessary to understand that after the diet need to eat moderately and wisely.</p>

<h2>Menu diet for 9 days:</h2>

<p>This diet consists of three phases.</p>

<p><strong>The first stage</strong> - three days to eat only rice, honey and drink the water.</p>

<p>On the day we take 250g long grain white rice, 2-2.5 liters of mineral water without gas, and 3 teaspoons of honey spoon.</p>

<p>On the night of rice soaked with cold water. In the morning, wash the rice in a colander to wash most of the cereal starch. Further boil in a saucepan for 15 minutes, adding rice and water in a ratio of 1:2, respectively.</p>

<p>Cooked rice divide into 5 equal portions and we eat it all day long, trying to avoid the strong feelings of hunger. Last time you can eat no later than eight o'clock in the evening. In between meals and after-meal drink water, distributing evenly. In the evening, lean on the liquid is not worth it. Also included in the diet of honey which eat in parallel with rice and water during the day. Honey is not spread on bread or cookies, eat a teaspoon with water.</p>

<p>Why this diet is effective? Figure acts as enterosorbent he cleans accumulated for a long time, toxins from the gastrointestinal tract, which actually promotes <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/1kg-per-day-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>.</p>

<p><strong>The second stage</strong> - the next 3 days, you can eat chicken or fish, water and honey.</p>

<p>On the day we need 1.2-1.3kg chicken or lean fish 700-800g, as well as water (2-2.5 l) and three teaspoons of honey.</p>

<p>Chicken or lean fish cook in a double boiler. In the morning we drink a glass of water, and then proceed to the meal.</p>

<p>If you chose the chicken, then it is necessary to remove the peel, then eat a whole piece of the leg and the back, that is where a fifth part of the carcass. Then carve the chicken, separating the meat from the bones, mix white and red meat, divide into equal portions and eat up during the remainder of the day. Last time we eat no later than seven o'clock in the evening.</p>

<p>If you <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="choose">choose</a> the fish, it should be divided into 5-6 pieces and eat as well as chicken, for a whole day in equal portions, trying to avoid feeling hungry. To fish was delicious, you can add a little greenery and lemon juice.</p>

<p>You can alternate days fish and chicken to the diet was not too bothersome. As in the early days of drinking water, and we eat the honey.</p>

<p>Why do we lose weight? Receipt of protein contributes to the fact that fat cells break up fat, which contributes to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="rapid weight loss">rapid weight loss</a>.</p>

<p><strong>The third stage</strong> - the next 3 days, we eat only vegetables, water and honey.</p>

<p>Take a day 1 kg of vegetables, 2-2.5l mineral water without gas, and 3 teaspoons of honey spoon.</p>

<p>It is better to give preference to white, and green vegetables such as cabbage, zucchini, onions, etc. But also do not forget about beets, tomatoes and carrots, but take them to a lesser extent. Please take a pound of vegetables, finely chopped, and simmer, remaining vegetables, we are preparing a salad brush.</p>

<p>What do you need? Raw beet, raw carrots, some cabbage, fresh herbs, a few drops of lemon juice, a teaspoon of olive oil, tablespoon water.</p>

<p><strong>How to cook?</strong> Clean the vegetables and rub on a coarse grater or chop finely. Add the olive oil, lemon juice and water for juiciness.</p>

<p>Then we share the steamed vegetables into three parts and a salad as a brush into three equal parts. It is necessary to alternate the meals throughout the day.</p>

<p>Due to the vegetables in the body is reduced vitamin and mineral complex. Belly immediately becomes smaller, because effectively cleans all the deposits on the walls of the intestine.</p>

<p>Diet is over, and we can return to a normal diet. But because it is necessary to exclude:</p>

<ul>
<li>Too salty foods and foods</li>
<li>Sweet soda water.</li>
</ul>


<p>What can you eat? Eat low-fat cheese, no more than 50g a day, bread from wheat flour, no more than 4 slices per day. Also drink water in large quantities and keep the schedule meals. You need not eat more than 4 times a day in small portions at most 250g at a time no later supper seven hours.</p>

<p>The proposed diet is not too &quot;hungry&quot;, but it is quite specific. You do not need to combine diet with exercise, fitness, work in the country and other complex procedures. But on the contrary leave more move, walk, swim, dance - just relax actively.</p>

<h2>Helpful advice</h2>

<p>Ladies, if you know that you can not abandon all kinds of temptations on holiday, it is better to give up this diet once and for all! It is better to learn to enjoy its appearance as it is. If you can not resist the goodies and will be broken, then all your efforts will be in vain. And remember that any woman can be sexy, regardless of the splendor of forms. The main thing - it is a smiling, good spirits and good humor.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[1kg Per Day Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/1kg-per-day-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-04T14:28:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/1kg-per-day-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/1kg-per-day/img.jpg" alt="1kg per day diet">When a person in one day looking in the mirror and finds that his figure needs to be corrected, he goes online and begins to look for ways to lose weight out there. Moreover, a gradual decrease in weight was not satisfied. Man must necessarily lose weight quickly, to ensure a minimum duration period, when it will have to limit yourself to food. Many people tend to lose weight by 1 kg per day, but whether this is real rate of decrease body fat? Diets in which the authors promise such high rates of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/citrus-diet-for-weight-loss-diet-menus-on-citrus-reviews-recipes/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>, there, and now we will discuss the most common ones.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Some women use a day diet allows you to lose 1 kg of weight. Note that minus 1 kg of body mass - is not the same as the minus 1 kg of fat. This one-day diet is often recommended on the Internet, but few mention one of its features. In the early days of any fat diets are extremely reluctant to leave, so the weight is reduced by emptying the intestines and excretion of fluids. At the same time the stomach will become flatter, but the thickness of the subcutaneous fat layer will remain unchanged.</p>

<ol>
<li>Duration - exactly one day.</li>
<li>Diet painted strictly by the hour, can not deviate from it.</li>
<li>Weight loss occurs by reducing the amount of body fluids and faeces in the intestine.</li>
<li>Diet - 8 times per day, so it is advisable to sit on this mini-diet at the weekend, so it does not interfere with the work schedule.</li>
<li>Salt prohibited - this measure will bring the body of liquid without the use of diuretics.</li>
</ol>


<p><em>Diet Menu minus 1 kg for 1 day on the clock:</em></p>

<p>7:00 - unsweetened black tea (0 kcal);
9:00 - boiled egg (80 calories);
11:00 - tablespoon of raisins (25 kcal);
13:00 - 100 grams of boiled chicken (180 calories);
15:00 - a glass of tomato juice (40 calories);
17:00 - boiled egg (80 calories);
21:00 - a cup of yogurt (100 kcal).</p>

<p>Total - 555 <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/" title="calories">calories</a> for the entire day. If you observe a diet all the time, then quickly led to full order of the figure. Another thing is that to sustain this meager menu longer than 1 day, akin to a feat. Surely you will torment hunger. In addition, such a diet can hardly be called healthy and balanced.</p>

<p>Diet minus 1 kg per day - it&rsquo;s an ambulance to your figure. If your body is not too much fat, you will be visually slimmer. This allows you to look better the next day after the diet. It should be understood that the body fat mass will remain unchanged, so you will get only a temporary result. For sustainable weight loss diet should be longer.</p>

<p>There are longer diets are designed for weight loss of 1 kg per day. In general, they are designed for a week. Subsequently diets simply lose their effectiveness. The fact that lose 1 kg of fat per day impossible. Even if you are physically active, and thus did not eat hardly lose a day more than 500 grams of fat. Moreover, even such pitches are possible only in the first few days, and then the body will reduce the metabolic rate to conserve energy in the hungry period.</p>

<p>Diet minus 1 kg per day is only for 7 days, because in this period to achieve weight loss can be achieved by removing the liquid and purgation of faeces. Naturally, when the old food out of the intestines, and the new comes in miniscule amounts, you become easier. Similarly, reduced body weight when the body takes the water. But infinitely away she can not, so the process of so-called &quot;<a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="slimming">slimming</a>&quot; rapidly slowing.</p>

<p>One of the most common schemes power save enable presumably to 1 kg per day, referred to as &quot;favorite diet&quot;. Who loves it, and most importantly - for what, history is silent. Here&rsquo;s her menu on days:</p>

<p>Monday - you can drink anything you want, in any quantity, but can not eat.
Tuesday - you can eat vegetables in any quantity.
Wednesday - you can drink, but you can not have.
Thursday - you can eat only fruit.
Friday - allowed to eat boiled meat and fish low-fat varieties, eggs and seafood.
Saturday - only to drink, but can not eat.
Sunday - the day the menu includes servings of vegetable salad, two eggs, two servings of fruit salad and cup of soup.</p>

<p>This diet is stupid, ineffective, it contains a whole bunch of unnecessary regulations. Perhaps someone once coined it for a joke, and the rest was picked up and distributed over the Internet. You can not reset using this diet 1 kg daily. However, any result you will surely get. Three of the seven days you are not allowed to consume food. It is unlikely that these will be the days of drinking in vain for your figure.</p>

<p>The Internet goes the myth that diet singer Valeria, which is designed for three days, on a daily basis allows a person to lose 1 kg of weight. It is based on the use of buckwheat porridge without fat and salt. Most sources say that buckwheat acquires special fat-burning properties, if you do not cook it in boiling water and leave overnight to infuse in hot water.</p>

<p><em>In the diet of the singer Valeria only two rules:</em></p>

<ol>
<li>There are only buckwheat water, but in any amount.</li>
<li>Water should be drinking at least 2 liters per day.</li>
</ol>


<p>It is not known whether this diet Valery complied with in reality, or is it another tabloids fiction, but a way to lose weight, we do not recommend because of poor performance. Buckwheat - is a product that eating large amounts can not reduce weight, but on the contrary, grow side. But even if you keep yourself from overeating calorie diet buckwheat these three days will be enough low for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="rapid weight loss">rapid weight loss</a>.</p>

<p>Undoubtedly, the top most stupid diets for weight loss led power scheme, which is based on the daily consumption of fruit alone. Here is your menu for 6 days:</p>

<p>Monday - 1 kg of fruit.</p>

<p>While other human diet literally forced to drink the water in high amounts, fruit diet restricts liquid to 500 ml per day. It is obvious that no advantage is not such a diet. But it has drawbacks whole bunch:</p>

<ul>
<li>fruit contained in the composition of organic acids, which stimulate intestinal motility, causing the secretion of digestive juices and hunger provoking;</li>
<li>fruits contain a lot of carbohydrates, including simple sugars, but the protein in them is very small, so the diet is unhealthy and little use for the figure;</li>
<li>people with diseases of the gastrointestinal tract diet is contraindicated due to the possible aggravation of her background of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/gastritis.html" title="gastritis">gastritis</a> or <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/diagnosis-of-peptic-ulcer-disease.html" title="peptic ulcer">peptic ulcer</a>.</li>
</ul>


<p>You may be able to lose weight on a little fruit. But if the pitches are, they are clearly not amount to 1 kg per day. The diet is unhealthy, poorly tolerated and has a very low efficiency. Perhaps these three reasons enough to abandon it.</p>

<p>The most zealous fans of freebies do not want only a few days to fix a figure, but still wish to do so without dieting. The emergence of the desire to contribute to sellers of various additives, belts, bracelets and other rubbish, supposedly allowing lose weight at least 1 per kg per day without dieting and effort. Typically, such a person desire to end waste of money, human expectations and decreased motivation to further weight loss.</p>

<p>&quot;Minus 1 kg a month without dieting&quot; - that should sound like your goal, if you do not want to limit themselves in power. It is likely that you do not need to diet adjustment, if you will exercise the utmost physical activity:</p>

<ul>
<li>always walk, if possible;</li>
<li>perform yoga exercises in the gym under the supervision of a trainer;</li>
<li>active rest, but not in front of the TV.</li>
</ul>


<p>But you have to understand that provide a negative energy balance in the body without the use of diet is extremely difficult. To do this, you must spend a lot of calories. Although theoretically possible weight loss without dieting, weight reduction achieved in real life, keeping the old diet - it is a very difficult task that requires human willpower, discipline and dedication.</p>

<p>Lose 1 kg per day - this is achievable task. But it is feasible only in the case if you follow a diet plan is not more than 1 day. If you are set to lose fat, not water, and feces, such a goal is unrealistic, regardless of the presence or absence of the desire to diet.</p>

<p>Minus 1 kg per day - a task that will take you just a waste of money. You again sell another &quot;miracle pill&quot; for $100, or &quot;fat burning&quot; zone for $500. Set a goal adequate. Lose weight gradually, and then over time you normalize the weight of his body, without harm to health and damage to the purse.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[90-day Diet of a Separate Food]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/90-day-diet-of-a-separate-food/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-04T10:47:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/90-day-diet-of-a-separate-food</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/90-day-diet-of-a-separate-food/img.jpg" alt="alt"><strong>90 days, a separate food</strong> - the original scheme, based on the classic separation of power, which is strictly regulated on certain days. The eponymous book authors promise us neither more nor less than the acceleration of metabolism, dumping 25 kilograms, and no side effects to health. Let&rsquo;s try to find out how justified their claims, why lovers always sweet like this program and what are the medical background to find on the course. <!--more-->In general, the authors Polyanshek Hrobart and popular Slovak writer and their book far exceeded the circulations of the world best sellers - it&rsquo;s hard to say what is more: a good system or a successful advertising campaign. Doctors do not support the principles of a separate food are no randomized studies that clearly indicate the usefulness of this approach. But <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/citrus-diet-for-weight-loss-diet-menus-on-citrus-reviews-recipes/" title="reviews">reviews</a> the system works, it also trains the habits of a healthy diet and discipline, and it is important in the fight against excess weight.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<h2>90 days separate food</h2>

<p>All three months divided into four &quot;block&quot;, which alternate in succession - before the end of the scheme does not change course. Each four-day cycle is required for the execution, and if you have broken at any point, it is necessary to go back to the beginning of the cycle. If the failure lasted more than a week, you need a hitch (not necessary to continue to destroy the pastries and drink) and return to the beginning of the diet. The scheme is simple and intuitive catchy. Breakfast at any stage is minimal and you build it yourself from a glass of any fruit, starting and ending with exotic blueberries or any fruit as one. Do you want a banana? No problem, eat it, from one end of the world banana come.</p>

<p><strong>Protein loading</strong> - mostly animal protein, although you can use nuts. The preferred fish, lean meat, tofu, cottage cheese, fermented baked milk. Permission is granted to a little lettuce and a small slice of wholemeal bread. No sugar or other carbohydrates, do not forget about seafood, to get a normal fat.</p>

<p><strong>Amyloid day</strong> - this type of vegetables, potatoes, legumes, and complex carbohydrates. On this day, the protein should be minimized and should only be fats and vegetable absolutely necessary amounts for cooking. Salt use smaller, replace it seasonings.</p>

<p><strong>Pure carbohydrate a day</strong> - a favorite day sweet tooth. Fruits and even chocolate are allowed - only in moderation. Moreover, for dinner you can eat a little dessert. But remember, the less simple (fast) carbohydrates, the better.</p>

<p><strong>Vitamin day</strong> - it can still be called a discharge. Unsweetened fruit, some salad, seeds and nuts.</p>

<p><strong>Fully discharge day</strong> on mineral water at the end of a cycle of 29 consecutive days, consider carefully.</p>

<p>The main requirement - strict eating regime, as &quot;the book says&quot;. With breakfast you realize no amateur, fruit and berries, but the rest of the diet are allowed to enjoy in a strictly allotted time - from 12 am to 19 pm. The principle is simple - for lunch you can eat food to satiety, and for dinner have to eat a third less dining portions.</p>

<p>Drinking regime to do the maximum to the bottom of the vitamin and supplements can be taken from ascorbic acid and fish oil.</p>

<ul>
<li>Scrambled eggs with grated cheese, seafood cocktail;</li>
<li>A glass of broth, boiled beef, a slice of corn bread;</li>
<li>Broth of vegetables, boiled or baked potatoes;</li>
<li>Buckwheat with fat and a small piece of bread.</li>
<li>Pasta with tomato sauce;</li>
<li>Oatmeal on skim milk;</li>
<li>A piece of chocolate and crackers - sweet on this day are allowed to, you can even eat some ice cream.</li>
<li>Thick compote of dried fruits;</li>
<li>Fresh fruit salad with honey sauce;</li>
<li>Juice, fresh vegetable salad, pine nuts.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Pros and cons of the diet 90 days separate food</h2>

<p>Considered a long course, with detailed instructions, unloading days and the possibility of a smooth and controlled diet.</p>

<p>One of the few diets which completely &quot;legal&quot; you can eat chocolate, cookies and ice cream.</p>

<p>Change &quot;modes&quot; and the abundance of food is not even allowed to pall after a couple of months from the start of the diet. In addition, the alternation of days will help get rid of the glycogen stores in the muscles, which will accelerate the burning of fat from the stock.</p>

<p>Ability to make fasting day and return to the beginning of the cycle in the event of unauthorized use of a product or holidays, most diets have to start again.</p>

<p>We need a serious preparation, planning and cooking meals for the next day - discipline is very important.</p>

<p>There is no proven medical reason for separate meals, also proved that inhibit enzymes friend - friend, in case of splitting of food from various sources.</p>

<p>Many nutritionists speak of separate principles of nutrition, as a pseudoscientific delirium, likely losing weight will be due to lower caloric content and depletion of glycogen stores. All thinking about the health benefits can be safely omitted - such data is unavailable.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citrus Diet for Weight Loss. Diet Menus on Citrus, Reviews, Recipes]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/citrus-diet-for-weight-loss-diet-menus-on-citrus-reviews-recipes/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-27T18:19:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/citrus-diet-for-weight-loss-diet-menus-on-citrus-reviews-recipes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/citrus-diet-for-weight-loss/img.jpg" alt="alt">Citrus diet - it&#39;s a great way to cleanse the body and get rid of excess weight, suitable for those who like oranges, grapefruits, lemons, mandarins and pomelo.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Citrus diet slimming: the essence, the benefits and features</h2>

<p>The main feature of citrus diet for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> is considered to be the ability to citrus fat burning.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Everybody knows, for example, is used in many grapefruit weight correction techniques due to the presence therein arginine - a substance that promotes the safe destruction of fat cells.</p>

<p>Other products from the diet on citrus are also of great benefit to the body:</p>

<ul>
<li>Lemons normalize hormonal balance, stabilize your metabolism, remove toxins and waste products;</li>
<li>Oranges are rich in ascorbic acid, improves cellular metabolism, lower <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a>, stimulate <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a> and strengthen the immune system;</li>
<li>Mandarins restore the balance of vitamins, improve the patient&#39;s condition at <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/pulmonology/colds.html" title="colds">colds</a>;</li>
<li>Pomelo strengthens the heart muscle, normalizes the functioning of all systems of the body, increases the elasticity of vessel walls.</li>
</ul>


<p>The benefits of citrus diet are as follows:</p>

<ul>
<li>All citrus fruits are well satisfy hunger, so move the diet is not too difficult, despite the rather &quot;hungry&quot; menu;</li>
<li>With this power technique can completely clean your body of harmful substances and strengthen the immune system;</li>
<li>This power supply system is quite effective, and allows you to lose weight in a short time.</li>
</ul>


<p>Any diet has its drawbacks, and this - is no exception:</p>

<ul>
<li>Some of the menu is still very poor, and the feeling of hunger will periodically visit;</li>
<li>The diet is not suitable for people with allergies, because citrus can trigger the emergence of allergies. It is also forbidden to resort to such a <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7">weight loss</span> during <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a>, breastfeeding or if you have any chronic diseases.</li>
</ul>


<h3>How many kilos of leaves on citrus diet</h3>

<p>Because quite strict <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/avocado-diet-for-weight-loss/" title="menus">menus</a>, weight loss on citrus lets throw 5-7 kilos per week, at the same time every day turns out not to consume more than 1,000 <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/" title="calories">calories</a>. Another issue is whether the amounts spent on citrus diet: indeed, literally disappears in 3-4 days bulging tummy, but things can return to their circles, if at the end of a <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/low-calorie-diet.html" title="low-calorie diet">low-calorie diet</a> to begin again to eat fatty foods.</p>

<p>What products, besides citrus, may be present in the menu:</p>

<ul>
<li>Eggs;</li>
<li>Dairy products;</li>
<li>Juices;</li>
<li>Porridge;</li>
<li>Low-fat types of fish and meat;</li>
<li>Vegetables;</li>
<li>Greenery.</li>
</ul>


<p>What is forbidden to use:</p>

<ul>
<li>Any fatty, salted, smoked or pickled foods;</li>
<li>Pickles and Sweets.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Citrus Diet: Rules, menus, popular recipes</h2>

<p><em>Slimming rules citrus diet:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>It is necessary to drink as much purified water to accelerate the excretion of excess fluid, and as a result - weight loss;</li>
<li>It is not allowed the presence of other foods during monodiets and when weight loss occurs only on two specific dishes.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Citrus diet for 3 days</h3>

<p>Express-method allows to get rid of 3 kg of excess weight, eating according to this principle:</p>

<ul>
<li>Every day, eat up to 1.2 kg of any citrus fruit;</li>
<li>We drink 1 glass of water every 1.5-2 hours.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Citrus diet for 4 weeks</h3>

<p>To lose up to 15 kilograms, you need to eat any food allowed, using this example menu:</p>

<ul>
<li>We have breakfast grapefruit, unsweetened tea and a loaf;</li>
<li>For lunch we drink 200 grams of fat-free yogurt;</li>
<li>Lunch with any kind of citrus fruit in unlimited quantities;</li>
<li>Supper boiled meat and vegetable salad.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Egg - citrus diet</h3>

<p>The duration of such a diet should not exceed three days:</p>

<ul>
<li>We have breakfast 200 grams of orange juice;</li>
<li>For lunch we eat boiled soft-boiled egg;</li>
<li>Lunch grapefruit juice (200 ml), and a jar of low-fat yogurt;</li>
<li>Afternoon snack boiled egg;</li>
<li>For dinner, drink orange juice (1 cup).</li>
</ul>


<h3>Dieting on citrus juice</h3>

<p>Throughout the week, you need to strictly adhere to the following diet:</p>

<ul>
<li>In the morning we eat two boiled eggs, &#189; grapefruit;</li>
<li>For lunch we eat oranges and drinking orange juice in any quantity;</li>
<li>We have supper cooked rice (100 g), and orange juice.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Protein - citrus diet</h3>

<p>Within 8 days allowed to eat any citrus fruits, dairy products, fish and meat:</p>

<ul>
<li>We have breakfast low-fat yogurt and four mandarins;</li>
<li>Lunch portion of boiled buckwheat with added prunes, drink a glass of juice;</li>
<li>Lemon drink and an afternoon snack tangerine;</li>
<li>Supper grapefruit with honey, tea and loaf.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Dieting on citrus fruits and yogurt</h3>

<p>This menu can be used for the three days of discharge:</p>

<ul>
<li>We drink every day up to 1 liter of 1% kefir;</li>
<li>Eat up 1 kg of any citrus fruit.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Dieting on citrus and chicken</h3>

<p>In this case, as permitted, and 100 grams of cheese per day, and so you can not eat more than a week:</p>

<ul>
<li>We have breakfast grapefruit and cottage cheese;</li>
<li>For lunch we eat 100 grams of boiled chicken breast;</li>
<li>Lunch any citrus;</li>
<li>Afternoon snack chicken;</li>
<li>Supper citrus.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Fish - citrus diet</h3>

<p>For those who are more like fish than chicken, fits this menu:</p>

<ul>
<li>Oranges have breakfast in any amount;</li>
<li>For lunch drink citrus juice;</li>
<li>Lunch cooked fish and orange fruit;</li>
<li>Afternoon snack juice;</li>
<li>At dinner, lunch, diet repeat.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Citrus fruit - vegetable diet</h3>

<p>This menu can be used no more than 10 days:</p>

<ul>
<li>We have breakfast a couple of apples and oranges;</li>
<li>For lunch we drink a cup of tea;</li>
<li>Lunch vegetable salad;</li>
<li>Afternoon snack glass of orange juice;</li>
<li>We have supper of boiled beef and greens.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Citrus fat burning diet for weight loss: reviews, results, real stories slimming</h2>

<p>Doctors have a wide variety of specializations do not approve strict diet menus on citrus, as overreliance on such fruit can increase the acidity of the stomach and lead to a variety of disorders.</p>

<p>The optimal duration of weight loss - not more than a week. The only exception is the diet for up to a month: it is balanced, and not likely to cause significant harm to health.</p>

<p>Very important is the correct way of citrus diet:</p>

<ul>
<li>In the first week you need to increase the amount of fruits and vegetables on the menu;</li>
<li>Starting with the second - to introduce more fish and meat.</li>
</ul>


<p>Diet for weight loss results on citrus fruits in general a positive effect on the body, if you do not abuse the technique and use it no more than three times a year:</p>

<ul>
<li>Normalization of metabolism;</li>
<li>Enhance immunity;</li>
<li>Improving the appearance of the skin;</li>
<li>Rapid weight loss.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Figs Diet for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-22T10:57:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/img.jpg" alt="Figs diet reviews of lost weight">Figs diet - an easy way of getting rid of excess weight, which can be used by anyone who wants to have a slim figure and good immunity.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Figs natural diet: the essence, the use of slimming features</h2>

<p>Figs consumed canned, dried or fresh: it is added to salads, and even cook him soup.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Many people wonder whether it is possible to use figs for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>, and for this you need to know the calorie content: 100 g of the product is 49 kcal, which is a very good indicator for <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7">successful weight loss</span>.</p>

<p>The essence of the dietFigs on a diet is that this fruit has a number of useful elements, favorably affecting the health and figure:</p>

<ul>
<li>Vitamin C boosts the immune system;</li>
<li>Fiber improves bowel motility;</li>
<li>Trace elements stabilize the cardiovascular system and gastrointestinal tract.</li>
</ul>


<p>It is worth noting that the dried figs in the diet has a higher caloric value than fresh: in 100 g contains 214 calories, but eat it a lot in any case it does not, because it is quite satisfying.</p>

<h3>Pros and cons figs diet</h3>

<p><em>The main advantages of weight loss with figs:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>It is possible to eat any <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-much-protein-fat-and-carbohydrates-you-need-in-a-day-to-lose-weight/" title="low-calorie foods">low-calorie foods</a>, so hunger is not felt;</li>
<li>There are several types of diets figs on how to set, and weight loss;</li>
<li>Calorie diet on the figs are no more than 1500-1700 calories a day, so it can help you lose weight very well.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Not everyone can eat figs, and diet it is contraindicated in the following diseases:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Gout;</li>
<li>Exacerbation of inflammatory bowel disease;</li>
<li>Diabetes.</li>
</ul>


<h3>How much can you lose on a diet with figs</h3>

<p>Depending on the variety of techniques, it takes an average of up to 5 kg per week. EfficiencyFigs diet is largely determined by the weight of the original, and what it more - the faster the weight loss.</p>

<p>Those who wonder if the volume on the goFigs diet, you should know that in any case, with the decrease in Endangered kilograms and volume of the body, but this applies only to the waist and hips.</p>

<p><em>What products can be used in the dietFigs:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Low-fat cottage cheese, yogurt, milk;</li>
<li>Fruit;</li>
<li>Vegetables;</li>
<li>Broth hips;</li>
<li>Cereals cereals;</li>
<li>Greenery;</li>
<li>Green tea;</li>
<li>Lean meat and fish.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>What is forbidden to eat during a diet:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Flour;</li>
<li>Sweets;</li>
<li>Smoked;</li>
<li>Pickles;</li>
<li>Fried.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Diet with figs slimming menus, recipes, rules</h2>

<p><em>Weight loss diet rules Figs:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Figs need to eat separately from other food and all day you can eat no more than 15 dried fruits;</li>
<li>It is advisable to go to 4 meals a day, and every day to drink 1.5 liters of water.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet for dried figs</h3>

<p>In this case, it allowed to use any non-nutritive foods:</p>

<ul>
<li>Instead of lunch or dinner, eat 3-4 pieces. figs;</li>
<li>The pre-soaked dried fruit in water.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet figs with yogurt</h3>

<p>If you select this option for weight loss, then 3 days of its use will be able to lose up to 4 kg of weight and cleanse the intestines:</p>

<ul>
<li>Every day, eat 500 grams of figs;</li>
<li>Drink 1.5 liters of nonfat yogurt.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet figs with milk</h3>

<p>Those who are more like milk than yogurt, can also be successfully used it to lose weight in 3 days 3 kg:</p>

<ul>
<li>Eat up to 2 liters of low-fat milk;</li>
<li>Eat up to 400 grams of dried fruit.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet figs with dried apricots</h3>

<p>To lose 5-7 kilograms per month, indulging in your favorite foods, it is necessary at night to take 1 ch. L. mixture prepared according to this recipe:</p>

<ul>
<li>Grind senna, prunes, figs and apricots (100 g);</li>
<li>Mix, store in the refrigerator.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet figs with honey</h3>

<p>A mixture of figs with honey can not only get rid of the <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/pulmonology/cough.html" title="cough">cough</a>, but also to lose weight fast:</p>

<ul>
<li>Mix 10 pcs. dried figs with Article 10. l. honey;</li>
<li>Take 1 tsp.. in the morning and in the evening;</li>
<li>The capacity of the composition of reserve in the refrigerator.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet figs with lemon</h3>

<p>It is enough to replace the usual dinner this salad, and weight loss will be noticeable within a month:</p>

<ul>
<li>Rub the beets and carrots, figs and prunes soaked after 5 minutes add the vegetables;</li>
<li>Passed through a garlic press, squeeze the juice of one lemon, add 1 tsp.. olive oil and dressed with a mixture of lettuce.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Figs diet for weight gain</h3>

<p>If you wish not to reduce, but to gain weight, you should eat a sweet mixture should be every morning for 40 days:</p>

<ul>
<li>Soak in warm milk 4 pcs. figs and 5 pcs. almond nuts;</li>
<li>After 3 chasa means is ready for use.</li>
</ul>


<h3>The diet of figs breastfeeding</h3>

<p>The fig contains many trace elements beneficial for both mother and for the baby, but it should be administered cautiously in <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="slimming">slimming diet</a>:</p>

<ul>
<li>The first 3 days to eat one piece. Dried fruits, observe the reaction of the baby;</li>
<li>If a child is not a rash or <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/diarrhea.html" title="diarrhea">diarrhea</a> - and this may be due to the emergence of a new product or an <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/allergology/allergy.html" title="allergy">allergy</a> to it - adding another 2 pcs. figs every day, reaching up to 10 pcs.;</li>
<li>We eat figs for breakfast only.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Recipes for a diet figs</h2>

<p><em>Recipe salad with figs:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Soaked in water 150 grams of prunes, mix it with the figs and cut;</li>
<li>Parboiled almonds, remove it with a peel and shred it;</li>
<li>Mix, sprinkle with orange zest and pour acidophilus.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Recipe curd dessert with figs:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Grind through a low-fat cottage cheese, purify and ground orange, cut the figs;</li>
<li>Add a little honey and stir.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Spanish soup recipe with figs:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Clear the pen and cut onions, potatoes;</li>
<li>Grind onion, cook the broth;</li>
<li>Put the vegetables in the broth, cook for half an hour, salt, fill with low-fat cream and whisk blender;</li>
<li>Cut the figs and bacon, fry them in a pan in butter;</li>
<li>Cut a baguette into strips, fry in a pan as well;</li>
<li>Pour soup bowls, spread the figs and bacon baguette;</li>
<li>We eat for lunch only. Suitable for those who want to gain weight.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Persimmon Nutrition for Weight Loss. Persimmon Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/persimmon-nutrition-for-weight-loss-persimmon-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-07T07:31:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/persimmon-nutrition-for-weight-loss-persimmon-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/persimmon-nutrition-for-weight-loss-persimmon-diet/img.jpg" alt="Persimmon nutrition for weight loss.  Persimmon diet">For those who love sweets on persimmon diet works best: it allows you to quickly get rid of a few extra kilos and is very useful for health.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Persimmon nutrition: the benefits, the essence, advantages and disadvantages</h2>

<p>Calorie 100 g of fruit varies from 60 to 70 calories, so many people is not in question, can I use persimmon diet.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
This miracle fruit contains a large amount of nutrients has a positive impact on the human body:</p>

<ul>
<li>Vitamins;</li>
<li>Minerals;</li>
<li>Proteins;</li>
<li>Organic acids;</li>
<li>Fiber;</li>
<li>Tannin and pectin.</li>
</ul>


<p>The essence of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> on a persimmon nutrition is that a person uses a small amount of calories, due to which the weight starts to drop. Thus, the shortage of energy the body has to produce its own, breaking down existing fat deposits.</p>

<h3>Pros and cons of persimmon nutrition</h3>

<p>Slimming with persimmon has a lot of advantages:</p>

<ul>
<li>This fruit prevents kidney disease, is useful in nervous disorders and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/vascular-disease/" title="cardiovascular diseases">cardiovascular diseases</a>;</li>
<li>With this technique, you can quickly lose kilograms;</li>
<li>If all the rules harm health is not possible;</li>
<li>Dried persimmon and diet - the concept is almost incompatible, since it contains 274 kcal per 100 g It can be only replace meal - for example, dinner - and then will lose weight.</li>
</ul>


<p>Contraindicated eat persimmons people with diabetes and problems with the digestive tract, but during <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a> it is recommended by many doctors because of the fact that it has the most necessary elements for the normal development of the fetus.</p>

<h3>How much can you lose on a persimmon nutrition</h3>

<p>It is difficult to imagine a more <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7">effective product for weight loss</span> than the persimmon, and her diet helps to reduce the weight by 1 kg per day, if you are using strict menus, and up to 500 grams for the same period - if it is just to eat dinner instead.</p>

<p>Is the volume on the go with persimmon diet as well as weight? Of course, with the disposal of kilograms after some time it can be seen that the waist and hips become less than a few centimeters in volume, and remained the same breast.</p>

<p>Calorie diet on a persimmon depends on the menu, but it is usually possible to consume per day to 1,500 Kcal.</p>

<p>What products may be diet:</p>

<ul>
<li>Vegetables;</li>
<li>Fruit;</li>
<li>Fermented beverages;</li>
<li>Porridge;</li>
<li>Lean meat and fish;</li>
<li>Greenery;</li>
<li>Boiled eggs;</li>
<li>Hard cheese;</li>
<li>Cottage cheese.</li>
</ul>


<p>As in any other weight loss method, it is strictly forbidden to eat any high-calorie and sweet dishes, and if the menu is limited to just one product - to use once it is resolved.</p>

<p>The effectiveness of the persimmon nutrition is achieved precisely because throughout it has to restrict itself slightly in the food, but soon you can be sure that such restrictions are not in vain.</p>

<h2>Persimmon nutrition: diet menus, recipes, rules</h2>

<p><em>Slimming rules using persimmon:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Persimmon can eat in the usual form, or to cook from her salad when not using mono-diet;</li>
<li>To quickly clear the body and lose weight, you need every day to drink 1.5 liters of clean water without gas;</li>
<li>When used in foods only for 1-2 days it is recommended to refrain from strenuous exercise.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Strict persimmon diet: a menu for 3 days</h3>

<p><em>The most rigid diet is not designed for more than 3 days:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Eat up to 2 kg of persimmon;</li>
<li>Drink water, herbal or green tea.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Persimmon nutrition and yogurt</h3>

<p><em>A further embodiment can also be used not more than three days:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>We eat for the whole day, no more than 6 fruits;</li>
<li>We drink a maximum of 1.5 liters of nonfat yogurt.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Persimmon nutrition and apples</h3>

<p><em>You can replace the yogurt to apples, using this strict diet:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>We drink for 1-3 days 1 kg of apples and persimmons;</li>
<li>As for drinks, leaving only green tea and water.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet and persimmon bran</h3>

<p><em>It is known that bran well cleanse the body and strengthen the immune system and eating salad, cooked them and persimmon, you can lose a couple of extra kilos:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Persimmon grind, mix with a third cup of dry bran, pour all the fat yogurt;</li>
<li>We eat a dish for lunch, and on all other meals ready-made meals from the authorized products.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet persimmon and honey</h3>

<p><em>For weight loss per month for 7-10 kg can be used and this menu:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>We eat any food allowed;</li>
<li>For dinner, we eat a persimmon and 1 ch. L. honey.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Persimmon nutrition and rice</h3>

<p><em>Mono-diet, which lasts up to 7 days, to successfully get rid of 5-7 kg of excess weight:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>We eat only boiled rice without salt (500 g per day);</li>
<li>Eat up to 1 kg of persimmon.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Valerie Diet persimmon</h3>

<p><em>Singer periodically uses this 7-day diet to keep fit:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Breakfast porridge, cooked with water;</li>
<li>Lunch vegetable soup, and a steam cutlet;</li>
<li>Supper persimmons and glass of kefir.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Persimmon nutrition for pregnant persimmon</h3>

<p><em>During childbearing eating persimmon great benefit: eliminating the edema, strengthens the nervous system, removes excess fluid from the body, saturating it with potassium. To get rid of the astringency of the fruit, you can use one of the methods:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Keeping persimmon in warm water 12 hours;</li>
<li>Frozen and then thawed fruit;</li>
<li>Give the fruit ripen on the windowsill, if it is not fully ripened.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Recipes for a diet with persimmons</h3>

<p><em>Recipe salad of persimmons:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Clear the persimmons, cut it into circles;</li>
<li>Cut slices mozzarella cheese;</li>
<li>We spread the cheese on the persimmon, alternating with each other circles;</li>
<li>Sprinkle with pepper and pour olive oil.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Recipe soup with persimmon:</h3>

<ul>
<li>Cut into cubes of onion, sweet pepper and persimmon;</li>
<li>Fry the onion in vegetable oil, add the tomato paste and paprika, simmer on low heat for 5 minutes;</li>
<li>Add to the pan and persimmon pepper, simmer for 7 minutes;</li>
<li>Place the vegetables in a pre-cooked vegetable broth, boil, salt and pepper;</li>
<li>Before serving, sprinkle with herbs.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Recipe dessert with persimmon:</h3>

<ul>
<li>Pour boiling water over prunes, give him shall be melted;</li>
<li>Clean up and cut a persimmon;</li>
<li>We spread in a glass dessert first layer of low-fat cottage cheese, and more - prune and persimmons;</li>
<li>Finally, dressed with yogurt and sprinkle with cinnamon.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avocado Diet for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/avocado-diet-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-01T09:38:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/avocado-diet-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/avocado-diet-for-weight-loss/img.jpg" width="200" height="150" alt="Avocado diet: reviews of lost weight">For those who love sweetish fruit ripe avocado, there is a special diet that allows you to quickly get rid of excess weight.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>A diet with avocado: the essence, the benefits, advantages and disadvantages</h2>

<p>Due to the fact that oily taste the fruit is quite high in calories - 208 kilocalories per 100 grams, many question arises: is it possible to use the avocado diet?</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
It is worth bearing in mind that he quickly satisfies hunger, because to comply with the usual diet will need no more than 5 fruits per day and thus be able to eat no more than 1,100 kcal - this is a very small figure.</p>

<p>The essence of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> on a diet of avocados is precisely to reduce calorie intake, as well as its useful functions for the body:</p>

<ul>
<li>Avocados have no <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a> and it contains monounsaturated fatty acids perfectly clean vessels, eliminate cholesterol plaques and removal of residues;</li>
<li>Turning to your diet avocados contribute to a speedy cure digestive diseases, thyroid and stabilization in <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/cardiology/hypertension.html" title="hypertension">hypertension</a>, as well as skin rejuvenation.</li>
</ul>


<p>It is because of these useful properties of avocado diet is especially appreciated by physicians: they believe that this product is the best suited to make a slim figure.</p>

<h3>Pros and cons of diet with avocado</h3>

<p>In <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7">weight loss</span> with avocado has a number of advantages:</p>

<ul>
<li>The very diet transferred easily, because the ripe juicy fruit reduce appetite and quickly satisfy hunger;</li>
<li>Methods suitable for all, except for pregnant women, children and the elderly;</li>
<li>Many other products on the menu, if it is not strictly mono version.</li>
</ul>


<p>Use avocado diet has a small disadvantage: only one fruit can not be eaten for a long time, as this may lead to metabolic disorders.</p>

<h3>How much can you lose on a diet with avocado</h3>

<p>Calorie diet on the avocado, regardless of its particular species is never higher than 1500 kcal, which allows for 1 day to get rid of 800-900 g weight.</p>

<p>Many people wonder whether the volumes with avocado diet goes, and in this case it is important to know that weight loss always involves a reduction in its volume - in particular, hips and waist.</p>

<h3>Avocado and diet: what foods can be eaten</h3>

<p>During maintenance diet following products may be used in menu:</p>

<ul>
<li>Cereal porridge;</li>
<li>Fruits and vegetables;</li>
<li>Lean meat and fish;</li>
<li>Greenery;</li>
<li>Fermented beverages.</li>
</ul>


<p>Under the ban are all sweet, fatty, smoked or salted food, as they reduce the effectiveness of the diet on the avocado.</p>

<h2>Diet avocado diet menus, recipes, rules</h2>

<p><em>Diet rules with the help of an avocado:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>The fruit should be just ripe, and before use should be cut into two pieces, and remove pits;</li>
<li>Eat must be at least 4 times a day in small portions, and be sure to drink 2 liters of water daily.</li>
</ul>


<h3>A strict diet for avocados: Menu</h3>

<p>To lose up to 4 kilos, you need to follow this menu for the 3 days:</p>

<ul>
<li>Every day, we eat 5 fruit avocado, dividing them into several portions;</li>
<li>2 liters of drinking water, and more.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Avocado diet and yogurt</h3>

<p>A softer version of the three-day diet includes the following:</p>

<ul>
<li>Also, we eat at 5 avocados;</li>
<li>To drink 1 liter of nonfat yogurt.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Avocado diet avocado and cottage cheese</h3>

<p>For 5 days using this menu, you can lose weight by 5 kg:</p>

<ul>
<li>In the morning we eat half an avocado and 50 g of fat-free yogurt;</li>
<li>For lunch we eat a salad with cucumber, green onions, &frac12; avocado and egg;</li>
<li>Supper 100 g of boiled beef, a half avocado and boiled egg.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Avocado diet with ginger</h3>

<p>During the month of application of such a diet turns to throw up to 10 kg:</p>

<ul>
<li>We eat any food from the list of permitted;</li>
<li>For dinner, we eat 40 grams of avocado and drink tea with ginger.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet avocado puree</h3>

<p>This diet is suitable for fasting days:</p>

<ul>
<li>We eat up to 700 grams of mashed avocado pulp;</li>
<li>For breakfast, we eat, and further 100 g of cottage cheese.</li>
</ul>


<h3>A diet with avocado Julia Roberts</h3>

<p>The technique is designed for 28 days, during which the need to eat on the menu the following example:</p>

<ul>
<li>Steam have breakfast omelette and avocado;</li>
<li>For lunch drink fruit juice;</li>
<li>Lunch baked fish and vegetable salad;</li>
<li>Afternoon snack low-fat yogurt;</li>
<li>We have supper of boiled fish and 100 g of fruit.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet blueberry avocado and ginger</h3>

<p>According to the well-known TV presenter, there is the easiest way to lose weight with the help of three products:</p>

<ul>
<li>Avocado: eliminate fat;</li>
<li>Ginger: relieves bloating;</li>
<li>Blueberries: it reduces appetite and has anti-inflammatory effects.</li>
</ul>


<p>All three ingredients must be present in the diet, which is equal to the caloric content of 1500 kcal, while you can eat anything you want, adhering to the specified limit.</p>

<h3>Recipes for a diet with avocado</h3>

<p><em>Recipe mashed avocado:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Clear the number of fruit, remove them from the brush;</li>
<li>Pulp transform into a puree using a blender or corolla.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Recipe salad with avocado:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Boil chicken breast, cut into cubes it together with tomato, cucumber and avocado;</li>
<li>Mix, sprinkle with herbs and pour the lemon juice.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Recipe soup with avocado:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Boil potatoes, peeled avocado and zucchini;</li>
<li>Add salt and pepper;</li>
<li>Beat blender;</li>
<li>Before serving, add a little lemon juice.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
