<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-07-12T17:09:43+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hysteria: what symptoms? Being hysterical]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/hysteria-what-symptoms-being-hysterical/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-12T17:05:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/hysteria-what-symptoms-being-hysterical</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/hysteria-what-symptoms-being-hysterical/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="hysteria, hysterical personality, hysterical conversion, hysterical somatization" alt="Hysteria: what symptoms? Being hysterical">Hysteria, this term is often used in common parlance usually means in this context quite different things.</p>

<p>You are hysterical sometimes means: &ldquo;You get mad for nothing&rdquo;, &ldquo;You really added&rdquo; or &ldquo;I do not understand your operation!&rdquo;</p>

<p>However, the term hysteria has a different meaning in psychiatric medicine that hysteria itself corresponds to the symptoms found in the foreground in a pathological personality type, hysterical personalities.</p>

<h2>How is a person suffering from hysteria?</h2>

<p>Specific attitudes of hysteria are being representing. When you see such a person, you feel that it is too: it seems to be in a movie, play a role; it dramatizes, dramatize, exaggerate, in add. It is in excess, talking loudly, quickly, occupies the ground, laughed too, makes great gestures, uses formulas disproportionate to what it says. Some TV presenters or some actors therefore logically hysterical personality.</p>

<p>Hysteria up to the mythomanie when the affected person really adds some too. It can go up lie, misrepresent reality. However hysteria does not always go to this extreme.</p>

<p>Another very common element in hysteria is seduction: human relationships are eroticized, we try to seduce you, in life in general, but also in the sexual realm. In humans, hysteria is often linked to philandering, a tendency to collect relationships. However, this seductive attitude is often associated with a poor sex, inhibited difficult. For hysteria is a facade that hides gaps.</p>

<h2>What are the thoughts related to hysteria?</h2>

<p>The hysterical behavior and therefore hysterical symptoms, are exposed because they are caused by inner thoughts. In other words, a person with hysterical tendencies thoughts explaining his behavior.</p>

<p>It may be varied cognition:</p>

<p>&ldquo;I must be the center of attention&rdquo;;
&ldquo;I need you to notice me&rdquo;;
&ldquo;I&rsquo;m afraid to be alone&rdquo;;
&ldquo;I need to charm, to please&rdquo;;
&ldquo;I do not want you see my weaknesses, my fears&rdquo;;
&ldquo;I need the others because I do not know just do it myself&rdquo;;
&ldquo;I want you to find me irresistible&rdquo;&hellip;</p>

<h2>The deep emotions of hysteria</h2>

<p>If signs of hysteria are related to thoughts, these thoughts are related, deeper emotions. These emotions are especially fears that seek to be erased by the hysterical behavior:</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m afraid you do not love me&hellip; So I&rsquo;m doing what I think suitable for you love me.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m afraid I do not exist&hellip; So I do everything for you notice me and feel me exist.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m afraid I can not do it myself&hellip; So I need to charm around me that are helping me.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m afraid to be unhappy face myself&hellip; So I&rsquo;m dizzy from others, so do not find me alone with myself.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m afraid that my weaknesses are noticed&hellip; Then I add, I boast, I invent, I overplayed to try to hide my limits.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Overall, the hysterical symptoms, fairly simple to spot, and sometimes annoying for the environment actually correspond to deep fears and significant gaps. Perhaps by being aware, we can all show more empathy for people working in this register.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to calibrate their cholesterol. Triglyceride and HDL-cholesterol]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-10T01:15:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="cholesterol, cholesterol tests" alt="When to calibrate their cholesterol, Triglyceride and HDL-cholesterol">Certain periods of life, habits and diseases should motivate them to calibrate their cholesterol.</p>

<p>Recall that cholesterol is accompanied at first no symptoms until the day cardiovascular complications occur (myocardial infarction, stroke)!</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>At what times of life should you calibrate their cholesterol?</h2>

<h3>A adolescence</h3>

<p>A first cholesterol test is recommended between 16 and 30 years. Some people are more at risk than others and our lifestyle plays an important role, explaining that high cholesterol can occur in childhood. But during this period of life, the &ldquo;bad cholesterol&rdquo; is gradually deposited on the arterial walls and turns into plaque at the end of adolescence. In addition, it is to the age of 18 that cholesterol binds permanently.</p>

<blockquote><p>In other words, if cholesterol is high in adolescence, it will be a lifetime.</p></blockquote>

<h3>From 45 years for men and 55 years for women</h3>

<p>From these ages, a cholesterol test is recommended every 3 years. Is that with advancing age, the risk of having too much cholesterol in the blood is increased.</p>

<blockquote><p>As is also the case for other cardiovascular risk factors (hypertension, physical inactivity, overweight&hellip;), it must be particularly vigilant.</p></blockquote>

<h3>At the time of menopause</h3>

<p>In women, a dosage once installed menopause is wise. Indeed, major hormonal changes that occur at this time of life can lead to a significant increase in cholesterol.</p>

<blockquote><p>Menopause is a key period to make a determination of its cholesterol.</p></blockquote>

<h2>What are the diseases that require close monitoring cholesterol?</h2>

<ul>
<li>A <strong>type 2 diabetes</strong> imposes a cholesterol test every year.</li>
<li><strong>Overweight or obesity promoting cholesterol</strong>, it is necessary to conduct regular dosages. This is also the case when the waist is high: greater than 88 cm for women and 102 cm for men.</li>
<li><strong>Some diseases such as chronic renal failure and untreated hypothyroidism cause high cholesterol</strong> and impose specific monitoring.</li>
<li>Finally, <strong>some drugs affect blood lipids</strong>. Talk to your doctor.</li>
</ul>


<h2>What are the habits that require regular cholesterol test?</h2>

<ul>
<li>Smoking (or stopped for less than 3 years), especially if combined with an oral contraceptive.</li>
<li>Inactivity.</li>
<li>A diet rich in meat, animal products and fats.</li>
</ul>


<h2>What dose do we exactly?</h2>

<p>The determination of total cholesterol in the blood is commonly prescribed as part of a screening or surveillance.</p>

<p>However, to get a clearer picture, it is necessary to make an assessment of lipid abnormalities, including:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>The Triglyceride and HDL- cholesterol</strong> (normal: From 0.35 to 0.75 g/l).</li>
<li><strong>On the LDL-cholesterol</strong> is calculated from the values ??of the previous (normal: 1 to 1.6 g/l).</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Products debilitating arthritis pain]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/products-debilitating-arthritis-pain/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-05T12:52:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/products-debilitating-arthritis-pain</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/products-debilitating-arthritis-pain/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="arthritis pain, arthritis, diet, ñhondroprotectors, dairy products" alt="Products debilitating arthritis pain">Arthritis &ndash; an inflammatory disease of the joint (or more joints), and among the main causes various infections diseases, injuries, nervous system disorders, allergy, metabolic disorders, vitamin deficiencies. The disease occurs quite often, and do not always get sick elderly people (although they are certainly more often).</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Arthritis &ndash; a set of measures, including medication, mud hirudotherapy, physiotherapy, and, alas, sometimes it comes to surgery. But the disease could have been avoided or at least significantly delay it, if in time, that is, from his youth to think about its prevention. And this, above all, the right diet. But never too late to start, the people who have been diagnosed with arthritis, it is recommended to stick to a certain diet &ndash; in conjunction with the main treatment this will substantially reduce joint pain and slow the progression of the disease.</p>

<h2>Fighting overweight</h2>

<p>There have arthritis your &ldquo;favorites&rdquo;, but rather &ldquo;darling&rdquo; &ndash; is obese women overstepped 50-year milestone. As a rule, most of these ladies are suffering from any disease of the joints &ndash; this arthritis and osteoarthritis and gout, etc. It is important to understand that the further progression of these diseases in a short time can lead to disability and, of course, very spoil the quality of life, and that is why it is now important in combination with other therapeutic measures to think about weight loss. This not only helps to improve the condition of the joints, but also contribute to the overall improvement of the body.</p>

<h2>Priority products</h2>

<p>Is not a secret that vegetarians are significantly less likely to suffer from diseases of the joints than avid meat-eaters. Besides diet, based fresh fruits and vegetables containing fiber, promote rapid weight loss.</p>

<p>For example, people suffering from arthritis, recommended in all kinds of cabbage. It contains sulforaphane &ndash; a substance which prevents the destruction of the cartilage tissue. In this sense, all the good cabbage varieties, but especially broccoli. Cabbage also contains a record number of vitamins, micro and macro, and therefore not only helps prevent joint pain, but also enhances the body&rsquo;s resistance to many diseases. And by the way, the constant use of cabbage effectively helps to cope with the problem of constipation, if any.</p>

<p>Summer must eat cherries. These berries contain a lot of antioxidants (anthocyanins), which due to their anti-inflammatory properties, act as an anesthetic. Arthritis, osteoarthritis and gout even able to retreat before the cherries.</p>

<p><strong>Collagen</strong> is essential for building bone and cartilage, muscles and ligaments. He is in aspic jelly or which are prepared on the basis of bone broth.</p>

<p><strong>Chondroprotectors</strong> &ndash; another substance which promotes the restoration of the cartilaginous tissue and enhances the production of synovial fluid. Pharmacopeia offers a variety of drugs for the treatment of arthritis, based on glucosamine and chondroitin them who belong to the group chondroprotectors. Contains a substance in food gelatin, so do not forget to prepare a more delicious dessert and low-cal like jelly.</p>

<p>It must be treated gently <strong>proteins</strong>, such as red meat is recommended to exclude completely, but that does not mean that you should go to the protein-free diet. Proteins are needed to build new tissue and to restore the cartilage that covers the articular surfaces of bones. &ldquo;Take&rdquo; protein from lean white meat, fish and vegetable of buckwheat and legumes (peas, beans, lentils). By the way, the protein is better absorbed if the meat is cooked for a couple of stewed or boiled. Contribute to the restoration of the joints and dairy products, particularly useful dairy products &ndash; yogurt, fermented baked milk, cottage cheese.</p>

<p>One of the causes of joint diseases is metabolic disorders, so patients with arthritis need fats. It should be fats of vegetable origin, also allowed a small amount of butter.</p>

<p>Body needs B vitamins &ndash; they play an important role in the proper metabolism. A lack of these vitamins in addition to arthritis can appear many other diseases, is caused by impaired metabolism.</p>

<p>Vitamin D &ndash; is another important vitamin, its deficiency leads to excessive deposition of calcium in the articular cartilage to reduce its elasticity. Result &ndash; the cartilage is gradually destroyed. Compensate for the deficiency of this vitamin helps the fish oil &ndash; it requires not only children but also adults.</p>

<p>Drink a lot! Water &ndash; the basis of any diet in the treatment of arthritis. Dehydration is extremely harmful for our joints, and, as they say, do not lead to sin, it is understood that dehydration occurs in the joints long before a person starts to feel thirsty. But the fluid can not be abused &ndash; excess fluid leads to edema, and this disrupts the blood supply and food joints. So drink plenty of fluids, but be careful to avoid edema.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your legs get restless? This is the restless legs]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/your-legs-get-restless-this-is-the-restless-legs/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-01T16:14:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/your-legs-get-restless-this-is-the-restless-legs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/your-legs-get-restless-this-is-the-restless-legs/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="legs, restless legs, sleep, impatience, disease" alt="Your legs get restless? This is the restless legs">The restless legs syndrome is not known.
<strong>It appears at the two legs of impatience, temporarily relieved by movement.</strong><!-- more --></p>

<h2>Restless: twice as many women as men</h2>

<p>The restless legs also called &ldquo;impatience&rdquo; is due to an abnormality of the neurotransmitters dopamine (unlike Parkinson&rsquo;s disease, there is no neuronal death). It affects twice as many women than men, especially after age 50, and there is often a family history. This syndrome also occurs more often during pregnancy and after menopause without really knowing why, although a role of hormones is suspected.</p>

<blockquote><p>The impatience manifested by discomfort in both legs with the urge to move the legs, causing an almost immediate relief but short.</p></blockquote>

<p>This very unpleasant feeling has the characteristic to occur exclusively at rest, sitting or lying down, preferably in the evening and in the early part of the night.
<strong>This results in great difficulty in falling asleep, making restless legs the second leading cause of sleep disorders after sleep apnea syndrome.</strong></p>

<p>In 80% of cases, patients also suffer from automatic and periodic limb movements. The incidence of disorders varies greatly, ranging from several days to a few times a year by seizures.</p>

<p><em>Note that the restless legs seems to correlate with the occurrence of hypertension, diabetes and obesity.</em></p>

<h2>Restless Legs: strong repercussions in everyday life</h2>

<p>One can easily imagine the dramatic social and professional repercussions, due to insomnia and exhaustion, abnormal movements and the immediate need to move, making it impossible entertainment, transport or sitting at the hairdresser.</p>

<p>The medical check passes first by looking for an iron deficiency, which improves the correction disorders. Then the treatment is based on the administration of dopamine at lower than those used in Parkinson&rsquo;s disease doses.</p>

<blockquote><p>In conclusion, it should be noted that the restless legs syndrome exists and treated.
And if you suffer from sleep disorders, do not forget about your impatience to your doctor!</p></blockquote>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Factors of hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/factors-of-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-15T00:03:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/factors-of-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/factors-of-hemorrhoids/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="factors of hemorrhoids, causes of hemorrhoids, hemorrhoid treatment, proctology, Venapro" alt="Factors of Hemorrhoids">Hemorrhoids &ndash; an inflammatory disease that may affect the pathological expansion of hemorrhoidal veins and the formation of knots. According to medical statistics, hemorrhoids often occurs in people older than 45 years.</p>

<p>The exact cause of hemorrhoids is still not established. The main possible causes of the disease, modern medicine treats vascular pathology (dysfunction between the blood flow through the arteries and the flow of blood through the cavernous veins) and disruption of the muscular system, retaining hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Factors of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Promote the development of hemorrhoids are many factors among which are:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>Genetic predisposition</strong>. Some people venous network in the anus has a very dense plexus, which complicates the flow of blood through the vessels. In case of violation of vascular permeability develops blood stagnation that contributes to the inflammatory process.</li>
<li><strong>Pregnancy and childbirth</strong>. During pregnancy the uterus increases in size, which leads to a displacement of the movable upward while the rectum is pressed against the pelvis. Thus, the clamped venous blood vessels, which leads to an overflow of the cavernous bodies.</li>
<li><strong>Physical inactivity</strong>. Sedentary lifestyle contributes to the development of venous insufficiency, in particular to the development of stagnation in the pelvic organs. Reduce the chance of developing hemorrhoids is possible if regularly moderate exercise.</li>
<li><strong>Failure to comply with the rules of hygiene</strong>. When excessive hygiene anus, as well as the use of low-quality toilet paper mucosa irritated anus, thereby increasing the probability of acute hemorrhoids.</li>
<li><strong>Bad habits</strong>. Smoking worsens the condition of vessels, including hemorrhoidal veins. Also, smoking increases the severity of bleeding. As for alcoholic beverages, the alcohol helps dilate blood vessels, which in turn leads to stagnation of blood in the hemorrhoids.</li>
<li><strong>Malnutrition</strong>. Excessive consumption of hot and spicy food, as well as lack of fiber is a significant negative factor in the development of inflammatory processes in the rectum.</li>
<li><strong>Chronic constipation</strong>. Disturbances of feces leads to frequent constipation. Solid stool, lingering in the intestines, put pressure on the choroid plexus of the rectum, thereby helping to expand the hemorrhoidal veins. Also promotes the development of hemorrhoids during defecation habit to push.</li>
<li><strong>Hypothermia</strong>. Hypothermia leads to circulatory problems that can cause the development of inflammation in the rectal area. In particular, avoid hypothermia lower body (not sit on a cold surface, dress appropriately to weather conditions).</li>
<li><strong>Physical activity</strong>. Excessive exercise (weightlifting, bodybuilding, etc.) is likely to disrupt the tone of the muscular apparatus of the anus. Muscle weakness contributes anus prolapsed hemorrhoid. Furthermore, physical overload cause delay of blood in the veins, which increases the likelihood of developing hemorrhoids.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Hemorrhoid Treatment</h2>

<p>Any disease is always easier to prevent than to cure. At elimination of negative factors likely to develop hemorrhoids is minimal. Even hereditary predisposition to hemorrhoids may not materialize if lead a healthy lifestyle and eat right.</p>

<p>If the hemorrhoids are still developed, it is necessary as soon as possible to begin treatment. Depending on severity of the disease may be used as a conservative and surgical treatment.</p>

<p>Medication hemorrhoids includes use of anti- inflammatory, analgesic and hemostatic (if bleeding) drugs.</p>

<p>The most effective use of local products in the form of rectal suppositories. One such drug is Venapro. This combination drug, which includes an anti-inflammatory bufexamac, wound healing agent and bismuth subgallate anesthetic lidocaine component.</p>

<p>Venapro hemorrhoids is useful for a 1-2 stages, as well as diseases such as proctologic anal fissure, proctitis, anal eczema and other.</p>

<p>Available Venapro in rectal suppositories, which makes it very convenient to use. The likelihood of side effects from the drug is extremely low.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[He does not like hemorrhoids?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/he-does-not-like-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-02T23:05:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/he-does-not-like-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/he-does-not-like-hemorrhoids/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="aggravation, contraindication factor, hypothermia, lack of exercise, physical activity, dietary fiber" alt="He does not like hemorrhoids?">Follow the advice of doctors and avoid the negative factors contributing to aggravate hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Why do I get hemorrhoids?</h2>

<p>Doctors say that lately hemorrhoids much &ldquo;younger&rdquo;. Most likely, the reason for that are the negative factors contributing to the development of the disease with which modern man often encountered. These factors include:</p>

<ul>
<li>pregnancy and childbirth;</li>
<li>heredity;</li>
<li>sedentary lifestyle;</li>
<li>unhealthy diet;</li>
<li>poor hygiene;</li>
<li>hypothermia;</li>
<li>chronic gastrointestinal disorder;</li>
<li>excessive exercise.</li>
</ul>


<p>The combination of these factors leads to the development of pathological enlargement of hemorrhoidal veins and implementation of disease. At the first symptoms should immediately contact a doctor, mainly because hemorrhoids characterized by chronic course with periodic exacerbations. In order to reduce the appearance of the disease and minimize the likelihood of an exacerbation, the patient must be aware of what not to do with hemorrhoids. Especially effective prevention of hemorrhoids is the first stage of the disease when the disease symptoms have not yet pronounced.</p>

<h2>Contraindications for hemorrhoids</h2>

<p><strong>Food contraindications</strong></p>

<p>When hemorrhoids diet is very important. As a preventive measure, doctors recommend eating foods containing large amounts of fiber. Such food will reduce the number of exacerbations and the severity of hemorrhoids. When varicose veins hemorrhoids may want to limit the consumption of these foods and dishes:</p>

<ul>
<li>fried foods;</li>
<li>hot and spicy dishes, irritating;</li>
<li>semolina;</li>
<li>mashed potatoes;</li>
<li>eggs;</li>
<li>jelly;</li>
<li>alcohol;</li>
<li>black tea, coffee.</li>
</ul>


<p><strong>Hypodynamy</strong></p>

<p>Sedentary lifestyle contributes to stagnation in the pelvic organs, which only aggravates the disease. At risk are people who have to be for a long time without moving (office workers, drivers). Try as much as possible to do a little workout. On the way to and from work, try to walk more. And best of all to engage in moderate exercise regularly. Jogging, swimming, walking trails and many other kinds of physical activity will only benefit.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bleeding internal hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/bleeding-internal-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-30T07:07:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/bleeding-internal-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/bleeding-internal-hemorrhoids/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Bleeding internal hemorrhoids" alt="Bleeding internal hemorrhoids"> <strong>Hemorrhoids.</strong> One of the main symptoms of this disease is the hemorrhoidal bleeding.</p>

<p>Literature data of recent years have pointed out that the cause of hemorrhoids is a violation of the outflow of blood from the venules of the cavernous bodies, which are located in the wall of the rectum (the largest cluster of notes on 3-7-11 hours on the dial) and is a substrate haemorrhoid. <!-- more -->Therefore, if the wall of the cavernous bodies, which is filled with blood directly from the arterial bed is damaged, the stands out of scarlet, oxygen saturation arterial blood.</p>

<p>Bleeding at internal hemorrhoids characterized in that the blood volume, wherein is of a few drops to 100-200 ml per day and with frequent hemorrhage causes the development of anemia. In some cases, hemorrhage may be inkjet and pulsating.</p>

<p><strong>Diagnosis.</strong> Under gentle disclosure of the edges of the anus hemorrhoids are defined as swollen formations bluish color, soft-elastic consistency, covered with a mucous membrane. Necessarily carry out the finger, mirroring studies and sigmoidoscopy. Soft hemorrhoids are rarely detected by digital examination, but this study is an important method for the differential diagnosis. When the mirror examination may reveal the bleeding internal hemorrhoids.</p>

<p><strong>Treatment.</strong> We must remember that the causes of intestinal bleeding may be tumors (benign and malignant) of rectum and colon. Only after exclusion of these diseases should begin to targeted treatment of hemorrhoidal bleeding.</p>

<p>In chronic hemorrhoids, which manifests itself only bleeding internal hemorrhoids without a loss of knots, in the absence of common anorectal thrombosis recommends a hemostatic therapy with Venapro. 10 percent calcium chloride, 5 percent solution of aminocaproic acid as well as with the use of adrenaline suppositories by recipe.</p>

<p>In the absence of contraindications is possible to use an injection of sclerosing agents.</p>

<p>Contraindications to this kind of treatment are diseases of the prostate and hypertension, in which if there is no severe anemia, such  bleeding is as would damping. At presence of infectious diseases, inflammatory changes in the walls of the anal canal and rectal mucosa injection of sclerosing agents is contraindicated. Relative contraindications for sclerotherapy are loss of internal hemorrhoids and frequent exacerbation of chronic hemorrhoids, because the presence of these complications are indications for surgical treatment.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[External hemorrhoid. Thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/external-hemorrhoid-thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-11T19:56:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/external-hemorrhoid-thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid-treatment/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment" alt="External hemorrhoid. Thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment"> As the most common disease of the rectum, hemorrhoids can proceed in different forms. Depending on where the knots are located, allocate hemorrhoids external, internal and combined. All these forms are equally common, delivered to the patient a lot of discomfort.</p>

<p>The disease has been well studied, and in the modern medical literature contains enough information how to manifested the external hemorrhoids and how to treat this pathology.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Characteristic for external hemorrhoids is that the knots are located always outside around the anus and without exacerbation absolutely not bother man. They may have different sizes and formed by extending and hemorrhoidal plexus, which is normally located under the skin of the perineum near the anus.</p>

<p>What causes this disease? What are the symptoms it is manifested? And how to get rid of external hemorrhoids?</p>

<h2>What are the causes of external hemorrhoids?</h2>

<p>To the formation of external hemorrhoids predisposes congenital weakness of the venous wall, however protrude knots only under certain conditions:</p>

<p>If a person moves a little, but mostly sits or stands.
If there is a problem with a stools, trouble with constipation, and defecation is accompanied by long waiting or straining.
If a person is forced by type of activity to lift weights, or engaged in power sports.
If the patient&rsquo;s favorite food &ndash; meat dishes flavored with a good dose of hot spices and alcohol.
In women often arises external hemorrhoids during pregnancy and after birth, especially repeated.</p>

<p>Under the action of all these factors, overflow occurs veins of the pelvis and perineum of blood, that the weakness of the vein wall leads to its stretching and protrusion, that is, to the formation of knots, and can be formed as external hemorrhoids and the internal simultaneously.</p>

<h2>What are the symptoms external hemorrhoids?</h2>

<p>Often, the first symptoms of the disease appear even before the significant increase of knots:</p>

<p>Itching and discomfort in the anal area. If herewith to comb the skin, there arises yet irritation.
Traces of blood on the toilet paper. Bleedings is usually not characteristic for external hemorrhoids, especially if the knots of small size. But with their increasing dense stool can injure the skin with the release of a small amount of blood. In addition, when there are external hemorrhoids &ndash; bleeding at a defecation can arise from anal fissures, that often accompany this form of the disease.
In the event of aggravation, when the knots are inflamed, swell, appears one more symptom &ndash; the pain during stool, but in a calm state, with remission of this symptom is not.
And, of course, bumps around the anus, which can have different sizes, and which the patient gropes fingers.
As a rule, external hemorrhoids &ndash; symptoms which are not so are numerous &ndash; begins to disturb human at an exacerbation of the disease and in remission no specific complaints.</p>

<h2>Complications of external hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Sometimes external hemorrhoids can be complicated by thrombosis of the knot. In this case appears typical clinic with acute symptoms. Therefore thrombosed external hemorrhoids attributed to the acute forms of the disease.</p>

<p>Thrombosis unit develops through prolonged of stagnation of blood, which leads to its condensation and the thrombus formation. A blood clot inside knot expands causing severe pain, aggravated by movement, coughing, sneezing.</p>

<p>The knot itself with a bluish color, edematous, tense and sharply painful when touched.
Acute external hemorrhoids may be accompanied by inflammation. Then, on a background of intense pain in humans raises of temperature, and local redness of the skin appears around the knot, and soft tissue swelling.</p>

<p>If the inflammation extends to the subcutaneous tissue, then the redness and swelling captures all area of the perineum, and pains become more intense and felt not only in the knot itself, but also around it.</p>

<p>If in time and competently did not handle this situation, process may result in purulent paraproctitis or fistula adrectal formation. Therefore, thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment, especially with inflammation, should be initiated as early as possible.</p>

<p>The diagnosis of external hemorrhoids usually straightforward because the knots are located outside, and they can be seen even with a simple inspection of the anal area.</p>

<h2>Treatment of external hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment are usually directed to ensure that remove the inflammation in the knot and remove associated with it edema and pain. Used for this purpose are different anti-hemorrhoidal drugs.
External hemorrhoids treatment folk remedies can also be quite effective, but on condition that the knots are small, and no thrombosis.</p>

<p>In order to remedy to cure of external hemorrhoids had the desired action, it must be properly chosen according to with those processes that are taking place in the knot.</p>

<p>Local therapy can be carried out and candles and ointments. All modern anti-hemorrhoidal ointments and candles from external hemorrhoids include several components. First, there is some hormonal substance with powerful anti-inflammatory, anti-edematous and antipruritic effect. Secondly &ndash; a local anesthetic, which gives analgesic effect. And, thirdly, the component blood thinner and prevents thrombosis, or resorptional have already a blood clot. Most often, this substance is heparin.</p>

<p>Some suppositories and liniments contain other components, for example, accelerating the healing process and has an antibacterial effect. Simply apply ointment on the external knots, therefore preference is given it her rather than suppositories.</p>

<p>If there is no thrombosis of knot possibly external hemorrhoid treatment at home. Of folk remedies are used steam and hip baths, natural-based ointments and various lotions.
Hip baths can be done with cold water, with hot water and anti-inflammatory herbal concoctions (chamomile, calendula, series), propolis, garlic, onion skins. No less popular and such folk remedies for external hemorrhoids as steam baths onion and garlic, as well as bath with alum</p>

<p>If arises a thrombosed external hemorrhoid &ndash; treatment should be started immediately, and treat should only proctologist. Pursuing a self-medication, especially folk remedies, you can lose valuable time, that is fraught with serious consequences. Because any natural cure for external hemorrhoids acts more gently and not so fast as pharmaceuticals, and thrombosis knot, especially with inflammation, every minute counts.</p>

<p>In addition to local means when external hemorrhoid thrombosing &ndash; treatment may include the ingestion of non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs and and venotonic medications. In addition, there are anti-inflammatory drugs of natural origin, the ingredients of which are natural and have vegetable nature. One of these drugs &ndash; Venapro, is the most efficient of its kind. It includes witch hazel, horse chestnut, st.mary &rsquo;s thistle, krameria mapato, arnica montana, fluoride of lime. Furthermore that the drug very is effective against external hemorrhoids, especially in the early stages of the disease, its merits can be attributed more ease of use (available as tablets and spray), and the harmlessness of its components can take it during pregnancy and during breast-feeding her baby.</p>

<p>If the spent therapy when the patient&rsquo;s condition does not improve or, on the contrary is compounded resort to knot dissection and removal of the thrombus. It is therefore very important that the patient, who appeared thrombosed external hemorrhoid, treatment received under the supervision of a doctor. This allows enough time to apply radical measures and avoid serious consequences.</p>

<p>Generally, when in a patient is external hemorrhoids &ndash; treatment methods envisage only two approaches &ndash; conservative and surgical, with removal of external hemorrhoids is made in the case, when conservative measures fail, and the aggravation is saved practically constant.</p>

<p>Extra care must external hemorrhoids treatment during pregnancy, and in fact need to remove symptoms, and the child no harm. Therefore all means as medicinal as well as folk can recommend a doctor. This condition must respected in the event that, when there is external hemorrhoids after childbirth, and a woman is breastfeeding.</p>

<p>How to thrombosed external hemorrhoid treat once and for all? You can remove already formed knots. But if a person&rsquo;s life are all the precipitating factors, then after a time in another place will be new. So the main thing condition, which will help to prevent both internal and external hemorrhoids &ndash; is a lifestyle change and parting with the habits and the factors that lead to disease.</p>

<p>If you want to know what it looks like external hemorrhoids, on the our website has a page with photos of the disease. There you will see different pictures of external hemorrhoids. Some of them will help you understand what is uncomplicated external hemorrhoids and  photos of thrombosed and inflamed knots will provide insight on how to appear complications of the disease.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thrombosis - Thrombosed hemorrhoid]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/thrombosis-thrombosed-hemorrhoid/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-10T22:06:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/thrombosis-thrombosed-hemorrhoid</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-hemorrhoid/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Thrombosed hemorrhoid" alt="Thrombosis - Thrombosed hemorrhoid"> <strong>Thrombosed hemorrhoid</strong>, also called acute hemorrhoids &ndash; a disease which occurs in almost 10% of all adults. This is a problem that everyone knows, but prefer not to talk, because it&rsquo;s embarrassing. And meanwhile, it is the patients reluctance seeking medical attention leads to what the disease becomes chronic late stage.</p>

<p>The cause of the disease are blood clots of external or internal hemorrhoids that drop out. If you look, the blood clot is a hematoma near the anus, which brings a man a lot of inconvenience and pain.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Simultaneous thrombosis of external and internal nodes is fairly rare. It can spread to all anus around (in this case it is called the circular), or to be on only one side, covering the anus of a semicircle.</p>

<h2>Causes and symptoms of Thrombosed hemorrhoid</h2>

<p>Reasons for the formation of blood clots in hemorrhoids diverse. It can be physical exertion &ndash; weight lifting, pregnancy or childbirth, as well as diarrhea, constipation, hypothermia and even alcohol abuse. In addition, for unpleasant consequences can result sedentary lifestyle work-related (pilots and drivers), or some sports &ndash; weightlifting, cycling, horseback riding.</p>

<p>Any stress, leading to a rush of blood to the pelvis can cause rupture of the vessel in the perianal region and lead to thrombosed external hemorrhoid. In this case, the thrombus begins to put pressure on the vessel wall from within, irritating nerve endings and causing pain. It is these symptoms of hemorrhoids cause a &ldquo;duck&rdquo; gait of patients.</p>

<p>Most often in the early stages, the disease is accompanied by itching, burning and secretions from anus. Patients rarely turn to doctors with such complaints, because they consider them uncritical, or just shy of his problem. Most often they are accompanied by still bleeding. First, rare and meager &ndash; only a few drops during stool, and then they become regular. And when there is a prolapsed hemorrhoid and the pain becomes unbearable and avoid a visit to a specialist is can not.</p>

<h2>Thrombosed hemorrhoid treatment</h2>

<p>The easiest and fastest way to treat hemorrhoids &ndash; is surgery. It is performed under local anesthesia and takes only a few minutes. During the operation, the doctor-proctologist makes minimal incision (up to 5 mm) and through it removes the blood clot from the node, after which the pain immediately goes away. Sometimes, to achieve a cosmetic effect, thrombus excised together with the node. After these operations, the man does not lose the ability to work, and the wound is healing on-site intervention is less than a week.</p>

<p>The only drawback to this method is that the operation &ndash; not a radical cure for hemorrhoids. A blood clot will not appear on the site was operated, but could come close. Therefore, this method of treatment is used to advanced stages of the disease as a means of emergency medicine, as soon as possible to save people from pain.</p>

<p>In all other cases, and at the unwillingness of the patient subjected to surgery, treatment is carried out with the use of medication ointments, rectal suppositories and warm baths. This method gives the effect only after a month and in the future does not preclude the emergence of a blood clot in the same place. Therefore, in order to avoid undesirable effects during treatment should follow a diet, eliminating alcohol and spicy foods, as well as limit physical exertion and less walking.</p>

<p>Speaking of non-surgical treatment of hemorrhoids can not pay attention to the drug Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula, which has proved its effectiveness in the fight against this disease. This drug is made from natural ingredients and with proper treatment recovery comes faster than with other drugs. It is particularly effective in the early stages of hemorrhoids when hemorrhoid nodes have not fallen out. Its also worth taking after recovery as prophylaxis to prevent any re-occurrence of a blood clot.</p>

<p>Remember, <strong>thrombosed hemorrhoid</strong> is always easier to cure in the early stages, and delayed treatment or lack of it at all can lead to complications.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acute hemorrhoids - Thrombosed external hemorrhoid]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/acute-hemorrhoids-thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-09T22:50:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/acute-hemorrhoids-thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Thrombosed external hemorrhoid" alt="Acute hemorrhoids - Thrombosed external hemorrhoid"> A patient with <strong>thrombosed external hemorrhoid</strong> can be found on the &ldquo;duck gait&rdquo; with which they come into the doctor&rsquo;s office. Asked to sit down on a chair, meet the &ldquo;thank you I&rsquo;ll stand by foot&rdquo;. Why is that? Because concerned about pain in the anal area, at whom are moderate, at whom expressed.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>The cause of acute hemorrhoids is different: constipation, diarrhea, hypothermia, weight lifting, alcohol, pregnancy, childbirth, anal sex, etc. With an increase in intra-abdominal pressure occurs powerful rush of blood to pelvis, because of what could &ldquo;explode&rdquo; vein in the perianal area and formed <strong>thrombosed external hemorrhoid</strong>. In fact, this hematoma, which is located under the skin gives a lot of pain and discomfort. This occurs because blood clot presses on the inner tissues thereby stretching the nerve endings, followed by pain. Many people ask this hematoma can get to the heart? No description of a single case of getting thrombosed blood clot (hematoma) of the haemorrhoid in the heart.</p>

<p>Thrombosed external hemorrhoid is more often a unit, can occur immediately 2-3 thrombosed node and can be circular when the swells all perianal area. As well found thrombosis of internal hemorrhoids. This occurs against the background of already existing hemorrhoids during stool internal nodes drop out further as a consequence of the sphincter spasm nodes are infringed, there is an infringement of outflow of blood, swelling knotswith subsequent thrombosis. With such an aggravation of internal hemorrhoids pain for so many severe that patients can not &ldquo;neither sit nor stand up&rdquo; and some call the &ldquo;911&rdquo;. What to do if diagnosed acute hemorrhoids?</p>

<h2>How to treat thrombosed external hemorrhoid</h2>

<p>Treatment hemorrhoid thrombosis. Usually in such cases, you need to limit yourself to walking, exercise, spicy foods, alcohol. Appointed by warm baths and heating pads 2-3 times a day for 20-30 minutes (due to the heat accelerates the resorption of blood clots). When the external manifestations of thrombosis knots rectal suppositories are ineffective. The good effect of acute hemorrhoids gives a natural product such as «Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula». Locally thrombosed knots must be lubricated with ointments Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Hytone, Locoid Lipocream, Locoid, Westcort, that also helps to speed up the resorption process thrombosed clots. All the foregoing conservative therapy will surely give effect, it should be noted that in the conservative treatment process of resorption may take 1-1.5 months. After the complete disappearance of the phenomenon of acute hemorrhoids, on the site of the thrombosed knot almost always remains so-called fringe anal hemorrhoidal.It should be noted that in the future, at the same location, under the influence of any factor may again appear thrombosis node.</p>

<p>Now the information for those who do not like long to be treated. The most rapid and effective treatment of thrombosis, it is certainly a thrombectomy (forced removal of thrombus from the knot). Under anesthesia thrombosed clots are removed from the cut of up to 0.5 cm. Node decreases and the pain immediately stoped. The procedure takes about 1-2 minutes. At the site of thrombectomy wound remains (0.5 cm) that heals for an average of 4 days. In this case, the need for rectal suppositories, ointments, warm baths already not. However, it is recommended prophylactic course of Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula (1 month). After 15 minutes of thrombectomy and recommendations of the patient to go home. Ability to work after the procedure is not lost. Frequently offer remove thrombosed clots together with the node in this case addition to the rapid relief of pain is achieved cosmetic effect. Already at this point there is no thrombotic conditions, but in other places around the circumference of the anus can appear. Why? Because thrombectomy and removal of a thrombosed external hemorrhoid is not a radical operation.</p>

<p>In some cases, when exacerbation passes at available hemorrhoids II-IV stage, radical surgery is acceptable for time reasons. After this operation is a complete cure patients from hemorrhoidal disease and the appearance thrombosed external hemorrhoid of this place for many decades (may appear elsewhere). Risks and complications at radical surgery for time reasons do not exceed those for planned interventions.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to cure hemorrhoids. Hemorrhoid home treatment]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-cure-hemorrhoids-hemorrhoid-home-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-08T21:58:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-cure-hemorrhoids-hemorrhoid-home-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoid-home-treatment/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Hemorrhoid home treatment" alt="How to cure hemorrhoids. Hemorrhoid home treatment"> When we say the word &ldquo;hemorrhoid&rdquo;, many are experiencing negative, sometimes reaching up to phobias, feelings. However, this disease is not so bad, especially in the early stages. It occurs due to poor nutrition, physical inactivity and sedentary lifestyle. It may be provoke a heredity.</p>

<p>In order to answer the question of how to treat hemorrhoids, you need to give it a clear definition. Hemorrhoids are vascular cavernous body. These are formed in the rectum (in the lower part). Nodes can be internal or external. Simultaneously, at the patient may be present both species, in this case will help only complex treatment.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Characteristically reluctance of a large number of patients to see a doctor in the early stages of this disease. They do not ask how to cure hemorrhoids and how to pick a remedy for hemorrhoids, even experiencing pain and discomfort. However, the need to go to a specialist as soon as possible. It is better to hemorrhoid home treatment, than to resort to complex surgery, which in some cases does not bring the proper favor and alleviate suffering.</p>

<p>There are four stages of this disease:</p>

<ol>
<li>The formation hemorrhoid nodes inside the rectum (internal hemorrhoids);</li>
<li>There is a loss of nodes of the rectum after a bowel movement, they themselves reduce a back;</li>
<li>The nodes do not reduce a own but it can still be done with your fingers;</li>
<li>Impossible to reduce fallen nodes (external hemorrhoids).</li>
</ol>


<p>Effective hemorrhoid home treatment is possible only on the first and second stages. On the third and fourth often have to resort to surgery.</p>

<p>In spite of the obvious symptoms of many ill in no hurry to seek medical help. They will not go to the doctor, as a result, they develop hemorrhoids third and fourth stage. For some reason, some people think hemorrhoids are something shameful. They hide their illness from others. This trend is not exclusive to the United States, but also in many European countries. However it is better to learn from experts how to treat hemorrhoids, rather than later hospital treatment needed or, worse, in the outpatient and dispensary observation.</p>

<p>Today, a large amount of useful information on how to cure hemorrhoids, can also find on the Internet. In a network there are enough sites on which there is information about the problem of the disease, the mechanisms of its development, prevention methods and hemorrhoid home treatment.</p>

<h2>How to treat hemorrhoids. The main methods</h2>

<ol>
<li>Non-medical impact. Effective only in the early stages, is to change the lifestyle and diet, increasing physical activity.</li>
<li>Drug therapeutic impact.</li>
<li>Reducing the pressure in the anal canal (the means for doing so are drug «Venapro» and ointments such as Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Locoid etc.).</li>
<li>Non-surgical methods of influence.</li>
<li>Surgical treatment.</li>
</ol>


<p>In the early stages of the disease and as a prophylactic course after surgical treatment is <strong>very effective natural product «Venapro»</strong>.</p>

<p>Identify hemorrhoids simply by the following symptoms:
&ndash; Bleeding during bowel movements, blood in faeces.
&ndash; The occurrence of burning and itching in the anal area.
&ndash; Pain when sitting, walking, bowel movements.
&ndash; The emergence of a sense of gravity or presence of a foreign body in the rectum.
&ndash; Inflammation of hemorrhoid nodes. They be palpated, this gives rise to pain.
&ndash; Occurs loss of nodes of the rectum.</p>

<p>It should, as soon as possible, seek medical attention if these symptoms.</p>

<h2>Hemorrhoid home treatment. Traditional methods</h2>

<p>The use drug treatment is usually only gives a relief of symptoms of the disease in the third and fourth stages. To effectively deal with hemorrhoids, you need to use an integrated approach.</p>

<p>Modern medicine offers to hemorrhoid home treatment is not only tablets but also in other ways. In the early stages helps to get rid of the pain and reduce inflammation of the nodes special diet. Of the food exclude alcohol, spicy and fatty foods, condiments and spices. A diet enriched with plant-based diet high fiber content. Recommended for early hemorrhoids long walks, special exercises, including squats, press load, tilts, etc. It is necessary to make a thorough hygiene of the anus after defecation.</p>

<p>However, the disease exacerbation of those measures will not be enough. In the acute form of hemorrhoid home treatment will require the use of anal suppositories, ointments, and cold lotions. When it is impossible to stop the periodic occurrence of venous bleedings knots injected sclerosing solutions.</p>

<p>By resorting to surgery only in cases where there are prolonged and severe bleeding, constantly drop nodes, at a jamming. All the same any form of treatment is useless if you do not aimed at removing underlying causes of the disease. They only temporarily make easier the patient&rsquo;s condition, reduce pain and symptoms.</p>

<p>In the complex treatment of hemorrhoids is to include products «Venapro &ndash; Hemorrhoid formula». It is especially effective in the early stages of the disease.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thrombosed hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/thrombosed-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-08T21:56:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/thrombosed-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-hemorrhoids/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Thrombosed hemorrhoids" alt="Thrombosed hemorrhoids"> Thrombosed hemorrhoids usually occurs when you straining during bowel movements due to swelling of the dropped out nodes. Sphincter of the rectum spasm  increases the swelling, leads to stagnation of blood in the lower rectal plexus and thrombosed of external hemorrhoids. The patient complained of pain, swelling, discharge from the rectum with an unpleasant odor and difficulties at defecation. At survey are determined dropped out not reduce a edematous internal hemorrhoids, often with fibrinous coating.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>In 70-80% of cases,  complicated by inflammation of the transition to subcutaneous tissue and the anal area. In this case drugs are being used in combination with a water soluble ointments having potent anti-inflammatory action. These include Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Hytone, Locoid Lipocream, Locoid, Westcort.</p>

<p>In acute hemorrhoids and the early stages of chronic hemorrhoids hold conservative treatment. Its main purpose &ndash; relieve pain and inflammation, normalize blood circulation in the rectal area, adjust the digestion. Thrombosed hemorrhoids is an indication for the use of anticoagulants local action. This group of medications include ointments Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Hytone, Locoid Lipocream, Locoid, Westcort. As a preparation for the topical treatment of hemorrhoids established itself particularly Anusol HC. As an agent for the prevention and treatment of hemorrhoids of its in the early stages established itself a natural product Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula. Each component of the drug exerts its beneficial effects in thrombosed hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>Conservative treatment is common: increasing venous tone tablets, improve blood flow in small vessels and cavernous veins (for example Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula); and local: wound healing, pain relievers and antipruritic ointments, suppositories, microclysters and baths. At the same time is appointed antihemorrhoidal diet: vegetables, fruits, bran, and that&rsquo;s about spices, spicy food and alcohol have to forget.</p>

<p>In surgical treatment under local anesthesia, produce diaplasis dropped nodes, and then perform ligation of the internal nodes latex rings and thrombectomy of the radial incisions at accompanying acute thrombosis of external hemorrhoids. The intervention is performed on an outpatient basis. Short-and long-term results are good. Thrombosis, complicated hemorrhoids stage IV requires urgent hemorrhoidectomy.</p>

<p>Thrombectomy &ndash; removal of thrombus (venous blood clot). Thrombectomy represents a thrombosed node dissection and removal of a blood clot. Thrombectomy is assigned to the nodes are large and cause severe discomfort to the patient, and conservative therapy is ineffective or may take too time. This procedure does not require hospitalization. After thrombectomy is rapid a relief, hemorrhoid, after a while, collapses.
Excision of external hemorrhoid: a procedure which can eliminate the root cause of thrombosis &ndash; an external hemorrhoid. This is the most effective method for the treatment of external thrombosed hemorrhoids, as it allows get rid in a subsequent of the recurring exacerbations. Excision of the outdoor knot assigned when acute thrombosis, when conservative therapy is ineffective, or thrombosed knot brings strong discomfort. In most cases this procedure is performed on an outpatient basis under local anesthesia and does not require hospitalization. Excision of external hemorrhoid can be done with a scalpel conventional or a high-frequency electro-scalpel.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The effectiveness of the hemorrhoid creams proven practices]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/the-effectiveness-of-the-hemorrhoid-creams-proven-practices/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-07T23:53:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/the-effectiveness-of-the-hemorrhoid-creams-proven-practices</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoid-creams/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Hemorrhoid creams" alt="The effectiveness of the hemorrhoid creams proven practices"> In the hemorrhoid treatment efficient are not only suppositories and ointment, creams but also.  The basic doctors precept in the hemorrhoids treatment is precisely the use of these drug form.</p>

<p>The superiority of the <strong>hemorrhoid creams</strong> to the ointment lies in the fact that it is more easily absorbed and short term relieves symptoms such as itching, burning and pain. In addition, the creams can also have long-term effect: relieve inflammation, restore the elasticity of blood vessels, eliminates congestion, tone up your rectum, have a cosmetic effect, heal anus wounds and cracks, have antibacterial properties and hemostatic.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>The advantage of hemorrhoid creams before rectal suppositories is that with external hemorrhoids suppositories is not effective, while an internal hemorrhoid they penetrate too deep into the rectum and does not facilitate patient suffering. But creams often are effective for external and internal hemorrhoids, removing the symptoms and eliminating the cause of the disease. They help in the treatment of anal fissures and the lower portion of the rectum, anal itching eliminate, and erosive changes in the structure of organs and tissues.</p>

<p>Nitroglycerin-based cream is used to relieve pain from hemorrhoids and relieves spasm of the sphincter.</p>

<p>The structure of the <strong>hemorrhoid creams</strong> typically include substances such as petroleum jelly, beeswax, purified sulfur, lanolin, extracts of raspberry, chestnut, oak bark, black poplar, essential oils of lemon and cypress. Also there may be present alcohols, organic acids, vitamins. These drugs provide short-term local anesthesia. Some components have astringent properties to help stop bleeding. Essential oils and plant extracts prevent complications, strengthen blood vessels walls, reduce hemorrhoids, facilitate defecation. This component as phenylephrine hydrochloride, promotes constrict blood vessels of the anus, the normalization of blood circulation, relieves swelling, eliminates the presence of serous discharge, effectively treats itching, reduces the production of exudate. Have a softening effect and other vegetable oils &ndash; such as corn, as well as mineral oil and glycerin.</p>

<p>Always together with creams should take the drug Venapro, which greatly enhances the effectiveness of treatment. Venapro also should be taken as a prevention for some time after recovery (preferably drink away monthly course of medication), as well as people who are prone to hemorrhoidal disease (sedentary lifestyle, heredity, etc.).</p>

<p>Hemorrhoid creams may have some contraindications. Thus, their use is not recommended for people who have an increased sensitivity to drug components, to children under the age of 12 years, as well as the propensity to thromboembolism and granulocytopenia (drugs often lead to an increase in blood clotting). The cream can cause a side effects such as dermatitis and allergic reactions.</p>

<p>Not recommended to use hemorrhoid creams patients who are taking medications such groups as antidepressants, antihypertensive drugs, monoamine oxidase inhibitors. In such situations, the appointment is only possible under strict medical indications. Pregnant and lactating women appoint hemorrhoid creams is only entitled to an experienced and qualified specialist this area. Use of the drug in such cases should be maximum careful to avoid the possibility of putting even a the slightest harm to the child or fetus.</p>

<p>As a rule, cream is used in the morning and evening, and after defecation. However, it should be remembered that it is not recommended to use the drug more than four times a day. Before applying the medication necessary to fulfill the hygienic cleansing of corresponding area. The cream is applied on the area around the anus and into the anus. The approximate duration of treatment &ndash; 1 week. If after this period to facilitate does not come, should urgently to see a specialist.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Features and external hemorrhoid treatment]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/features-and-external-hemorrhoid-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-07T23:51:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/features-and-external-hemorrhoid-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/external-hemorrhoid-treatment/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="External hemorrhoid treatment" alt="Features and external hemorrhoid treatment"> Below the skin anus are located veins of external hemorrhoidal plexus. Expansion and inflammation of these veins is called external hemorrhoids. Formed in this hemorrhoids hanging outside the anal ring on the edge. They are skin folds, which can be large in the form of large petals.</p>

<p>Such external hemorrhoids usually cause discomfort when moving, irritate the skin of the anus. Also, accompanied by itching and maceration. This variety of the disease may be caused by stagnation of blood in the anal area. In the absence of inflammation such hemorrhoids do not bleed and do not hurt! As a rule, they are symptoms of hemorrhoids combined and indicator of a pathological condition of the rectum.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>However, inflammation of internal hemorrhoids and other acute anorectal disorders external hemorrhoids may become congestive phase. In this case, there are large purple knots.</p>

<p>Also external hemorrhoids are prone to thrombosis. In the acute phase of thrombosis can be very painful. It lasts for two to four days. Not uncommon at this place bleeding and ulceration of the site. After the pain subsides, the inflamed site gradually decreases and then disappears. This usually is a skin fold near the anus. It can deliver a lot of inconvenience &ndash; from the itching and burning to discharge from the anus. External hemorrhoid treatment of with acute thrombosis may be different. When a doctor prescribes pain bearable anesthetics and special therapy. If the pain is hard to bear, hemorrhoid is removed surgically. The intervention is performed on an outpatient basis under local anesthesia.</p>

<h2>External hemorrhoids and treatment of its symptoms</h2>

<p>Before you assign a therapy or other forms of treatment, doctor determines present whether the patient has symptoms of anal hemorrhoids external, internal, or combined form.</p>

<p>Symptoms may appear as follows:
&ndash; There is a feeling wet anus.
&ndash; Pain in the anus.
&ndash; There are itching and burning.
&ndash; Bleeding occurs during or after a bowel movement.
&ndash; There are bulging or prolapsed hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>Usually, the diagnosis &ldquo;External hemorrhoids&rdquo; Becoming a doctor When patients do not have pain from the resulting knots. This disease can pass itself or gradually calm down and appear again. However its more severe form &ndash; complications in the form thrombosis &ndash; affords a person the lot of nuisances. Some experts believe that such an acute form should not neglect in any case. Necessary as soon as possible ask qualified doctor, because of possible more serious complications including cancer of the rectum.</p>

<p>Each stage of the external hemorrhoids requires a specific approach.</p>

<p>External hemorrhoid treatment may need:
&ndash; In the conservative method of exposure.
&ndash; The surgical method of exposure.
&ndash; The operational method of exposure.</p>

<p>A complex effect aimed at elimination of inflammation of the anus, as well as the regulation of blood circulation in the rectum, normalization of intestinal peristalsis, called conservative of external hemorrhoid treatment. Usually it is in the local and general therapy. Are used proved themselves pharmaceutical drugs. Moreover, are produced special procedures and used drugs for local effects on external hemorrhoids including drug &ldquo;Venapro Hemorrhoid Formula&rdquo;.</p>

<p>When inflammatory processes repeated periodically, especially at the stage of remission, surgery may be required.</p>

<p>In acute complications, the same thrombosis and bleeding heavily, pathological prolapsed of internal knots resorting to surgery.</p>

<p>When hemorrhoids is a complex disease, that is, there are internal and external knots, you should carefully choose the treatment. It also must be versatile, able to eliminate the whole range of symptoms. Usually in these cases, the external knots are a result of strong internal breaches in the anus. This anal hemorrhoids will require both special diet and physical activity, of gymnastic exercises and drug treatments, local effects on the internal and external knots via suppositories, ointments or gels.</p>

<p>Man again will acquire the moral and physical well-being, if the time to identify external hemorrhoids and to treat its symptoms to use effective comprehensive measures.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get rid of allergies forever. Allergies causes]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/get-rid-of-allergies-forever-causes/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-02T20:54:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/get-rid-of-allergies-forever-causes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/get-rid-of-allergies-forever/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Get rid of allergies forever, pathogenic microflora of the intestine, causes of allergies" alt="Get rid of allergies forever. The causes of allergies"> Of allergy contributes to the pathogenic intestinal microflora. Scientists around the world are studying the causes of allergies, because in the last few decades, the world has seen a rapid increase in allergic diseases and according to WHO every fifth child is born with allergies. Allergies &ndash; is an individual reaction to certain substances (allergens) after contact with them.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>The causes of allergies and current treatments</h2>

<p>In parallel with the increasing number of allergies and a list of allergens, which began to get even the most innocent-looking substance. Currently, there are so many new allergens that to protect itself from them, and to exclude from your diet and environment is not possible. Allergic reactions can cause food, household dust, pollen and plant fluff, pet hair, cosmetics, medicines and much more.</p>

<p>Allergy symptoms in different people as diverse &ndash; coughing, sneezing, snot, itching, rash on the body, swelling of the mucous membranes and even asthma. In severe cases, anaphylactic shock can occur &ndash; the most dangerous manifestation of allergic reaction, which in the absence of immediate medical attention to result in death. If there are signs of anaphylactic shock, such as seizures, loss of consciousness, shortness of breath, vomiting, rash all over the body, involuntary urination and defecation, you should immediately call an ambulance.</p>

<p>Modern drugs, widely advertised in the media, unfortunately, do not eliminate the causes of the emergence and development of allergies, and are directed only by addressing its symptoms and relief of the patient. Allergy treatment passes through the standard procedure &ndash; first samples are taken to establish the allergen in order to avoid contact with him, and then assigned to an antihistamine and immune-boosting drugs. But this approach can not be considered the treatment because the treatment of any disease it is important to establish the root cause that caused it, and fix it.</p>

<p>Also popular method of treatment of specific immunotherapy (SIT), the essence of which is the regular administration of low doses of a specific allergen with a gradual increase, which stimulates the immune system and leads to a resistance to it. SIT prolonged treatment and more efficient &ndash; reducing the need for medications the patient, the symptoms are greatly reduced, which is especially important in asthma attacks. SIT is a basic treatment of asthma, by which it is possible to achieve a prolonged remission.</p>

<p>The method is definitely more effective than the simple application of antihistamines, but the downside of it is that in allergic reaction rarely occurs on a single allergen. Most of several allergens and their number increases with time. Develop immunity to any one allergen, the body begins to react to the new stuff, and so on to infinity, because the cause of allergies is still not resolved.</p>

<h2>Get rid of the allergy will forever intestinal microflora</h2>

<p>Scientists still can not name the exact cause of the allergy, why the same adverse environmental and technological conditions in some relatively healthy people cause allergies and others do not. But already found exactly what one of the main causes of allergies is to reduce the number of beneficial microflora in the gut colonization and its pathogenic microbes is called dysbiosis (dysbiosis).</p>

<p>Many people underestimate the lack of knowledge of the role of beneficial microflora for normal body function. Useful healthy human intestinal flora consists of 2-3 kg microorganisms which produce fiber of a variety of vitamins, hormones, amino acids, enzymes, hemoglobin and improve immunity, promote good assimilation of iron. In addition, the intestinal microflora and neutralizes harmful pathogens.</p>

<p>If a person prevails in the gut microflora useful, it copes with its tasks. If the number of beneficial microflora is reduced, which most often occurs with antibiotic treatment, it took place immediately pathogenic bacteria that without meeting resistance, are beginning to multiply, causing inflammation of the gastro &ndash; intestinal tract.</p>

<p>Then begin to destroy pathogenic microflora integrity of the intestinal mucosa, and decreases its protective barrier function, whereby allergens and toxins may enter freely into the body. In addition, pathogenic microflora begins to actively produce histamine and other substances promoting the development of allergy. Therefore, doctors have long known rule that the cure is dysbiosis, and allergic reactions immediately back down, appearing less frequently or disappear completely.</p>

<p>Dysbacteriosis contributes not only to the emergence of symptoms of allergies, but also metabolic disorders, cardiovascular and endocrine diseases and even depression. Scientists have found a clear link between the presence of dysbiosis and the level of anxiety a person who at dysbiosis increased almost 3 times. And the fact that the problems with the skin, hair and nails can not be removed any creams and cosmetics, without solving the problem of dysbiosis, long time it is not a secret.</p>

<p>Therefore, it can be said without exaggeration that the intestinal microflora is the key to the health of the body and each person has to take care of her, not only to get rid of all allergies, but also to avoid the many other diseases. For this it is necessary to organize your diet to a diet rich in plant-dominated fiber and fiber products, especially vegetables, fruits, cereals from whole grains, bran bread, and milk products.</p>

<p>If you want to be healthy, in any case, do not overeat, start a one-day fasting yourself to help the body as excess food is not digested and starts to rot in the gut, poisoning it. German physician Max Gerson, a lifetime studying the dependence of cancer from power in his book &ldquo;The treatment of cancer,&rdquo; says that in his research of 10,000 cancer cases, only one came from irreversible changes in the body, and all the rest of 9999 are the result of poisoning their own</p>

<p>If you regularly take care of the purity of his bowel and healthy nutrition necessary for the beneficial microflora, then not only will get rid of allergies, but in the future and avoid many serious diseases.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diseases of the thyroid gland. Causes and symptoms of hypothyroidism and hyperthyroidism]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diseases-of-the-thyroid-gland/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-02T20:53:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/diseases-of-the-thyroid-gland</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/thyroid-disease-hypothyroidism/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Thyroid disease, hypothyroidism, hypothyroidism symptoms, hyperthyroidism causes, hyperthyroidism symptoms" alt="Diseases of the thyroid gland. Causes and symptoms of hypothyroidism and hyperthyroidism"> Thyroid disorders require prompt diagnosis and treatment. Thyroid gland without reason called the small conductor of a large orchestra, emphasizing that at small sizes (at a rate of about 15-20 grams), it plays a vital role in directing the overall operation of the complex formation as the human body.</p>

<p>It is the most important part of a complex human endocrine system, along with the pituitary gland, adrenal glands, pancreas, thymus gland and gonads.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>These glands produce and secrete into the blood of about 50 types of hormones. The thyroid gland produces only two kinds of hormones thyroxine (T4) and triiodothyronine (T3), but no! With their help, it regulates the body&rsquo;s metabolism, the cardiovascular and central nervous system, and manages the psycho &ndash; emotional and sexual activity.</p>

<p>It is up to the thyroid gland depends on the psycho-emotional state of a person, that is, whether he is irritable, aggressive, quick-tempered and ready at any moment to lose self-control, or, conversely, apathetic, passive and indifferent to everything.</p>

<p>From these two hormones depends on body temperature, heart rate, the rate of burning calories and more. A healthy body produces these hormones for as long as necessary for the proper function. But, for failures of the thyroid gland, the necessary hormones starts to be produced more or less the norm, which is equally bad.</p>

<h2>The causes and symptoms of hypothyroidism</h2>

<p>Causes of hypothyroidism &ndash; reduced function of the thyroid gland, in which hormone production becomes insufficient, which is manifested lethargy, apathy, drowsiness, chilliness, fatigue, decreased immunity and slowing metabolism. The main symptoms of hypothyroidism, which should pay close attention &ndash; the appetite is reduced, but the weight increases, performance decreases bowel, constipation appear also thinner nails, they appear grooves and thickening.</p>

<p>Hypothyroidism begins quietly, and all of these symptoms, you see, we are usually easy to explain to stress, fatigue and tiredness. Instead check your thyroid hormone levels and normalize metabolism, sit on a diet, the result of which will not, and harm to an unbalanced diet, typical of nearly all diets, we currently add.</p>

<p>The main causes of hypothyroidism, according to doctors &ndash; an inflammation of the thyroid gland, thyroid congenital anomalies, of her injury, radiation exposure, lack of function of the pituitary hormones, multiple surgeries and a lack of iodine in the body. Doctors are advised to adjust your diet so that the table is always present iodine-containing foods such as seaweed, sea fish, citrus fruits, beets, potatoes, tomatoes.</p>

<p>Most of iodine contained in seaweed and fish products in the rest of his relatively few. But it is worth noting that all is good in moderation, and foods containing iodine, is also not be abused. For example, now so popular Japanese dish, like rolls, contain too much iodine, because it uses algae, which can negatively affect the thyroid gland.  Therefore, doctors are advised to eat no more than 2-3 rolls a week.</p>

<h2>The causes and symptoms of hyperthyroidism</h2>

<p>The symptoms and causes of hyperthyroidism hypothyroidism are opposite, because in this disease the thyroid gland begins to produce hormones more than the norm and its function increases. The main symptoms of hyperthyroidism &ndash; a person loses weight rapidly, experiencing constant hunger, frequent diarrhea, becomes irritable, aggressive, his trembling fingers and eyelids appear the most frequent symptoms of hypertension &ndash; heart palpitations and high blood pressure.</p>

<p>In addition, hyperthyroidism is often a major cause of insomnia and dangerous complications of pregnancy. Pregnancy in hyperthyroidism requires mandatory compensation of the disease, because the excess hormones affect the fetus is extremely toxic and may cause his death, and various deformities.</p>

<p>Also in patients with hyperthyroidism often appears so-called &ldquo;exophthalmia&rdquo;, which creates additional problems of cosmetic nature and are often complex.</p>

<p>According to the eminent physician and scientist Botkin, the main causes of hyperthyroidism &ndash; neuro-psychiatric disorders, depression, and emotional breakdowns that disrupt the function of the thyroid gland. Hyperthyroidism is often referred to as a &ldquo;professional&rdquo; illness singers and artists because their work forces to be always &ldquo;on edge&rdquo;, a state of stress. In many patients, the disease was the primary cause psychological trauma, along with unfavorable heredity.</p>

<p>Not for nothing now, many doctors before diagnosis, are asked to make thyroid ultrasound and donate blood on hormones, because the root of many diseases lies in deviations in the thyroid gland. Hypothyroidism and hyperthyroidism are equally dangerous and need to see a doctor because if left untreated, these symptoms not only persist, but eventually amplified.</p>

<p>If the processing of any scratches with iodine you find traces of iodine disappear quickly (for example, for lubrication in the evening &ndash; no traces in the morning), it is likely iodine in your body is missing. And if you are, in addition, in his notice listed in this article symptoms of thyroid disease, be sure to turn in at the first opportunity blood on hormones, particularly TSH (thyroid stimulating hormone). This analysis is absolutely show, do you have any thyroid disease.</p>

<p>If there are any deviations in the analysis, then do not panic, do not be afraid to seek medical attention. Believe me, the thyroid gland is not afraid, afraid of the consequences when people are not treated. Do not be afraid &ldquo;terrible&rdquo; words hormones, having heard horror stories of incompetent people. The hormone thyroxine, which is prescribed to drink in low thyroid function, consists of only 4 atoms of iodine &ndash; as you may see, it is not, it is completely harmless.</p>

<p>Endocrinologists also argue that the more and more people nervous, the more strained his thyroid. So, do not bring your health to a critical state, all you need &ndash; to protect the nerves and the nerves of your loved ones and receive regular medical examinations, thereby maintaining their health.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily care of oily skin. Homemade masks for oily skin]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/daily-care-of-oily-skin-homemade-masks-for-oily-skin/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-02T20:52:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/daily-care-of-oily-skin-homemade-masks-for-oily-skin</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/daily-care-of-oily-skin/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Daily care of oily skin, homemade mask for oily skin" alt="Daily care of oily skin. Homemade masks for oily skin"> Homemade masks for oily skin to help maintain its freshness and youth. The main reason for oily skin &ndash; increased activity of the sebaceous glands, which is due to increased production of the hormone in the body protesterona. Most often very oily problem skin occurs in young women in a period of intense hormonal changes. Especially brings grief oily skin on the forehead and nose.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Fortunately, after the end of active hormonal processes, the skin begins to produce much less excess fat, which greatly improves its appearance and reduces the appearance of rashes, pimples and blackheads. In addition, the undoubted advantage of oily skin is that thanks to the natural lubrication she is aging more slowly than other types of skin and wrinkles appear on it much later.</p>

<h2>Caring for oily skin</h2>

<p>Only a small percentage of adult women are problems remain after 30 years. In such cases, you need to consult a doctor, an endocrinologist at the presence of hormonal disorders and treat excess fat under the supervision of a specialist. In all other cases, no specific treatment is required, you need only a competent and proper daily care of oily skin, as well as protection from the cold, ultraviolet radiation and other environmental challenges.</p>

<p>The biggest problem that arises with this type &ndash; enlarged pores, delivering a lot of problems and disappointments for women. The fact that the large pores become clogged very quickly, because in them the ingress of dirt, excess oil and dead skin cells. In cutaneous fat are beginning to breed bacteria, resulting in a person becoming an ugly gray and pimples. Furthermore, chronic acne further stretched and expanded pores.</p>

<p>In order to avoid such problems is of critical importance proper washing, and, it does not mean that you need to wash many times a day. Enough to wash twice a day, morning and evening, but at the same time to apply special means &ndash; gel for oily skin and brush. It is important to start washing with warm, almost hot water: this is done in order to clogged pores open, which does not happen when washing your face with cold water. Then lather gel, apply it to his face and massage brush. Following this simple procedure when enlarged pores perfectly cleansed, you need to wash with cold water, which will narrow them and make it less noticeable.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homemade masks for oily hair. Proper care and cleaning oily hair]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/homemade-masks-for-oily-hair-proper-care-and-cleaning-oily-hair/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-30T14:33:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/homemade-masks-for-oily-hair-proper-care-and-cleaning-oily-hair</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/causes-of-greasy-hair/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Causes of greasy hair, oily hair wash, homemade mask for oily hair" alt="Homemade masks for oily hair. Proper care and cleaning oily hair"> Greasy hair requires frequent washing. Oily hair often lead women to despair and cause a lot of inconvenience to them that quickly gryazneyut and by the end of the day look greasy and stale, even if they are washed in the morning. But experts urge not to get upset and argue that care for them is much easier than in the dry, which, moreover, are often brittle and weakened. In addition, oily hair, thanks to the high fat content, have a huge advantage over the dry, because they, like oily skin, thanks to the natural lubrication, well protected from adverse external influences.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Causes of oily hair</h2>

<p>The main reason is the high fat content is that the sebaceous glands work too active and produce more sebum than necessary. Increased sebum secretion is often caused by genetics, but could be evidence of violations of the endocrine system.</p>

<p>In addition, increase the separation of fat intake of antibiotics, poor nutrition, extreme temperatures, severe stress and improper care. Experts believe that the right care for oily hair will avoid many of the problems and ensure that they always look nice and neat.</p>

<h2>Wash oily hair</h2>

<p>A very important question is the frequency of washing. And if you have recently called for beauticians do not wash my hair 1-2 times a week, so as not to stimulate increased zhirootdelenie, now come to the conclusion that it is much more harmful to walk with excessively oily hair. If you do not wash your hair for a long time, the upper protective layer of the scalp are beginning to proliferate microscopic fungi and yeasts that cause itching, dandruff, acne on his head and a variety of inflammatory processes. In addition, the hair follicles become clogged with fat and sebaceous ducts harden, causing the hair to stop growing, thin and hard fall.</p>

<p>Therefore, wash oily hair should be implemented as necessary, at least every day. Water for washing should not be too hot, as hot water activates the sebaceous glands. Before washing, you need to carefully comb hair &ndash; it will partially remove dirt, dandruff and protect themselves from tangling. Shampoo need not be applied directly to the hair, because in this case it is not evenly distributed.</p>

<p>It is best to dilute a small amount of shampoo to wash with water and the resulting solution, or to put it first in the palm of your hand. Lather oily hair better twice, distributing shampoo soft circular motions and without scratching the skin nails.</p>

<p>It is important to thoroughly rinse the hair after washing, because of the remnants of shampoo they are faster and have gryazneyut adhesive and matte appearance. After washing, do not immediately need to comb your hair, they need to dry out a bit. Try to use a hair dryer only when absolutely necessary, because the temperature changes are bad for oily skin and stimulate the strengthening zhirootdeleniya.</p>

<h2>Shampoo for oily hair</h2>

<p>Shampoo for oily hair should be selected very carefully, studying the composition indicated on the label. A well-chosen shampoo helps to restore proper operation of the sebaceous glands and remove the irritation and the use of the wrong shampoo will only worsen the situation. Choose a shampoo transparent natural colors &ndash; white or off-white, creamy shampoos because the bright colors often contain poisonous unnecessary and harmful dyes.</p>

<p>The most effective are the shampoos with herbal extracts &ndash; nettle, chamomile, sage, mother and stepmother, and also contain algae, vitamins A, K, C, and zinc. In the presence of dandruff shampoos choose from zinc, sulfur and tar. Do not buy shampoos, if they contain silicone, because they are heavier hair and make them even fatter.</p>

<p>Great popularity in recent years become dry shampoos that are especially useful on business trips, travel and the absence of hot water and time. These shampoos are available in powder form and are applied by spray. After 5-10 minutes, when the powder to soak up all the grease and dirt, his combed comb.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Depression, anxiety and fear - not a sentence, all curable]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/depression-anxiety-and-fear-not-a-sentence-all-curable/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-30T14:31:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/depression-anxiety-and-fear-not-a-sentence-all-curable</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/mood/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Mood, vitality, there is no meaning in life" alt="Depression, anxiety and fear - not a sentence, all curable"> Depression is treated successfully with antidepressants. The problem of depression and other psycho-emotional disorders in this age of high speed is very urgent.</p>

<p>According to the WHO, the scale and speed of the spread of this disease are devastating, on the heels of such a &ldquo;popular&rdquo; diseases such as stroke, heart attack and diabetes. And the age of patients getting younger &ndash; if earlier depression affecting people after 40 years, but now the problem is widespread and adolescence.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>According to the same WHO, now every fourth &ndash; fifth of the Earth suffers what &ndash; or mental disorders, and by 2020 it is expected that depression will be the first in the world in disease.</p>

<p>However, do not confuse the real, medical depression with the usual blues and just a bad mood, because, at the household level depression &ndash; is sadness, grief and anguish. If you have just the blues, then there are many ways to cheer yourself and force of will to withdraw from this state.</p>

<p>Many people are faced with the phenomenon of temporary loss of mood and vitality, and everyone finds themselves out of this situation, what &ndash; something out. Who &ndash; is beginning to go hard in the gym who &ndash; that finds relief in the church, some with just dipped his head into some interesting job or hobby, alternate setting or go to rest. But if, unfortunately, you caught a real depression, then just your efforts will, unfortunately, will not be enough.</p>

<p>Depression, according to the definition in Wikipedia &ndash; is a mental disorder that is characterized by constantly depressed mood, loss of ability to experience pleasure, low self-esteem, and the complete loss of interest in life, and to that previously happy. The fact is that depression and mood decline is easily explained on a chemical level, and due to lack of production of the hormone serotonin in the body.</p>

<p>The role of this hormone in the human body is impressive &ndash; he is responsible for the process of cognitive activity, locomotor activity and muscle tone. But most importantly, it creates in us a sense of lifting mood and happiness, and so it is called the hormone of happiness. Normal levels of serotonin gives a person self-control, emotional and stress.</p>

<p>Some researchers have found that people who are dominant in society, have high levels of serotonin. People with a low level of serotonin, on the contrary, self-control, emotional stress and so reduced that the slightest pretexts are stressful, and as a result, depressed.</p>

<p>Very often people who are depressed, not knowing what was happening to them and trying to dull the emotional pain and anxiety begin to take alcohol or psychotropic substances, and this signing his own death warrant, because with the help of drugs and alcohol can only be purchased chronic alcoholism or drug addiction,  In this case, the craving for alcohol and drug abuse is secondary and serves the purpose of relieving anxiety and tension inherent in depression.</p>

<p>Moreover, the relatives of a person suffering from depression and alcohol secondary lapsed into alcoholism, of course, the best of intentions, are his &ldquo;encode&rdquo; to eliminate the pernicious craving for alcohol. But we must understand that &ldquo;coding&rdquo; refers to the psycho-terrorist methods and is based on an elementary intimidation sick that he could not lead a person to recovery, since no alcohol, no depression can not be cured in this way.</p>

<p>The big problem also lies in the fact that in our country are depressed people, especially young men, are often embarrassed to admit their psycho &ndash; emotional problems, ignore the problem and do not seek medical attention, thereby only exacerbating their condition.</p>

<p>Depression, as mentioned above, the only cure at will or not alcohol. This disease is treated with special drugs, which are called antidepressants, their effect on the regulation of the level of serotonin in the brain. There are so many antidepressants and use them to learn to successfully treat depression. Although long-term treatment and under mandatory supervision of a physician, but defeat disease is now possible once and for all.</p>

<p>Ashamed of their condition is not necessary, because it is the same disease as any other. Depression does not destroy the mind and human intelligence, it just does not allow him to live fully, and in a state of neglect often even leads to suicide.</p>

<p>Depression affects many of the greatest and brightest of today. British Prime Minister Winston Churchill struggled all his life with depression and called it &ldquo;the black dog that with me all my life.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Therefore, if you are suffering from depression and she does not go alone for a long time, do not worry, nothing bad has happened to you, just dropped us a much-needed level of the hormone serotonin. Entrust your problems doctor and competent therapist with the necessary medicines will return the joy in your life.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nail fungus. Fungal nail disease, symptoms and prevention]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nail-fungus-fungal-nail-disease-symptoms-and-prevention/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-30T14:29:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/nail-fungus-fungal-nail-disease-symptoms-and-prevention</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/nail-fungus/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Fungal nail disease, nail fungus" alt="Nail fungus. Fungal nail disease, symptoms and prevention"> Fungal nail disease and still require early treatment and prevention. Fungal nail disease and stop its rapid growth concern dermatologists around the world. According to their estimates, is suffering from a quarter of the world&rsquo;s population, especially in large cities with high population density, and this figure continues to grow.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Causes and Symptoms of fungal infections of nails and feet</h2>

<p>Ways of getting a lot of fungus in the body, you can catch anywhere, but most often it is on the beach, in the bath, in the pool, the sauna or the shoes of people infected.</p>

<p>Nail Fungus transmitted not only from person to person, but also from animals to humans, and from the external environment. Complicating the situation is that there is a great variety of mushrooms, more than 1.5 million of them are pathogenic to humans about 500 species.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, fungal infections do not produce immunity, and a person can be infected by the same form of the fungus many times. Fungi remarkably tenacious, as evidenced by the scientists conducted an unusual experiment &ndash; they put the shoes sick fungus man in a locker, and when 20 years later got her out of there, the spores of the fungus were fully viable. Therefore a crucial role in the fight against fungi plays prevention of fungal nail diseases and personal hygiene.</p>

<p>Mushrooms particularly active subject in humidity, heat and poor ventilation, and excessive use of soaps and detergents do not give that effect, which we expect hard observing hygiene. The fact that the surface of our skin has a protective, so-called lipid layer, the finest film of fat that they live in our &ldquo;native&rdquo; beneficial bacteria designed to protect us from the adverse effects of the environment.</p>

<p>Doctors do not recommend to wash with soap and water often, as when washing wool we literally rip off off this protective film, and a variety of micro-organisms, bacteria and fungi literally stick to our body without resistance, is not completely restore the natural cover, which takes about</p>

<p>An interesting scientific fact &ndash; in the 30-ies of the last century, during the establishment of the Soviet regime, the Chukchi, Evenki and other northern nations have become hard to teach hygiene, wash with soap making. The result was so unexpected that at first the doctors just shrugged and could not understand why Aboriginal started such a colossal death.</p>

<p>As it turned out later, soap destroying the protective layer of fat covering their skin and they were completely defenseless against the invasion of microorganisms. By the way, the researchers argue that it is for this same reason, and we often get sick after a bath, and not from the fact that hypothermia is commonly thought. Nature, as we know, did not know soap, the use of detergents &ndash; is a recent invention of European civilization. If you do not want to kill a cat or dog, do not wash them with soap or shampoo, because the animal can not live long in such a &ldquo;sterile&rdquo;.</p>

<p>If it affects the human fungal disease, first, as a rule, there are cracks between the toes and on the soles, and then passes the infection on your nails. It is believed that the fungus uncured stop sooner or later turns into a nail fungus from which escape is not so easy. Man begins to disturb the symptoms of fungal nail diseases &ndash; itching, discomfort and bad breath. Nail changes color becomes dull, opaque, crumbles, deformed, thickened. If the disease is not treated in time, the nail may collapse completely, and the fungus will eventually hit the nails on the hands.</p>

<p>If you do not fight the infection, the fungus begins to &ldquo;walk&rdquo; around the body, releasing toxins that affects the lymphatic and circulatory systems, reduces immunity and causes multiple allergies, sometimes even able to hit the brain. Man gets tired quickly, feel malaise, nausea, frequent colds.</p>

<h2>Prevention of fungal nail diseases</h2>

<p>Nail fungal disease is considered to be the surrender of immunity, so it is often susceptible to it people with weakened or immature immune, that is, children and the elderly. Considered a risk factor for various scratches, abrasions and other skin damage through which the fungus is easier to penetrate into the body, which are the gateway for incoming infections.</p>

<p>If you notice the first signs of fungal nail disease, such as discoloration of the nail, its transparency, thickening of the nail plate, an inflammation of the skin around the nail, as well as itching and redness between the toes, it is necessary without delay to see a doctor &ndash; dermatologist and deliver  The fungus is now successfully treated thanks to the arsenal of physicians in a large range of antifungal drugs. Most importantly, time to start treatment and prevent total capture of infection in your body.</p>

<p>If the affected area is small, it is often possible to cope with the fungus by local treatment. If the process of infection went away, then the treatment will be more time consuming, but, in any case, it should bring to an end, as the untreated fungus necessarily continue its destructive work. In the treatment of a family member, all others should also be examined, as most at risk of infection.</p>

<p>Better prevention of fungal infections of nails and feet &ndash; a thorough safety precautions to prevent re-infection. If you have been in a public bath and not too sure of its sterility, the best means of prevention is the treatment of foot boric alcohol or vinegar diluted as 1 tablespoon per cup of water, the media is detrimental to the fungus. Do not wear someone else&rsquo;s shoes, dry the feet, all the scratches and damage immediately treated with iodine or green paint.</p>

<p>When buying shoes, choose a spacious, comfortable, preferably made of natural materials and vented, because, as mentioned above, the fungus loves moist environment without air. Their shoes and do not forget to air regularly and periodically wipe the inside with a solution of vinegar, which kills germs, while leaving no odor.</p>

<p>If you nail fungal diseases is very important to strengthen your own immune system, destroyed the invasion of fungal infection. So, get the overall strengthening and healing the body &ndash; drink plenty of water, eat only healthy food with the required amount of vitamins and minerals, do not overeat, sometimes it is better to starve. And certainly normalize intestinal function, go in uncomplicated physical exercise, get enough sleep and maximize protect yourself from the stress.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
