<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Other | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/other/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-05-01T15:45:15+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Not to Eat Before Blood Donation?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/what-not-to-eat-before-blood-donation/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-11T15:03:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/what-not-to-eat-before-blood-donation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/what-not-to-eat-before-blood-donation/img.jpg" title="What not to eat before blood donation?" alt="before the blood test, before the blood test can have, before taking a blood test, eat before the blood test">Dietary restrictions - that&rsquo;s what a lifetime many times faced everyone. Aggravated <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/gastritis.html" title="gastritis">gastritis</a> - you can not eat spices, fried, sweet, salty and fresh fruits and vegetables; performance scales began to &quot;off-scale&quot; higher positions - sit on a diet and generally deprive ourselves of the majority of gastronomic pleasures. Even the blood can not pass so do without taboos&hellip;</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>


<h2>Restrictions before taking blood samples</h2>

<p>Regardless of whether it is for a study you donate blood (for general analysis, sugar, for biochemical research, hormones, infection, etc.), preparation steps for the procedure will always be roughly the same.</p>

<p>In the first place, it will need to come fasting, i.e., not less than 6-8 hours after the last (not tight) meal. In some sources you can find that prior to entering the treatment room you for 12 hours or more in any case can not even look in the direction of the refrigerator. This is not true; the period of voluntary hunger strike for a period of 6-8 hours is enough.</p>

<p>As a rule, the complexities of this preparatory measure does not arise, because usually all the research blood is taken in the morning and after a nap, not every person is experiencing severe famine.</p>

<p>Most people have heard, and that before the analysis can not eat anything, but that their knowledge in preparation for the blood collection procedure usually exhausted. Nevertheless, there are certain restrictions and for the earlier period of the preparation. To analysis showed the most reliable results, for 2 days before the nurse bring to your hand syringe needle, you have to sit on a special diet. You are not recommended to eat:</p>

<ul>
<li>Fatty, fried, smoked foods;</li>
<li>Sweets and confectionery products in large quantities;</li>
</ul>


<p>If donating blood on a general analysis, it can be a bit neglected (that many, by the way, do), but more complex investigations such as biochemical analysis, determination of antibodies to infections, detection of cancer markers, immunogram, etc., require from patients greater diligence.</p>

<p>It is believed that before the blood sugar should be almost a week to refuse the use of carbohydrates in any form. In fact, it will need only a couple of days a sensible diet.</p>

<p>Carbohydrate consumed quickly or stocking up body, transformed into glycogen or fat, so that within a few hours after their use in the blood should not be a trace of &quot;extra&quot; sugar - if the patient is certainly not ill severe diabetes. But for such situations, people usually know in advance, so already receiving treatment and control your diet.</p>

<p>Very often patients confidentially divided among themselves that they have ignored the preparation for a particular study, and they &quot;had nothing&quot;. For this reason, some people are also beginning to question the logic of the requirements of the doctor. There is a thought: &quot;And what will happen if you do not prepare for the analysis?&quot; Of course, it may be that you&rsquo;re lucky and it will not affect the quality of the results. However, excesses of food before a <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/analysis-and-research/blood-test-biochemical.html" title="blood test">blood test</a> can cause false data receipt.</p>

<p>Here&rsquo;s a simple example. After the meal, there is a man called physiologic leukocytosis - cells are white blood cells at a time out of the tissues into the bloodstream, and the amount of blood increases.</p>

<p>If you make a general analysis of the patient, who has recently eaten, this figure could be his inflated, because of what the doctor will suggest the presence of infection in the body and starts up and down to survey the unfortunate patient who is merely frivolous attitude to training&hellip; similar erroneous situations can occur at the time of other analyzes.</p>

<h2>Restrictions before taking blood donation</h2>

<p>But here the situation is different, however, the differences are not so great.</p>

<p>As for the early transition to comply with the above diet, this requirement exists for donors. Eating fatty, fried and other junk food before taking the blood impairs the quality of harvested materials. Incidentally, the &quot;no&quot; in this case, apply also on protein foods - meat, cheese, eggs, cheese, etc., they create a large load on the immune system and human kidney, which are transfused components of your blood.</p>

<p>It is characteristic that, if you do not follow a diet and to the right to take the plasma you immediately incriminate insufficient training. The plasma (blood serum) in patients who are on the eve of fat eaten, a little cloudy, and has a unique, slightly grayish-greenish tint&hellip;</p>

<p>Restrictions before taking blood or plasma donation on more serious than before the tests, but the day of the procedure, the donor is not waiting for the hunger strike, but rather an indulgence in the diet. He can afford a light breakfast (no forbidden foods), best of all, consisting of carbohydrate foods.</p>

<p>Tea or coffee with biscuits, drying, or a pair of candy fit perfectly. Once at the station transfusion his blood examined and the person will give the &quot;green light&quot; for the change, there he asked to drink more tea and biscuits and chocolate. Besides, you do not have to carry a thermos and a bag with a sweet, nice bonus that will be given to you right there.</p>

<p>So, whether you are pursuing your own interests (donates blood for tests) or doing good to others (sacrifice her as a donor), before the procedure of putting in something have to deny yourself a little sit on a diet. Do not let that upset, because in both cases, your goals deserve to suffer some inconvenience for them. Moreover, the dietary restrictions will last very long&hellip;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alzheimers Disease Called Diabetes Brain]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/alzheimers-disease-called-diabetes-brain/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-14T21:50:22+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/alzheimers-disease-called-diabetes-brain</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It was found that the human brain has evolved in the direction of finding food that has a high amount of fat and sugar, but the advantage has arisen for survival in times of plenty deformed into an irresistible craving to self-destruct, according to New Scientist.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The link between Alzheimer&rsquo;s and diabetes in an article number in the printed edition. Title of the publication of &quot;Diabetes brain: the perfect food nightmare&quot;, carried on the cover of the magazine.</p>

<p>Obesity and diabetes is improper diet. New Scientist notes that &quot;in recent years become known to more and more data pointing to the identical nature of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease/" title="Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease">Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease</a>, and so some researchers regard this disease of neurodegeneration as another form of diabetes&quot;.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>&quot;If this is indeed the case, then the relationship between these two diseases is simply disastrous consequences&quot;, - stated in the publication. &quot;Today the world is faced with an unprecedented epidemic of diabetes, and the prospect of a parallel epidemic of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease more terrible for the suffering that the disease causes to people and material costs really scared&quot;, the newspaper writes.</p>

<p>One way to prevent this threat, according to the New Scientist, - the intervention of lawyers. Earlier attempts had to prosecute companies that provide catering services, because they contribute to the <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a> epidemic. Now, if it is confirmed the causal link between the sweet, fatty foods with Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease, while the number of such claims will certainly rise, confident authors of the publication.
A little earlier, in the same year by 2 independent groups of researchers published the results of scientific experiments that show the relationship between changes in protein metabolism and insulin signaling pathway structures inherent in Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease - the appearance of amyloid plaques in neurons. Thus, it has been shown that increasing the concentration of the protein beta-amyloid, which is a cause of amyloid plaques occurs because of irregularities of the base level of activity of various molecules of insulin signaling pathway in the human brain.</p>

<p>The results of other experiments, was the idea that insulin resistance cells in the brain can be regarded as a characteristic early sign of the same Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease. This finding allowed scientists to classify conditionally neurodegenerative disease to diabetes of the third type.</p>

<p>The researchers predict that by 2015. Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease is able to hit about 115 million. people on the planet.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mortally Dangerous Dengue Fever Returns to Greece]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/mortally-dangerous-dengue-fever-returns-to-greece/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-14T21:47:43+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/mortally-dangerous-dengue-fever-returns-to-greece</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In Greece, the old man died, presumably from a forgotten dengue. This is the first recorded human cases of dengue in Greece, more than 80 in recent years, the country&rsquo;s health authorities reported.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The man, whose age was more than 80 years, died in late August. According to the Hellenic Centre for Disease Control, the man developed severe kind of infamous <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/dengue-fever.html" title="dengue fever">dengue fever</a>, which is almost always accompanied by a hemorrhagic syndrome.</p>

<p>Now tests are made to determine whether other people are infected.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Recall that the dengue <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/fever.html" title="fever">fever</a> in Greece was defeated after the epidemic of 1920. She later reappeared in Europe, which has entered the Asian tiger mosquito. Several cases of the disease recorded in 2010 in France and Croatia.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
