<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Health-and-beauty | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/health-and-beauty/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-01-21T22:48:55+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Degree of Obesity. How to Determine the Degree of Obesity]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/the-degree-of-obesity-how-to-determine-the-degree-of-obesity/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-21T17:16:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/the-degree-of-obesity-how-to-determine-the-degree-of-obesity</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/the-degree-of-obesity-how-to-determine-the-degree-of-obesity/img.jpg" title="The degree of obesity. How to determine the degree of obesity?" alt="abdominal obesity, abdominal adiposity, visceral obesity">Obesity is a disease in which the body weight is increased by increasing the content of fatty tissue. Besides the obvious harm to health (people with its presence will develop diabetes, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/cardiology/atherosclerosis.html" title="atherosclerosis">atherosclerosis</a> and other disorders), the disease significantly spoils the appearance, worsening and even disfiguring figure.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Furthermore, the term &quot;<a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>&quot; means a pathology, this word is unpleasant, is clearly negative, to some extent condemneth group. Naturally, neither one nor the other owners do not like excess weight, which often prefer to call his lack of completeness, obesity, but not this definition. However, there is a way to dot the &quot;i&quot;: some simple calculations help to distinguish the fullness of obesity.</p>

<h2>What is BMI and what is it for?</h2>

<p>On the body mass index (BMI), we have repeatedly said in other posts, devoted to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>. It refers to the ratio of height and weight, which is expressed by a numerical value and gives an indication of normal, insufficient or overweight humans. It calculated it is very simple: the value of the body weight in kilograms divided by the square of height in meters.</p>

<h2>More clearly this can be represented as follows:</h2>

<p>The normal value of the index in women vary in the region from 19 to 25. The difference between these figures is large enough that allows index capture growth-weight ratios in people of any stature. For this reason and asthenics fragile and strong hypersthenics have at its mass index &quot;fit&quot; into the gap from 19 to 25. If the resulting number is greater than the upper limit, it is clearly talking about excess weight and justification of the mighty physique and broad bone this case untenable.</p>

<p>To make it easier to navigate in the calculations, we give an example. Take the girl with above average growth of 170 cm and weighing 60 kg, and calculate her BMI.</p>

<p>Thus, a person with such parameters do not suffer deficiency and excess weight. Unfortunately, some can only envy like&hellip; And now, when we have understood the basics, let&rsquo;s go further.</p>

<p>There are many ways to define obesity and its powers, of which we give only the most used. However, regardless of what kind of degree is awarded this disorder, obesity must be fought. However, many Americans do not agree with us. In the US, there is even a special thick society; once a certain time, its members come from different cities and states, arrange meetings and meetings to teach &quot;newbies&quot; that being overweight - this is normal, and we must love themselves as they are. We will not challenge the right of others to their own opinion, but remain at its European convictions <strong>obesity - it is not the norm, and the disease that it is necessary to get rid of.</strong></p>

<h2>Determining the degree of obesity by BMI. Method one</h2>

<p>In this case, the degree is determined depending on the body mass index.</p>

<ul>
<li>BMI of 19-25 is the norm;</li>
<li>BMI of 25-30 indicates a &quot;pre-obese&quot; - increased body weight, which is necessary to normalize;</li>
<li>BMI of 30-35 corresponds to the first degree of obesity;</li>
<li>BMI of 35-40 speaks of the second degree;</li>
<li>BMI above 40 indicates the presence of third-degree obesity.</li>
</ul>


<p>Let&rsquo;s see, would be considered our hypothetical woman slim, if not weighed 60 and 90 kilograms.</p>

<p>The result - the first degree. As you can see, this method is quite liberal, because even at much lower weight, people often consider themselves full and try to get rid of the extra kilos to look like the most aesthetically pleasing.</p>

<h2>Determining the degree of obesity. Method two</h2>

<p>The second method is to determine overweight relative to the norm in percentage is used much less frequently than the first.</p>

<p>If &quot;preponderance&quot; is not more than 10%, it is not obese and completion. With an excess of 10-29% are diagnosed with &quot;1 degree of obesity&quot;, with 30-49% - the second degree, at 50% and more - the third degree.</p>

<p>For example, initially the girl, which in our example &quot;recovered&quot; from 60 to 90 kg, had asthenic constitution, that is, the notorious 60 kg were her ideal weight. Calculate how much it exceeded its weight &quot;limit&quot; when the stout up to 90 kg. Let us remember and construct elementary arithmetic proportion, although, in principle, you can make calculations in mind.</p>

<p>X = 150%, that is excess relatively normal weight is 50%.</p>

<p>The result - our &quot;guinea&quot; came to the last, third-degree obesity! It turns out, the use of different methods give very different results&hellip; What does this mean? Only that <strong>ideal system for determining the degree of obesity does not exist, and the calculations are made to give only approximate figures.</strong></p>

<p>In fact, it is very difficult to put on the same level with people very different physique, height, shape and features, etc., and provide a single formula for all. At the present time to determine the presence of obesity and its degrees are the first of the designated ways, but objectively can hardly be considered the ideal. Imagine yourself: well, how can not very tall woman weighing 90 kg be considered &quot;little&quot; full?</p>

<p>However, morality is not in it. We will not complain about the errors of the individual formulas, as well as distressed relative imperfection of the health system and the structure of the world as a whole. We draw attention to something else: thinking about the state of the figure, do not indulge in the calculations and determine how many kilograms you can without remorse &quot;eat&quot; that is not officially regarded as a thick. Control yourself: honest look in the mirror will tell you much more than any arithmetic, it will show you your weaknesses will help you plan activities and then when you are prefer to allow a joy to watch the progress. And then you will cease to care about the issue, there you are overweight or not: You will continuously work on ourselves and better understand that the main thing - not the absence of too full hips or too wide waist, which can be just your feature and exercise, a relief, the harmony of the entire body.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baths With Sea Salt for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/baths-with-sea-salt-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-21T14:30:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/baths-with-sea-salt-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/baths-with-sea-salt-for-weight-loss/img.jpg" title="Baths with sea salt for weight loss" alt="bath with salt for weight loss">Sea salt has been used in ancient Greece and was used as a treatment for various diseases: nervous, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/vascular-disease/" title="vascular disease">cardiovascular diseases</a>, diseases of the musculoskeletal system. Today, in the foreground is the use of sea-salt diet and getting rid of cellulite. Is it worth it to consider this remedy so much a reliable partner in the fight against <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>?</p>

<!--more-->


<p>It is known that sea salt has a rich mineral structure, which ensures its beneficial properties. Seawater contains almost half of the periodic table, and a similar chemical composition is derived from its salt. Today sea salt is obtained in the same ways that a century ago - by evaporation. The elements contained in sea water in the greatest concentration, remain dry sea salt. These include:</p>

<p><em>Sodium and potassium</em> - contribute to the removal of the cells of the body of metabolic products.</p>

<p><em>Bromine</em> - has a calming effect on the nervous system.</p>

<p>In small quantities of sea salt in the presence of <em>gold, silver, palladium, selenium, boron, manganese, zinc, silicon, nickel</em>, and other minerals.</p>

<p>Concentrated saline is slightly irritating epidermis, increasing blood flow in small blood vessels. Because of this, the metabolic processes in the cells of the skin and subcutaneous tissue increase. Thus, salt bath help to improve skin appearance and to some extent reduce the appearance of cellulite. Salt also has anti-inflammatory properties, dries small foci of inflammation, so that the skin after bath salt looks more smooth and even.</p>

<p>Although bath and cosmetic products with sea salt is recommended for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>, the very salt of any fat burning properties are not allowed. And &quot;weight loss&quot; after a bath with sea salt does not occur because of the volume reduction of body fat. Just by dissolving the salt in water to create a hot hyperosmotic solution that extends from the body &quot;extra&quot; liquid and reduces swelling.</p>

<p>Soothing or, conversely, a tonic effect bath with sea salt can be obtained by adding to the water an essential oil or a decoction of herbs with the appropriate action.</p>

<p>The implications are clear: such procedures do not allow to lose weight, but they may help a bit to lose weight by providing the body drain effect. They also help in the fight against cosmetic defects of the skin and affect overall health.</p>

<p>Sea salt bath can be purchased in almost any pharmacy or store. It is better to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="choose">choose</a> a salt without any coloring and flavoring agents, because the contact with them may cause skin irritation or allergic reaction.</p>

<p>The amount of salt required for a bath, generally indicated on the packaging. Typically, the means take 300-500 grams per 200 liters of water. Adding more salt than is recommended, in the hope of a more pronounced effect, you only get increased dryness and flaking of the skin. Keep this in mind and avoid &quot;overdose&quot;.</p>

<p>Before taking a bath with sea salt Rinse under the shower. The required quantity of salt is dissolved in a liter of hot water, and then pour the solution into the water bath. You should select water temperature in the bath, it is comfortable for you, but remember that it should not be higher than 38 degrees. More hot water will dry the skin. In the water you can add your favorite essential oil or a decoction of herbs that enhance the action of the bath. Thus, essential oils of citrus fruits (lemon, orange, grapefruit) increase the effect of anti-cellulite treatments.</p>

<p>Immersed in the bath must not more than 10-20 minutes, at this region of the heart must remain above water. After the bath, you need to take a shower and put on a skin moisturizer. Then comes <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/body-wraps-for-weight-loss-belly/" title="wrap">wrapped</a> in a sheet or a bathrobe and sit or lie down quietly for half an hour. Within 1-2 hours before and after the bath should not eat, but you can drink green tea or herbal decoction.</p>

<p>Baths with sea salt are not for everyone, and have a list of contraindications. These include skin, heart and gynecological diseases, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/vascular-disease/varicose-veins.html" title="varicose veins">varicose veins</a>, increased body temperature, the condition of alcoholic intoxication, <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a>. If you have doubts about their safety for you personally, before the start of the procedures would be better to consult a doctor.</p>

<p>You can find a variety of opinions about the use of baths with sea salt. Among them there are also totally implausible: that someone has lost 10 kilograms in just a two weeks alone baths. To believe such statements are not worth it.</p>

<p>More than adequate people actually experienced the effects of sea salt, write to relieve fatigue and improve skin after these procedures. Weight is reduced by only a few kilograms in such baths combined with diet and physical activity. The achieved result is possible to keep under the same conditions.</p>

<p>From the available options in the sale of sea salt most people like the salt of the Dead Sea. Indeed, it has a unique chemical composition, wherein the proportion of sodium chloride accounts for only about 20%, and the remaining 80% - other minerals. Their relatively high content, and provides a more pronounced effect of water treatments.</p>

<p>Thus, a bath with sea salt should not be considered as the basis for weight loss, but rather as an aid provider cosmetic and soothing effect. But weight loss is still achieved a healthy diet and exercise, and do not expect that without them you can achieve noticeable results in the achievement of harmony.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove the Thighs?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-remove-the-thighs/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-11T15:57:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-remove-the-thighs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-remove-the-thighs/img.jpg" title="How to remove the thighs?" alt="how to remove the thighs in a week">Let&rsquo;s face it: most normal men do not like fat women&rsquo;s thighs. Maybe a huge ass resembles the consistency of jelly, a decoration for female hippo, but not for normal Russian women. With thighs need to do something about it, otherwise you will soon not be able to leave the house because they do not fit through the doorway. Believe me, the skirt is not fastened, not because she sat down after washing. The problem is not in the clothes, you just ate too long and heated for three ass on the couch instead of sitting on a diet and regularly move.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>You can not only remove fat from the thighs, therefore, to remove the thighs, you have to lose weight. Start exercise. Join a fitness club, to work under the supervision of professional trainers. These are experienced people who know how fast you drive away with three sweat, and along with the fat thighs. Do not be ashamed of his fat ass. Believe me, you will not be alone. Next you will be engaged in such an aunt, next to which you feel Thumbelina.</p>

<p>If you are torn complexes, and you do not want to show others their fat thighs, practicing <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="at home">at home</a>. But remember, in this case, you will be more difficult to achieve the expected result. Too low load will not bring the desired effect. If you on the contrary, will overload the muscles, they increase in volume, and in spite of reducing the amount of fat thighs become even thicker.</p>

<p>Great impact on your figure light exercise - walking, dancing, swimming. You will spend more time on them, but the results are sure you will enjoy. With them, you will not build muscle mass, but spent most amount of calories that allow you to lose weight. Lose weight, you remove not only the thighs and belly.</p>

<h2>Stop overeating</h2>

<p>If you are keen to remove the thighs, from this point on your favorite delicacy should be cucumbers, tomatoes and cabbage. Forget about the sweets. For years, you catered to his stomach, ignoring the interests of the hips. Is it any wonder that the thighs swollen with jealousy? Now you have to take care of them, and it will have to severely limit your daily diet.</p>

<p>Eat as little as possible carbohydrate foods. You should also limit the intake of fats. Against the background of such a diet is necessary to increase the protein content in the diet. So you have <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="every day">every day</a> to eat meat, fish, dairy products.</p>

<p>Surely you will torment hunger. You can get rid of it using anorectics drugs. If you do not want to poison your body with pills, you can use other methods. They are also effective, and totally free of charge:</p>

<ul>
<li>Eat raw fruits and vegetables;</li>
<li>Distracts from the food with the help of interesting activities or entertainment;</li>
<li>Hang in the kitchen designs, cause you disgust (worms, feces, human entrails, etc.);</li>
<li>Take a picture of your fat thighs and hang the picture on the fridge.</li>
</ul>


<p>They say that massage promotes <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>. Allegedly, on the one hand, it improves blood circulation, stimulating fat burning, and with another - leads to a decrease in the problem areas of the body due to mechanical action hand massage. Do not believe, you do not lose weight from massage. Still, this procedure can have a positive impact on the size of your thighs.</p>

<p>Even if you spend days aged in the massage table, exposing her ass skillful hands of a masseur, you still can not lose weight. But over time, get rid of cellulite. In addition, by improving the microcirculation and eliminate venous stasis of tissue accumulated leave them liquid.</p>

<p>Simply put, the swelling will go away. That they bear part of the blame for the fact that your thighs covered with orange peel. That swelling make your ass look even thicker than it actually is.</p>

<p>How to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="choose">choose</a> a massage? The interior offers a lot of options: hardware, vacuum, manual, honey, anti-cellulite&hellip; Choose any, they all give the same result. Perhaps a more pronounced effect you get from the anti-cellulite massage. But keep in mind that after a week you will groan, sitting on a chair. During the procedure, you feel as if the skin is separated from the body, and after the massage thighs covered with bruises. However, the beauty demands victims. Other types of massage differ in the way of, but not on the end result. Choose one that will be more enjoyable for you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Belly Massage for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/belly-massage-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-08T11:18:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/belly-massage-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/belly-massage-for-weight-loss/img.jpg" title="WBelly massage for weight loss" alt="belly massage for weight loss at home"><strong>Massage</strong> - a method that has long been in service with the conventional medicine. It is approved by the Ministry of Health, and is used to treat a huge number of diseases. Of course, as an auxiliary method of therapy. Massage is used in virtually all areas of medicine. He is firmly entrenched in our lives, and probably in the world there is not one person who would never lay on a massage table.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>The effectiveness of massage</h2>

<p>The effectiveness of massage has long been proved. It can help you improve the condition of the patient, regardless of the disease, which he suffers. However, the inability of the placebo-controlled studies leaves some doubt as to the mechanism of its effects. Which factor plays the most important role: the psychological or physiological? What makes a person feel relieved: relaxation and faith in the healing power of massage or mechanical effect on the soft tissues of the body?</p>

<p>This question remains open for the time being. We are interested in, whether it is possible with the help of abdominal massage to lose at least a few kilograms? Agree, it would be great: no need to starve, no strain, just lie down on the table, belly up, and wait for someone skilled hands make short work of your fat. Is it possible? Let&rsquo;s deal.</p>

<p>All the effects of the massage can be divided into psychological and physiological. The first is certainly very useful, but are unlikely to have a specific and predictable effect on the weight of your body. Therefore, it makes no sense to consider them, go directly to the physiological. We will not engage in speculation, use a pseudo-data, for example, on energy currents - too. That&rsquo;s the impact on the human body has a significantly abdominal massage:</p>

<ul>
<li>Warms the skin due to emitted as a result of mechanical friction heat;</li>
<li>Stimulates the microcirculation of the skin by heating;</li>
<li>It stimulates the flow of lymph and venous blood due to mechanical compression of blood vessels;</li>
<li>Relaxes the muscles by mechanical action on them, as well as enhance blood flow.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Belly massage and weight loss</h2>

<p>Which of these mechanisms, in your opinion, can contribute to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>? Let&rsquo;s look at them all in turn.</p>

<p>Obviously, warm skin of the abdomen can not dissolve fat. It does not melt like wax, so the effect of massage is unlikely to reduce the weight of your body. Judge for yourself if the increase in skin temperature contribute to weight loss, for the acquisition of a slim figure you would rather stick a couple of yellow cards in the stomach, or heat it with an ordinary table lamp. From the sea, everything is back to not only rested, but also slim, because the fat left on the beach not only the stomach, but also from the entire body.</p>

<p>The skin temperature increases by touching hand massage, so the blood vessels dilate to give away excess heat. This is one of the mechanisms of thermoregulation, protects the body from overheating. Due to dilation of small blood vessels nutrition improves soft tissues, primarily the skin. Does this mean that fat belly will start to leave? No, otherwise all alcoholics with red faces would not wear belly in his hands, and would look more slender birch. Medicines from the group of proofreaders microcirculation, led by pentoxifylline, have themselves become popular drugs for weight loss.</p>

<p>This effect helps to eliminate stagnant lymph and venous blood. Thus, the massage display allows the liquid that has accumulated in the soft tissues. Perhaps it is this feature made people consider massage as a regular method of losing weight. <strong><em>Firstly</em></strong>, with the fluid leaves the body weight, that causes a person to believe that massage helped him to break down fat. <strong><em>Second</em></strong>, visually stomach becomes more flat. This is due to improvement of the skin and removal of liquid. <strong><em>Third</em></strong>, the possible reduction in waist circumference, again, due to the removal of edema.</p>

<p>At the young age of these effects may not occur at all, or to be mild, but after 40 years, when the body breaks down the balance of hormones, a change in metabolism, fluid accumulates more actively. Accordingly, massage is more effective way to reduce body weight. Of course, the effect of massage is very useful for the figure. But make no mistake, the fat remains in place, leaving only water.</p>

<p>Surprisingly, making the opposite action, a lot of people waiting to get on the output a result. Shaking the press, they are straining the abdominal muscles, hoping to lose weight. Visiting massage people relax the same muscle groups, waiting for an identical effect - weight loss. So what still needs to be done with the muscles? Perhaps, after all, cut, and as often as possible. If muscle relaxation accompanied by weight loss, people have lost weight during the holidays. To enhance the effect, he tried to muscle relaxants and antispasmodics - drugs that reduce muscle tone.</p>

<p>Lose weight with the help of belly massage can be in only one case: if you are doing it yourself. And preferably more than once per day. Massage takes away a lot of strength and energy, so you&rsquo;ll save calories, and with them - the extra weight. But lying on the table and making the masseur knead your stomach, you just get rid of the money that paid for his services. Of excess weight - is unlikely.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing a Anti Stretch Marks Cream After Giving Birth]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-06T11:50:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/img.jpg" width="250" title="Choosing a cream for stretch marks after giving birth" alt="anti stretch mark cream, stretch marks, choose, pregnancy, childbirth, anti stretch cream">Congratulations! You became my mother and one of the most difficult stage of your life - pregnancy - over. Unfortunately, stretch marks on the body remained. We advise you not to delay and as soon as possible to remove them.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Of course, now difficult times - in the hands of your newborn, you&rsquo;re tired, exhausted, and now need to find the time and energy to fight stretch marks.</p>

<p>Not all that bad. In fact, all it did not take much of your time. In general, you should not take this as a &quot;war&quot; against stretch marks. The procedures can be used as the rare moments of relaxation when you are busy only themselves. This is a great opportunity to catch your breath in the hectic first few months after <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/childbirth.html" title="childbirth">childbirth</a>.</p>

<p>Well, if during <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a> you have followed our advice and engaged in the prevention of stretch marks. But even if they could not avoid, get rid of them after delivery possible.</p>

<p>Of course, the list of steps for the elimination of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/best-stretch-marks-creams-for-pregnant-women-how-to-choose-a-popular-brand/" title="stretch marks">stretch marks</a> is not limited by the choice of the best anti stretch mark cream. But in other ways to get rid of them you can find in other sections of the site! Now we will focus on how to choose the right cream for stretch marks after giving birth.</p>

<h2>How to choose a best anti stretch marks creams</h2>

<p>Let us examine what requirements need regulations for stretch marks which you intend to use after pregnancy. There is enough pitfalls.</p>

<p>Firstly, if you are breast-feeding a baby, and stretch marks have appeared in this area, the cream should be safe for a newborn. And it must be harmless both in body contact and do not cause allergies in children who drink milk mom.</p>

<p>For the same reason, most likely, will not work with a strong and cream (or) a pungent odor. Therefore, selecting the best anti stretch mark cream, first find out whether it is hypoallergenic and does not have a strong flavor.</p>

<p>Best of all, even without purchasing the anti stretch mark creams, to hold the sample. Find a store where there is the presence of probes. Well if they give out for free, but in a pinch, and you can buy. Much offensive would happen if you chose an expensive means of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/allergology/allergy.html" title="allergy">allergy</a>. Spread the anti stretch mark cream on the skin site. If during the day is no allergic reaction has not appeared - that this cream is safe for you.</p>

<p>The next item - the cream should be suitable for the time of use. There are anti stretch mark creams that can be used immediately after birth. And there are those that are recommended to apply to the skin a few months after birth. Note that. Mix funds. Start with one that is safe to use immediately after birth and go on a more serious money later. Of course it would be better if the cream will be the same make and brand.</p>

<p>Choose a cream for a specific type of stretch marks. If you have any stretch marks on thighs, do not try to eliminate them with a cream designed to combat stretch marks on the abdomen. Pay attention to the fact against any problem areas focused cream.</p>

<p>If you have stretch marks in several places, each zone may need your vehicle. In this case, too, it is desirable to use products of one brand.</p>

<h2>Deciphering the composition cream</h2>

<p>And now try to understand the composition of selected tools and understand the role played by each of the components. And that should be present in a good anti stretch marks creams.</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>Retinol.</strong> This ingredient has to be in each of the anti stretch marks cream after giving birth. It is responsible for the regeneration and constant hydration of your skin.</li>
<li><strong>Collagen and elastin.</strong> Protein molecules directly responsible for the elasticity of the skin and its renewal. That decrease in their development as a result of hormonal changes and often leads to stretch marks.</li>
<li><strong>Jojoba oil and Shea.</strong> These two components significantly improves blood circulation in the skin. They can be found in almost any means of best anti stretch marks or cellulite cream.</li>
<li><strong>Essential oils.</strong> Various different oils for the skin, but they improve the total weight of the metabolism in the skin and increase the elasticity.</li>
<li><strong>Vitamins and <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids/" title="amino acids">amino acids</a>.</strong> Prerequisites that feed the skin and promote the rapid regeneration.</li>
</ul>


<p>List of different means of stretching with reviews, features description, composition and other important data can be found in the section Means against stretch marks.</p>

<h2>How to use a anti stretch marks cream</h2>

<p>A few tips on proper use of anti stretch mark cream.</p>

<p>Firstly, the cream should be applied to clean and dry skin. If you take a shower or bath, before it should be carefully wipe. In general, the adoption of water treatments (eg, contrast shower) before applying the best anti stretch mark creams after giving birth, if not necessary, it is desirable.</p>

<p>Typically, the cream is applied twice a day - morning and evening. The second time the application is best to plan before you go to bed.</p>

<p>Third, just before rubbing, the skin is better &quot;warm&quot; light massage. This promotes better wicking agent components and increases their efficacy.</p>

<p>The cream is applied in a circular massage until completely absorbed.</p>

<h2>Additional ways to deal with stretch marks</h2>

<p>As we wrote above, other ways of dealing with stretch marks after giving birth you can find in the relevant sections of the site. Yet, briefly enumerate what other steps to take if you seriously want to get rid of stretch marks after pregnancy.</p>

<p>Massage areas with stretch marks. This procedure is best done using a chosen using the tips in this article means.</p>

<p>Contrast showers and swimming. This practice is great affect on the skin. It helps strengthen blood circulation in the subcutaneous tissue and make the skin more elastic.</p>

<p>Physical exercises. One of the main ways to get rid of stretch marks. Exercising helps your muscles to keep the skin toned and helps to regenerate tissue in it.</p>

<p>The use of essential oils as a massage, and special baths. We have a special article on the application of essential oils pregnant. It must be remembered that this method has contraindications.</p>

<p>To consume the necessary amount of water. Often, problems with the skin and the appearance of stretch marks due to the low water content in the body. The skin becomes more fragile and prone to damage. And most importantly - the water out of the body and subcutaneous tissue hazardous substances.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
