<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Health-and-beauty | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/health-and-beauty/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-01-11T22:26:00+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove the Thighs?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-remove-the-thighs/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-11T15:57:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-remove-the-thighs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-remove-the-thighs/img.jpg" title="How to remove the thighs?" alt="how to remove the thighs in a week">Let&rsquo;s face it: most normal men do not like fat women&rsquo;s thighs. Maybe a huge ass resembles the consistency of jelly, a decoration for female hippo, but not for normal Russian women. With thighs need to do something about it, otherwise you will soon not be able to leave the house because they do not fit through the doorway. Believe me, the skirt is not fastened, not because she sat down after washing. The problem is not in the clothes, you just ate too long and heated for three ass on the couch instead of sitting on a diet and regularly move.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>You can not only remove fat from the thighs, therefore, to remove the thighs, you have to lose weight. Start exercise. Join a fitness club, to work under the supervision of professional trainers. These are experienced people who know how fast you drive away with three sweat, and along with the fat thighs. Do not be ashamed of his fat ass. Believe me, you will not be alone. Next you will be engaged in such an aunt, next to which you feel Thumbelina.</p>

<p>If you are torn complexes, and you do not want to show others their fat thighs, practicing <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="at home">at home</a>. But remember, in this case, you will be more difficult to achieve the expected result. Too low load will not bring the desired effect. If you on the contrary, will overload the muscles, they increase in volume, and in spite of reducing the amount of fat thighs become even thicker.</p>

<p>Great impact on your figure light exercise - walking, dancing, swimming. You will spend more time on them, but the results are sure you will enjoy. With them, you will not build muscle mass, but spent most amount of calories that allow you to lose weight. Lose weight, you remove not only the thighs and belly.</p>

<h2>Stop overeating</h2>

<p>If you are keen to remove the thighs, from this point on your favorite delicacy should be cucumbers, tomatoes and cabbage. Forget about the sweets. For years, you catered to his stomach, ignoring the interests of the hips. Is it any wonder that the thighs swollen with jealousy? Now you have to take care of them, and it will have to severely limit your daily diet.</p>

<p>Eat as little as possible carbohydrate foods. You should also limit the intake of fats. Against the background of such a diet is necessary to increase the protein content in the diet. So you have <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="every day">every day</a> to eat meat, fish, dairy products.</p>

<p>Surely you will torment hunger. You can get rid of it using anorectics drugs. If you do not want to poison your body with pills, you can use other methods. They are also effective, and totally free of charge:</p>

<ul>
<li>Eat raw fruits and vegetables;</li>
<li>Distracts from the food with the help of interesting activities or entertainment;</li>
<li>Hang in the kitchen designs, cause you disgust (worms, feces, human entrails, etc.);</li>
<li>Take a picture of your fat thighs and hang the picture on the fridge.</li>
</ul>


<p>They say that massage promotes <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>. Allegedly, on the one hand, it improves blood circulation, stimulating fat burning, and with another - leads to a decrease in the problem areas of the body due to mechanical action hand massage. Do not believe, you do not lose weight from massage. Still, this procedure can have a positive impact on the size of your thighs.</p>

<p>Even if you spend days aged in the massage table, exposing her ass skillful hands of a masseur, you still can not lose weight. But over time, get rid of cellulite. In addition, by improving the microcirculation and eliminate venous stasis of tissue accumulated leave them liquid.</p>

<p>Simply put, the swelling will go away. That they bear part of the blame for the fact that your thighs covered with orange peel. That swelling make your ass look even thicker than it actually is.</p>

<p>How to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="choose">choose</a> a massage? The interior offers a lot of options: hardware, vacuum, manual, honey, anti-cellulite&hellip; Choose any, they all give the same result. Perhaps a more pronounced effect you get from the anti-cellulite massage. But keep in mind that after a week you will groan, sitting on a chair. During the procedure, you feel as if the skin is separated from the body, and after the massage thighs covered with bruises. However, the beauty demands victims. Other types of massage differ in the way of, but not on the end result. Choose one that will be more enjoyable for you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Belly Massage for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/belly-massage-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-08T11:18:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/belly-massage-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/belly-massage-for-weight-loss/img.jpg" title="WBelly massage for weight loss" alt="belly massage for weight loss at home"><strong>Massage</strong> - a method that has long been in service with the conventional medicine. It is approved by the Ministry of Health, and is used to treat a huge number of diseases. Of course, as an auxiliary method of therapy. Massage is used in virtually all areas of medicine. He is firmly entrenched in our lives, and probably in the world there is not one person who would never lay on a massage table.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>The effectiveness of massage</h2>

<p>The effectiveness of massage has long been proved. It can help you improve the condition of the patient, regardless of the disease, which he suffers. However, the inability of the placebo-controlled studies leaves some doubt as to the mechanism of its effects. Which factor plays the most important role: the psychological or physiological? What makes a person feel relieved: relaxation and faith in the healing power of massage or mechanical effect on the soft tissues of the body?</p>

<p>This question remains open for the time being. We are interested in, whether it is possible with the help of abdominal massage to lose at least a few kilograms? Agree, it would be great: no need to starve, no strain, just lie down on the table, belly up, and wait for someone skilled hands make short work of your fat. Is it possible? Let&rsquo;s deal.</p>

<p>All the effects of the massage can be divided into psychological and physiological. The first is certainly very useful, but are unlikely to have a specific and predictable effect on the weight of your body. Therefore, it makes no sense to consider them, go directly to the physiological. We will not engage in speculation, use a pseudo-data, for example, on energy currents - too. That&rsquo;s the impact on the human body has a significantly abdominal massage:</p>

<ul>
<li>Warms the skin due to emitted as a result of mechanical friction heat;</li>
<li>Stimulates the microcirculation of the skin by heating;</li>
<li>It stimulates the flow of lymph and venous blood due to mechanical compression of blood vessels;</li>
<li>Relaxes the muscles by mechanical action on them, as well as enhance blood flow.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Belly massage and weight loss</h2>

<p>Which of these mechanisms, in your opinion, can contribute to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>? Let&rsquo;s look at them all in turn.</p>

<p>Obviously, warm skin of the abdomen can not dissolve fat. It does not melt like wax, so the effect of massage is unlikely to reduce the weight of your body. Judge for yourself if the increase in skin temperature contribute to weight loss, for the acquisition of a slim figure you would rather stick a couple of yellow cards in the stomach, or heat it with an ordinary table lamp. From the sea, everything is back to not only rested, but also slim, because the fat left on the beach not only the stomach, but also from the entire body.</p>

<p>The skin temperature increases by touching hand massage, so the blood vessels dilate to give away excess heat. This is one of the mechanisms of thermoregulation, protects the body from overheating. Due to dilation of small blood vessels nutrition improves soft tissues, primarily the skin. Does this mean that fat belly will start to leave? No, otherwise all alcoholics with red faces would not wear belly in his hands, and would look more slender birch. Medicines from the group of proofreaders microcirculation, led by pentoxifylline, have themselves become popular drugs for weight loss.</p>

<p>This effect helps to eliminate stagnant lymph and venous blood. Thus, the massage display allows the liquid that has accumulated in the soft tissues. Perhaps it is this feature made people consider massage as a regular method of losing weight. <strong><em>Firstly</em></strong>, with the fluid leaves the body weight, that causes a person to believe that massage helped him to break down fat. <strong><em>Second</em></strong>, visually stomach becomes more flat. This is due to improvement of the skin and removal of liquid. <strong><em>Third</em></strong>, the possible reduction in waist circumference, again, due to the removal of edema.</p>

<p>At the young age of these effects may not occur at all, or to be mild, but after 40 years, when the body breaks down the balance of hormones, a change in metabolism, fluid accumulates more actively. Accordingly, massage is more effective way to reduce body weight. Of course, the effect of massage is very useful for the figure. But make no mistake, the fat remains in place, leaving only water.</p>

<p>Surprisingly, making the opposite action, a lot of people waiting to get on the output a result. Shaking the press, they are straining the abdominal muscles, hoping to lose weight. Visiting massage people relax the same muscle groups, waiting for an identical effect - weight loss. So what still needs to be done with the muscles? Perhaps, after all, cut, and as often as possible. If muscle relaxation accompanied by weight loss, people have lost weight during the holidays. To enhance the effect, he tried to muscle relaxants and antispasmodics - drugs that reduce muscle tone.</p>

<p>Lose weight with the help of belly massage can be in only one case: if you are doing it yourself. And preferably more than once per day. Massage takes away a lot of strength and energy, so you&rsquo;ll save calories, and with them - the extra weight. But lying on the table and making the masseur knead your stomach, you just get rid of the money that paid for his services. Of excess weight - is unlikely.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing a Anti Stretch Marks Cream After Giving Birth]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-06T11:50:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/img.jpg" width="250" title="Choosing a cream for stretch marks after giving birth" alt="anti stretch mark cream, stretch marks, choose, pregnancy, childbirth, anti stretch cream">Congratulations! You became my mother and one of the most difficult stage of your life - pregnancy - over. Unfortunately, stretch marks on the body remained. We advise you not to delay and as soon as possible to remove them.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Of course, now difficult times - in the hands of your newborn, you&rsquo;re tired, exhausted, and now need to find the time and energy to fight stretch marks.</p>

<p>Not all that bad. In fact, all it did not take much of your time. In general, you should not take this as a &quot;war&quot; against stretch marks. The procedures can be used as the rare moments of relaxation when you are busy only themselves. This is a great opportunity to catch your breath in the hectic first few months after <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/childbirth.html" title="childbirth">childbirth</a>.</p>

<p>Well, if during <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a> you have followed our advice and engaged in the prevention of stretch marks. But even if they could not avoid, get rid of them after delivery possible.</p>

<p>Of course, the list of steps for the elimination of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/best-stretch-marks-creams-for-pregnant-women-how-to-choose-a-popular-brand/" title="stretch marks">stretch marks</a> is not limited by the choice of the best anti stretch mark cream. But in other ways to get rid of them you can find in other sections of the site! Now we will focus on how to choose the right cream for stretch marks after giving birth.</p>

<h2>How to choose a best anti stretch marks creams</h2>

<p>Let us examine what requirements need regulations for stretch marks which you intend to use after pregnancy. There is enough pitfalls.</p>

<p>Firstly, if you are breast-feeding a baby, and stretch marks have appeared in this area, the cream should be safe for a newborn. And it must be harmless both in body contact and do not cause allergies in children who drink milk mom.</p>

<p>For the same reason, most likely, will not work with a strong and cream (or) a pungent odor. Therefore, selecting the best anti stretch mark cream, first find out whether it is hypoallergenic and does not have a strong flavor.</p>

<p>Best of all, even without purchasing the anti stretch mark creams, to hold the sample. Find a store where there is the presence of probes. Well if they give out for free, but in a pinch, and you can buy. Much offensive would happen if you chose an expensive means of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/allergology/allergy.html" title="allergy">allergy</a>. Spread the anti stretch mark cream on the skin site. If during the day is no allergic reaction has not appeared - that this cream is safe for you.</p>

<p>The next item - the cream should be suitable for the time of use. There are anti stretch mark creams that can be used immediately after birth. And there are those that are recommended to apply to the skin a few months after birth. Note that. Mix funds. Start with one that is safe to use immediately after birth and go on a more serious money later. Of course it would be better if the cream will be the same make and brand.</p>

<p>Choose a cream for a specific type of stretch marks. If you have any stretch marks on thighs, do not try to eliminate them with a cream designed to combat stretch marks on the abdomen. Pay attention to the fact against any problem areas focused cream.</p>

<p>If you have stretch marks in several places, each zone may need your vehicle. In this case, too, it is desirable to use products of one brand.</p>

<h2>Deciphering the composition cream</h2>

<p>And now try to understand the composition of selected tools and understand the role played by each of the components. And that should be present in a good anti stretch marks creams.</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>Retinol.</strong> This ingredient has to be in each of the anti stretch marks cream after giving birth. It is responsible for the regeneration and constant hydration of your skin.</li>
<li><strong>Collagen and elastin.</strong> Protein molecules directly responsible for the elasticity of the skin and its renewal. That decrease in their development as a result of hormonal changes and often leads to stretch marks.</li>
<li><strong>Jojoba oil and Shea.</strong> These two components significantly improves blood circulation in the skin. They can be found in almost any means of best anti stretch marks or cellulite cream.</li>
<li><strong>Essential oils.</strong> Various different oils for the skin, but they improve the total weight of the metabolism in the skin and increase the elasticity.</li>
<li><strong>Vitamins and <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids/" title="amino acids">amino acids</a>.</strong> Prerequisites that feed the skin and promote the rapid regeneration.</li>
</ul>


<p>List of different means of stretching with reviews, features description, composition and other important data can be found in the section Means against stretch marks.</p>

<h2>How to use a anti stretch marks cream</h2>

<p>A few tips on proper use of anti stretch mark cream.</p>

<p>Firstly, the cream should be applied to clean and dry skin. If you take a shower or bath, before it should be carefully wipe. In general, the adoption of water treatments (eg, contrast shower) before applying the best anti stretch mark creams after giving birth, if not necessary, it is desirable.</p>

<p>Typically, the cream is applied twice a day - morning and evening. The second time the application is best to plan before you go to bed.</p>

<p>Third, just before rubbing, the skin is better &quot;warm&quot; light massage. This promotes better wicking agent components and increases their efficacy.</p>

<p>The cream is applied in a circular massage until completely absorbed.</p>

<h2>Additional ways to deal with stretch marks</h2>

<p>As we wrote above, other ways of dealing with stretch marks after giving birth you can find in the relevant sections of the site. Yet, briefly enumerate what other steps to take if you seriously want to get rid of stretch marks after pregnancy.</p>

<p>Massage areas with stretch marks. This procedure is best done using a chosen using the tips in this article means.</p>

<p>Contrast showers and swimming. This practice is great affect on the skin. It helps strengthen blood circulation in the subcutaneous tissue and make the skin more elastic.</p>

<p>Physical exercises. One of the main ways to get rid of stretch marks. Exercising helps your muscles to keep the skin toned and helps to regenerate tissue in it.</p>

<p>The use of essential oils as a massage, and special baths. We have a special article on the application of essential oils pregnant. It must be remembered that this method has contraindications.</p>

<p>To consume the necessary amount of water. Often, problems with the skin and the appearance of stretch marks due to the low water content in the body. The skin becomes more fragile and prone to damage. And most importantly - the water out of the body and subcutaneous tissue hazardous substances.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Lose Weight at Home?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-05T08:48:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/img.jpg" title="rapid weight loss, how to lose weight fast at home, rope, exercise for weight loss and press" alt="How to lose weight at home?">It&rsquo;s not a secret that proper healthy diet is essential for maintaining the health and control their weight. To overcome the overweight should be, above all, to overcome their bad eating habits, such as overeating, eating before going to sleep, irregular eating, eating unhealthy foods. Remember that the stomach - a hollow muscular organ that easily expands as binge eating, and later - in the normal diet in order to achieve a sense of saturation required to eat large amounts of food, because the stomach is already &quot;accustomed&quot; to be stretched. Consumption while healthy but high-calorie foods in quantities exceeding the energy intake necessary for you daily energy requirement, a sedentary lifestyle, low physical activity also contribute to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>. Therefore, to maintain a slim figure of the ideal need to eat regularly and properly balanced, and exercise more.</p>

<!--more-->


<p><strong>Willpower and mood of success</strong> - your first allies in the difficult task to lose weight. There should be a clear desire to get rid of the extra kilos. Do not give up until you shake the ill-fated arrow on the mechanical balance in the smaller side, or until crawl down the numbers on the display of electronic scales.</p>

<p><strong>Learn to say a firm &quot;no&quot; to temptation</strong> and fast food, but, unfortunately, bad nutrition. Before you succumb to the temptation to buy a pizza, sugary sodas, delicious fries, a double burger with cheese or soft flour cakes, bathed in chocolate - think about the number of calories that are contained in them and imagine how they will be stored in the fat folds of your limp body.</p>

<p>Eat <strong>more foods with dietary fiber</strong>. They give food volume contribute to the rapid filling of the stomach and thus less food will cause a feeling of fullness in the brain. In addition, dietary fiber contribute to the removal of toxic products of metabolism from the gut, serve as a substrate for the intestinal flora, stool form, in part serve as prevention of unpleasant intestinal conditions like <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/constipation.html" title="constipation">constipation</a> and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/diarrhea.html" title="diarrhea">diarrhea</a>. Where to contain dietary fiber? Vegetables, fruits, bran, cereals, wholemeal bread. All of these products can and should be consumed in large quantities under the emergency measures for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> at home.</p>

<p>Wash consumed foods. <strong>Drink plenty of fluids</strong>, because the water speeds up metabolism and promotes breeding and disposal of harmful metabolic products in the urine, feces, evaporation through the surface of the skin (sweating) and lungs. Drinking water reduces hunger and helps <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a>. Remember that an adequate daily fluid intake is the key to the proper functioning of the internal organs of the human body, especially the liver.</p>

<p>Part of the daily routine should be a morning <strong>exercise, stretching, exercises with weights</strong>, and better training on a stationary bike or treadmill - on any simulator that you can install at home. It would be even better to regularly engage in gyms, make daily walks and engage in a variety of active sports.</p>

<p>Remember that any kind of mental pressure lead to the emergence of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a> and even <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/depression.html" title="depression">depression</a>. Stress, in turn, can lead to <strong>emotional overeating</strong>. So try not to be nervous, overexcited and do not take to heart the negative attitudes of other individuals. A good practice would be breathing exercises, such as, for example, deep breaths, different meditation technique, oriental health exercises. Do not forget about the rest. Remember that proper rest (not a computer screen) currently has therapeutic effects on the body. The same applies to bed. You must sleep at least 7 hours a day.</p>

<p>What else can be done at home for a successful weight loss? Remember that <strong>you need not only eat well, but also regularly</strong>. Eat 5 times a day in small portions, rather than 2-3 times larger. Perfect breakfast should be low calorie, low fat and high content of dietary fiber. For lunch, eat anything, the main thing that it was useful and tasty (do not forget to enjoy a healthy meal). Do not wait with dinner. The evening meal should be completed in 2-3 hours before bedtime. Do not forget that the number of calories consumed can be reduced by increasing the content of fruits and vegetables in the diet, but they also contain large amounts of vitamins and minerals.</p>

<p>So remember that your daily energy expenditure in the <strong>form of exercise</strong> must exceed the consumption of food in terms of kilocalories contained therein. Unfortunately, however, the intensity of modern life does not always give us the opportunity to be engaged enough in gyms, leisure or sports outside the home, so why do not we engage in more physical activity where we spend about half of my life - that is the house? But in any case, do not take physical exercise as a burden his duties enthusiastically approach to employment, involve family members, including your favorite TV channel or the necessary music. And finally, here are 9 public exercises which you can do at home without having to buy special equipment or equipment:</p>

<ul>
<li><em>Walks around the house (walking):</em> This is the best kind of exercise, you generally do not need to do this only functioning legs. However, if you live in a cramped home, or if the weather is really very good, you can take the opportunity to walking on the street. Necessarily involve your home for this event. Even banal raising and lowering the stairs leading to tone your muscles.</li>
<li><em>Jumping rope:</em> it is itself energy-intensive way of exercise and an occasion for pleasant childhood memories of girls.</li>
<li><em>Ups:</em> Although this type of exercise is given quite difficult, many people prefer push-ups, because they are well trained muscles in the arms and shoulders.</li>
<li><em>Lifting legs:</em> the perfect exercise to strengthen the muscles of the lower extremities and abdomen. For best results, you want to raise the straight legs, but if you feel that it is very difficult, it is possible to bend them a little.</li>
<li><em>Lift the body to the knees from a prone position on the back:</em> This type of exercise is essential for abdominal exercise. Down with flabby abdominal wall with large accumulations of fat! Long live the &quot;cubes&quot;! Cheers &quot;cubes&quot;! By the way, &quot;blocks&quot; are formed by constrictions tendon rectus abdominis muscle, so you need to train this muscle. Just remember that the cubes can be seen when the fat content in the body is about 10% lower.</li>
<li><em>Sports running:</em> very good exercise to train the cardiovascular and respiratory systems, as well as to optimize the consumption of calories. Everyone can jogging or even brisk walking, while listening to the radio, music or just enjoying nature. The only thing you need - a couple of good shoes, and, of course, a strong belief in getting rid of unnecessary kilograms.</li>
<li><em>Squat:</em> have a striking impact on glutes and leg muscles. Even better would be if you crouch not alone, but in company with two charming brunette - dumbbells and Rosa Clara.</li>
<li><em>Weightlifting:</em> if you are a girl and did not want to spend money to buy glamorous dumbbell, you can start to lift weights that are easy to get at home - a laptop man, iron, grown fat cat, two-liter bottle of Coca-Cola (stop, people dumping kilograms, there should be no sugary sodas in the fridge) and large capacity air-conditioned for the washing machine (it is convenient to do just to lift).</li>
<li><em>Dance:</em> yes, dance - it is also an interesting exercise. They increase the speed of your metabolism and give a sense of overall satisfaction.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gone Month After Weight Loss. How to Restore the Month Following the Diet?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-05T08:35:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/menstruation-after-weight-loss/img.jpg" title="title" alt="alt">This problem is very common among girls, too much carried away by losing weight. Heavy training in the gym, wasting the minimum calorie diet, unbalanced power - all this, acting together, can disrupt the hormonal balance of the female body and lead to amenorrhea - the cessation of menstruation. Their absence is a sign of serious damage to health and can cause other, more terrible consequences. So, if the problem you have encountered, you should take as soon as possible for its decision.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The normal termination of a woman&rsquo;s menstruation should occur only in 45-55 years, when she, because of age, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/menopause.html" title="menopause">menopause</a>. In younger years cycle disorders are a symptom of a more or less serious violations.</p>

<p>Some girls are easy enough to react to the fact that <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/body-wraps-for-weight-loss-belly/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> after they begin the long delays or even complete absence of menstruation. This is probably due to all the well-known myth, if sportswomen month did not happen. However, in reality, only to suffer a similar professional athletes, usually engaged in power sports, and often taking specific means to improve their physical condition, such as steroids. At the same time, they make a conscious choice between sports achievements and his health - in favor of the first, as you may have guessed.</p>

<p>You do not engage in professional sports, but just decided to lose a few pounds, so you should not be like this. Maybe for you, even absence of menstruation seems convenient, but keep in mind that it is able to do a lot of damage to health.</p>

<p>If you are a long time did not receive a sufficient amount of food nutrients, it could contribute to the emergence of anemia, disturbance of the production of sex hormones, changes in metabolism, resulting in a disruption of the normal functioning of the ovaries. At first it is fixable, but then atrophy and other changes in the reproductive system are becoming more stable and may even be irreversible.</p>

<p>Significantly it is not proved, but experts believe that, given the long absence of menstruation due to weight loss, women may develop complications. Moreover, their appearance is possible even if the cycle is still possible to recover. In particular, the likelihood of complications include dishormonal disorders: dysfunctional uterine <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/injuries-and-accidents/bleeding.html" title="bleeding">bleeding</a>, the development of hormone-dependent benign tumors, polycystic ovaries, and cysts. Ultimately, in particularly serious cases, this can lead to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/infertility.html" title="infertility">infertility</a>.</p>

<p>The key point for safe weight loss - it is a slow or moderate speed weight loss. If you are struggling to the results &quot;minus 30 kg per month&quot;, and ready for this fast and torturing your body unbearable load it one way or another will have an effect: someone - a stomach ulcer, someone - violations of the cycle.</p>

<p>The second rule, which will save you from the problems of women&rsquo;s health - is striving for a balanced diet, even against the background diet. In particular, you even in small amounts, but should eat fat-containing animal products, because it is based on <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a>, which you are so afraid, are built molecule hormones. This does not mean that you can not use a mono-diet, or fat-free diet, simply by practice over several days rather than months in a row.</p>

<h2>What should I do to restore menstruation?</h2>

<p>Take action, and fast. Of course, the emergence of amenorrhea on the background of weight loss does not require as much emergency treatment to the doctor, as a traumatic brain injury, or other medical emergency, but to think you should not spend more than a week.</p>

<p>It is desirable to bring to the solution of the problem of a specialist. If you do not understand, which is why it&rsquo;s happened, he will explain the reason for cessation of menstruation, to recommend changes in diet and prescribe drugs for the treatment. It will be hormonal. Do not be afraid of what you prescribe them because now they are needed. Artificial hormones entering the body, will lead to the cyclic operation of the reproductive organs and quickly restore cycle. In a few months you will be able to give them up.</p>

<p>You can also simultaneously - not as a basis, in the form of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/aids.html" title="aids">aids</a>! - To use national treatment. As the herbs that have a positive impact on women&rsquo;s health are known upland uterus, lovage, chamomile, parsley. Their decoctions and infusions is also possible to use if you do not have contraindications to herbal medicine, in particular <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/allergology/allergy.html" title="allergy">allergy</a> to grass.</p>

<p>So, if on the background of intensive weight loss you have gone monthly, restore them as soon as possible. Doing this is through a combination of good nutrition, medication, prescribed by a physician, and, if desired, the use of aids. Even if you have not yet reached their ultimate goal in losing weight, you better time to interrupt this process and pay attention to their health. Let this situation will give you some lessons and will help you understand that you can not scoff at his body with impunity. Hopefully, you will restore your health, and in the future, you will not be so foolish to strive for weight loss.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
