<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Health-and-beauty | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/health-and-beauty/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2017-03-13T17:16:21+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Quickly and Properly Lose Weight by Summer]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-quickly-and-properly-lose-weight-by-summer/"/>
    <updated>2017-03-12T16:17:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-quickly-and-properly-lose-weight-by-summer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-quickly-and-properly-lose-weight-by-summer/img.jpg" alt="How to quickly and properly lose weight by summer">Very soon, there will come a season of short skirts, swimsuits and beach photos in social networks. In order to look good in these photos, you need to prepare your body in advance for the summer.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Schedule work front</h2>

<p>Do not expect a miracle. Training for a couple of weeks before the summer, no matter how intense they may be, will not bring any result - only disorders. You need to lose weight in a complex and in advance. And it&rsquo;s better not to start on Monday, but right now. Determine how much you need to lose by the summer - 5 kg, 10 or all 20. And starting from this, make your plan - yourself or with your personal trainer. We need to set ourselves tasks for each week and strive to fulfill them. To control the process of losing weight and provide additional motivation, you can take photos once a week in full growth.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<h2>Healthy food</h2>

<p>You can believe in fairy tales as much as you want, that there are miraculous ways to lose weight without diets, but this is not so. Proper <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-on-cellulose/" title="nutrition">nutrition</a> - in itself already a kind of diet for the body, which is used to chips, chocolates and fried potatoes with ketchup. Therefore, we must abandon the sweet, flour, roast and smoked in favor of products containing protein, as well as herbs, cereals, vegetables and fruits.</p>

<p>The golden rule of a <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/pineapple-diet/" title="healthy">healthy diet</a> is regularity. You need to clearly divide your diet for breakfast, lunch and dinner and give up snacks. If the appetite has greatly developed, you can eat an apple, carrots or just drink a glass of water or a cup of tea.</p>

<p>Also it is necessary to refuse fast food. Dishes cooked with their own hands are more useful, but this requires strength and time, which is not always enough. Instead of buying a cake in the store, it is worth trying a couple of times to cook it in your kitchen. Most likely, this process will seem too laborious for you, and the cake itself will not be so much wanted.</p>

<h2>Doing sports</h2>

<p>One correct diet is not enough. Physical loads will accelerate the process of losing weight and make you more enduring. The easiest option is to buy a subscription for a couple of months in the fitness center. The administrator will help you to create a convenient schedule. Two or three classes a week will be enough to throw off a few kilograms by the summer. In addition, fitness centers can be used not only on simulators. Choose any sport that is closer to you, for example, swimming or aerobics. Girls can sign up for yoga, body-ballet or another kind of dance, where you need to move a lot. If you want to not lose weight, and adjust your <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/" title="figure">figure</a>, it is best to hire a personal trainer who has drawn up a plan of classes and tells you how to eat.</p>

<p>If there is no possibility to go to group or individual lessons, you can go in for sports yourself. On the Internet there is a huge number of master classes from fitness trainers, which will show what exercises you need to perform to achieve your goal. Nobody canceled the old and effective way - morning runs in the park before work and banal exercises in the morning.</p>

<h2>Lead a healthy lifestyle</h2>

<p>A healthy lifestyle is not only about proper nutrition and exercise. To lose weight, you must abandon the frequent use of alcohol. Smoking also does not help losing weight. Ideal - completely get rid of this addiction, or at least significantly reduce the number of cigarettes smoked per day.</p>

<p>People are surrounded by a huge number of irritating factors, not contributing to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/watermelon-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>. It is better to try once again to avoid <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a>, at least for the sake of your figure. And, finally, you need to sleep enough to have a good mood and enough strength to exercise.</p>

<h2>Massages, baths and creams</h2>

<p>Many go to the masseurs, to the sauna or buy expensive cream in the hope of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="rapid weight loss">rapid weight loss</a> without any effort. All this is effective only in conjunction with proper nutrition and exercise. By themselves, these methods are useless and will not yield a significant result.</p>

<p>It is worth to be afraid of various &quot;teas&quot;  for losing weight. No matter how they are advertised in social networks, at best, such a tea will contain diuretics that will simply remove water from the body, at worst - narcotic drugs.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diet for the Skin]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-for-the-skin/"/>
    <updated>2017-02-25T18:50:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-for-the-skin</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/diet-for-the-skin/img.jpg" alt="Diet for the skin">
There are contraindications, consult your doctor.</p>

<p>Every woman wants to have a clean, beautiful, well-groomed, youthful skin. The youngest must be skin on the face, as her <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="every day">every day</a> see the surrounding. To be beautiful, a woman uses cosmetics and skin care products, but this is not always enough. To skin remains smooth and youthful, you need proper <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-on-cellulose/" title="nutrition">nutrition</a>.</p>

<!--more-->




<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Usually <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/" title="diet">diet</a> does not last long - a week, two weeks, a month, sometimes more. Still, any diet sooner or later ends. For beautiful skin one week or one month is not enough nutrition. Follow dietary recommendations you have for life.</p>

<p>Through nutrition, you can not stop the aging process of your skin. You still will be wrinkles, whatever you do. Nature is relentless, and with the passage of time it takes away from the <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet/" title="beauty">beauty</a> of women. But for sure you pay attention, that in 50 years, a woman looks like an old woman, while for the other, the same age as her, still invited on a date a man.</p>

<p>Someone facial skin aging earlier, and someone later. Diet - is one of the ways to keep the skin in good condition. You should consume enough of:</p>

<ol>
<li><p><strong>Vitamins</strong>. Have you ever noticed that the writing on the banks with vitamins pharmaceutical companies? Usually there can be read, that multivitamin preparation will improve the condition of your skin. However, the vitamins can be obtained not only from the cans. They are full of in food. Eat more vegetables, fruits. Regularly eat liver - it has accumulated a huge amount of vitamins.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Water</strong>. When the body lacks fluids, skin becomes dry, limp, ugly. It is necessary to drink water regularly. If your body is constantly in a state of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/dehydration.html" title="dehydration">dehydration</a>, the skin of your face will quickly become flabby and wrinkled.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>PUFAs</strong>. Polyunsaturated fatty acids should be present continuously in the diet. The use flaxseed oil and fish as their source.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Iron</strong>. Do not iron deficiency in the body. It is part of the protein hemoglobin, which carries oxygen. Naturally, the chronic oxygen <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/starvation.html" title="starvation">starvation</a> of the skin over time is not well reflected in your face. Iron is found in:</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Antioxidants</strong>. The substances that destroy free radicals, slow down skin aging. Therefore, your diet must be present in large quantities fruits contain antioxidants in abundance. Many of them also present in green tea.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>Women with problem skin constantly have to deal with the emerging pigmentation in the face, red spots, inflammatory elements. She sweats, gaining weight, and shows the black dots and white pimples. To face skin looked normal, you need to use cosmetics, do cosmetic procedures. But diet is also able to assist in the fight against skin problems.</p>

<p>The following products should be restricted:</p>

<ol>
<li><p><strong>Sweets</strong>. It is believed that the confectionery increase the likelihood of skin inflammatory elements. It is not known, however, these or not. But in any case, limit sweets will not be superfluous, since it is well reflected not only on the face, but also in the <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/" title="figure">figure</a>.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Water in the evening</strong>. Water is essential to the skin of the face lacked moisture. It should not dry. But excess water in the evening will cause swelling on the face in the morning. The more frequently in the morning you will suffer from edema, the faster you will have wrinkles. Therefore, from late teas should be abandoned.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Alcohol</strong>. Alcoholic drinks are harmful to all organs and systems. Of course, alcohol and harm the skin. If you do not believe me, look, it looks like the skin of women who abuse alcohol. 40 They are worse than some 60.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Coffee</strong>. On some sites, you can read that coffee appear on the skin pigmentation. Apparently, this assumption is due to the black beverage. It is unlikely that coffee you will have pigmentation on the face. But for problem skin drink it is harmful, because it enhances the separation of sebum.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Sol</strong>. From her appear edema. For this reason, if you have problem skin, better to limit the intake of salt. This does not mean that you should eat salted insufficiently dishes. Just give up salted fish, chips, cheese suluguni and other products containing salt in excessive quantities.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>There diet for cleaning intestines, kidneys, blood, or whole organism. Diet for cleansing the face too. Another thing is how effective it is? A woman who wants to clean the skin, it is recommended to use:</p>

<p>There are diets that have a duration of 3, 7 or 10 days, and the alleged need to make your skin cleaner. In fact, to purify it, it is not enough food. To do this, you need:</p>

<ul>
<li>treating the skin with special lotions;</li>
<li>visit a beautician and perform cleaning procedures.</li>
</ul>


<p>None of these products, you make eating the skin of your face clean. First of all, you should pay attention to skin care and lifestyle that you lead.</p>

<p>Oily skin - a real problem for women. It should not just wipe the face with a napkin, as a person immediately becomes unkempt appearance. For oily skin, constantly emerging inflammatory elements, and it can not please women. Unfortunately, this problem can not be solved with diet. The skin does not become less oily, if you limit the amount of fat in their diets.</p>

<p><em>You may want to reduce the consumption of the following products:</em></p>

<p>Theoretically, such a diet can make your skin a little less fatty. But in practice, no significant difference you will likely not see. Therefore, use cosmetics, drugs to reduce sebum production, regularly visit a beautician. The only way to significantly reduce the oiliness of the skin and the amount of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/acne.html" title="acne">acne</a> on the face.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove Stretch Marks on Thighs&#58; Change Life for the Better]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-remove-stretch-marks-on-thighs-change-life-for-the-better/"/>
    <updated>2016-07-03T18:46:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-remove-stretch-marks-on-thighs-change-life-for-the-better</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-remove-stretch-marks-on-thighs-change-life-for-the-better/img1.jpg" alt="How to remove stretch marks on thighs">The reasons for the appearance of stretch marks on thighs a lot of pregnancy, hormonal changes the body during adolescence maturing, a sharp weight gain or weight loss. In addition to this disease it may be associated with a genetic predisposition commonplace. How to remove stretch marks on thighs, treatment and causes of the disease - everything is in the article proposed to your attention.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Main reasons for appearance of stretch marks</h2>

<p>Young girls are often scared of such manifestations, think these marks on the skin remain forever and will be very noticeable. But stretch marks that appear on thighs during adolescence is nothing but a small skin&rsquo;s ability to stretch, not in time behind the growth of the organism. Often, a similar phenomenon can be seen at the athletes lift weights. Thus, the main causes of stretch marks:</p>

<ul>
<li>Sudden changes in weight</li>
<li>Changes in hormonal balance: the skin loses its elasticity, thinning, stretch marks appear red (inner anguishes with bright color)</li>
<li>Genetic predisposition</li>
<li>Local blood circulation failures</li>
<li>The strong skin stretching at playing sports, weight lifting.</li>
</ul>


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Causes - it is clear, but it is always more concerned not why there are white stretch marks on thighs, and how to get rid of them. By the way, white stretch marks are often the result of excessive weight: at strong stretching skin overstrain. Blood vessels are emptied over time, changing the red color on white.</p>

<h3>How to remove stretch marks on thighs: simple and affordable ways</h3>

<p>Main remedy for stretch marks on thighs - is the maintenance of elasticity of the skin at any age. Subject to the fluid balance in the body, the use of proper diet and moderate exercising can never worry about stretch marks. But life is making, often <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="stretching occurs during pregnancy">stretching occurs during pregnancy</a>, and women who had gathered to become a mother, it is important to know how to remove stretch marks on thighs.</p>

<p>In the fight for a beautiful body approach absolutely every means, both homemade as well as medication. The problem of disposal should cover the full range of measures, from rubbing to change diet. Only some ointments and creams for stretch marks on thighs do not get rid of. It is important to understand that the poor condition of stretch marks, the more difficult and sometimes impossible to cope with them. However, regular use of the total volume of advice if you remove stretch marks completely, but would make them virtually invisible. There are many ways of treatment. It is necessary to be aware of some of them.</p>

<h4>Available recipes to get rid of stretch marks</h4>

<p>Learn how to remove stretch marks on thighs at home, it is easy, it is important to understand that it requires complete dedication and patience:</p>

<ol>
<li>Use plant extracts, mask and cream for stretch marks on thighs, essential oils, elastin and collagen to maintain balance and prevent stretch marks.</li>
<li>Home remedies - a natural scrubs (salt, caramel, coffee coarser, any stone fruits).</li>
<li>In addition, well help the oils: almond, olive, peach - they need to be rubbed into the already appeared striae and in places of possible manifestations.</li>
<li>Massage - the best and literally a healing agent. Simply stroking while rubbing oils, tougher rubbing or anticellulite massage - all options are suitable here. The main thing - do not be lazy and do it consistently.</li>
</ol>


<p>In addition to knowledge of how to remove stretch marks on thighs, we must also know how to avoid them. And here too there are tricks:</p>

<ul>
<li><p>Train yourself, your body and raise the tone of the skin. Never forget that the skin - this is the only clothes that can not be removed, ironed and darned. When applying the cream, pinch it to enhance absorbency, stroking and patting. Improve skin tone will douches (unless contraindicated). In addition, it is very nice, it is also harden the vessels, burn extra calories and add vitality throughout the body. After such a soul the whole body will be grateful to accept oils, creams and ointments.</p></li>
<li><p>Sport! It&rsquo;s not just life or health, in the case of prevention and the appearance of stretch marks - that&rsquo;s the beauty. Gradually, in small doses, with rest and plenty of approaches begin to engage in physical exercise. Jogging, brisk walking, swimming, skis or roller skates - it is quite easy, it does not take much time and will be an excellent way to deal with stretch marks on thighs.</p></li>
<li><p>Food. The main reason for the appearance of stretch marks is overweight. Review diet. Eat more healthy food with vitamins, minerals and easily digestible. But do not try to lose weight fast, it will not lead to anything good. Find your diet, a balanced diet and to choose the best products to help dietician.</p></li>
</ul>


<p>A healthy lifestyle, exercise, maintenance of skin tone and timely prevention - it is excellent. But even using all possible means, some women are unable to avoid the appearance of stretch marks, and even more to get rid of them. Do not worry. Even if there were stretching on the inner side of the thigh, can reduce their visibility to a minimum, so that they do not cause inconvenience. This is - by any forces of the fair sex.</p>

<p><em>Beauty salons offer a wide range of services for the removal of stretch marks, but the prices of these procedures are very high. But do not despair: the latest developments in the field of cosmetic products can solve the problem in a fairly short time and at home. Emulsions, creams, ointments can be selected in any price range from budget to exclusive brands. Their main action is aimed at improving the blood supply, causing and improves skin tone.</em></p>

<p><strong>Persistently and consistently going to the purpose, do not forget that the class should be regular!</strong> Mirror - here is your main judge in the fight against stretch marks. The slightest change you will see at once, but if extensions do not go to the end - that&rsquo;s no reason to give up. Smartness figure, radiant skin, confident look and optimism - that every woman seeks. And that is what you can get, doing all of the above recommendations.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Rid of Stretch Marks on Breasts and Return the Former Beauty of the Body]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-get-rid-of-stretch-marks-on-breasts-and-return-the-former-beauty-of-the-body/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-26T10:59:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-get-rid-of-stretch-marks-on-breasts-and-return-the-former-beauty-of-the-body</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-get-rid-of-stretch-marks-on-breasts-and-return-the-former-beauty-of-the-body/img.jpg" alt="How to get rid of stretch marks on breasts and return the former beauty of the body">How to get rid of stretch marks on breasts we describe here. All women want to have beautiful skin of the breast, which in fact is not surprising and fine. Most breast skin spoil streamers, which are the majority of women. In medicine, they are called striae, they appear due to the excessively sharp reduction or weight gain. Most <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="childbirth">stretch marks appear after childbirth</a> or nursing. Naturally, in such a situation, women are beginning to look for the most effective means, to once and for all get rid of stretch marks on his chest.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Despite the progress of modern medicine, to get rid of stretch marks on his chest stuffy today is almost impossible. But if you start to deal with them as soon as they appear on your skin, as they are painted in pink and have not yet become pale, then you will be a good result. With proper care, fresh stretch marks disappear forever from the life.</p>

<p>Today there are a lot of beauty, as well as drugs that help remove and prevent the appearance of stretch marks. It is the most effective means of oil, namely lemon, almond, flax, orange. You need to choose any of these oils and systematically rub it into the skin to get rid of stretch marks on his chest.</p>

<p>Below we will acquaint you with several methods of removing stretch marks, which help to quickly resolve the problem.</p>

<h2>Water treatments</h2>

<p>It is known that cold shower improves circulation and strengthens blood vessels, which in turn helps the skin to become more elastic so you do not have to worry about How to get rid of stretch marks on breasts. You must perform the procedure in a circular motion, starting from the right, for a few minutes. Carry out this procedure every day. It is not necessary to increase the duration of the procedure, since it is possible to chill the breast and cause a variety of inflammatory diseases and not to get rid of stretch marks on breasts.</p>

<p>Also get rid of stretch marks on breasts, you can wipe the chest with the help of small pieces of ice, this procedure gives a lifting effect that accelerates the elimination of stretch marks.</p>

<p>It helps as well and wiping with a wet towel. You need to soak a towel in normal water and then grind them to his chest. When you need to take the dry, warmed towel and dry breasts.</p>

<h2>Cosmetic procedures</h2>

<p>Wraps and masks also good help to get rid of stretch marks on breasts. They improve the skin and lead to normal metabolism.</p>

<p>Recipe mask: should be thoroughly mixed cheese and olive oil, add sour cream, honey, egg, and then apply the mixture on the chest. Keep this weight is necessary for twenty minutes and then gently rinse and apply a quality moisturizer.</p>

<h2>Massage</h2>

<p>Breast massage is one of the most important processes of care for your body and the way to get rid of stretch marks on his chest. Because it improves circulation, tightens muscles, improves lymph drainage. To eliminate stretch marks is the best Taoist and Manual massage.</p>

<p>Taoist massage to get rid of stretch marks is carried out as follows: take a breast in his hand and make a couple of rotational movement in the direction from the shoulder to the center, and then you need to embrace the breasts with his hands and make a couple of pressings on the exhale.</p>

<p>Manual massage is carried out in several stages. First, prepare the breasts using light circular movements, after the tips of his fingers begin to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/neurology/stroke.html" title="stroke">stroke</a> his chest in the direction of the nipple. Next you need to go to the main part of the massage, take a breast in his hand and a second hand work out easy blows on his hand. Then just keep breasts in his hands and produce oscillatory motion from the nipple to the shoulder. Complete massage should be light stroking. Of course, it is desirable to entrust the conduct of massage professionals as they make the procedure more qualitatively and pick methodology taking into account the individual characteristics of a person.</p>

<h2>Physical culture</h2>

<p>It is useful to combine all the above activities, physical exercise, as it will accelerate the receipt of the result aimed at is to get rid of stretch marks on breasts.</p>

<p>The best approach is swimming, but if such an opportunity you do not, just go a special course at the fitness center or perform exercises on their own. To go to the main part of the session you must first warm up the muscles of the body is good, it needs to do a couple of turns of the shoulders, head and make the slopes and so on. Now we go to the main exercise.</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>The first exercise</strong>. We must come face to the wall, lean on her hands and make ten pusher movements in the wall.</li>
<li><strong>The second exercise</strong>. Stand up straight, well-pressed hands to the body, and then try to connect their blades. You should do eight sets of ten seconds each.</li>
<li><strong>The third exercise</strong>. It is necessary to connect the front of the palm and try to squeeze them much, do it eight times in five seconds.</li>
<li><strong>The fourth exercise</strong>. You need to be back to the wall and make a hundred motions simulating swimming breaststroke.</li>
</ul>


<p>In the fight against stretch marks you need to remember that everyone has their genetics, and for this reason, exercise can not give you the desired result. If any method fails, then try another until you find your method.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[90-day Diet of a Separate Food]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/90-day-diet-of-a-separate-food/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-04T10:47:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/90-day-diet-of-a-separate-food</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/90-day-diet-of-a-separate-food/img.jpg" alt="alt"><strong>90 days, a separate food</strong> - the original scheme, based on the classic separation of power, which is strictly regulated on certain days. The eponymous book authors promise us neither more nor less than the acceleration of metabolism, dumping 25 kilograms, and no side effects to health. Let&rsquo;s try to find out how justified their claims, why lovers always sweet like this program and what are the medical background to find on the course. <!--more-->In general, the authors Polyanshek Hrobart and popular Slovak writer and their book far exceeded the circulations of the world best sellers - it&rsquo;s hard to say what is more: a good system or a successful advertising campaign. Doctors do not support the principles of a separate food are no randomized studies that clearly indicate the usefulness of this approach. But <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/citrus-diet-for-weight-loss-diet-menus-on-citrus-reviews-recipes/" title="reviews">reviews</a> the system works, it also trains the habits of a healthy diet and discipline, and it is important in the fight against excess weight.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<h2>90 days separate food</h2>

<p>All three months divided into four &quot;block&quot;, which alternate in succession - before the end of the scheme does not change course. Each four-day cycle is required for the execution, and if you have broken at any point, it is necessary to go back to the beginning of the cycle. If the failure lasted more than a week, you need a hitch (not necessary to continue to destroy the pastries and drink) and return to the beginning of the diet. The scheme is simple and intuitive catchy. Breakfast at any stage is minimal and you build it yourself from a glass of any fruit, starting and ending with exotic blueberries or any fruit as one. Do you want a banana? No problem, eat it, from one end of the world banana come.</p>

<p><strong>Protein loading</strong> - mostly animal protein, although you can use nuts. The preferred fish, lean meat, tofu, cottage cheese, fermented baked milk. Permission is granted to a little lettuce and a small slice of wholemeal bread. No sugar or other carbohydrates, do not forget about seafood, to get a normal fat.</p>

<p><strong>Amyloid day</strong> - this type of vegetables, potatoes, legumes, and complex carbohydrates. On this day, the protein should be minimized and should only be fats and vegetable absolutely necessary amounts for cooking. Salt use smaller, replace it seasonings.</p>

<p><strong>Pure carbohydrate a day</strong> - a favorite day sweet tooth. Fruits and even chocolate are allowed - only in moderation. Moreover, for dinner you can eat a little dessert. But remember, the less simple (fast) carbohydrates, the better.</p>

<p><strong>Vitamin day</strong> - it can still be called a discharge. Unsweetened fruit, some salad, seeds and nuts.</p>

<p><strong>Fully discharge day</strong> on mineral water at the end of a cycle of 29 consecutive days, consider carefully.</p>

<p>The main requirement - strict eating regime, as &quot;the book says&quot;. With breakfast you realize no amateur, fruit and berries, but the rest of the diet are allowed to enjoy in a strictly allotted time - from 12 am to 19 pm. The principle is simple - for lunch you can eat food to satiety, and for dinner have to eat a third less dining portions.</p>

<p>Drinking regime to do the maximum to the bottom of the vitamin and supplements can be taken from ascorbic acid and fish oil.</p>

<ul>
<li>Scrambled eggs with grated cheese, seafood cocktail;</li>
<li>A glass of broth, boiled beef, a slice of corn bread;</li>
<li>Broth of vegetables, boiled or baked potatoes;</li>
<li>Buckwheat with fat and a small piece of bread.</li>
<li>Pasta with tomato sauce;</li>
<li>Oatmeal on skim milk;</li>
<li>A piece of chocolate and crackers - sweet on this day are allowed to, you can even eat some ice cream.</li>
<li>Thick compote of dried fruits;</li>
<li>Fresh fruit salad with honey sauce;</li>
<li>Juice, fresh vegetable salad, pine nuts.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Pros and cons of the diet 90 days separate food</h2>

<p>Considered a long course, with detailed instructions, unloading days and the possibility of a smooth and controlled diet.</p>

<p>One of the few diets which completely &quot;legal&quot; you can eat chocolate, cookies and ice cream.</p>

<p>Change &quot;modes&quot; and the abundance of food is not even allowed to pall after a couple of months from the start of the diet. In addition, the alternation of days will help get rid of the glycogen stores in the muscles, which will accelerate the burning of fat from the stock.</p>

<p>Ability to make fasting day and return to the beginning of the cycle in the event of unauthorized use of a product or holidays, most diets have to start again.</p>

<p>We need a serious preparation, planning and cooking meals for the next day - discipline is very important.</p>

<p>There is no proven medical reason for separate meals, also proved that inhibit enzymes friend - friend, in case of splitting of food from various sources.</p>

<p>Many nutritionists speak of separate principles of nutrition, as a pseudoscientific delirium, likely losing weight will be due to lower caloric content and depletion of glycogen stores. All thinking about the health benefits can be safely omitted - such data is unavailable.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
