<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Health-and-beauty | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/health-and-beauty/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-01-04T11:25:36+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cellulite. Causes, Symptoms, Treatments]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/cellulite-causes-symptoms-treatments/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-03T15:43:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/cellulite-causes-symptoms-treatments</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/cellulite-causes-symptoms-treatments/cellulite-causes-symptoms-treatments.jpg" title="Cellulite" alt="Cellulite. Causes, symptoms, treatments"><strong>Cellulite</strong> in medicine refers to inflammation of subcutaneous fat.</p>

<p>But really popular word &quot;cellulite&quot; was when he began to communicate with the perennial problem, which is so concerned about the people who want to have a beautiful body. Known to most people <strong>cellulite - it changed the appearance of skin with subcutaneous fat</strong>. Cellulite usually occur on the thighs, buttocks and stomach, at least - in the armpits, chest, upper arms.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Cellulite - is not a disease, but an <strong>esthetic problem, which is inherent in the female constitution</strong>. He varying severity occurs in about 80% of women aged over 20 years. A common misconception - is that cellulite is only complete. Most characteristic changes occur in women of normal weight and even located on the lower limit of normal body mass index.</p>

<h2>The mechanism of formation of cellulite</h2>

<p>Under the influence of certain factors (heredity, diet, hormonal factors, physical inactivity, the deterioration of the microcirculation and others.) In the fat cells increases the deposition of fat and reducing its metabolic degradation. As a result, fat cells subcutaneous tissue <strong>uneven increase in size</strong>. Strong long connective partitions between them tightened and pressed into the part of the fat cells, and on the sides of the strands of fat portions protrude more, leading to even more uneven skin surface.</p>

<h2>Causes and risk factors of cellulite</h2>

<p><strong>Overweight</strong> - an increase in body fat in itself leads to increased levels of estrogen in the blood, which exacerbates the appearance of cellulite.</p>

<p><strong>Hormones</strong>: growth of fat cells is dependent on the level of the female hormone <em>estrogen</em>, so women with a higher concentration of estrogen in the blood more prone to the risk of the appearance of cellulite. This again indicates that the light level of cellulite it is almost normal, but its <strong>first manifestations should be a signal to work on yourself</strong>. In the case of predisposition to cellulite you need to keep yourself in good shape, so as not to aggravate the appearance of cellulite.</p>

<p><strong>Use of hormonal contraceptives</strong> - an artificial change in the blood levels of sex hormones also affects the rate of growth of fat cells.</p>

<p><strong>Poor circulation and lack of exercise</strong> - are interrelated. Circulatory disturbance occurs when a long stay in one position, low muscle tone and lack of physical activity, wearing tight underwear, stockings, a long walk in high heels.</p>

<p><strong>Heredity</strong> - often cellulite occurs in those who have a genetic predisposition to develop it. So if someone in your immediate family has any degree of cellulite, you need to start it early prevention. The best prevention of cellulite - proper nutrition and physical activity.</p>

<h2>The symptoms of cellulitis</h2>

<p>The skin is covered with small pits and often reminiscent of orange peel. Cellulite is different depending on the severity. In mild cases it is visible only when the skin is trapped in the fold. In more severe cases, it gives the skin an uneven appearance with dimples and pits. Symptoms of cellulite worsens with age as the skin loses its elasticity.</p>

<p>Cellulite is not a serious medical problem, and compulsory treatment is <strong>not necessary</strong>. Although if you believe in complete aesthetic disaster on your thighs or buttocks, you can seek help from a doctor or dermatologist plastic surgeon. The skilled artisan will prompt the most effective ways to solve the problem and give an approximate forecast of the results of different methods of treatment for you.</p>

<h2>Cellulite Treatment</h2>

<p>Many advertised ways to combat cellulite - creams, massage devices - promise significant results. But, unfortunately, most of these methods are &quot;not fulfill&quot; promises. The most effective methods to combat cellulite:</p>

<ul>
<li><p><strong>Weight loss</strong> - a healthy diet and regular exercise - at the moment it is the <strong>most effective and safe way</strong> to treat cellulite. Strengthening the muscles of the legs, buttocks, arms, abdominals and obliques, and getting rid of extra kilos can significantly improve the landscape and appearance of the skin. Do not expect immediate results from these methods, and the more you can not throw a healthy lifestyle, a week later if you did not notice the changes. On strengthening the muscles it takes time more than one week. In addition, cellulite is sometimes tends to diminish some time after returning to a normal weight. Although the results are usually still visible after a few weeks of starting treatment. In addition, proper low-calorie food coupled with exercise - it is the only method that does <strong>not threaten your health and life, and just goes in his favor</strong>.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Operation with a laser</strong> - is currently considered the most promising surgical method. There are several methods of laser treatment. One method involves a combination of tissue massage, radiofrequency exposure to fatty tissue and infrared radiation. Another method is to deliver into the subcutaneous tissue diode laser energy. The third technique uses high-frequency effects on the deep and superficial layers of the subcutaneous tissue. All varieties of laser treatment to produce results post treatment. The result, however, unstable, and the average remains about 6 months. Laser treatment is considered minimally invasive (causing minimum damage to the tissues of the body) and produces a purposeful destruction of fat cells with accompanying skin tightening.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Liposuction</strong> - the name of the operation for a long time at the hearing. During surgery, the surgeon places through small incisions under the skin of a narrow tube through which oil is pumped out and destroyed. But liposuction does not eliminate cellulite, because it comes from the superficial layers of the subcutaneous tissue and fat is removed from the deeper layers. Therefore, liposuction can sometimes even worsen the appearance of cellulite.</p></li>
</ul>


<p><strong>Local treatment - cream with a variety of active extracts, massage</strong>. The most successful proven extracts of grapefruit. Although the effect of it is very different and poorly defined. Also, according to recent studies, creams containing 0.3% retinol shown to be effective against cellulite after 6 months of use. But these resources, however, and massage can be used only as an adjunct to a healthy diet and physical activity.</p>

<p>Remember that surgical treatments always carry a certain risk (reaction to anesthesia, extensive tissue damage), so before you use them, it is better to try the safest way: strengthening of muscles and weight loss. If you once will acquire the habit of a healthy and active lifestyle, it will bring you in addition to the disappearance or reduction of cellulite and many other useful &quot;bonus&quot;. So try to choose the most convenient method to combat cellulite.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corrective Underwear Abdomen and Waist]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/corrective-underwear-abdomen-and-waist/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-02T13:58:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/corrective-underwear-abdomen-and-waist</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/corrective-underwear-abdomen-and-waist/corrective-underwear-abdomen-and-waist.jpg" title="Corrective underwear abdomen and waist" alt="Corrective underwear abdomen and waist">Corrective underwear - is clothing for women, which hides figure flaws. More often than not buy it because of the extra weight. Corrective underwear hides fat folds, reduce the number of waist circumference, to give a figure more slender look. Some manufacturers of such clothing argue that it promotes weight loss or getting rid of cellulite, which is not true.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Linen can be of different types, depending on the problem area, where it will be used.</p>

<p>To improve the appearance of the abdomen is the best choice corsets, kombidressy, shorts with a high waist.</p>

<p>The main mechanism of action of corrective underwear abdomen and waist - is concealing folds of fat and improve body contours. Some unscrupulous manufacturers also indicate in the advertisement that the clothes by nanotechnology or massage promotes weight loss and improvement of women. It is not true.</p>

<p>Benefits of using corrective underwear, compared with the actual weight loss:</p>

<ul>
<li>Immediate effect - it does not need to wait for weeks or months;</li>
<li>You can quickly improve the figure before the holiday, corporate, date or an important business meeting.</li>
</ul>


<p>The disadvantages of using corrective underwear:</p>

<ul>
<li>There is no improvement of health;</li>
<li>There is no significant change in body contours - the effect is very moderate;</li>
<li>Uncomfortable to wear - underwear compresses the body.</li>
</ul>


<p>The correct choice of corrective underwear - this is very important as picking the wrong size, you can not improve, but on the contrary, visually impair the figure. Apart from the size, you should pay attention to:</p>

<ul>
<li>Fabric - Linen has slimming properties, and it should not lose elasticity after a few days of use;</li>
<li>An inner layer - underwear should be comfortable to wear, not to provoke sweating, do not rub the skin;</li>
<li>The thickness of the fabric - do not buy the warm summer corrective underwear;</li>
<li>The degree of tightening - if necessary, buy rigid correction underwear corset with black inserts and a silicone impregnation;</li>
<li>Absence of seams, which can be seen under clothing.</li>
</ul>


<p>Note that corrective underwear vendors often provide unreasonable promises about the results of its use. In particular, it is often argued that visually you reduce 2 sizes. That&rsquo;s not true, this effect is not possible. Reducing waist circumference will be minimal. The main purpose of corrective underwear - it is smoothing the contours of the body, rather than contraction.</p>

<p>It is not necessary to wear a corrective underwear abdomen and waist during pregnancy, damaged or rash on the skin at the site of the alleged contact with the tissue. It should not be too zealous in the use of such clothing. No need to wear it for too long and too often - it can negatively affect the skin condition. Exerting pressure on the body, corrective underwear thereby impairs blood circulation and may eventually worsen the appearance of cellulite.</p>

<p>Corrective underwear is designed to improve the appearance of women. It hides the fat folds, smoothing the contours of the body. This significant reduction in waist circumference does not occur. Shaping lingerie gives a temporary result. It can not be an alternative to weight loss and is not conducive to it. The clothes should be taken only in size. If it is less or more than you need, you can worsen rather than improve the appearance of the figure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists Have Questioned the Benefits of Organic Products]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/scientists-have-questioned-the-benefits-of-organic-products/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-14T21:31:53+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/scientists-have-questioned-the-benefits-of-organic-products</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Organic food is no longer useful and safe for human health than the ordinary. To this conclusion was reached by researchers from Stanford University (USA), after an analysis of 240 publications, which have been devoted to food that have appeared in the scientific literature since 1966. The work group was headed by Dan Bravat, it has become the most extensive research in this area, and was published September 4 in the journal Annals of Internal Medicine.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The so-called organic food - food is grown without the use of pesticides, antibiotics, hormones, etc. - Positioned as much more useful and safer than usual because it is more pure and contains more vitamins, minerals and other nutrients. Organic foods are sometimes almost twice as expensive as products grown using traditional methods, but, despite this, their popularity, especially among the population of developed countries has multiplied over the past decade. For example, in the United States since 1997. by 2011. organic food market has increased from $3600000000 to $24400000000.</p>

<p>To confirm or refute the thesis regarding the significant advantage of one of two types of food over another, the authors conducted a systematic study of the results of 240 reports. 223 of these reports were devoted to a comparison grown by organic or conventional fruits, grains, vegetables, meat, eggs and milk on the content of trace elements, fungal and bacterial contamination and pesticide. The remaining 17 publications covered the health indicators in the context of food consumed. Fully entire array analyzed data published in the scientific literature since January 1966.</p>

<p>The only significant advantage over conventional organ`ic products, in terms of their content of vitamins and minerals, was a higher content of phosphorus, which, according to the authors, can be very useful for people who suffer a deficit of this trace element.</p>

<p>As vitamins, and other beneficial agents for humans, there is clinically significant for human health differences were found. Thus, the authors note that protein and fat composition of organic and ordinary milk were approximately the same, although in some publications and held assumption that organic milk may contain higher amounts of unsaturated fatty acids.</p>

<p>Also, the authors found no convincing evidence that conventional food is much more harmful to health than organic. However, the latter, with 30% less likely contaminated with pesticides than usual, although they can not be called completely free of toxic chemicals. In addition, this difference is hardly noticeable in the case of exceeding the shelf life of products. As bacterial contamination indicators are also approximately equal. The authors suggest that the use of organic chicken and pork reduces the risk of developing resistance to antibiotics, and note that the clinical evidence of this assumption does not exist.</p>

<p>Commenting on the results, the authors noted that they could easily affect the heterogeneity of research methods used in the studies, as well as various factors that affect the safety and quality of products, such as weather, soil composition, methods of farming, etc.
It should be noted that the conclusions made by experts at Stanford University, the same, in general, the results of a study conducted by scientists at the London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine in 2009.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genital Herpes: 4 Out of 5 Patients Unaware of Being Infected With This Virus]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/genital-herpes-4-out-of-5-patients-unaware-of-being-infected-with-this-virus/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-22T23:50:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/genital-herpes-4-out-of-5-patients-unaware-of-being-infected-with-this-virus</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/genital-herpes-4-out-of-5-patients-unaware-of-being-infected-with-this-virus/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="herpes, genital herpes" alt="Genital herpes : 4 out of 5 patients unaware of being infected with this virus!">Two million americans are affected by the virus that causes <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/genital-herpes.html" title="genital herpes">genital herpes</a>.
Worse, four out of five do not know! In side The drug prescription information and patient education are therefore key stages of care.</p>




<!--more-->




<h2>Herpes types</h2>




<p><strong>Herpes labialis</strong>
He is responsible for cold sores. Frequent, nearly 10 million americans suffer at least one thrust per year. It preferentially affects women (3 women to 2 men).</p>




<p><strong>Genital herpes</strong>
Number of herpes infection carriers subjects estimated 2 million against only 350,000 cases diagnosed! Thus, four out of five are unaware of being infected.</p>




<h2>An impaired life quality</h2>




<p>Genital herpes diagnosis is often difficult because of the lesions diversity or too late consultation and outside attacks. However, the impact on quality of life is very important.</p>




<p>Patients are afraid to have sex because of pain or disease transmitting fear. They are 34% to easily manage their social life and 33% have <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/depression.html" title="depression">depression</a>.</p>




<p>However, drug treatments exist.</p>




<h2>A little known illness surrounded by taboos</h2>




<p>It is necessary to open the dialogue and break the taboos surrounding this little known disease patients. As well as medication, inform and educate patients is an management integral part. Contamination must be explained, as well as the potential for treatment to facilitate compliance. This stops the immediate effect in virus replication, pain and shortens the surge duration, but virus remains in body.</p>




<p><strong>Infection is severe in late <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a></strong>
In addition, this infection can be very serious in late pregnancy. It entails a neonatal infection risk (1-2 cases per 100,000 births), the consequences can be serious for infants if treatment is not started quickly.</p>




<h2>How to prevent transmission  herpes virus?</h2>




<p>During a herpes outbreak:</p>




<ul>
<li>Wash hands after touching the lesions and do not scratch the lesions.</li>
<li>Do not share his towels.</li>
<li>Avoid sexual intercourse, even protected by a condom.</li>
<li>Avoid physical contact with newborns, pregnant women, people with skin lesions (eczema, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/psoriasis.html" title="psoriasis">psoriasis</a>, etc.)., Immunocompromised individuals (AIDS, organ transplant, chemotherapy).</li>
</ul>




<p>Outside breakouts, use a condom if the partner has never come into contact with the herpes virus.</p>




<p>In case of herpes labialis (cold sores) to avoid oral-genital sex (sex/mouth) because this virus on the lips can be transmitted to the partner genitals.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fungus Toenails. Onychomycosis]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/fungus-toenails-onychomycosis/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-21T09:30:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/fungus-toenails-onychomycosis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/fungus-toenails-onychomycosis/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="nail fungus, fungus toenails, onychomycosis" alt="Fungus toenails, onychomycosis">If you find they thicken, become brittle, change color, check out quickly.</p>




<p>The fungus toenails is extremely contagious and can lead to the loss of the nail, then there are effective treatments.</p>




<!--more-->




<h2>The fungus toenails is common</h2>




<p>The fungus toenails is common and transmissible. It affects 3-10% of the French population. Professionals use the term of onychomycosis, which designates a nail infection caused by fungi of three kinds (dermatophytes, yeasts Candida, molds).</p>




<h2>First signs of a nail fungus</h2>




<p>The infection settles slowly. It reaches first the skin between the toes forming a fissure that does not heal. Gradually, the nail is reached. It thickens, crumbles, changes color (yellow or white spots) and becomes painful. In the absence of treatment, it may peel off.</p>




<h2>What are the risk factors for nail fungus?</h2>




<p>Older age, male sex, sports, trauma and repeated injury, a humid environment and certain diseases (bone and joint diseases, diabetes, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>, peripheral <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/vascular-disease/" title="vascular disease">vascular disease</a>, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/psoriasis.html" title="psoriasis">psoriasis</a>?).</p>




<p>The infection is caught easily in collective public places humid and warm where you walk barefoot (pool, sauna, dance halls, dressing rooms, etc..).</p>




<p>You can also pass the family, walking barefoot on the carpet, suitable slippers or in the bathroom, including towels or nail clippers. Maceration in shoes, especially sport shoes or boots, is also a major risk factor. Also predispose strain nails or toes that overlap (common in older people).</p>




<h2>In case of nail fungus, early treatment is essential</h2>




<p>A <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nail-fungus-fungal-nail-disease-symptoms-and-prevention/" title="nail fungus">nail fungus</a> does not heal on its own and instead risk spreading to other nails.</p>




<p>Similarly, the more care is delayed, the more healing is long and difficult. Hence the importance of regularly inspecting her nails, especially if you are part of those at risk.</p>




<p>At the slightest anomaly, talk to your doctor.</p>




<p>A sample of the nail for a mycological examination is necessary to identify the fungus cause and prescribe the appropriate antifungal therapy. Depending on the degree of achievement of the nail, it will be local (application of a varnish) and/or oral. However, be patient and be sure to follow your doctor&rsquo;s instructions. Indeed, the treatment is long (often more than 6 months), as the nail grows very slowly.</p>




<h2>Tips to avoid a nail fungus</h2>




<ul>
<li>Systematically and thoroughly dry your feet, especially between each toe.</li>
<li>Avoid walking barefoot.</li>
<li>Wear personal sandals by the pool, in the locker room&hellip;</li>
<li>Do not lend your slippers.</li>
<li>Do not pay either your towel.</li>
<li>Disinfect with alcohol scissors, nail files and nail clippers used for toenails.</li>
<li>Cut your toe nails short and straight.</li>
<li>Limit wearing sneakers your physical activity.</li>
<li>Wear leather shoes, which limit maceration.</li>
<li>Avoid tight shoes, too tightly in plastic.</li>
<li>Try not to your shoes, especially sport.</li>
<li>Adopt cotton socks, especially for sports.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
