<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: health and beauty | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/health-and-beauty/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-12-02T20:59:08+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kefir buckwheat diet. Recipes buckwheat diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/kefir-buckwheat-diet-recipes/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-02T20:55:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/kefir-buckwheat-diet-recipes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/buckwheat-diet/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/buckwheat-diet/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Recipes buckwheat diet, essence of buckwheat diet, buckwheat diet, diet menu buckwheat&rsquo; &lsquo;Kefir buckwheat diet. Recipes buckwheat diet&rsquo;" > Buckwheat diet, despite the fact that is sufficiently rigid mono-diet (one product) has gained great popularity in the whole world for its effectiveness. Its adherence to quickly get rid of excess weight and lose up to 10 pounds in a week, in order to bring the figure in a short time and do not stretch the process of losing weight for weeks and months.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>The essence of buckwheat diet</h2>

<p>The essence of buckwheat diet is that the body is not getting out of the usual fast food carbohydrates, forced to earn them, splitting the internal fat.</p>

<p>Therefore, a person begins to lose weight quickly. Buckwheat diet belongs to the category of low-carb protein mono diet and is designed for no more than 7-14 days, depending on the &ldquo;severity&rdquo; of compliance. Longer terms are undesirable and can have negative consequences as buckwheat, for all its usefulness and uniqueness are not able to supply the body with all the necessary.</p>

<p>To stringent restrictions in the diet did not cause the body shock, nutritionists advise, before you get on a long diet, try a fasting day on buckwheat and look at your health. In addition, doctors warn that the buckwheat diet, like the popular Japanese now, is not for everyone, it is not recommended for people with diseases of the gastrointestinal tract, hypertension, diabetes, and pregnant and lactating mothers. No matter how you were pleased with the results achieved, it is not recommended to re-sit her sooner than 1-1.5 months after the end of the previous and provided adequate nutrition, not to cause irreparable harm to the body.</p>

<h2>Kefir buckwheat diet</h2>

<p>Kefir buckwheat buckwheat diet modification is because except buckwheat main component in it, usually a yogurt. The combination of buckwheat and yogurt is very effective because it provides optimal for the body proportions of proteins and carbohydrates. Buckwheat is not only tasty and useful, but also very nutritious, thus avoiding the strong feelings of hunger. In addition, due to the presence in its composition of fiber, buckwheat absorbs and actively removes toxins, allowing the body to cleanse well during the diet. Kefir buckwheat diet, other than rapid weight loss, gives a sense of lightness in the body, perfectly cleans the intestines and removes the weight of the abdomen.</p>

<p>In order to remain in buckwheat all nutrients, it does not boil, and cook in the evening on the day according to the following recipe: the dealer busts, pour over boiling water, the water is drained. Then pour boiling water over the rump (based on 1 cup of buckwheat by 1.5 &ndash; 2 cups of water), wrap up warm blanket and leave to infuse overnight. You can insist buckwheat in a thermos, in which case the cooking time will be reduced to 2 hours.</p>

<p>Kefir need to buy 1%, preferably one day, because after 3 days from the date of production, he begins to have a bonding effect. During the day you can drink no more than 1 liter of yogurt. It is best to drink it away from buckwheat, half an hour before meals or half an hour after, but is also allowed to wash down with buckwheat or fill it with yogurt.</p>

<p>Buckwheat can eat in a day unlimited, it is desirable to divide evenly into 5-6 meals, the last meal try to finish in 4 hours before bedtime. If a strong feeling of hunger before bedtime drink a glass of buttermilk, but do not forget that its total amount should not exceed 1 liter. During the day, drink plenty of water, at least 2 liters a day, as well as green tea without sugar.</p>

<p>Kefir buckwheat diet is strict, no more than 7 days, which are only present in the diet of buckwheat and kefir, and gentle, which allows for some food relief and can last up to 14 days. Not so intrusive option bystroeffektiven as strict, but can lose weight very comfortable.</p>

<h2>Menu buckwheat diet</h2>

<p>Even for the most ardent fans of buckwheat withstand rigorous monodiet quite hard because in a few days, usually on buckwheat no longer want to watch. Therefore, in order not to break, you need to pre-compose personalized menus using popular recipes buckwheat diet to best diversify your diet.</p>

<p>Menu buckwheat diet can include the following food products:</p>

<ul>
<li>Dried fruit &ndash; some stuff dried apricots or prunes can be added to porridge or eat separately.</li>
<li>A couple of unsweetened fruit or low-fat yogurt, preferably green apples, but the can and other fruit, except bananas, cantaloupe, watermelon, grapes.</li>
<li>Fresh salad or boiled beets and carrots &ndash; are prepared without salt and sugar, add a little olive oil.</li>
<li>Soy sauce &ndash; can be added to improve the taste of buckwheat porridge.</li>
<li>Honey &ndash; are allowed to add to tea or water, if to be mental work, it is best not to swallow the honey immediately, but first suck in your mouth.</li>
<li>Fresh herbs &ndash; dill, parsley, green onions.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Recipes buckwheat diet</h2>

<p>A variety of recipes buckwheat diet can have a delicious and nutritious meals to an empty buckwheat quickly &ldquo;does not become boring&rdquo;.</p>

<p>Cook the viscous buckwheat porridge, add soy, mix thoroughly. Form small patties and place in the oven or microwave for 25 minutes. To improve the taste you can sprinkle with sesame seeds.</p>

<p>To prepare the required boiled carrots, fresh tomatoes and lightly protushennaya cabbage. Grease a baking sheet with vegetable oil, put it on until half-cooked buckwheat porridge, top layers of carrots, tomatoes, cabbage. Bake in the oven until tender, and eat with a green salad.</p>

<p>To buckwheat porridge, add the egg, yogurt, a little flour and mix until a homogeneous viscous mass. Fry the pancakes on a small amount of olive oil.</p>

<h2>Onion frying to buckwheat porridge</h2>

<p>On a heated pan drip a little vegetable oil and lightly fry it finely chopped onion. Apple peel, cut and add to the onions, hold the pan a couple of minutes. The resulting frying season with porridge.</p>

<h3>Buckwheat diet for 7 days. Buckwheat diet for 14 days</h3>

<p>Strict buckwheat diet for 7 days is very effective, but to sit on it pretty hard due to the severe food restrictions. So many people, so as not to break, prefer to extend the period to 14 days, but more comfortable feel and more diverse eating.</p>

<p>Buckwheat diet for 14 days has quite a varied menu and allows you to lose 7 to 12 pounds.</p>

<p>Breakfast: buckwheat, a glass of buttermilk and buckwheat bread.
Lunch: cereal, 2 cups buttermilk, 2 buckwheat cakes.
Dinner: buckwheat pie, a cup of yogurt.</p>

<p>Breakfast: cup of yogurt, buckwheat bread
Lunch: 3-4 pieces of buckwheat pancakes, 2 cups of yogurt</p>

<p>On the night pour buckwheat yogurt, divided into 4-5 portions and eat all day, drinking water or yogurt.</p>

<p>Breakfast: a glass of buttermilk and buckwheat pancakes.
Lunch: cereal, 2 cups of yogurt, bread.
Dinner: cereal, a cup of yogurt, fruit salad.</p>

<p>Breakfast: cereal, a glass of kefir, a boiled egg.
Lunch: porridge, cabbage salad, tea.
Dinner: cereal, yogurt, diet salad.</p>

<p>Exit after kefir, buckwheat diet for 14 days, must be smooth to keep the achieved results and to do no harm to health. It is impossible to go for flour, fat and sweet. During weight loss stomach significantly decreased in volume, so do not overeat and stretch it again.</p>

<p>Fish and meat introduced into the diet gradually, for example, eat an egg for breakfast, for lunch &ndash; low-fat soup or salad with meat or fish, and dine again buckwheat with yogurt. Despite the fact that buckwheat you already pretty bored of the diet, continue to include it in their daily menu at least for a week to help the body get used to the new weight and not lose the results achieved.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get rid of allergies forever. Allergies causes]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/get-rid-of-allergies-forever-causes/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-02T20:54:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/get-rid-of-allergies-forever-causes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/get-rid-of-allergies-forever/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/get-rid-of-allergies-forever/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Get rid of allergies forever, pathogenic microflora of the intestine, causes of allergies&rsquo; &lsquo;Get rid of allergies forever. The causes of allergies&rsquo;" > Of allergy contributes to the pathogenic intestinal microflora. Scientists around the world are studying the causes of allergies, because in the last few decades, the world has seen a rapid increase in allergic diseases and according to WHO every fifth child is born with allergies. Allergies &ndash; is an individual reaction to certain substances (allergens) after contact with them.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>The causes of allergies and current treatments</h2>

<p>In parallel with the increasing number of allergies and a list of allergens, which began to get even the most innocent-looking substance. Currently, there are so many new allergens that to protect itself from them, and to exclude from your diet and environment is not possible. Allergic reactions can cause food, household dust, pollen and plant fluff, pet hair, cosmetics, medicines and much more.</p>

<p>Allergy symptoms in different people as diverse &ndash; coughing, sneezing, snot, itching, rash on the body, swelling of the mucous membranes and even asthma. In severe cases, anaphylactic shock can occur &ndash; the most dangerous manifestation of allergic reaction, which in the absence of immediate medical attention to result in death. If there are signs of anaphylactic shock, such as seizures, loss of consciousness, shortness of breath, vomiting, rash all over the body, involuntary urination and defecation, you should immediately call an ambulance.</p>

<p>Modern drugs, widely advertised in the media, unfortunately, do not eliminate the causes of the emergence and development of allergies, and are directed only by addressing its symptoms and relief of the patient. Allergy treatment passes through the standard procedure &ndash; first samples are taken to establish the allergen in order to avoid contact with him, and then assigned to an antihistamine and immune-boosting drugs. But this approach can not be considered the treatment because the treatment of any disease it is important to establish the root cause that caused it, and fix it.</p>

<p>Also popular method of treatment of specific immunotherapy (SIT), the essence of which is the regular administration of low doses of a specific allergen with a gradual increase, which stimulates the immune system and leads to a resistance to it. SIT prolonged treatment and more efficient &ndash; reducing the need for medications the patient, the symptoms are greatly reduced, which is especially important in asthma attacks. SIT is a basic treatment of asthma, by which it is possible to achieve a prolonged remission.</p>

<p>The method is definitely more effective than the simple application of antihistamines, but the downside of it is that in allergic reaction rarely occurs on a single allergen. Most of several allergens and their number increases with time. Develop immunity to any one allergen, the body begins to react to the new stuff, and so on to infinity, because the cause of allergies is still not resolved.</p>

<h2>Get rid of the allergy will forever intestinal microflora</h2>

<p>Scientists still can not name the exact cause of the allergy, why the same adverse environmental and technological conditions in some relatively healthy people cause allergies and others do not. But already found exactly what one of the main causes of allergies is to reduce the number of beneficial microflora in the gut colonization and its pathogenic microbes is called dysbiosis (dysbiosis).</p>

<p>Many people underestimate the lack of knowledge of the role of beneficial microflora for normal body function. Useful healthy human intestinal flora consists of 2-3 kg microorganisms which produce fiber of a variety of vitamins, hormones, amino acids, enzymes, hemoglobin and improve immunity, promote good assimilation of iron. In addition, the intestinal microflora and neutralizes harmful pathogens.</p>

<p>If a person prevails in the gut microflora useful, it copes with its tasks. If the number of beneficial microflora is reduced, which most often occurs with antibiotic treatment, it took place immediately pathogenic bacteria that without meeting resistance, are beginning to multiply, causing inflammation of the gastro &ndash; intestinal tract.</p>

<p>Then begin to destroy pathogenic microflora integrity of the intestinal mucosa, and decreases its protective barrier function, whereby allergens and toxins may enter freely into the body. In addition, pathogenic microflora begins to actively produce histamine and other substances promoting the development of allergy. Therefore, doctors have long known rule that the cure is dysbiosis, and allergic reactions immediately back down, appearing less frequently or disappear completely.</p>

<p>Dysbacteriosis contributes not only to the emergence of symptoms of allergies, but also metabolic disorders, cardiovascular and endocrine diseases and even depression. Scientists have found a clear link between the presence of dysbiosis and the level of anxiety a person who at dysbiosis increased almost 3 times. And the fact that the problems with the skin, hair and nails can not be removed any creams and cosmetics, without solving the problem of dysbiosis, long time it is not a secret.</p>

<p>Therefore, it can be said without exaggeration that the intestinal microflora is the key to the health of the body and each person has to take care of her, not only to get rid of all allergies, but also to avoid the many other diseases. For this it is necessary to organize your diet to a diet rich in plant-dominated fiber and fiber products, especially vegetables, fruits, cereals from whole grains, bran bread, and milk products.</p>

<p>If you want to be healthy, in any case, do not overeat, start a one-day fasting yourself to help the body as excess food is not digested and starts to rot in the gut, poisoning it. German physician Max Gerson, a lifetime studying the dependence of cancer from power in his book &ldquo;The treatment of cancer,&rdquo; says that in his research of 10,000 cancer cases, only one came from irreversible changes in the body, and all the rest of 9999 are the result of poisoning their own</p>

<p>If you regularly take care of the purity of his bowel and healthy nutrition necessary for the beneficial microflora, then not only will get rid of allergies, but in the future and avoid many serious diseases.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diseases of the thyroid gland. Causes and symptoms of hypothyroidism and hyperthyroidism]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diseases-of-the-thyroid-gland/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-02T20:53:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/diseases-of-the-thyroid-gland</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/thyroid-disease-hypothyroidism/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/thyroid-disease-hypothyroidism/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Thyroid disease, hypothyroidism, hypothyroidism symptoms, hyperthyroidism causes, hyperthyroidism symptoms&rsquo; &lsquo;Diseases of the thyroid gland. Causes and symptoms of hypothyroidism and hyperthyroidism&rsquo;" > Thyroid disorders require prompt diagnosis and treatment. Thyroid gland without reason called the small conductor of a large orchestra, emphasizing that at small sizes (at a rate of about 15-20 grams), it plays a vital role in directing the overall operation of the complex formation as the human body.</p>

<p>It is the most important part of a complex human endocrine system, along with the pituitary gland, adrenal glands, pancreas, thymus gland and gonads.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>These glands produce and secrete into the blood of about 50 types of hormones. The thyroid gland produces only two kinds of hormones thyroxine (T4) and triiodothyronine (T3), but no! With their help, it regulates the body&rsquo;s metabolism, the cardiovascular and central nervous system, and manages the psycho &ndash; emotional and sexual activity.</p>

<p>It is up to the thyroid gland depends on the psycho-emotional state of a person, that is, whether he is irritable, aggressive, quick-tempered and ready at any moment to lose self-control, or, conversely, apathetic, passive and indifferent to everything.</p>

<p>From these two hormones depends on body temperature, heart rate, the rate of burning calories and more. A healthy body produces these hormones for as long as necessary for the proper function. But, for failures of the thyroid gland, the necessary hormones starts to be produced more or less the norm, which is equally bad.</p>

<h2>The causes and symptoms of hypothyroidism</h2>

<p>Causes of hypothyroidism &ndash; reduced function of the thyroid gland, in which hormone production becomes insufficient, which is manifested lethargy, apathy, drowsiness, chilliness, fatigue, decreased immunity and slowing metabolism. The main symptoms of hypothyroidism, which should pay close attention &ndash; the appetite is reduced, but the weight increases, performance decreases bowel, constipation appear also thinner nails, they appear grooves and thickening.</p>

<p>Hypothyroidism begins quietly, and all of these symptoms, you see, we are usually easy to explain to stress, fatigue and tiredness. Instead check your thyroid hormone levels and normalize metabolism, sit on a diet, the result of which will not, and harm to an unbalanced diet, typical of nearly all diets, we currently add.</p>

<p>The main causes of hypothyroidism, according to doctors &ndash; an inflammation of the thyroid gland, thyroid congenital anomalies, of her injury, radiation exposure, lack of function of the pituitary hormones, multiple surgeries and a lack of iodine in the body. Doctors are advised to adjust your diet so that the table is always present iodine-containing foods such as seaweed, sea fish, citrus fruits, beets, potatoes, tomatoes.</p>

<p>Most of iodine contained in seaweed and fish products in the rest of his relatively few. But it is worth noting that all is good in moderation, and foods containing iodine, is also not be abused. For example, now so popular Japanese dish, like rolls, contain too much iodine, because it uses algae, which can negatively affect the thyroid gland.  Therefore, doctors are advised to eat no more than 2-3 rolls a week.</p>

<h2>The causes and symptoms of hyperthyroidism</h2>

<p>The symptoms and causes of hyperthyroidism hypothyroidism are opposite, because in this disease the thyroid gland begins to produce hormones more than the norm and its function increases. The main symptoms of hyperthyroidism &ndash; a person loses weight rapidly, experiencing constant hunger, frequent diarrhea, becomes irritable, aggressive, his trembling fingers and eyelids appear the most frequent symptoms of hypertension &ndash; heart palpitations and high blood pressure.</p>

<p>In addition, hyperthyroidism is often a major cause of insomnia and dangerous complications of pregnancy. Pregnancy in hyperthyroidism requires mandatory compensation of the disease, because the excess hormones affect the fetus is extremely toxic and may cause his death, and various deformities.</p>

<p>Also in patients with hyperthyroidism often appears so-called &ldquo;exophthalmia&rdquo;, which creates additional problems of cosmetic nature and are often complex.</p>

<p>According to the eminent physician and scientist Botkin, the main causes of hyperthyroidism &ndash; neuro-psychiatric disorders, depression, and emotional breakdowns that disrupt the function of the thyroid gland. Hyperthyroidism is often referred to as a &ldquo;professional&rdquo; illness singers and artists because their work forces to be always &ldquo;on edge&rdquo;, a state of stress. In many patients, the disease was the primary cause psychological trauma, along with unfavorable heredity.</p>

<p>Not for nothing now, many doctors before diagnosis, are asked to make thyroid ultrasound and donate blood on hormones, because the root of many diseases lies in deviations in the thyroid gland. Hypothyroidism and hyperthyroidism are equally dangerous and need to see a doctor because if left untreated, these symptoms not only persist, but eventually amplified.</p>

<p>If the processing of any scratches with iodine you find traces of iodine disappear quickly (for example, for lubrication in the evening &ndash; no traces in the morning), it is likely iodine in your body is missing. And if you are, in addition, in his notice listed in this article symptoms of thyroid disease, be sure to turn in at the first opportunity blood on hormones, particularly TSH (thyroid stimulating hormone). This analysis is absolutely show, do you have any thyroid disease.</p>

<p>If there are any deviations in the analysis, then do not panic, do not be afraid to seek medical attention. Believe me, the thyroid gland is not afraid, afraid of the consequences when people are not treated. Do not be afraid &ldquo;terrible&rdquo; words hormones, having heard horror stories of incompetent people. The hormone thyroxine, which is prescribed to drink in low thyroid function, consists of only 4 atoms of iodine &ndash; as you may see, it is not, it is completely harmless.</p>

<p>Endocrinologists also argue that the more and more people nervous, the more strained his thyroid. So, do not bring your health to a critical state, all you need &ndash; to protect the nerves and the nerves of your loved ones and receive regular medical examinations, thereby maintaining their health.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily care of oily skin. Homemade masks for oily skin]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/daily-care-of-oily-skin-homemade-masks-for-oily-skin/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-02T20:52:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/daily-care-of-oily-skin-homemade-masks-for-oily-skin</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/daily-care-of-oily-skin/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/daily-care-of-oily-skin/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Daily care of oily skin, homemade mask for oily skin&rsquo; &lsquo;Daily care of oily skin. Homemade masks for oily skin&rsquo;" > Homemade masks for oily skin to help maintain its freshness and youth. The main reason for oily skin &ndash; increased activity of the sebaceous glands, which is due to increased production of the hormone in the body protesterona. Most often very oily problem skin occurs in young women in a period of intense hormonal changes. Especially brings grief oily skin on the forehead and nose.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Fortunately, after the end of active hormonal processes, the skin begins to produce much less excess fat, which greatly improves its appearance and reduces the appearance of rashes, pimples and blackheads. In addition, the undoubted advantage of oily skin is that thanks to the natural lubrication she is aging more slowly than other types of skin and wrinkles appear on it much later.</p>

<h2>Caring for oily skin</h2>

<p>Only a small percentage of adult women are problems remain after 30 years. In such cases, you need to consult a doctor, an endocrinologist at the presence of hormonal disorders and treat excess fat under the supervision of a specialist. In all other cases, no specific treatment is required, you need only a competent and proper daily care of oily skin, as well as protection from the cold, ultraviolet radiation and other environmental challenges.</p>

<p>The biggest problem that arises with this type &ndash; enlarged pores, delivering a lot of problems and disappointments for women. The fact that the large pores become clogged very quickly, because in them the ingress of dirt, excess oil and dead skin cells. In cutaneous fat are beginning to breed bacteria, resulting in a person becoming an ugly gray and pimples. Furthermore, chronic acne further stretched and expanded pores.</p>

<p>In order to avoid such problems is of critical importance proper washing, and, it does not mean that you need to wash many times a day. Enough to wash twice a day, morning and evening, but at the same time to apply special means &ndash; gel for oily skin and brush. It is important to start washing with warm, almost hot water: this is done in order to clogged pores open, which does not happen when washing your face with cold water. Then lather gel, apply it to his face and massage brush. Following this simple procedure when enlarged pores perfectly cleansed, you need to wash with cold water, which will narrow them and make it less noticeable.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homemade masks for oily hair. Proper care and cleaning oily hair]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/homemade-masks-for-oily-hair-proper-care-and-cleaning-oily-hair/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-30T14:33:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/homemade-masks-for-oily-hair-proper-care-and-cleaning-oily-hair</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/causes-of-greasy-hair/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/causes-of-greasy-hair/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Causes of greasy hair, oily hair wash, homemade mask for oily hair&rsquo; &lsquo;Homemade masks for oily hair. Proper care and cleaning oily hair&rsquo;" > Greasy hair requires frequent washing. Oily hair often lead women to despair and cause a lot of inconvenience to them that quickly gryazneyut and by the end of the day look greasy and stale, even if they are washed in the morning. But experts urge not to get upset and argue that care for them is much easier than in the dry, which, moreover, are often brittle and weakened. In addition, oily hair, thanks to the high fat content, have a huge advantage over the dry, because they, like oily skin, thanks to the natural lubrication, well protected from adverse external influences.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Causes of oily hair</h2>

<p>The main reason is the high fat content is that the sebaceous glands work too active and produce more sebum than necessary. Increased sebum secretion is often caused by genetics, but could be evidence of violations of the endocrine system.</p>

<p>In addition, increase the separation of fat intake of antibiotics, poor nutrition, extreme temperatures, severe stress and improper care. Experts believe that the right care for oily hair will avoid many of the problems and ensure that they always look nice and neat.</p>

<h2>Wash oily hair</h2>

<p>A very important question is the frequency of washing. And if you have recently called for beauticians do not wash my hair 1-2 times a week, so as not to stimulate increased zhirootdelenie, now come to the conclusion that it is much more harmful to walk with excessively oily hair. If you do not wash your hair for a long time, the upper protective layer of the scalp are beginning to proliferate microscopic fungi and yeasts that cause itching, dandruff, acne on his head and a variety of inflammatory processes. In addition, the hair follicles become clogged with fat and sebaceous ducts harden, causing the hair to stop growing, thin and hard fall.</p>

<p>Therefore, wash oily hair should be implemented as necessary, at least every day. Water for washing should not be too hot, as hot water activates the sebaceous glands. Before washing, you need to carefully comb hair &ndash; it will partially remove dirt, dandruff and protect themselves from tangling. Shampoo need not be applied directly to the hair, because in this case it is not evenly distributed.</p>

<p>It is best to dilute a small amount of shampoo to wash with water and the resulting solution, or to put it first in the palm of your hand. Lather oily hair better twice, distributing shampoo soft circular motions and without scratching the skin nails.</p>

<p>It is important to thoroughly rinse the hair after washing, because of the remnants of shampoo they are faster and have gryazneyut adhesive and matte appearance. After washing, do not immediately need to comb your hair, they need to dry out a bit. Try to use a hair dryer only when absolutely necessary, because the temperature changes are bad for oily skin and stimulate the strengthening zhirootdeleniya.</p>

<h2>Shampoo for oily hair</h2>

<p>Shampoo for oily hair should be selected very carefully, studying the composition indicated on the label. A well-chosen shampoo helps to restore proper operation of the sebaceous glands and remove the irritation and the use of the wrong shampoo will only worsen the situation. Choose a shampoo transparent natural colors &ndash; white or off-white, creamy shampoos because the bright colors often contain poisonous unnecessary and harmful dyes.</p>

<p>The most effective are the shampoos with herbal extracts &ndash; nettle, chamomile, sage, mother and stepmother, and also contain algae, vitamins A, K, C, and zinc. In the presence of dandruff shampoos choose from zinc, sulfur and tar. Do not buy shampoos, if they contain silicone, because they are heavier hair and make them even fatter.</p>

<p>Great popularity in recent years become dry shampoos that are especially useful on business trips, travel and the absence of hot water and time. These shampoos are available in powder form and are applied by spray. After 5-10 minutes, when the powder to soak up all the grease and dirt, his combed comb.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
