<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: health and beauty | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/health-and-beauty/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-11-30T14:44:24+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homemade masks for oily hair. Proper care and cleaning oily hair]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/homemade-masks-for-oily-hair-proper-care-and-cleaning-oily-hair/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-30T14:33:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/homemade-masks-for-oily-hair-proper-care-and-cleaning-oily-hair</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/causes-of-greasy-hair/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/causes-of-greasy-hair/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Causes of greasy hair, oily hair wash, homemade mask for oily hair&rsquo; &lsquo;Homemade masks for oily hair. Proper care and cleaning oily hair&rsquo;" > Greasy hair requires frequent washing. Oily hair often lead women to despair and cause a lot of inconvenience to them that quickly gryazneyut and by the end of the day look greasy and stale, even if they are washed in the morning. But experts urge not to get upset and argue that care for them is much easier than in the dry, which, moreover, are often brittle and weakened. In addition, oily hair, thanks to the high fat content, have a huge advantage over the dry, because they, like oily skin, thanks to the natural lubrication, well protected from adverse external influences.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Causes of oily hair</h2>

<p>The main reason is the high fat content is that the sebaceous glands work too active and produce more sebum than necessary. Increased sebum secretion is often caused by genetics, but could be evidence of violations of the endocrine system.</p>

<p>In addition, increase the separation of fat intake of antibiotics, poor nutrition, extreme temperatures, severe stress and improper care. Experts believe that the right care for oily hair will avoid many of the problems and ensure that they always look nice and neat.</p>

<h2>Wash oily hair</h2>

<p>A very important question is the frequency of washing. And if you have recently called for beauticians do not wash my hair 1-2 times a week, so as not to stimulate increased zhirootdelenie, now come to the conclusion that it is much more harmful to walk with excessively oily hair. If you do not wash your hair for a long time, the upper protective layer of the scalp are beginning to proliferate microscopic fungi and yeasts that cause itching, dandruff, acne on his head and a variety of inflammatory processes. In addition, the hair follicles become clogged with fat and sebaceous ducts harden, causing the hair to stop growing, thin and hard fall.</p>

<p>Therefore, wash oily hair should be implemented as necessary, at least every day. Water for washing should not be too hot, as hot water activates the sebaceous glands. Before washing, you need to carefully comb hair &ndash; it will partially remove dirt, dandruff and protect themselves from tangling. Shampoo need not be applied directly to the hair, because in this case it is not evenly distributed.</p>

<p>It is best to dilute a small amount of shampoo to wash with water and the resulting solution, or to put it first in the palm of your hand. Lather oily hair better twice, distributing shampoo soft circular motions and without scratching the skin nails.</p>

<p>It is important to thoroughly rinse the hair after washing, because of the remnants of shampoo they are faster and have gryazneyut adhesive and matte appearance. After washing, do not immediately need to comb your hair, they need to dry out a bit. Try to use a hair dryer only when absolutely necessary, because the temperature changes are bad for oily skin and stimulate the strengthening zhirootdeleniya.</p>

<h2>Shampoo for oily hair</h2>

<p>Shampoo for oily hair should be selected very carefully, studying the composition indicated on the label. A well-chosen shampoo helps to restore proper operation of the sebaceous glands and remove the irritation and the use of the wrong shampoo will only worsen the situation. Choose a shampoo transparent natural colors &ndash; white or off-white, creamy shampoos because the bright colors often contain poisonous unnecessary and harmful dyes.</p>

<p>The most effective are the shampoos with herbal extracts &ndash; nettle, chamomile, sage, mother and stepmother, and also contain algae, vitamins A, K, C, and zinc. In the presence of dandruff shampoos choose from zinc, sulfur and tar. Do not buy shampoos, if they contain silicone, because they are heavier hair and make them even fatter.</p>

<p>Great popularity in recent years become dry shampoos that are especially useful on business trips, travel and the absence of hot water and time. These shampoos are available in powder form and are applied by spray. After 5-10 minutes, when the powder to soak up all the grease and dirt, his combed comb.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Depression, anxiety and fear - not a sentence, all curable]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/depression-anxiety-and-fear-not-a-sentence-all-curable/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-30T14:31:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/depression-anxiety-and-fear-not-a-sentence-all-curable</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/mood/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/mood/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Mood, vitality, there is no meaning in life&rsquo; &lsquo;Depression, anxiety and fear &ndash; not a sentence, all curable&rsquo;" > Depression is treated successfully with antidepressants. The problem of depression and other psycho-emotional disorders in this age of high speed is very urgent.</p>

<p>According to the WHO, the scale and speed of the spread of this disease are devastating, on the heels of such a &ldquo;popular&rdquo; diseases such as stroke, heart attack and diabetes. And the age of patients getting younger &ndash; if earlier depression affecting people after 40 years, but now the problem is widespread and adolescence.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>According to the same WHO, now every fourth &ndash; fifth of the Earth suffers what &ndash; or mental disorders, and by 2020 it is expected that depression will be the first in the world in disease.</p>

<p>However, do not confuse the real, medical depression with the usual blues and just a bad mood, because, at the household level depression &ndash; is sadness, grief and anguish. If you have just the blues, then there are many ways to cheer yourself and force of will to withdraw from this state.</p>

<p>Many people are faced with the phenomenon of temporary loss of mood and vitality, and everyone finds themselves out of this situation, what &ndash; something out. Who &ndash; is beginning to go hard in the gym who &ndash; that finds relief in the church, some with just dipped his head into some interesting job or hobby, alternate setting or go to rest. But if, unfortunately, you caught a real depression, then just your efforts will, unfortunately, will not be enough.</p>

<p>Depression, according to the definition in Wikipedia &ndash; is a mental disorder that is characterized by constantly depressed mood, loss of ability to experience pleasure, low self-esteem, and the complete loss of interest in life, and to that previously happy. The fact is that depression and mood decline is easily explained on a chemical level, and due to lack of production of the hormone serotonin in the body.</p>

<p>The role of this hormone in the human body is impressive &ndash; he is responsible for the process of cognitive activity, locomotor activity and muscle tone. But most importantly, it creates in us a sense of lifting mood and happiness, and so it is called the hormone of happiness. Normal levels of serotonin gives a person self-control, emotional and stress.</p>

<p>Some researchers have found that people who are dominant in society, have high levels of serotonin. People with a low level of serotonin, on the contrary, self-control, emotional stress and so reduced that the slightest pretexts are stressful, and as a result, depressed.</p>

<p>Very often people who are depressed, not knowing what was happening to them and trying to dull the emotional pain and anxiety begin to take alcohol or psychotropic substances, and this signing his own death warrant, because with the help of drugs and alcohol can only be purchased chronic alcoholism or drug addiction,  In this case, the craving for alcohol and drug abuse is secondary and serves the purpose of relieving anxiety and tension inherent in depression.</p>

<p>Moreover, the relatives of a person suffering from depression and alcohol secondary lapsed into alcoholism, of course, the best of intentions, are his &ldquo;encode&rdquo; to eliminate the pernicious craving for alcohol. But we must understand that &ldquo;coding&rdquo; refers to the psycho-terrorist methods and is based on an elementary intimidation sick that he could not lead a person to recovery, since no alcohol, no depression can not be cured in this way.</p>

<p>The big problem also lies in the fact that in our country are depressed people, especially young men, are often embarrassed to admit their psycho &ndash; emotional problems, ignore the problem and do not seek medical attention, thereby only exacerbating their condition.</p>

<p>Depression, as mentioned above, the only cure at will or not alcohol. This disease is treated with special drugs, which are called antidepressants, their effect on the regulation of the level of serotonin in the brain. There are so many antidepressants and use them to learn to successfully treat depression. Although long-term treatment and under mandatory supervision of a physician, but defeat disease is now possible once and for all.</p>

<p>Ashamed of their condition is not necessary, because it is the same disease as any other. Depression does not destroy the mind and human intelligence, it just does not allow him to live fully, and in a state of neglect often even leads to suicide.</p>

<p>Depression affects many of the greatest and brightest of today. British Prime Minister Winston Churchill struggled all his life with depression and called it &ldquo;the black dog that with me all my life.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Therefore, if you are suffering from depression and she does not go alone for a long time, do not worry, nothing bad has happened to you, just dropped us a much-needed level of the hormone serotonin. Entrust your problems doctor and competent therapist with the necessary medicines will return the joy in your life.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nail fungus. Fungal nail disease, symptoms and prevention]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nail-fungus-fungal-nail-disease-symptoms-and-prevention/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-30T14:29:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/nail-fungus-fungal-nail-disease-symptoms-and-prevention</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/nail-fungus/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/nail-fungus/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Fungal nail disease, nail fungus&rsquo; &lsquo;Nail fungus. Fungal nail disease, symptoms and prevention&rsquo;" > Fungal nail disease and still require early treatment and prevention. Fungal nail disease and stop its rapid growth concern dermatologists around the world. According to their estimates, is suffering from a quarter of the world&rsquo;s population, especially in large cities with high population density, and this figure continues to grow.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Causes and Symptoms of fungal infections of nails and feet</h2>

<p>Ways of getting a lot of fungus in the body, you can catch anywhere, but most often it is on the beach, in the bath, in the pool, the sauna or the shoes of people infected.</p>

<p>Nail Fungus transmitted not only from person to person, but also from animals to humans, and from the external environment. Complicating the situation is that there is a great variety of mushrooms, more than 1.5 million of them are pathogenic to humans about 500 species.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, fungal infections do not produce immunity, and a person can be infected by the same form of the fungus many times. Fungi remarkably tenacious, as evidenced by the scientists conducted an unusual experiment &ndash; they put the shoes sick fungus man in a locker, and when 20 years later got her out of there, the spores of the fungus were fully viable. Therefore a crucial role in the fight against fungi plays prevention of fungal nail diseases and personal hygiene.</p>

<p>Mushrooms particularly active subject in humidity, heat and poor ventilation, and excessive use of soaps and detergents do not give that effect, which we expect hard observing hygiene. The fact that the surface of our skin has a protective, so-called lipid layer, the finest film of fat that they live in our &ldquo;native&rdquo; beneficial bacteria designed to protect us from the adverse effects of the environment.</p>

<p>Doctors do not recommend to wash with soap and water often, as when washing wool we literally rip off off this protective film, and a variety of micro-organisms, bacteria and fungi literally stick to our body without resistance, is not completely restore the natural cover, which takes about</p>

<p>An interesting scientific fact &ndash; in the 30-ies of the last century, during the establishment of the Soviet regime, the Chukchi, Evenki and other northern nations have become hard to teach hygiene, wash with soap making. The result was so unexpected that at first the doctors just shrugged and could not understand why Aboriginal started such a colossal death.</p>

<p>As it turned out later, soap destroying the protective layer of fat covering their skin and they were completely defenseless against the invasion of microorganisms. By the way, the researchers argue that it is for this same reason, and we often get sick after a bath, and not from the fact that hypothermia is commonly thought. Nature, as we know, did not know soap, the use of detergents &ndash; is a recent invention of European civilization. If you do not want to kill a cat or dog, do not wash them with soap or shampoo, because the animal can not live long in such a &ldquo;sterile&rdquo;.</p>

<p>If it affects the human fungal disease, first, as a rule, there are cracks between the toes and on the soles, and then passes the infection on your nails. It is believed that the fungus uncured stop sooner or later turns into a nail fungus from which escape is not so easy. Man begins to disturb the symptoms of fungal nail diseases &ndash; itching, discomfort and bad breath. Nail changes color becomes dull, opaque, crumbles, deformed, thickened. If the disease is not treated in time, the nail may collapse completely, and the fungus will eventually hit the nails on the hands.</p>

<p>If you do not fight the infection, the fungus begins to &ldquo;walk&rdquo; around the body, releasing toxins that affects the lymphatic and circulatory systems, reduces immunity and causes multiple allergies, sometimes even able to hit the brain. Man gets tired quickly, feel malaise, nausea, frequent colds.</p>

<h2>Prevention of fungal nail diseases</h2>

<p>Nail fungal disease is considered to be the surrender of immunity, so it is often susceptible to it people with weakened or immature immune, that is, children and the elderly. Considered a risk factor for various scratches, abrasions and other skin damage through which the fungus is easier to penetrate into the body, which are the gateway for incoming infections.</p>

<p>If you notice the first signs of fungal nail disease, such as discoloration of the nail, its transparency, thickening of the nail plate, an inflammation of the skin around the nail, as well as itching and redness between the toes, it is necessary without delay to see a doctor &ndash; dermatologist and deliver  The fungus is now successfully treated thanks to the arsenal of physicians in a large range of antifungal drugs. Most importantly, time to start treatment and prevent total capture of infection in your body.</p>

<p>If the affected area is small, it is often possible to cope with the fungus by local treatment. If the process of infection went away, then the treatment will be more time consuming, but, in any case, it should bring to an end, as the untreated fungus necessarily continue its destructive work. In the treatment of a family member, all others should also be examined, as most at risk of infection.</p>

<p>Better prevention of fungal infections of nails and feet &ndash; a thorough safety precautions to prevent re-infection. If you have been in a public bath and not too sure of its sterility, the best means of prevention is the treatment of foot boric alcohol or vinegar diluted as 1 tablespoon per cup of water, the media is detrimental to the fungus. Do not wear someone else&rsquo;s shoes, dry the feet, all the scratches and damage immediately treated with iodine or green paint.</p>

<p>When buying shoes, choose a spacious, comfortable, preferably made of natural materials and vented, because, as mentioned above, the fungus loves moist environment without air. Their shoes and do not forget to air regularly and periodically wipe the inside with a solution of vinegar, which kills germs, while leaving no odor.</p>

<p>If you nail fungal diseases is very important to strengthen your own immune system, destroyed the invasion of fungal infection. So, get the overall strengthening and healing the body &ndash; drink plenty of water, eat only healthy food with the required amount of vitamins and minerals, do not overeat, sometimes it is better to starve. And certainly normalize intestinal function, go in uncomplicated physical exercise, get enough sleep and maximize protect yourself from the stress.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hemorrhoids - Causes]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoids-causes/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-24T20:14:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoids-causes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/causes-of-hemorrhoids/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/causes-of-hemorrhoids/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Causes of hemorrhoids&rsquo; &lsquo;Hemorrhoids &ndash; Causes, Symptoms, stages and modern methods of treatment&rsquo;" > Modern methods of hemorrhoid treatment eliminates the need for surgery. Hemorrhoids called the veins of the rectum, resulting in the formation hemorrhoids that cause severe pain (especially in the act of defecation), bleed, fall out and cause a lot of people suffering physical and social problems.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Unfortunately, hemorrhoids have traditionally been considered &lsquo;shameful&rsquo; intimate problem and therefore postponed the visit to the doctor, as a rule, to the last, when the disease has already started and is accompanied by a strong unbearable bolyu.Po to the proctologist, about 70% of people experience these or other symptoms</p>

<h2>Causes of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Causes of hemorrhoids are quite diverse &ndash; an impetus to the development of the disease can provide both genetic factors (congenital anomalies of venous walls) and the error in the diet, unhealthy lifestyle, chronic internal diseases and pregnancy.</p>

<p><strong>Among the main causes of the disease doctors are the following:</strong></p>

<p>Long-term sedentary work leads to stagnation of blood in the pelvic organs. Therefore, the risk of disease has traditionally include all workers of &ldquo;sedentary&rdquo; jobs &ndash; drivers, accountants, operators, programmers, and the like</p>

<p>A sedentary lifestyle also contributes to the development of hemorrhoids, as due to lack of physical activity, and there is blood stasis is formed venous insufficiency.</p>

<p>Finding feet long and considerable physical load is not less harmful than hypodynamy as delay provokes blood in the veins and increase the pressure therein, resulting in venous wall gradually loses its elasticity. This process is most susceptible to teachers, dancers, hair stylists, as well as loaders and lifters.</p>

<p>Chronic constipation, according to the doctors, are the most common cause of hemorrhoids. As a result of constipation bowel movement feces inside difficult, it accumulates in the lower parts of it and pinched the vein, thus significantly impairing blood flow. In addition, further increase intra-abdominal pressure attempts suffering severe constipation in the act of defecation.</p>

<p>Alcohol and spicy food. Hot spices contribute to a strong flow of blood to the rectum and irritate the delicate lining of her. Alcohol provokes an excessive expansion of blood vessels and blood stagnation in the formation and inflammation of hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>Different tumors and inflammation in the pelvis often causes the development of hemorrhoids. These include gynecological problems (fibroids, uterine fibroids), inflammation of the prostate, liver cirrhosis, cancer of the rectum, as well as fistulas, ulcers and fissures.</p>

<p>Pregnancy and childbirth. During pregnancy, the growing uterus displaces all the organs of the pelvis up and the rectum, on the contrary, pressed down to the pelvic bone, squeezing blood vessels and helping to expand the veins and the formation of hemorrhoids. In the process of childbirth situation is further aggravated by the strong attempts mothers.</p>

<h2>Internal and external hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Hemorrhoids is divided into inner and outer, depending on where the hemorrhoids are located outside or inside.</p>

<p>When an internal hemorrhoid nodes are located in the lumen of the rectum. Outside the acute stage they are not visible to the eye and are determined only by special equipment. In the initial stage of internal hemorrhoids person usually has no idea of ​​developing the disease, while internal hemorrhoids do not begin to emerge in the act of defecating outside.</p>

<p>For external hemorrhoids nodes are outside around the anus, where they can be easily detected during normal feeling, even in the primary, painless stage. In practice, quite often (about 50% of cases) occurs combined hemorrhoids, which combines features of external and internal types.</p>

<h2>Symptoms and stages of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>The first symptoms of hemorrhoids are usually quite low, so they do not pay too much attention. However, as the disease progresses, all the unpleasant and painful sensations are enhanced.</p>

<p>First, the disease manifests itself only a feeling of heaviness or a sensation of a foreign body in the anus &ndash; this is due to swelling of the internal tissues of the anal canal.</p>

<p>After that arise in the anus itching and burning &ndash; a consequence of increasing the hemorrhoids, which is accompanied by minor blood and mucus secretions and causes irritation of the skin around the anus.</p>

<p>Then there are regular bleeding during discharge (of varying intensity). If at this stage to start emergency treatment hemorrhoids begin to precipitate and severe pain is constant, not only during defecation, but also in a sitting position and walking.</p>

<p>Proctologists distinguish 4 stages of hemorrhoids, depending on how much enlarged nodes, and how developed the degenerative process in the tissues muscle.</p>

<p>The first stage &ndash; increasing hemorrhoids, there is itching, burning, foreign body sensation in the anus, there are slight discharge of blood at the time of discharge. Because these symptoms are not permanent and occur only occasionally, the vast number of patients at this stage of hemorrhoids do not go to the doctor, the disease moves to the next stage.</p>

<p>The second stage &ndash; during bowel movements begin to &ldquo;creep&rdquo; nodules on toilet paper appearing regularly drop of blood. At this stage the nodes themselves are hiding back after bowel movements or a short period of time.</p>

<p>The third step &ndash; dropping nodes patient has to reduce a hand into the rectum to achieve more &ndash; less comfortable state. At this stage, the disease is already advanced, progressive and requires immediate medical attention, as the nodules begin to fall, not only during defecation, but also with any increase in intra-abdominal pressure (coughing, sneezing, lifting weights and even with little physical load).</p>

<p>The fourth stage &ndash; hemorrhoids will not reduce a fall or immediately after the reduction, look like bunch of grapes, very inflamed and painful. At this stage, very frequent bleeding, and pain in the anus is so strong that it is impossible to even touch the toilet paper. Intense frequent bleeding lead to anemia (low hemoglobin in the blood), which further worsens the patient&rsquo;s well-being.</p>

<p>In addition, the constant loss of hemorrhoids anal sphincter tone is reduced, and this may be total or partial incontinence of gas and liquid stool, which is a huge additional psychological problem for patients.</p>

<h2>Hemorrhoid Treatment at present</h2>

<p>Hemorrhoid Treatment in modern conditions completely depends on the stage of the disease &ndash; the sooner you start treatment, the better and faster will be the end result.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, the fourth stage of the disease, and, in some cases, with the third, no surgery do not work, so see your doctor as soon as possible and do not diagnose yourself by yourself. Self-treatment of hemorrhoids is dangerous because its symptoms such as itching, pain, bleeding and mucus, characteristic of many other diseases, including cancer.</p>

<p>According to medical statistics, in Europe, colorectal cancer ranks second among all diseases after lung cancer. This is due primarily to the fact that patients often go to the doctor too late, allowing you to develop many of the pathological processes and letting them start. There are cases where people have their own long-term cure hemorrhoids local Foot and micro enema, and as a result are hospitalized with terminal cancer of the colon.</p>

<p>If a proctologist after a comprehensive survey put you diagnose hemorrhoids, take responsibility for his recommendations, because the time to initiation of treatment will help in most cases, to avoid surgery and cure hemorrhoids without pain and complications. Under current conditions, only 5 -10% of cases of hemorrhoids require surgical intervention, in other successfully conducted minimally invasive non-surgical treatment methods.</p>

<p>In the first stage of hemorrhoids can be successfully treated with folk remedies, flebotropnyh drugs, various ointments, suppositories and preventive measures (special diet, therapeutic exercise, and the normalization of the bowel). If the disease is accompanied by hemorrhoidal bleeding, to eliminate it on the first and second stages of the disease is effective method of sclerotherapy.</p>

<p>After a few treatments of sclerotherapy improved tone of the anal canal, swelling and inflammation subside, the pain disappears. The procedure is as follows &ndash; a hemorrhoid or under the mucous membrane next to him is a special sklerotiruyuschim injection drug. Under the influence of drugs node is compacted, reduced in size and eventually atrophies (waived).</p>

<p>On the second and third stages of the patient may be asked to latekstnoe ligation sites &ndash; the newest popular method of treating hemorrhoids proctology in the world, which is a low-invasive, painless and performed on an outpatient basis. The essence of it is this &ndash; with the help of special devices on the hemorrhoid puts special latekstnoe ring that pinches the leg assembly and blocks blood flow in it. About a week and there is no manipulation of the node is expelled with the faeces.</p>

<p>Even if you have stage four of hemorrhoids, do not despair, modern proctology is not standing still and painful surgery hemorrhoidectomy with long-term disability benefits for a long time in the past. Instead, surgeons have successfully used the latest technology called &ldquo;dezarterizatsiya hemorrhoids through suture ligation.&rdquo; Dezarterizatsiya made, usually under local anesthesia in a day hospital, lasts no more than 30 &ndash; 40 minutes and a few hours after surgery, the patient may be allowed to go home.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The human papilloma virus - diagnosis]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/the-human-papilloma-virus-diagnosis/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-24T20:13:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/the-human-papilloma-virus-diagnosis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/human-papillomavirus-prevention/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/human-papillomavirus-prevention/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Human papillomavirus prevention&rsquo; &lsquo;The human papilloma virus &ndash; diagnosis, treatment and prevention&rsquo;" > Treatment of warts and warts laser can get rid of them forever. The human papilloma virus (HPV), or human papillomavirus, is a very common infectious viral disease that is transmitted from person to person, or sexual contact &ndash; through everyday.</p>

<p>According to medical statistics, it infected more than 50% of the population, especially vulnerable to his people with a weak immune system.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>What is the human papilloma virus</h2>

<p>The human papilloma virus &ndash; is the common name of a large group of viruses that includes more than 100 varieties.  ).</p>

<p>Doctors say that 75% of the adult population are healthy carriers of HPV, as many of his views of children are infected even in children&rsquo;s groups. However, before clinical manifestations, that is, warts, papillomas and warts, comes not always. In addition, the vast majority of infected children and young people (mostly under 25) appeared papillomas and warts go away on their own.</p>

<p>Fact that papilloma &ndash; virus, which does not penetrate deeply into the body and blood, it resides exclusively in the basal layer of the upper skin. Therefore, if an infected person&rsquo;s immune system is strong and powerful, he will banish HPV and HPV go away without treatment. If you have contracted the virus in adulthood and his expulsion did not happen for 1 &ndash; 3 years, you become a chronic carrier of it. In this case, with the papilloma &ndash; virus, most likely, you will have to put up with all my life, since drugs, completely killing it, scientists have not yet invented.</p>

<p>The incubation period of HPV infection usually lasts for several months, but in some cases may be increased up to several years. There are cases when HPV lives in the body for many years, sometimes from birth, not giving themselves known and seen for the first time in old age, under the influence of any adverse factors that triggered the depression of immunity.</p>

<p>Therefore, it is safe to say that, as in case of other viral and fungal infections (herpes, thrush), the appearance of papillomas and warts indicates a decline in immunity and only begins when the body&rsquo;s defenses weakened to such an extent that they are unable to  According to recent reports, even the formation of calluses on his feet through a type of papillomavirus.</p>

<p>Activation of HPV, in which the disease becomes invisible to the clinical stage, contribute to frequent change of sexual partners, urogenital infections (gerpevirus, chlamydia, ureomikoplazmoz, mycoplasmosis), immunodeficiency, hypothermia, severe stress, depression, alcohol abuse and smoking.</p>

<h2>Is it dangerous to papillomavirus</h2>

<p>When asked how dangerous papillomas and warts, doctors answer is that it depends only on the degree of tumorigenicity of the virus. There are viruses nizkoonkogennye (6, 11, 42, 43, 44), medium oncogenicity (31, 33, 35, 51, 52, 58) and a high degree of tumorigenicity (16, 18, 45, 56). Sometimes the same person can have multiple types of viruses at the same time.</p>

<p>Current laboratory methods for diagnosis of HPV, the most informative and sensitive of which is a PCR (polymerase chain reaction), allow to precisely determine the type of virus and its danger, that is, whether it is to oncogenic types.</p>

<p>Different types of virus in the human body often behave differently. It is known that the human papilloma virus type 2 is a non-tumorigenic, affects mainly the skin (skin papilloma virus) and causes warts and moles hanging on different parts of the body. The most frequent HPV in the neck, armpits, eyelids, under the breasts in women, but they can settle down and to the mucous membranes of the nose, throat, mouth, vocal cords, bladder, intestines and stomach.</p>

<p>Viruses 6 and 11 types are characterized by a low risk of carcinogenicity and provoke the development of papillomas of the mucous membranes of the genitals called genital genital warts or genital warts. Women warts often located on the labia, the cervix, the vagina, perineal urethra and anus. In men, they tend to focus on the head and body of the penis, sometimes in the urethra, which provokes a difficulty urinating, spraying urine and change in shape of the jet.</p>

<p>The most unfavorable for carcinogenicity are HPV types 16 and 18, often found in women with cervical cancer and in men with cancer lesions of the penis. Women who have found these types of HPV, for the prevention of cancer process, it is recommended mandatory vaccination.</p>

<h2>Diagnosis and treatment of warts and warts</h2>

<p>Treatment of HPV performed only in cases where there are any clinical manifestations &ndash; HPV or genital warts as well as their appearance indicates the activation of HPV. Completely remove the virus from the body, unfortunately, can not, can only be possible to suppress the activity of the viral infection and translate it into a &ldquo;sleep&rdquo; state, preventing relapse and reoccurrence of tumors.</p>

<p>Treatment of HPV infection consists of two stages &ndash; first performed the complete removal of papillomas (warts), and then held restorative therapy, aimed at strengthening the immune system and preventing relapse (receipt of antiviral drugs, vitamins, immunostimulants).</p>

<p>Now remove warts is carried out in many clinics modern and effective ways &ndash; by using a laser beam of liquid nitrogen (cryotherapy), by electrocoagulation (affecting papilloma electric current of high frequency) and radio waves. The most common methods of laser removal and removal of warts with nitrogen.</p>

<p>Laser removal of warts on the neck, eyelids, under the breasts, face and any other part of the body is made in a few minutes. The advantages of laser destruction include the fact that during the removal of warts laser they disappear forever, as the virus is killed by the heat of the laser beam. After the procedure in place papilloma dry crust is formed, under which there is healing. After 10 &ndash; 14 days it automatically disappears, while the skin is not different in color from the surrounding tissue.</p>

<p>Remove warts with liquid nitrogen is carried out, on the contrary, due to very low temperatures (&ndash; 196 C), with removable fabric from freezing completely destroyed and subsequently falls off, the skin underneath it loses its sensitivity and becomes white. Advantages of this method &ndash; after cryoablation procedure is left scars, does not require anesthesia, the wound heals quickly.</p>

<p>Remove Warts on the genitals or in the perineum, especially when a large area of ​​destruction, large-scale tumors or lesions of the anal canal, often requires general anesthesia. The main condition &ndash; all warts should be removed in a single session, to prevent the possibility of re-infection. After removal of warts patient assigned intramuscular injection analgesics for 5 &ndash; 6 days, and antiviral creams and ointments.</p>

<h2>Prevention of HPV infection</h2>

<p>In recent years, many people, especially young people, a very lightly to infections, sexually transmitted, trusting, if necessary, by means of powerful antibiotics. However, it is a dangerous delusion, because the viruses, including human papillomavirus, is not amenable to antibiotics. In addition, they are very unpredictable and difficult to establish.</p>

<p>By the cunning of HPV include the fact that the use of condoms during sex is not sufficiently reliable means of protection against papilloma infection, as well as from genital herpes because the ground is enough to infect the skin and mucous membranes. Therefore, prevention of HPV is becoming of major importance, especially for women.</p>

<p>If men, for the most part, after the infection are asymptomatic carriers of most types of HPV, the infection for women can have much more serious consequences &ndash; in 95% of women with cervical cancer and HPV diagnosed. That is why every woman should at least 1 time per year to visit the gynecologist and take a swab from the cervix to detect changes in the state of epithelial cells in the early stages.</p>

<p>This test, called «pap-smear» (PAP test), according to doctors, will significantly reduce the morbidity and mortality of women from cervical cancer in developed countries. In addition, infected women should do regular cervical colposcopy (examination of the state of the mucous membranes and tissues under a microscope), and if necessary, cytology suspicious areas.</p>

<p>According to the scientists, all of which appeared Hanging moles, warts and other growths should be removed prophylactically, without waiting for their rebirth in the disease. For example, if time does not make the removal of genital warts, they are self-propagating away from the area of ​​primary education, and to create all the new centers. In severe cases, the warts may coalesce with each other, getting kind of cauliflower, break away during intercourse, bleeding and even interfere with walking.</p>

<p>Since papilloma virus infection tends to recur after removal of tumors is necessary to carry out the mandatory control of cure and implement a set of measures that increase the activity of immune system and overall resistance to viruses and infections. To do this, you need to give up bad habits (smoking, alcohol), do not use without urgent need antibiotics, eat healthy, exercise regularly, walking in the fresh air and possibly to protect themselves from the stress.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
