<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: health and beauty | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/health-and-beauty/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-11-28T23:13:19+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hemorrhoids - Causes]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoids-causes/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-24T20:14:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoids-causes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/causes-of-hemorrhoids/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/causes-of-hemorrhoids/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Causes of hemorrhoids&rsquo; &lsquo;Hemorrhoids &ndash; Causes, Symptoms, stages and modern methods of treatment&rsquo;" > Modern methods of hemorrhoid treatment eliminates the need for surgery. Hemorrhoids called the veins of the rectum, resulting in the formation hemorrhoids that cause severe pain (especially in the act of defecation), bleed, fall out and cause a lot of people suffering physical and social problems.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Unfortunately, hemorrhoids have traditionally been considered &lsquo;shameful&rsquo; intimate problem and therefore postponed the visit to the doctor, as a rule, to the last, when the disease has already started and is accompanied by a strong unbearable bolyu.Po to the proctologist, about 70% of people experience these or other symptoms</p>

<h2>Causes of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Causes of hemorrhoids are quite diverse &ndash; an impetus to the development of the disease can provide both genetic factors (congenital anomalies of venous walls) and the error in the diet, unhealthy lifestyle, chronic internal diseases and pregnancy.</p>

<p><strong>Among the main causes of the disease doctors are the following:</strong></p>

<p>Long-term sedentary work leads to stagnation of blood in the pelvic organs. Therefore, the risk of disease has traditionally include all workers of &ldquo;sedentary&rdquo; jobs &ndash; drivers, accountants, operators, programmers, and the like</p>

<p>A sedentary lifestyle also contributes to the development of hemorrhoids, as due to lack of physical activity, and there is blood stasis is formed venous insufficiency.</p>

<p>Finding feet long and considerable physical load is not less harmful than hypodynamy as delay provokes blood in the veins and increase the pressure therein, resulting in venous wall gradually loses its elasticity. This process is most susceptible to teachers, dancers, hair stylists, as well as loaders and lifters.</p>

<p>Chronic constipation, according to the doctors, are the most common cause of hemorrhoids. As a result of constipation bowel movement feces inside difficult, it accumulates in the lower parts of it and pinched the vein, thus significantly impairing blood flow. In addition, further increase intra-abdominal pressure attempts suffering severe constipation in the act of defecation.</p>

<p>Alcohol and spicy food. Hot spices contribute to a strong flow of blood to the rectum and irritate the delicate lining of her. Alcohol provokes an excessive expansion of blood vessels and blood stagnation in the formation and inflammation of hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>Different tumors and inflammation in the pelvis often causes the development of hemorrhoids. These include gynecological problems (fibroids, uterine fibroids), inflammation of the prostate, liver cirrhosis, cancer of the rectum, as well as fistulas, ulcers and fissures.</p>

<p>Pregnancy and childbirth. During pregnancy, the growing uterus displaces all the organs of the pelvis up and the rectum, on the contrary, pressed down to the pelvic bone, squeezing blood vessels and helping to expand the veins and the formation of hemorrhoids. In the process of childbirth situation is further aggravated by the strong attempts mothers.</p>

<h2>Internal and external hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Hemorrhoids is divided into inner and outer, depending on where the hemorrhoids are located outside or inside.</p>

<p>When an internal hemorrhoid nodes are located in the lumen of the rectum. Outside the acute stage they are not visible to the eye and are determined only by special equipment. In the initial stage of internal hemorrhoids person usually has no idea of ​​developing the disease, while internal hemorrhoids do not begin to emerge in the act of defecating outside.</p>

<p>For external hemorrhoids nodes are outside around the anus, where they can be easily detected during normal feeling, even in the primary, painless stage. In practice, quite often (about 50% of cases) occurs combined hemorrhoids, which combines features of external and internal types.</p>

<h2>Symptoms and stages of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>The first symptoms of hemorrhoids are usually quite low, so they do not pay too much attention. However, as the disease progresses, all the unpleasant and painful sensations are enhanced.</p>

<p>First, the disease manifests itself only a feeling of heaviness or a sensation of a foreign body in the anus &ndash; this is due to swelling of the internal tissues of the anal canal.</p>

<p>After that arise in the anus itching and burning &ndash; a consequence of increasing the hemorrhoids, which is accompanied by minor blood and mucus secretions and causes irritation of the skin around the anus.</p>

<p>Then there are regular bleeding during discharge (of varying intensity). If at this stage to start emergency treatment hemorrhoids begin to precipitate and severe pain is constant, not only during defecation, but also in a sitting position and walking.</p>

<p>Proctologists distinguish 4 stages of hemorrhoids, depending on how much enlarged nodes, and how developed the degenerative process in the tissues muscle.</p>

<p>The first stage &ndash; increasing hemorrhoids, there is itching, burning, foreign body sensation in the anus, there are slight discharge of blood at the time of discharge. Because these symptoms are not permanent and occur only occasionally, the vast number of patients at this stage of hemorrhoids do not go to the doctor, the disease moves to the next stage.</p>

<p>The second stage &ndash; during bowel movements begin to &ldquo;creep&rdquo; nodules on toilet paper appearing regularly drop of blood. At this stage the nodes themselves are hiding back after bowel movements or a short period of time.</p>

<p>The third step &ndash; dropping nodes patient has to reduce a hand into the rectum to achieve more &ndash; less comfortable state. At this stage, the disease is already advanced, progressive and requires immediate medical attention, as the nodules begin to fall, not only during defecation, but also with any increase in intra-abdominal pressure (coughing, sneezing, lifting weights and even with little physical load).</p>

<p>The fourth stage &ndash; hemorrhoids will not reduce a fall or immediately after the reduction, look like bunch of grapes, very inflamed and painful. At this stage, very frequent bleeding, and pain in the anus is so strong that it is impossible to even touch the toilet paper. Intense frequent bleeding lead to anemia (low hemoglobin in the blood), which further worsens the patient&rsquo;s well-being.</p>

<p>In addition, the constant loss of hemorrhoids anal sphincter tone is reduced, and this may be total or partial incontinence of gas and liquid stool, which is a huge additional psychological problem for patients.</p>

<h2>Hemorrhoid Treatment at present</h2>

<p>Hemorrhoid Treatment in modern conditions completely depends on the stage of the disease &ndash; the sooner you start treatment, the better and faster will be the end result.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, the fourth stage of the disease, and, in some cases, with the third, no surgery do not work, so see your doctor as soon as possible and do not diagnose yourself by yourself. Self-treatment of hemorrhoids is dangerous because its symptoms such as itching, pain, bleeding and mucus, characteristic of many other diseases, including cancer.</p>

<p>According to medical statistics, in Europe, colorectal cancer ranks second among all diseases after lung cancer. This is due primarily to the fact that patients often go to the doctor too late, allowing you to develop many of the pathological processes and letting them start. There are cases where people have their own long-term cure hemorrhoids local Foot and micro enema, and as a result are hospitalized with terminal cancer of the colon.</p>

<p>If a proctologist after a comprehensive survey put you diagnose hemorrhoids, take responsibility for his recommendations, because the time to initiation of treatment will help in most cases, to avoid surgery and cure hemorrhoids without pain and complications. Under current conditions, only 5 -10% of cases of hemorrhoids require surgical intervention, in other successfully conducted minimally invasive non-surgical treatment methods.</p>

<p>In the first stage of hemorrhoids can be successfully treated with folk remedies, flebotropnyh drugs, various ointments, suppositories and preventive measures (special diet, therapeutic exercise, and the normalization of the bowel). If the disease is accompanied by hemorrhoidal bleeding, to eliminate it on the first and second stages of the disease is effective method of sclerotherapy.</p>

<p>After a few treatments of sclerotherapy improved tone of the anal canal, swelling and inflammation subside, the pain disappears. The procedure is as follows &ndash; a hemorrhoid or under the mucous membrane next to him is a special sklerotiruyuschim injection drug. Under the influence of drugs node is compacted, reduced in size and eventually atrophies (waived).</p>

<p>On the second and third stages of the patient may be asked to latekstnoe ligation sites &ndash; the newest popular method of treating hemorrhoids proctology in the world, which is a low-invasive, painless and performed on an outpatient basis. The essence of it is this &ndash; with the help of special devices on the hemorrhoid puts special latekstnoe ring that pinches the leg assembly and blocks blood flow in it. About a week and there is no manipulation of the node is expelled with the faeces.</p>

<p>Even if you have stage four of hemorrhoids, do not despair, modern proctology is not standing still and painful surgery hemorrhoidectomy with long-term disability benefits for a long time in the past. Instead, surgeons have successfully used the latest technology called &ldquo;dezarterizatsiya hemorrhoids through suture ligation.&rdquo; Dezarterizatsiya made, usually under local anesthesia in a day hospital, lasts no more than 30 &ndash; 40 minutes and a few hours after surgery, the patient may be allowed to go home.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The human papilloma virus - diagnosis]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/the-human-papilloma-virus-diagnosis/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-24T20:13:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/the-human-papilloma-virus-diagnosis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/human-papillomavirus-prevention/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/human-papillomavirus-prevention/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Human papillomavirus prevention&rsquo; &lsquo;The human papilloma virus &ndash; diagnosis, treatment and prevention&rsquo;" > Treatment of warts and warts laser can get rid of them forever. The human papilloma virus (HPV), or human papillomavirus, is a very common infectious viral disease that is transmitted from person to person, or sexual contact &ndash; through everyday.</p>

<p>According to medical statistics, it infected more than 50% of the population, especially vulnerable to his people with a weak immune system.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>What is the human papilloma virus</h2>

<p>The human papilloma virus &ndash; is the common name of a large group of viruses that includes more than 100 varieties.  ).</p>

<p>Doctors say that 75% of the adult population are healthy carriers of HPV, as many of his views of children are infected even in children&rsquo;s groups. However, before clinical manifestations, that is, warts, papillomas and warts, comes not always. In addition, the vast majority of infected children and young people (mostly under 25) appeared papillomas and warts go away on their own.</p>

<p>Fact that papilloma &ndash; virus, which does not penetrate deeply into the body and blood, it resides exclusively in the basal layer of the upper skin. Therefore, if an infected person&rsquo;s immune system is strong and powerful, he will banish HPV and HPV go away without treatment. If you have contracted the virus in adulthood and his expulsion did not happen for 1 &ndash; 3 years, you become a chronic carrier of it. In this case, with the papilloma &ndash; virus, most likely, you will have to put up with all my life, since drugs, completely killing it, scientists have not yet invented.</p>

<p>The incubation period of HPV infection usually lasts for several months, but in some cases may be increased up to several years. There are cases when HPV lives in the body for many years, sometimes from birth, not giving themselves known and seen for the first time in old age, under the influence of any adverse factors that triggered the depression of immunity.</p>

<p>Therefore, it is safe to say that, as in case of other viral and fungal infections (herpes, thrush), the appearance of papillomas and warts indicates a decline in immunity and only begins when the body&rsquo;s defenses weakened to such an extent that they are unable to  According to recent reports, even the formation of calluses on his feet through a type of papillomavirus.</p>

<p>Activation of HPV, in which the disease becomes invisible to the clinical stage, contribute to frequent change of sexual partners, urogenital infections (gerpevirus, chlamydia, ureomikoplazmoz, mycoplasmosis), immunodeficiency, hypothermia, severe stress, depression, alcohol abuse and smoking.</p>

<h2>Is it dangerous to papillomavirus</h2>

<p>When asked how dangerous papillomas and warts, doctors answer is that it depends only on the degree of tumorigenicity of the virus. There are viruses nizkoonkogennye (6, 11, 42, 43, 44), medium oncogenicity (31, 33, 35, 51, 52, 58) and a high degree of tumorigenicity (16, 18, 45, 56). Sometimes the same person can have multiple types of viruses at the same time.</p>

<p>Current laboratory methods for diagnosis of HPV, the most informative and sensitive of which is a PCR (polymerase chain reaction), allow to precisely determine the type of virus and its danger, that is, whether it is to oncogenic types.</p>

<p>Different types of virus in the human body often behave differently. It is known that the human papilloma virus type 2 is a non-tumorigenic, affects mainly the skin (skin papilloma virus) and causes warts and moles hanging on different parts of the body. The most frequent HPV in the neck, armpits, eyelids, under the breasts in women, but they can settle down and to the mucous membranes of the nose, throat, mouth, vocal cords, bladder, intestines and stomach.</p>

<p>Viruses 6 and 11 types are characterized by a low risk of carcinogenicity and provoke the development of papillomas of the mucous membranes of the genitals called genital genital warts or genital warts. Women warts often located on the labia, the cervix, the vagina, perineal urethra and anus. In men, they tend to focus on the head and body of the penis, sometimes in the urethra, which provokes a difficulty urinating, spraying urine and change in shape of the jet.</p>

<p>The most unfavorable for carcinogenicity are HPV types 16 and 18, often found in women with cervical cancer and in men with cancer lesions of the penis. Women who have found these types of HPV, for the prevention of cancer process, it is recommended mandatory vaccination.</p>

<h2>Diagnosis and treatment of warts and warts</h2>

<p>Treatment of HPV performed only in cases where there are any clinical manifestations &ndash; HPV or genital warts as well as their appearance indicates the activation of HPV. Completely remove the virus from the body, unfortunately, can not, can only be possible to suppress the activity of the viral infection and translate it into a &ldquo;sleep&rdquo; state, preventing relapse and reoccurrence of tumors.</p>

<p>Treatment of HPV infection consists of two stages &ndash; first performed the complete removal of papillomas (warts), and then held restorative therapy, aimed at strengthening the immune system and preventing relapse (receipt of antiviral drugs, vitamins, immunostimulants).</p>

<p>Now remove warts is carried out in many clinics modern and effective ways &ndash; by using a laser beam of liquid nitrogen (cryotherapy), by electrocoagulation (affecting papilloma electric current of high frequency) and radio waves. The most common methods of laser removal and removal of warts with nitrogen.</p>

<p>Laser removal of warts on the neck, eyelids, under the breasts, face and any other part of the body is made in a few minutes. The advantages of laser destruction include the fact that during the removal of warts laser they disappear forever, as the virus is killed by the heat of the laser beam. After the procedure in place papilloma dry crust is formed, under which there is healing. After 10 &ndash; 14 days it automatically disappears, while the skin is not different in color from the surrounding tissue.</p>

<p>Remove warts with liquid nitrogen is carried out, on the contrary, due to very low temperatures (&ndash; 196 C), with removable fabric from freezing completely destroyed and subsequently falls off, the skin underneath it loses its sensitivity and becomes white. Advantages of this method &ndash; after cryoablation procedure is left scars, does not require anesthesia, the wound heals quickly.</p>

<p>Remove Warts on the genitals or in the perineum, especially when a large area of ​​destruction, large-scale tumors or lesions of the anal canal, often requires general anesthesia. The main condition &ndash; all warts should be removed in a single session, to prevent the possibility of re-infection. After removal of warts patient assigned intramuscular injection analgesics for 5 &ndash; 6 days, and antiviral creams and ointments.</p>

<h2>Prevention of HPV infection</h2>

<p>In recent years, many people, especially young people, a very lightly to infections, sexually transmitted, trusting, if necessary, by means of powerful antibiotics. However, it is a dangerous delusion, because the viruses, including human papillomavirus, is not amenable to antibiotics. In addition, they are very unpredictable and difficult to establish.</p>

<p>By the cunning of HPV include the fact that the use of condoms during sex is not sufficiently reliable means of protection against papilloma infection, as well as from genital herpes because the ground is enough to infect the skin and mucous membranes. Therefore, prevention of HPV is becoming of major importance, especially for women.</p>

<p>If men, for the most part, after the infection are asymptomatic carriers of most types of HPV, the infection for women can have much more serious consequences &ndash; in 95% of women with cervical cancer and HPV diagnosed. That is why every woman should at least 1 time per year to visit the gynecologist and take a swab from the cervix to detect changes in the state of epithelial cells in the early stages.</p>

<p>This test, called «pap-smear» (PAP test), according to doctors, will significantly reduce the morbidity and mortality of women from cervical cancer in developed countries. In addition, infected women should do regular cervical colposcopy (examination of the state of the mucous membranes and tissues under a microscope), and if necessary, cytology suspicious areas.</p>

<p>According to the scientists, all of which appeared Hanging moles, warts and other growths should be removed prophylactically, without waiting for their rebirth in the disease. For example, if time does not make the removal of genital warts, they are self-propagating away from the area of ​​primary education, and to create all the new centers. In severe cases, the warts may coalesce with each other, getting kind of cauliflower, break away during intercourse, bleeding and even interfere with walking.</p>

<p>Since papilloma virus infection tends to recur after removal of tumors is necessary to carry out the mandatory control of cure and implement a set of measures that increase the activity of immune system and overall resistance to viruses and infections. To do this, you need to give up bad habits (smoking, alcohol), do not use without urgent need antibiotics, eat healthy, exercise regularly, walking in the fresh air and possibly to protect themselves from the stress.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-cellulite massage at home - cups]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/anti-cellulite-massage-at-home-cups/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-24T20:11:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/anti-cellulite-massage-at-home-cups</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/cellulite-massage-at-home/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/cellulite-massage-at-home/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Anti-cellulite massage at home&rsquo; &lsquo;Anti-cellulite massage at home &ndash; cups, honey, brush&rsquo;" > Anti-cellulite massage at home helps to keep the skin in pristine condition. Anti-cellulite massage at home is the most affordable and effective means of dealing with cellulite. Because it can significantly improve the condition of the &ldquo;problem&rdquo; areas, increase circulation of blood and lymph in the subcutaneous fat layer and accelerate the elimination of toxins, toxins and metabolic products from the intercellular space.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>The principles and techniques of anti-cellulite self-massage</h2>

<p>The basic principles of anti-cellulite self-massage is quite simple &ndash; having mastered them, you can always maintain your skin in perfect condition, without resorting to expensive beauty salons.</p>

<p>Cellulite self-massage should be carried out energetic, but lightly. Common misconception of many women is that, ostensibly, to use as much physical strength. If you overdo and you will be too hard to knead and squeeze the skin, you will make a reverse effect &ndash; the deterioration of the situation and the weakening of lymph flow. There are cases where the use of unnecessary force due to the effect of cellulite noticeably intensified.</p>

<p>To avoid compromising the lymph flow is prohibited to massage in the groin, thigh dimples, inner upper thighs and the area around the pubic area.</p>

<p>The massage should be required from the bottom up.</p>

<p>For best results, before a session of self-massage, heat the good body with exercise or a warm shower. Hands should also not be cold &ndash; warm them by rubbing your palms against each other.</p>

<p>In order to achieve rapid results cellulite self-massage is desirable to carry out daily, ideally twice a day &ndash; morning and evening for 15-30 minutes. The first tangible results in the fight against cellulite, with due diligence, typically appear after 1-2 months.</p>

<h2>Key anti-cellulite self-massage techniques of hand</h2>

<p>In the exercise of self-massage hand-applied 3 main reception &ndash; rubbing, squeezing and pat.</p>

<p>Grinding &ndash; is carried out in a circular motion (clockwise) of the entire surface of the palm. In the thighs rubbing should be done in a circular motion, and on his feet &ndash; from the bottom up.</p>

<p>Pressing &ndash; at this reception to grab with both hands as much as possible the skin and knead &ldquo;the dough&rdquo;, while avoiding compression of the skin. Pushing effectively improves the tone flabby muscles.</p>

<p>Pat &ndash; the most effective massage techniques, carried out or the whole hand, or knuckles, clenched in a fist. In this case, applied a series of rhythmic strokes of varying intensity. Pat can be done to rhythmic music, producing them in time.</p>

<p>The most popular win these types of anti-cellulite massage as domestic cups, honey, and self-massage with a brush.</p>

<h2>Brush-cellulite massage</h2>

<p>Cellulite massage brush, according to the beauticians, the best way to recover at home blood and lymph circulation. It is held by a special massage brush with a handle, which can be purchased in a pharmacy or a department funds for the care of the body.</p>

<p>The skin must be dry, without the use of oils and creams, not to injure the skin. Brush technique of self-massage is circular motions (clockwise) for each zone massaged enough for about 40 &ndash; 60 movements. Movements should be moderate, but the skin at the same time should get red in the face considerably. The feeling of warmth and redness typically lasts for an hour.</p>

<p>When selecting the brush, give preference to natural thick stubble. If the brush is new and with the rough nap before applying pour over it several times with boiling water and mash the pile to make it less prickly. Remember that after the massage you should not have any bruises, scratches and tingling.</p>

<p>Beginning self-massage brush, divide it into zones necessarily rising from the bottom up. The best option &ndash; consistently handle first calf, then the hips and buttocks. The standard course of treatments &ndash; 30 &ndash; 40 daily sessions. Never use a hand-held anti-cellulite massage for skin diseases, varicose and heart disease.</p>

<p>Once a week, instead of the brush is useful self-massage to treat the cellulite areas of sea salt and freshly ground coffee. To do this, take a warm-up shower and rub in a circular motion with salt coffee or problem areas. After the procedure, put on body cellulite cream.</p>

<h2>Cupping cellulite massage</h2>

<p>Antitsellyuitny Cupping massage, thanks to the action of vacuum, well softens thick subcutaneous fat, so it is very effective for the correction of the beautiful contours of the body. In addition, it is quite effective in the fight against stretch marks (striae), and reduces swelling problem areas.</p>

<p>For the canned anti-cellulite massage using special soft cans sold in pharmacies. Just click on the jar, attach to the body and release it &ndash; work the principle of suction cups, and it would be easy to drive on the skin.</p>

<p>To Bank slid easily through the body, the skin is oiled with anti-effect. These oils can be purchased at a pharmacy or make your own. The basis of a 50 ml linseed oil or olive oil and added to it the choice of essential oils. Here are a few options for adding essential oils to the base:</p>

<p>5 ml of essential oils of orange, grapefruit and anise;
2 ml of oil red pepper and 5 ml of tea tree oil;
5 ml of essential oil of tangerine, lemon and dill;
3 ml of essential oils of fennel, juniper, lemon, cypress and tea tree;
3 ml of essential oils of lemon, mandarin, cypress, and 5 ml of vetiver oil.</p>

<p>Before canned massage, take a warm shower or do gymnastics, so that the body and the muscles are warmed up. Then apply the skin oil, and rub hands well &ndash; you need to slide the bank only on the body, not in your hand.</p>

<p>Bank needs to keep pressing her fingers on the sides and ensure that the skin is pulled into no more than 1.5 centimeters. If you overdo it, and the pressure in the bank would be excessive, move it through the body becomes hard. After the first few sessions may be small bruises, that&rsquo;s fine, as long as the body is not used to the procedures. If the bruises keep appearing and then, then chances are you are doing something wrong.</p>

<p>In addition, you can massage do not have to experience the pain and discomfort. If you experience any pain, do not have to endure &ndash; loosen the grip banks as cellulite affected areas should not be exposed to excessive squeezing.</p>

<p>Move the bank should be very smooth and continuous, circular movements should be directed strictly clockwise. Finish with every massage movement toward the venous outflow, with the tightness of its banks to rearrange and only then continue the session.</p>

<p>In order for the body to gradually got used to the loads, increases gradually during procedures &ndash; ranging from 2-3 minutes, increasing to 5 &ndash; 15 minutes for each problem area. Cup massage is a potent tool, so it is recommended not to do it more often than once every 2 &ndash; 3 days, standard course usually consists of 10-12 procedures. After a full course must be sure to take a break of 10-15 days, and only then, if desired, repeat.</p>

<p>Wonderful effect is a combination of canned massage with brush and antitsellyuitnymi wraps (acetic, mud, using algae and others). Procedures for self-massage brush and cans perfectly complement each other, as frolement well with the brush massage strengthens the capillaries and blood vessels, and the impact of self-massage cupping-glass vacuum at adjusts the flow of blood and lymph tissue.</p>

<p>As can massage should be done once every 2 to 3 days, and brushing every day, in the days when both procedures are coming, try to separate them in time to survive the interval between 4 &ndash; 6 hours, but not later than 20.00.</p>

<p>Contraindication to the cupping-glass vacuum cellulite massage is an inflammatory disease of the skin, malignant and benign tumors, large birthmarks in the area of ​​massaging, tuberculosis, poor blood clotting, thrombosis, thrombophlebitis and varicose veins in the area of ​​massaging.</p>

<h2>Honey cellulite massage</h2>

<p>Honey-cellulite massage &ndash; a unique and extremely effective way to fight cellulite, known since ancient Tibet. The content in honey is almost half of the periodic table provides power not only the skin but also the muscles, many internal organs and tissues. In addition, the unique effect of honey on your skin and the entire body is that it absorbs into itself all the toxins and wastes, literally sucking them through the pores of the skin.</p>

<p>For the massage, you can use only 100% pure honey, free of impurities and not exposed to significant heat treatment. It is advisable to buy it, or at a friend&rsquo;s beekeepers, or from a very trusted brands that exclude the possibility of forgery. Candied honey is not heated directly, or in the microwave, allowed only warm (not hot) water bath.</p>

<p>Before the honey massage is recommended to warm up the skin slightly, spending for 3 &ndash; 5 minutes of easy kneading. Then the honey slowly rubbed into the skin of a heated until it begins to thicken, making the massage movements impossible. After this tactic is changing &ndash; at first hand in turn tightly close to the body, and then pull up sharply. Such otlepleniya continue as long as the skin turns red, and honey does not darken and should not go gray flakes. This typically requires from 8 to 15 minutes.</p>

<p>Formed from the remnants of honey flakes removed using a hot compress and move to the massing of the other parts of the body. After the completion of the massage to shower thoroughly, since the waste honey, absorbed harmful substances are extremely toxic. After you cross the bridge, apply a moisturizer to the skin.</p>

<p>As you can see, honey massage technique is fairly simple, but, unfortunately, very painful. And, if you were not hurt, then massage simply failed. Helpful Hint &ndash; with the massaged areas necessary first remove hairs that massage does not become a real torture.</p>

<p>In the first session, if you can not endure the pain, not allowed to conduct massaging his palm and fingertips, until the skin becomes less sensitive. Moreover, during the initial procedures otleplenie hands can carry out more gently subsequently making them more sharp. No additional slaps and pressure on the skin to produce not need.</p>

<p>The most effective is a course of anti-cellulite massage honey from 12 &ndash; 15 procedures in a day. It is contraindicated only for allergies to honey and weak, located close to the skin surface vessels.</p>

<p>Since cellulite is a problem that the years do not pay attention to solving it is necessary to approach the complex &ndash; than the recommended massage techniques, it is necessary to eliminate the causes of cellulite, give up bad habits, as well as to normalize their diet and lifestyle.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Herpes simplex virus types I and II]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/herpes-simplex-virus-types-i-and-ii/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:47:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/herpes-simplex-virus-types-i-and-ii</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/herpes-virus-type/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/herpes-virus-type/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Herpes virus type&rsquo; &lsquo;Herpes simplex virus types I and II. Prevention of herpes&rsquo;" > A good immune system &ndash; the best prevention of herpes. At the household level, people used to think that herpes &ndash; an ordinary &ldquo;cold&rdquo; or &ldquo;fever on the lips,&rdquo; but it is actually not so simple. Herpes (from the Greek herpes &ndash; creeping) &ndash; a viral disease that affects the mucous membranes and the skin of a person.</p>

<p>It has been known to mankind for a long time and was described by Hippocrates, who gave him the name because of the &ldquo;creeping&rdquo; nature of the spread of the disease. Among the huge number of viral diseases herpes is a leader because, according to the scientists, latent, that is hidden, &ldquo;sleeping&rdquo; form, it affects about 90% of the entire population of the planet.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>There are about 100 species gerpevirusa, but only eight of these are able to cause diseases in humans, the most common herpes first and second type.</p>

<h2>Herpes virus type</h2>

<p>Herpes virus (HSV-1) is passed as influenza, via droplets &ndash; coughing, sneezing and by contact with the skin or mucous membranes of an infected person. The people he called the &ldquo;common cold on the lips,&rdquo; because, though striking the whole body, outwardly manifested mainly on the lips and nose wings.</p>

<p>The first time it enters the body of the first type of herpes virus does not manifest itself clinically, people do not even realize that he is infected. Before the acute phase of the illness is called the incubation period lasting from 2 to 14 days, during which the virus is actively propagated and implemented.</p>

<p>When the virus starts to become more active on the lips appear very painful blisters with fluid, severe itching, burning, swelling, often increased body temperature and increased lymph nodes. Then the bubbles begin to burst, sores scab, which is also very painful and can last up to 10 days. After healing of wounds virus again &ldquo;hiding&rdquo; in the body and is waiting for a chance for recurrence, the timing of which can not be predicted.</p>

<p>Infection with the first type initially occurs most often between the ages of 3-4 years, and the children of the first years of life almost never get sick herpes because they have immunity from the mother, and by 5 years of age, as a rule, already have in your body  Antibodies to genital virus most often appear in adolescence, around 15 years, initially infection penetrates not only through sexual organs, but also through the mucous membranes of the mouth and skin.</p>

<p>Earlier traditionally believed that the first type of virus affects the upper part of the body &ndash; the face, mouth, eyes and lips, and the second type of virus &ndash; the lower half of the body, usually the genitals. But, now, this division is purely conditional, since there are cases genital lesions gerpevirusom first type.</p>

<h2>Herpes second type</h2>

<p>Second type of herpes virus (HSV-2), more commonly called genital because, unlike the first type, it affects mainly genital mucosa. Transmitted mainly through sex, but also there may be cases of infection through saliva, oral-genital contact. Less common infection through casual through linen and personal care products, as well as through medical procedures such as blood transfusions and organ transplants.</p>

<p>If it affects the human genital herpes incubation period ranging from 1 to 10 days, then comes the acute phase, characterized by fever, malaise, weakness and increased inguinal lymph nodes, which is extremely painful. On the genitals appear painful blisters, itching and pain. Primary genital gerpevirus can last a very long time to heal 3-5 weeks.</p>

<p>A particularly dangerous genital gerpevirus for pregnant women, because the child becomes infected it either in the womb or during childbirth when passing through an infected birth canal.  They are very common neurological disorders, blindness and death. In this regard, it is vital for women planning pregnancy, tested for the presence of viral infections to its occurrence, and if necessary undergo treatment.</p>

<p>Someone gets sick herpes every few years, and someone every few weeks, often the virus affects the same areas. And, if the first type of herpes manifests itself quite rare, mostly not more than three times a year, the second type of herpes recurrences gives every couple of months, and sometimes several times a month, delivering huge human physiological, moral and social issues. According to studies, one in two women suffering from genital gerpevirusom, lonely and Neustroev in his personal life, which often leads to depression and a variety of neuropsychiatric disorders.</p>

<h2>Prevention of herpes</h2>

<p>Despite the enormous prevalence of herpes, most people are passive carriers of it and only 20% of people observed symptoms. Scientists have found that the whole family gerpevirusov is our constant companion throughout life &ndash; to introduce into the body one day, they&rsquo;ll never leave. And only on the condition of the immune system depends on how the virus will behave in the body &ndash; whether it will just live quietly, without letting themselves known, or will regularly remind yourself endless recurrence.</p>

<p>From the primary contact virus gets into the bloodstream and lymph nodes, and future behavior is entirely dependent on the state of the human immune system. When good immunity develops local, or local form of herpes. If, however, reduced immunity, the virus penetrates further into the body, affecting such important organs such as the liver, kidney, spleen, adrenal glands.</p>

<p>The virus accumulates in the cells and in response to various trigger factors will periodically cause permanent relapses. It is promoted by exposure to cold, chronic fatigue, poor diet, excessive exercise, stress, alcohol, antibiotics.</p>

<p>Since the medicine of today has in its arsenal of medicines that allow to completely heal cold sores, it becomes clear that in the first place there is the problem of prevention of infections and the overall strengthening of the immune system. Protect against genital herpes, in contrast to the first type of herpes that is transmissible through airborne droplets, it is possible, respecting the rules of personal hygiene: Do not use someone else&rsquo;s lipstick, do not smoke a cigarette for two, drink, and eat only with their dishes, use a condom and do not in any way engage in oral sex if your partner has gerpevirusa blisters on the lips.</p>

<p>In order to prevent the insidious virus of the herpes host in your body and spoil your life, will make every effort to maximize strengthen your immune system and viruses then no you are not afraid. To do this, use the entire arsenal of tools for healthy living &ndash; nutrition with the presence of all necessary for the body of vitamins and minerals, the correct drinking regime, moderate exercise, healthy sleep, as well as smoking cessation and alcohol.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vegetative - vascular dystonia (VVD)]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/vegetative-vascular-dystonia-vvd/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:46:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/vegetative-vascular-dystonia-vvd</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/vegetative-dystonia/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/vegetative-dystonia/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Vegetative-vascular dystonia&rsquo; &lsquo;Vegetative-vascular dystonia (VVD) Causes, types and treatment&rsquo;" > Vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia (VVD), and neuro-circulatory dysfunction &ndash; the pathological state of the autonomic nervous system, which results in insufficient supply of oxygen to tissues and organs. According to doctors, with one or other signs of VSD face about 80% of people of all ages.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Vegetative &ndash; dystonia symptoms and signs</h2>

<p>Vegetative (autonomic) nervous system located in the brain and spinal cord, is an essential part of the human body &ndash; it is fully coordinate the activities of all internal organs, blood vessels and glands of internal secretion and provides them to adapt with changes in the external environment.</p>

<p>In particular, the autonomic nervous system regulates blood pressure, heartbeat, body temperature, and composition of extracellular fluid volume, blood flow, metabolic rate, thirst, hunger and satiety, sweat gland function, kidney function, muscle tone internal organs, circadian (daily</p>

<p>For dystonia, which is a consequence of a breach of vascular tone, characterized by the following symptoms:</p>

<p>Neuropsychiatric &ndash; weakness, lethargy, fatigue, low efficiency, dizziness, headaches, sleep disorders, fainting, decreased sexual activity, and panic attacks;
Thermoregulatory action for breach of sweating and thermoregulation &ndash; spontaneous fever, excessive sweating, fever, flushing, or, on the contrary, sensitivity to cold extremities;
Spider &ndash; the instability of the arterial and venous pressure;
Cardiology &ndash; disruption of the heart, frequent heart contractions and pain in the heart;
Breathing (respiratory) &ndash; shortness of breath, chest tightness and a feeling of lack of air;
Dyspeptic &ndash; a disorder of the stomach &ndash; intestinal tract (constipation, diarrhea), voiding dysfunction and gallbladder dyskinesia.</p>

<h2>Vegetative &ndash; dystonia types and causes</h2>

<p>Despite the fact that the uniform classification of the IRR does not exist, the following types are divided vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia:</p>

<p>The nature of the disease:</p>

<ul>
<li>Permanent form &ndash; occurs without abrupt jumps in the patient&rsquo;s condition;</li>
<li>Paroxysmal or paroxysmal &ndash; manifested in the form of attacks (or panic attacks crises), in the intervals between attacks manifestations of the disease are almost invisible;</li>
<li>Mixed ESP (permanently-paroxysmal) &ndash; combines the features of a permanent and paroxysmal forms;</li>
<li>Latent, or hidden form &ndash; in this type of VSD disease may not manifest themselves for quite a long time, until the trigger factors (stress, illness, fatigue).</li>
</ul>


<p>Depending on violations of cardio &ndash; vascular system:</p>

<ul>
<li>Hypertensive type or vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia of hypertensive type. Accompanied by a significant rise in blood pressure (145/90 &ndash; 175/95 mm Hg. c.), sometimes with heart palpitations, sudden excitement, fever, symptoms of a panic attack, and, the pressure can be increased not only in times of emotional stress, but also in a state of complete rest;</li>
<li>Hypertensive type or vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia hypotonic type. In this case, the blood pressure is substantially lower than normal and reaches 100/50 and even up to 90/45 mm Hg. Art. and is accompanied by lethargy, weakness, shortness of breath, nausea, sweating, fatigue patient, sometimes fainting;</li>
<li>Normotensive or heart (cardiac) does not depend on the type of blood pressure and heart disorders defined by the (slow heart rate, or, conversely, rapid, feelings fade and disruptions of the heart), as well as pain in the chest area;</li>
<li>Mixed type of VSD combines multiple symptoms and signs typical for any type.</li>
</ul>


<p>Depending on the cause of vegetative &ndash; vascular dystonia, the following types of VSD: genetic, infectious &ndash; allergic, traumatic, psychogenic (as a reaction to stress or traumatic situations), and arose as a result of excessive emotional or physical stress.</p>

<h2>Vegetative &ndash; dystonia treatment and prevention</h2>

<p>From the timely and correct diagnosis of VSD depends largely on the success of further treatment. If you have frequent attacks of headache, weakness, dizziness, fatigue, insomnia, unfounded anxiety, fear, jumps in blood pressure and heart rate, &ldquo;lump&rdquo; in the throat, shortness of breath, pain in the heart and stomach, as well as grow cold and numb limbs &ndash;</p>

<p>Do not listen to bad advice of friends and acquaintances in an &ldquo;ESP is not a disease and will pass without treatment.&rdquo; Doctors claim that untreated dystonia is very dangerous because it can be complicated by panic attacks and other serious disorders that occur on the wrong team, the autonomic nervous system and debilitating nervous system.</p>

<p>When panic attacks (Sympathoadrenal crisis) a person starts suddenly (often in a public place) to shake, choke and breaking into a cold sweat. At the same time, he has a wild fear of death, heart pounding jumps and pressure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
