<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Weight-loss | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/weight-loss/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-05-21T16:52:30+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Persimmon Nutrition for Weight Loss. Persimmon Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/persimmon-nutrition-for-weight-loss-persimmon-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-07T07:31:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/persimmon-nutrition-for-weight-loss-persimmon-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/persimmon-nutrition-for-weight-loss-persimmon-diet/img.jpg" alt="Persimmon nutrition for weight loss.  Persimmon diet">For those who love sweets on persimmon diet works best: it allows you to quickly get rid of a few extra kilos and is very useful for health.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Persimmon nutrition: the benefits, the essence, advantages and disadvantages</h2>

<p>Calorie 100 g of fruit varies from 60 to 70 calories, so many people is not in question, can I use persimmon diet.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
This miracle fruit contains a large amount of nutrients has a positive impact on the human body:</p>

<ul>
<li>Vitamins;</li>
<li>Minerals;</li>
<li>Proteins;</li>
<li>Organic acids;</li>
<li>Fiber;</li>
<li>Tannin and pectin.</li>
</ul>


<p>The essence of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> on a persimmon nutrition is that a person uses a small amount of calories, due to which the weight starts to drop. Thus, the shortage of energy the body has to produce its own, breaking down existing fat deposits.</p>

<h3>Pros and cons of persimmon nutrition</h3>

<p>Slimming with persimmon has a lot of advantages:</p>

<ul>
<li>This fruit prevents kidney disease, is useful in nervous disorders and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/vascular-disease/" title="cardiovascular diseases">cardiovascular diseases</a>;</li>
<li>With this technique, you can quickly lose kilograms;</li>
<li>If all the rules harm health is not possible;</li>
<li>Dried persimmon and diet - the concept is almost incompatible, since it contains 274 kcal per 100 g It can be only replace meal - for example, dinner - and then will lose weight.</li>
</ul>


<p>Contraindicated eat persimmons people with diabetes and problems with the digestive tract, but during <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a> it is recommended by many doctors because of the fact that it has the most necessary elements for the normal development of the fetus.</p>

<h3>How much can you lose on a persimmon nutrition</h3>

<p>It is difficult to imagine a more <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7">effective product for weight loss</span> than the persimmon, and her diet helps to reduce the weight by 1 kg per day, if you are using strict menus, and up to 500 grams for the same period - if it is just to eat dinner instead.</p>

<p>Is the volume on the go with persimmon diet as well as weight? Of course, with the disposal of kilograms after some time it can be seen that the waist and hips become less than a few centimeters in volume, and remained the same breast.</p>

<p>Calorie diet on a persimmon depends on the menu, but it is usually possible to consume per day to 1,500 Kcal.</p>

<p>What products may be diet:</p>

<ul>
<li>Vegetables;</li>
<li>Fruit;</li>
<li>Fermented beverages;</li>
<li>Porridge;</li>
<li>Lean meat and fish;</li>
<li>Greenery;</li>
<li>Boiled eggs;</li>
<li>Hard cheese;</li>
<li>Cottage cheese.</li>
</ul>


<p>As in any other weight loss method, it is strictly forbidden to eat any high-calorie and sweet dishes, and if the menu is limited to just one product - to use once it is resolved.</p>

<p>The effectiveness of the persimmon nutrition is achieved precisely because throughout it has to restrict itself slightly in the food, but soon you can be sure that such restrictions are not in vain.</p>

<h2>Persimmon nutrition: diet menus, recipes, rules</h2>

<p><em>Slimming rules using persimmon:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Persimmon can eat in the usual form, or to cook from her salad when not using mono-diet;</li>
<li>To quickly clear the body and lose weight, you need every day to drink 1.5 liters of clean water without gas;</li>
<li>When used in foods only for 1-2 days it is recommended to refrain from strenuous exercise.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Strict persimmon diet: a menu for 3 days</h3>

<p><em>The most rigid diet is not designed for more than 3 days:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Eat up to 2 kg of persimmon;</li>
<li>Drink water, herbal or green tea.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Persimmon nutrition and yogurt</h3>

<p><em>A further embodiment can also be used not more than three days:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>We eat for the whole day, no more than 6 fruits;</li>
<li>We drink a maximum of 1.5 liters of nonfat yogurt.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Persimmon nutrition and apples</h3>

<p><em>You can replace the yogurt to apples, using this strict diet:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>We drink for 1-3 days 1 kg of apples and persimmons;</li>
<li>As for drinks, leaving only green tea and water.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet and persimmon bran</h3>

<p><em>It is known that bran well cleanse the body and strengthen the immune system and eating salad, cooked them and persimmon, you can lose a couple of extra kilos:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Persimmon grind, mix with a third cup of dry bran, pour all the fat yogurt;</li>
<li>We eat a dish for lunch, and on all other meals ready-made meals from the authorized products.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet persimmon and honey</h3>

<p><em>For weight loss per month for 7-10 kg can be used and this menu:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>We eat any food allowed;</li>
<li>For dinner, we eat a persimmon and 1 ch. L. honey.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Persimmon nutrition and rice</h3>

<p><em>Mono-diet, which lasts up to 7 days, to successfully get rid of 5-7 kg of excess weight:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>We eat only boiled rice without salt (500 g per day);</li>
<li>Eat up to 1 kg of persimmon.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Valerie Diet persimmon</h3>

<p><em>Singer periodically uses this 7-day diet to keep fit:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Breakfast porridge, cooked with water;</li>
<li>Lunch vegetable soup, and a steam cutlet;</li>
<li>Supper persimmons and glass of kefir.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Persimmon nutrition for pregnant persimmon</h3>

<p><em>During childbearing eating persimmon great benefit: eliminating the edema, strengthens the nervous system, removes excess fluid from the body, saturating it with potassium. To get rid of the astringency of the fruit, you can use one of the methods:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Keeping persimmon in warm water 12 hours;</li>
<li>Frozen and then thawed fruit;</li>
<li>Give the fruit ripen on the windowsill, if it is not fully ripened.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Recipes for a diet with persimmons</h3>

<p><em>Recipe salad of persimmons:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Clear the persimmons, cut it into circles;</li>
<li>Cut slices mozzarella cheese;</li>
<li>We spread the cheese on the persimmon, alternating with each other circles;</li>
<li>Sprinkle with pepper and pour olive oil.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Recipe soup with persimmon:</h3>

<ul>
<li>Cut into cubes of onion, sweet pepper and persimmon;</li>
<li>Fry the onion in vegetable oil, add the tomato paste and paprika, simmer on low heat for 5 minutes;</li>
<li>Add to the pan and persimmon pepper, simmer for 7 minutes;</li>
<li>Place the vegetables in a pre-cooked vegetable broth, boil, salt and pepper;</li>
<li>Before serving, sprinkle with herbs.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Recipe dessert with persimmon:</h3>

<ul>
<li>Pour boiling water over prunes, give him shall be melted;</li>
<li>Clean up and cut a persimmon;</li>
<li>We spread in a glass dessert first layer of low-fat cottage cheese, and more - prune and persimmons;</li>
<li>Finally, dressed with yogurt and sprinkle with cinnamon.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pressure Therapy for Weight Loss: What Is It?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/pressure-therapy-for-weight-loss-what-is-it/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-23T12:16:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/pressure-therapy-for-weight-loss-what-is-it</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/pressure-therapy-for-weight-loss-what-is-it/img.jpg" title="Pressure therapy for weight loss: what is it" alt="pressure therapy, apparatus for pressure">Pressure therapy - a method of hardware cosmetology, which helps to improve the skin condition by increasing microcirculation, eliminate edema, venous and lymphatic congestion phenomena. Pressure therapy - not a method of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>, although the site of many beauty salons, practicing this procedure, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a> can be seen in the number of indications.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>


<p>Pressure therapy - it&rsquo;s just a physical therapy action, which we should not expect miracles. This method is necessary for people who have impaired microcirculation. The blood flow in small vessels of the skin can suffer because of the sedentary lifestyle of various diseases, as well as because of their age. In women 45-50 years after the hormonal changes that are often accompanied by swelling. Sometimes they are invisible to the eye but the circulation of blood and lymph vessels in usually broken, and the effect of these processes becomes cellulite.</p>

<p>I should say that pressotherapy - not the cheapest procedure. Its cost is around 1000-2000 rubles. The entire course of therapy typically consists of 10-12 sessions. These prices do not explain the high efficiency of the procedure, which is comparable to a conventional massage. But the machine, which is carried out using pressure therapy, of course, costs money, and considerable. Accordingly, the procedure is, by definition, be more expensive than the same massage, which requires only a table and skilful hands of the masseur.</p>

<p>Pressure therapy is painless, so the procedure does not need to be afraid. You will dress suit with compartments for air. Then you lie on the couch, and the air is pumped in a suit. This unit allows you to adjust the mode of pressure therapy. There are various programs that are usually either directed to a massage, or a lymphatic drainage.</p>

<p>In some salons are machines for pressure therapy with different &quot;twists&quot;. For example, with infrared heating, which in turn has a positive effect on the microcirculation. Temperature effect allows dilate blood vessels and improve blood flow. However, hardly heating significantly increases the effectiveness of the procedure, increase the temperature because the surface of the skin can be even <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="at home">at home</a>. For example, immersed in a hot bath. The value of these innovations is likely to hit the ear trusting client and persuade him to pay for the expensive procedure.</p>

<p>Does the pressure therapy to lose weight?</p>

<p>As already stated, pressure does not affect the body fat mass. Neither the temperature nor the massage effect is not able to save you from excess weight. &quot;Lose Ground&quot; - nothing more than a slogan to lure customers. Pressure therapy - is a good way to fight cellulite, but no way to lose weight.</p>

<p>Why, then, the Internet has a lot of positive feedback about the pressure therapy, just as the procedure for weight loss? Why do people say that the field a few sessions they managed to lose 1-3 kilograms of weight? The mechanism of this &quot;weight loss&quot; is similar to what happens after the use of diuretic teas or limit salt in food. Weight loss is due to excretion of 1-3 liters of fluid.</p>

<p>However, in contrast to the same diuretics, pressure really brings &quot;extra&quot; liquid. Exit the water that has accumulated in the intercellular space due to the deterioration of the microcirculation. She does not need the body, and only puts pressure on small blood vessels, narrowing of the lumen and preventing normal blood flow.</p>

<p>Pressure therapy - no more than a cosmetic procedure. It will improve the condition of your skin and help in the fight against cellulite, displays the excess fluid from the tissues and eliminate congestion. As a method of pressure therapy is useless for weight loss, so do not do it on a bet. Currently, the methods of weight loss without effort there.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Protein, Fat and Carbohydrates You Need in a Day to Lose Weight?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-much-protein-fat-and-carbohydrates-you-need-in-a-day-to-lose-weight/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-23T11:46:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-much-protein-fat-and-carbohydrates-you-need-in-a-day-to-lose-weight</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-much-protein-fat-and-carbohydrates-you-need-in-a-day-to-lose-weight/img.jpg" title="How much protein, fat and carbohydrates you need in a day to lose weight" alt="proteins as needed daily, as needed fat per day">Proteins, fats and carbohydrates <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="every day">every day</a> we get from food, and they are vital to us. These substances in a given amount contains almost any food and are called macronutrients. And why do we need them?</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Proteins - building blocks for all body cells. They are composed of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids/" title="amino acids">amino acids</a>, which are divided into essential and nonessential. Interchangeable can be synthesized in humans only essential to reach a food composition. Proteins are necessary for growth, development, and in general for any physiological process; thus, they are absolutely safe in terms of possible accumulation of excess weight. The sources of protein are meat, fish, dairy products and legumes.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Fats - are made up of fatty acids, which are divided into saturated, monounsaturated and polyunsaturated. Today at all on hearing beneficial omega-3 and omega-6 acids, belonging to the group of polyunsaturated and can lower <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a>. It is also necessary for the absorption of fats, vitamins, synthesis of a number of hormones, the normal operation of many systems of the body. They are contained in both animal food (meat, fish, dairy products) and plant (nuts, seeds, vegetable oil) origin. Excessive consumption of fat - a way to lose the harmony.</p>

<p>Carbohydrates - the main source of energy. They can be simple (glucose, sucrose, etc.) and complex (cellulose, glycogen). Splitting of carbohydrates gives the body energy, the unspent portion of which can be converted into body fat. The main sources of carbohydrates - fruits, vegetables, cereals and sweets.</p>

<p>The diet of an adult to maintain its health and permanent weight gain there should be a certain ratio of these nutrients. Thus, our daily menu should contain:</p>

<p>Once in the digestive system, proteins, fats and carbohydrates are exposed cleavage with release of energy necessary for vital processes. The resulting energy is measured in units - kilocalories (kcal), which, for brevity, often referred to as calories.</p>

<p>Energy value of macronutrients varies. 1 gram of carbohydrate and protein is cleaved to release 4 kcal, 1 gram of fat - 9 kcal.</p>

<h2>Caloric intake and the ratio of macronutrients for weight loss</h2>

<p>Weight person depends on how many calories enters the body, and how much is consumed. If these amounts are approximately equal, the mass remains stable. If it receives more calories than consumed energy postponed &quot;in reserve&quot; in the form of fat.</p>

<p>Accordingly, to reduce weight, it is necessary to spend more calories than is consumed with food.</p>

<p>To calculate daily calorie your diet and calculate the necessary amount of proteins, fats and carbohydrates, using a few simple formulas. Try to make the calculations for yourself using these formulas and examples.</p>

<p><strong><em>1. First you need to calculate your basal metabolism.</em></strong></p>

<p>For women: 655 + (9,6 x weight in kg) + (height x 1,8 cm) - (4,7 x age);</p>

<p>For men: 66 + (13.7 x weight in kg) + (5 x height in cm) - (6.76 x age).</p>

<p>For example, take a woman 30 years Height 165 cm and weight 65 kg.</p>

<p>Its main exchange will be equal to: 655 + (9.6 x 65) + (1.8 x 165) - (4.7 x 30) = 655 + 624 + 297 - 141 = 1435 kcal/day.</p>

<p><strong><em>2. Next you need to determine your level of activity, as measured by the coefficient of activity:</em></strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Inactive (complete absence or rare sports activity) - 1.2;</li>
<li>Sedentary (light load 1-3 times a week) - 1,375;</li>
<li>Medium (load average 3-5 days a week) - 1.55;</li>
<li>Very active (full load 6-7 days a week) - 1,725;</li>
<li>Hyperactive (very high physical activity and physical work 7 days a week) - 1.9.</li>
</ul>


<p>For example, our woman working in the office, mostly sedentary work, to which she gets in transport. However, it is housekeeping, she loves to go shopping and sometimes wanders into a fitness club. So, its activity coefficient - 1.375.</p>

<p><strong><em>3. Now you need to determine daily intake of calories by the formula:</em></strong></p>

<p>The main metabolic activity coefficient x.</p>

<p>In our example, it is 1435 kcal/day x 1.375 = 1973 kcal/day.</p>

<p><strong><em>4. By subtracting from the resulting figure of 500 kcal, we get the amount of calories that we need to consume to lose weight.</em></strong></p>

<p><strong><em>5. In order not to drive themselves in such rigid framework, calculate the so-called &quot;corridor calories&quot; by the formulas:</em></strong></p>

<p>Energy intake for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> - 250 = lower limit</p>

<p>Kalorazh <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="slimming">slimming</a> +100 = upper limit.</p>

<p>That is, our women to lose weight, you need to keep your calorie daily diet within the 1223 - 1573 kcal/day.</p>

<p>In these calculations, it is important to remember that the daily calorie intake for women should not be lower than 1200 kcal. Calories less than this figure have a negative impact on health. 1200 calories a day - it is also very small, so it is better to consume more calories. Keeping within the corridor of calories, you will still lose weight.</p>

<p>To do this, go back to their energy capacity and percentage in the daily diet - 10-25% protein, 20-35% fat and 45-65% carbohydrates. And calculate what proportion they should take, given the upper and lower limit of the corridor calories.</p>

<p>For our example, it will have the following meanings:</p>

<p>So, to lose weight, a woman from the example should be consumed in a day 30.5 - 98 g protein, 27 - 61 grams of fat and 137.5 - 256 grams of carbohydrates.</p>

<p>Of course, this is a rough estimate, and these amounts are not necessarily comply with the accuracy of a tenth of a unit.</p>

<h2>Another obstacle on the road to weight loss</h2>

<p>We hope you have successfully reached the end of the calculations, and now in front of you is a piece of the figures, which you will need to make your diet. And how to be? Here begins the next portion of the complexities. In light of almost no foods which comprise only proteins, but only fats or carbohydrates - all products are mixed with a predominance of certain compounds. So 100 grams of meat is not equivalent to 100 grams of protein. And try to lead your diet in perfect match with the results of your arithmetic exercises you do not succeed.</p>

<p>The daily diet of a person must be present all the major macronutrients. Refusal or severely restricting some of them have a negative impact on your health and well-being. On the other hand, every person is different, and the need for those or other substances may also differ.</p>

<p>Counting the number of proteins, fats and carbohydrates - only one of many ways to achieve harmony and health. However, while one of the most difficult to execute. So it is not necessarily strictly follow it. You will achieve no less results if just eat varied, trying to eat less animal fat and sweets. And freed from the complex calculations time you can spend more usefully: first - on a visit to the gym, and then - to update the wardrobe&hellip;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cottage Cheese Diet Maggie. Menu Curd Diet Maggi]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/cottage-cheese-diet-maggie-menu-curd-diet-maggi/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-21T16:55:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/cottage-cheese-diet-maggie-menu-curd-diet-maggi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/cottage-cheese-diet-maggie-menu-curd-diet-maggi/img.jpg" title="Cottage cheese diet Maggie. Menu curd diet Maggi" alt="cottage cheese diet maggi menu">Diet Maggi and its variety - egg and cheese - has been repeatedly mentioned earlier. About the egg we discussed in great detail, the time came to light the principles cheese Maggi, which enjoys enough popular among people who want to lose weight.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>It can be described as: a low-calorie, low-fat, low-carb, high-protein. At first glance, perfect, containing no food components, is converted into fat, and includes only the necessary nutrients for life. In general, this diet is really very effective and, importantly, not &quot;hungry&quot;, but it has its drawbacks, which we will touch upon later.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Diet lasts 4 weeks, and during this time you need to follow a well-defined menu, which occupies a central place cottage cheese. Excesses and going beyond the list of approved products is prohibited; not recommended even pick up food analogues suggested, for example, replace the chicken. If the menu designated fruit or vegetables, among the first need not <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="choose">choose</a> sweet (grape, melon, dried fruit, bananas), and among the second preference amyloid (especially potatoes).</p>

<p>Be sure to drink at least two liters of fluid per day; it can be tea, coffee, mineral water. Sweetening drinks, of course, impossible.</p>

<p>Creator warned that the slightest deviation from the prescribed diet - and diet does not work, stop ubavka weight, kilograms and then come back, so that any failure of supposedly required to start a diet again. We can not say that this statement seems to be true; This is likely just some measure of deterrence, which raises awareness at losing weight and motivates them to the strict implementation of the rules of cottage cheese diet Maggie. But in fact, rare and small errors in the menu do not carry such harm, as promised harsh author so casually allowing freedom in the diet, it is not necessary to return to the menu, the first day of the diet and then resign ourselves to a month of severe deprivation. This is not only pointless, but for some people may not be useful, given the kind of load on the body creates a <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="protein diet">high-protein diet</a> either.</p>

<h2>Menu curd diet Maggi</h2>

<p>It is not particularly different from the egg option, the biggest difference is that instead of eggs is recommended to use low-fat cottage cheese.</p>

<p><strong>Day 1.</strong> Morning: fruit, 200 g of cottage cheese. Day: any fruit. Evening: a little bit of beef, vegetable salad.</p>

<p><strong>Day 2.</strong> Morning: Same Day 1. Day: boiled chicken breast. Evening: fish, vegetable salad, 1 slice of the dried bread, 1 grapefruit or orange.</p>

<p><strong>Day 3.</strong> Morning: Same Day 1. Day: low-fat cheese or cottage cheese, 1 slice of the dried bread, tomatoes. Evening: meat, vegetables.</p>

<p><strong>Day 4.</strong> Morning: the same. Day: any fruit. Evening: meat, vegetables.</p>

<p><strong>Day 5.</strong> Morning: as the day 1. Day: 2 eggs, vegetables. Evening: fish, vegetables, 1 orange or a grapefruit.</p>

<p><strong>Day 6.</strong> Morning: as the day 1. Day: any fruit. Evening: meat, vegetables.</p>

<p><strong>Day 7.</strong> Morning: as the day 1. Day: chicken, cooked vegetables, tomatoes, 1 grapefruit or orange. Evening: boiled vegetables.</p>

<p><strong>Day 1.</strong> Morning: The same as in the first week. Day: cottage cheese and vegetables. Evening: fish, vegetables, grapefruit or orange.</p>

<p><strong>Day 4.</strong> Morning: the same. Day of cheese or cottage cheese, plus any vegetables. Evening: meat or fish, vegetables.</p>

<p><strong>Day 5.</strong> Morning: the same. Day: fish (shrimp), vegetables. Evening: fruit, cottage cheese.</p>

<p><strong>Day 6.</strong> Morning: the same. Day: meat, grapefruit or orange tomatoes. Evening: any fruit.</p>

<p><strong>Day 7.</strong> Morning: the same. Day: chicken, tomatoes, boiled vegetables, grapefruit or orange. Evening: the same as during the day.</p>

<p>In the third and fourth week of the list of products provided for the whole day, the products are distributed on the meals yourself.</p>

<p><strong>Day 3.</strong> Boiled vegetables, fresh vegetables, fresh fruit.</p>

<p><strong>Day 1.</strong> A little meat or chicken (200 g), 2 cucumbers, 3 tomatoes, fruit, 1 slice of bread, the dried, Bank of canned tuna without oil.</p>

<p><strong>Day 2.</strong> Similarly, only without the chicken (you can meat) and tuna.</p>

<p><strong>Day 3.</strong> 400 grams of cottage cheese, a piece of boiled vegetables, 2 tomato and cucumber 1 slice of bread, fruit.</p>

<p><strong>Day 4.</strong> Chicken 500 g, 3 tomatoes, 1 cucumber, 1 slice of bread, the dried fruit.</p>

<p><strong>Day 6.</strong> The hen, a little cheese or cottage cheese, 1 slice of bread, 2 cucumbers and tomatoes, fruit, yogurt.</p>

<p><strong>Day 7.</strong> 400 g of cottage cheese, a portion of boiled vegetables, cans of tuna, 2 tomato and cucumber, the dried slice of bread, fruit.</p>

<p>This diet is over, however, limit caloric intake to maintain the progress achieved is to comply in the future. Furthermore, the transition to its regular diet recommended gradually for about a week.</p>

<h2>Reviews and Results</h2>

<p>As already mentioned, the diet is in great demand - first of all, because it allows us to achieve significant results. On average, it can help people manage to lose 5 to 10 kilos, depending on the amount of food eaten (<a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="at home">at home</a> several days a number of foods you can eat all you want, but it is a great temptation), and level of physical activity.</p>

<p>Against the background of fitness rate of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>, as might be expected, increases, but many note that due to the low power energy value of their sporting achievements largely affected: fatigue sets in more quickly, decreasing resistance to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a>. If it appears moderately and fatigue does not apply to daily activities, do not pay attention to it: a little lack of energy against the backdrop of high-protein food is natural and expected. That it brings you as little as possible of experiences, choose those kinds of loads, which are easier for you, such as <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/why-should-you-run-benefits-and-harms-of-running/" title="jogging">jogging</a> or swimming breaststroke instead of strength training.</p>

<h2>Contraindications and precautions</h2>

<p>A person with good health can go without losing much required 4 weeks curd diet Maggi, but the presence of certain diseases such change of the composition of food can be dangerous. It is contraindicated for people suffering from <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/constipation.html" title="constipation">constipation</a>, exacerbation of diseases of the gastrointestinal tract (any!), To patients with liver disease, and especially with kidney disease, accompanied by violation of their functions. These people attempt to lose weight through diet Maggie can end is not particularly impressive. At best, they just have to interrupt their efforts and left with nothing, and at worst it leads to hospitalization.</p>

<p>To diet have harmed before its compliance costs to make sure that your health will not fail. If there is any doubt on this score, not too lazy to visit their primary care physician and nutritionist, both professionals and ask the same question as in your case it is advisable to observance of cheese diet. Do not worry if you advise to choose some other method of weight loss, even if he will not be as efficient and fast. The main thing that should interest you - it does not desire to put on as soon as possible is that little dress or jeans, and the ability to safely lose weight by following a diet that you can enjoy life and its &quot;new&quot; figure, and not to pass long-term treatment of its consequences.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baths With Sea Salt for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/baths-with-sea-salt-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-21T14:30:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/baths-with-sea-salt-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/baths-with-sea-salt-for-weight-loss/img.jpg" title="Baths with sea salt for weight loss" alt="bath with salt for weight loss">Sea salt has been used in ancient Greece and was used as a treatment for various diseases: nervous, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/vascular-disease/" title="vascular disease">cardiovascular diseases</a>, diseases of the musculoskeletal system. Today, in the foreground is the use of sea-salt diet and getting rid of cellulite. Is it worth it to consider this remedy so much a reliable partner in the fight against <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>?</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>


<p>It is known that sea salt has a rich mineral structure, which ensures its beneficial properties. Seawater contains almost half of the periodic table, and a similar chemical composition is derived from its salt. Today sea salt is obtained in the same ways that a century ago - by evaporation. The elements contained in sea water in the greatest concentration, remain dry sea salt. These include:</p>

<p><em>Sodium and potassium</em> - contribute to the removal of the cells of the body of metabolic products.</p>

<p><em>Bromine</em> - has a calming effect on the nervous system.</p>

<p>In small quantities of sea salt in the presence of <em>gold, silver, palladium, selenium, boron, manganese, zinc, silicon, nickel</em>, and other minerals.</p>

<p>Concentrated saline is slightly irritating epidermis, increasing blood flow in small blood vessels. Because of this, the metabolic processes in the cells of the skin and subcutaneous tissue increase. Thus, salt bath help to improve skin appearance and to some extent reduce the appearance of cellulite. Salt also has anti-inflammatory properties, dries small foci of inflammation, so that the skin after bath salt looks more smooth and even.</p>

<p>Although bath and cosmetic products with sea salt is recommended for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>, the very salt of any fat burning properties are not allowed. And &quot;weight loss&quot; after a bath with sea salt does not occur because of the volume reduction of body fat. Just by dissolving the salt in water to create a hot hyperosmotic solution that extends from the body &quot;extra&quot; liquid and reduces swelling.</p>

<p>Soothing or, conversely, a tonic effect bath with sea salt can be obtained by adding to the water an essential oil or a decoction of herbs with the appropriate action.</p>

<p>The implications are clear: such procedures do not allow to lose weight, but they may help a bit to lose weight by providing the body drain effect. They also help in the fight against cosmetic defects of the skin and affect overall health.</p>

<p>Sea salt bath can be purchased in almost any pharmacy or store. It is better to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="choose">choose</a> a salt without any coloring and flavoring agents, because the contact with them may cause skin irritation or allergic reaction.</p>

<p>The amount of salt required for a bath, generally indicated on the packaging. Typically, the means take 300-500 grams per 200 liters of water. Adding more salt than is recommended, in the hope of a more pronounced effect, you only get increased dryness and flaking of the skin. Keep this in mind and avoid &quot;overdose&quot;.</p>

<p>Before taking a bath with sea salt Rinse under the shower. The required quantity of salt is dissolved in a liter of hot water, and then pour the solution into the water bath. You should select water temperature in the bath, it is comfortable for you, but remember that it should not be higher than 38 degrees. More hot water will dry the skin. In the water you can add your favorite essential oil or a decoction of herbs that enhance the action of the bath. Thus, essential oils of citrus fruits (lemon, orange, grapefruit) increase the effect of anti-cellulite treatments.</p>

<p>Immersed in the bath must not more than 10-20 minutes, at this region of the heart must remain above water. After the bath, you need to take a shower and put on a skin moisturizer. Then comes <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/body-wraps-for-weight-loss-belly/" title="wrap">wrapped</a> in a sheet or a bathrobe and sit or lie down quietly for half an hour. Within 1-2 hours before and after the bath should not eat, but you can drink green tea or herbal decoction.</p>

<p>Baths with sea salt are not for everyone, and have a list of contraindications. These include skin, heart and gynecological diseases, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/vascular-disease/varicose-veins.html" title="varicose veins">varicose veins</a>, increased body temperature, the condition of alcoholic intoxication, <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a>. If you have doubts about their safety for you personally, before the start of the procedures would be better to consult a doctor.</p>

<p>You can find a variety of opinions about the use of baths with sea salt. Among them there are also totally implausible: that someone has lost 10 kilograms in just a two weeks alone baths. To believe such statements are not worth it.</p>

<p>More than adequate people actually experienced the effects of sea salt, write to relieve fatigue and improve skin after these procedures. Weight is reduced by only a few kilograms in such baths combined with diet and physical activity. The achieved result is possible to keep under the same conditions.</p>

<p>From the available options in the sale of sea salt most people like the salt of the Dead Sea. Indeed, it has a unique chemical composition, wherein the proportion of sodium chloride accounts for only about 20%, and the remaining 80% - other minerals. Their relatively high content, and provides a more pronounced effect of water treatments.</p>

<p>Thus, a bath with sea salt should not be considered as the basis for weight loss, but rather as an aid provider cosmetic and soothing effect. But weight loss is still achieved a healthy diet and exercise, and do not expect that without them you can achieve noticeable results in the achievement of harmony.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
