<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Weight-loss | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/weight-loss/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-06-06T18:45:36+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pineapple Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/pineapple-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-06T16:38:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/pineapple-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/pineapple-diet/img.jpg" alt="Pineapple diet">Who among us does not like <strong>pineapples</strong>? This is perhaps one of those tropical delicacies, which like almost all children and adults. But few know that the sweet and juicy fruit contains only 56 calories. Tasty, useful and non-nutritive - that&rsquo;s great!</p>

<!--more-->


<p>In addition, the pineapple contains an enzyme that in common called <em>&quot;enzyme harmony&quot;</em>, and in science - <em>bromelain</em>. Magic enzyme enhances the action of gastric juice, due to this substance protein <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a> occurs much faster. Many have already try pineapple <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="slimming">slimming</a> teas, tablets containing bromelain, but the pineapple diet is much healthier and tastier.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<h2>Rules pineapple diet:</h2>

<ol>
<li>It is necessary to write down <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="every day">every day</a> at least 2 liters of fruit (or herbal) tea or water.</li>
<li>Observe the correct diet - eat at least four times a day in small portions.</li>
<li>Daily diet should consist of two breakfast, a hearty lunch and a light dinner.</li>
</ol>


<h2>Breakfasts pineapple diet</h2>

<p>The menu for the first two breakfasts for all days the same diet pineapple.</p>

<p>Using a mixer or a blender to make a puree of fresh pineapple, peeled beforehand. Add 2 teaspoons of oatmeal and 100 g of low-fat yogurt with no sugar. To sweeten slightly, add sugar substitute, but it is better without it. Tasty and nutritious light breakfast of 170 kcal ready.</p>

<p>Boil hard boiled egg and make a delicious sandwich of rye bread, spread with butter and salmon (not more than 20 grams). Very hearty and very tasty!</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - raw boiled rice, seasoned with curry.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - potatoes on the original recipe and cheese sauce.</p>

<p>One potato medium size weighing 100g boiled in their skins. Mix 50g of fat-free yogurt with a tablespoon of sour cream (10% fat) and a teaspoon of horseradish raw (grate). By potato with cottage cheese sauce add pineapple. Calories - only 275 kcal.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - fried chicken with pineapple, cut into slices.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - salad of shrimp and pineapple.</p>

<p>Boil 100g and clean shrimp, cut in half. Cut the pineapple into small pieces. Add finely chopped celery and a small cucumber, sliced rings. Add salt to taste, pepper, finely chopped dill. Season salad with low-fat mayonnaise. Calories - 285 calories.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - vegetable salad with garlic sauce.</p>

<p>Diced pineapple, half a red pepper and two small tomatoes and place in a deep dish. Dress the salad with 1 cloves of garlic sauce, mustard and a teaspoon of horseradish frayed. Sprinkle vegetable oil (home) and lemon juice. Calorie dishes - 225kkal.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - sliced pineapple, braised turkey and 2 small loaf of rye.</p>

<p>100g turkey breast (breast), cut into thin strips, fry for 7-10 minutes with the addition of vegetable oil (no more than a teaspoon), add 1 tablespoon of finely chopped onion. Pour a quarter cup of water, salt the, cover and simmer 10 minutes. Calories - 350 calories.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - salad with chicken, orange and pineapple.</p>

<p>Cut into julienne chicken, pre-fried on the grill. 100g pineapple and three slices of an orange cut into cubes. Stir vegetables, chicken and 2 tablespoons. spoons of green peas. Season with 2 tablespoons of fat-free mayonnaise, salt the, add red pepper. Energy value - 290 kcal.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - vegetable soup with celery, pineapple slices 100g.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - puff pastry stuffed with (100-150g). Stuffing <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="choose">choose</a> to taste.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - boiled rice with pineapple.</p>

<p>Boil 2 tablespoons of brown rice, diced pineapple, stir. If desired, add sweetener to taste. Calorie dishes - 245kkal.</p>

<p><strong>Pineapple diet</strong> can rightly be called the most delicious, varied and interesting. But, despite this, it is very effective. The only disadvantage of this diet - relatively expensive, but in principle, it&rsquo;s nothing compared with the possibility of so good and so fast to lose weight. Magic enzyme enhances the action of gastric juice, due to this substance protein digestion occurs much faster. Many have already try pineapple slimming teas, tablets containing bromelain, but the pineapple diet is much healthier and tastier.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banana Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-06T13:35:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/banana-diet-menu/img.jpg" alt="Banana diet">Bananas - a fruit that have a sufficiently high calorific value. Most people are aware of this and try to avoid them in the diet. However, there are power circuits, which involve the use of banana as the major product. Is it possible to lose weight on these fruits? Are there effective diets that reduce weight with the help of bananas? Let&rsquo;s analyze the three most common <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet-for-3-days-and-7-days/" title="banana diet">banana diet</a> and make conclusions.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Banana diet for 3 days</h2>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Lose weight for 3 days - the dream of every woman. As a rule, such a need arises at them before going to the beach this weekend, in case of sudden visits or New Year&rsquo;s Eve. The majority of women for some reason do not realize that it is impossible to lose weight in 3 days. Even in the case of complete <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/starvation.html" title="starvation">starvation</a> the body begins to vigorously break down subcutaneous fat only a few days after the rejection of food.</p>

<p>But the most common version of the banana diet offers <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> was 3 days. According to this method of fans to reduce weight, such a short period of time is sufficient to reduce their body weight by three kilograms. Banana essence diet on day 3 is as follows:</p>

<ul>
<li>there can be only bananas;</li>
<li>three times a day people should eat a banana and wash it down with a glass of milk;</li>
<li>milk should be lean;</li>
<li>at other times any food and beverages except water, are prohibited.</li>
</ul>


<p>It is unlikely to 3 days on a diet could achieve a significant improvement in the figures. But surely abide by it will not be too difficult. Bananas and milk enough nutrients to not feel wild hunger in the diet period. At the same time they do not contain a lot of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/" title="calories">calories</a>, so the banana-milk days people will spend more energy than it will receive from food.</p>

<p>Still, 3 kilograms of weight to lose can not be sure. Even given that bananas have a mild diuretic effect due to the content of potassium salts from your body will not leave as much fluid you to become significantly easier. Banana diet for 3 days only help relieve digestive system, giving it a breathing space. But for weight loss need much longer.</p>

<h2>Banana diet for 7 days</h2>

<p>Banana diet for 7 days provides a more solid results. On the Internet you can read that it can help a person will lose one kilogram of weight per day. That is, the end of the diet he folds 7 kilograms of fat. These results are possible even in the event of complete failure of the food. Nevertheless, we will introduce you with such an embodiment of the banana diet. Its essence is as follows:</p>

<ul>
<li>you can only eat bananas;</li>
<li>restricted their consumption of 1.5 kg per day;</li>
<li>you can drink only water and green tea - in any quantity;</li>
<li>you can eat in either mode, but the last meal - no later than 19 hours;</li>
<li>to avoid starvation, it is desirable not to eat at one time more than one banana;</li>
<li>if bananas are completely fed up, you can enter into the diet of two boiled eggs in a day.</li>
</ul>


<p>Bananas - not the best diet product. It is not clear what criteria guided the creators of this diet, choosing bananas as the sole source of nutrients. They are sweet, because they have a lot of sugar. Even far from nutrition person knows that the sweet recover and not lose weight. Bananas have a high glycemic index, consist mainly of carbohydrates and thin because they are not very convenient.</p>

<h2>Cottage cheese and banana diet</h2>

<p>Cottage cheese and banana diet lasts for six days. Three of them - the banana. Yet three days - cheese. Start with cottage cheese day. Check, respectively, have a banana. The diet is more varied diet, compared with the previous power schemes. cheesecake of the day menu looks like this:</p>

<ul>
<li>breakfast - 120 grams of low fat cottage cheese, a grapefruit;</li>
<li>lunch - 120 grams of low fat cottage cheese, a slice of melon;</li>
<li>dinner - again, 120 g of cottage cheese and grapefruit.</li>
</ul>


<p>Why cheese? It contains a lot of protein and little sugar. It has a low calorie, but nourishes by a viscous consistency, high-volume, slow progress on the gastrointestinal tract.</p>

<p>Why grapefruit? Rumor has it that it promotes weight loss. And although it is fiction, many believe in the fat burning properties of grapefruit.</p>

<p>Why melon? Her presence in the diet does not seem logical. In this fruit a lot of sugar, and it has a high glycemic index. Melon is harmful for the figure, and most diets for weight loss exclude it from the diet.</p>

<p>Banana days include the following menu:</p>

<ul>
<li>breakfast - a banana and a glass of milk;</li>
<li>lunch - banana and boiled egg;</li>
<li>dinner - 200 grams of banana and chicken.</li>
</ul>


<p>Eggs, milk and chicken contain a lot of protein. They are low in carbohydrates, so these dietary products can be called. And that&rsquo;s why in this scheme bananas - are not known. If they were replaced by other, less high-calorie fruit, the good of diet would be more. However, not much. Like other short-circuit power for weight loss, banana curd diet does not allow to achieve significant results in reducing weight.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The American Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/the-american-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-06T11:31:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/the-american-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/the-american-diet/img.jpg" alt="The American diet">This diet is considered one of the most famous systems of combating <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a> worldwide. Many Hollywood stars stick to this <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet/" title="diet">diet</a> to stay in shape. Today, I can feel like a star each.</p>

<!--more-->


<p><strong>There are several types of the American diet:</strong></p>

<p>This diet is designed for 7 days. The main feature of the diet - is the lack of hunger due to a well balanced diet.</p>

<p>If you have eaten a fatty meal, be sure to seize him several slices of pineapple or grapefruit.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Drink plenty of liquids - it helps to remove waste products and toxins from the body. Eat only until five o'clock in the evening. It is necessary to eat only foods that are really useful to humans. Not allowed salt, sugar, pepper, vinegar, oil, fat and alcohol.</p>

<h2>American diet menu:</h2>

<p><strong>Breakfast for all days of the same</strong> - coffee with milk but no sugar, 2 apple or an orange, a slice of bread or toast, boiled egg.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - 200g of boiled or fried fish, 100g celery with lemon juice, tea or coffee (without sugar or milk).</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 100 g cooked meat (chopped finely, add a little onion and 1 egg yolk), a slice of bread from wheat flour, one apple or a glass of low-fat milk.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - 200g stewed spinach, 150g of boiled or fried veal liver, 2 boiled potatoes, tea or coffee.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 200 grams of fat-free yogurt, a salad of tomatoes, beets, carrots, cabbage, seasoned with vegetable oil, a slice of bread or toast, a slice of lean ham, boiled egg.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - orange or grapefruit, tomato juice, 200g of low-fat fried meat, lettuce, coffee or tea.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 200 low-fat yogurt, 2 boiled eggs, 2 tomatoes, a slice of bread or toast, an apple or a pear.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - 200g of boiled or fried chicken, 150 g of cabbage, croutons and a piece of bread, coffee or tea.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 50 g low-fat cottage cheese, you can add a little green onion, bell pepper, egg yolk (raw); 6 radishes, toast or a slice of bread, 200g of low-fat milk.</p>

<p><strong>Lunch</strong> - 250g grated carrots, 150g of cooked lean meat, 2 potatoes in their skins, toast, coffee or green tea.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 150 boiled beef with horseradish, apple, lettuce, 200g of low-fat milk.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 200 grams of cooked lean chicken, 100g of rice, 100g of lettuce leaves (chop and season with lemon juice), green apple, 200g of low-fat milk.</p>

<p><strong>Dinner</strong> - 200 grams of low-fat yogurt, 2 small chops, slice of bread, a green apple.</p>

<p><strong>The second option - a roller coaster:</strong></p>

<p>This diet is based on the principle of change in calorie daily diet. This makes it possible to achieve optimal results, because the body does not have time to tune in to a particular diet and constantly burns calories.</p>

<h2>The ration for the &ldquo;roller coaster&rdquo;:</h2>

<ul>
<li>The power supply system is designed for 3 weeks. Exclude from menu fatty food.</li>
<li>The first three days is necessary to consume 600 calories per day.</li>
<li>From the fourth to seventh day - 900 calories per day.</li>
<li>During the second week, the daily caloric diet is 1200 kcal.</li>
<li>The third is similar to the first week, that is, after 600 to 900 calories per day.</li>
</ul>


<p>This ration allows <strong>the american diet</strong> to lose 6-7 kg of excess weight, but for optimal results, it is best to combine this diet with exercise. If you play sports, the result can be more impressive - 8-9 kg in just one week.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nine-day Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-05T12:26:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/nine-day-diet/img.jpg" alt="Nine-day diet">Want to quickly bring your body in good shape before the long-awaited vacation? Nothing could be easier. Nine-day diet will help you deal with this problem in a few days.</p>

<p>And why is it always? All year flies by, but we did not have time to enroll in a gym, in the shaping or dance, we eat what we want, and grabs his head only when the time is almost gone. And as always in the holiday expectations we stand before the mirror and realize that all night snacks, salted potato chips and crisps, beer and cocktails are our figure does not help, but rather spoiled her beyond recognition. <!--more-->Looking in the mirror, we realize that with such a body to appear in a bikini on the beach - it&rsquo;s a crime. An urgent need to do something!</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
First of all you need to tune in to the fact that, following the right diet of this diet, you will lose weight in a day 0.5-1kg. This is certainly a serious <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a> to the body, so before starting the diet is better to consult a doctor. This diet is not suitable for those who have stomach ulcers, diseases of the cardiovascular system, or even the uncommon cold.</p>

<p>Next, you should understand that no diet compliance, a periodic &quot;jumping from diet&quot;, etc. It leads to the fact that all is well kilos gone back to his place, and maybe even &quot;friends&quot; with a lead. Began to lose weight - grow thin, you do not want to lose weight - do not sit on a diet. To fix the result, it is necessary to understand that after the diet need to eat moderately and wisely.</p>

<h2>Menu diet for 9 days:</h2>

<p>This diet consists of three phases.</p>

<p><strong>The first stage</strong> - three days to eat only rice, honey and drink the water.</p>

<p>On the day we take 250g long grain white rice, 2-2.5 liters of mineral water without gas, and 3 teaspoons of honey spoon.</p>

<p>On the night of rice soaked with cold water. In the morning, wash the rice in a colander to wash most of the cereal starch. Further boil in a saucepan for 15 minutes, adding rice and water in a ratio of 1:2, respectively.</p>

<p>Cooked rice divide into 5 equal portions and we eat it all day long, trying to avoid the strong feelings of hunger. Last time you can eat no later than eight o'clock in the evening. In between meals and after-meal drink water, distributing evenly. In the evening, lean on the liquid is not worth it. Also included in the diet of honey which eat in parallel with rice and water during the day. Honey is not spread on bread or cookies, eat a teaspoon with water.</p>

<p>Why this diet is effective? Figure acts as enterosorbent he cleans accumulated for a long time, toxins from the gastrointestinal tract, which actually promotes <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/1kg-per-day-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>.</p>

<p><strong>The second stage</strong> - the next 3 days, you can eat chicken or fish, water and honey.</p>

<p>On the day we need 1.2-1.3kg chicken or lean fish 700-800g, as well as water (2-2.5 l) and three teaspoons of honey.</p>

<p>Chicken or lean fish cook in a double boiler. In the morning we drink a glass of water, and then proceed to the meal.</p>

<p>If you chose the chicken, then it is necessary to remove the peel, then eat a whole piece of the leg and the back, that is where a fifth part of the carcass. Then carve the chicken, separating the meat from the bones, mix white and red meat, divide into equal portions and eat up during the remainder of the day. Last time we eat no later than seven o'clock in the evening.</p>

<p>If you <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="choose">choose</a> the fish, it should be divided into 5-6 pieces and eat as well as chicken, for a whole day in equal portions, trying to avoid feeling hungry. To fish was delicious, you can add a little greenery and lemon juice.</p>

<p>You can alternate days fish and chicken to the diet was not too bothersome. As in the early days of drinking water, and we eat the honey.</p>

<p>Why do we lose weight? Receipt of protein contributes to the fact that fat cells break up fat, which contributes to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="rapid weight loss">rapid weight loss</a>.</p>

<p><strong>The third stage</strong> - the next 3 days, we eat only vegetables, water and honey.</p>

<p>Take a day 1 kg of vegetables, 2-2.5l mineral water without gas, and 3 teaspoons of honey spoon.</p>

<p>It is better to give preference to white, and green vegetables such as cabbage, zucchini, onions, etc. But also do not forget about beets, tomatoes and carrots, but take them to a lesser extent. Please take a pound of vegetables, finely chopped, and simmer, remaining vegetables, we are preparing a salad brush.</p>

<p>What do you need? Raw beet, raw carrots, some cabbage, fresh herbs, a few drops of lemon juice, a teaspoon of olive oil, tablespoon water.</p>

<p><strong>How to cook?</strong> Clean the vegetables and rub on a coarse grater or chop finely. Add the olive oil, lemon juice and water for juiciness.</p>

<p>Then we share the steamed vegetables into three parts and a salad as a brush into three equal parts. It is necessary to alternate the meals throughout the day.</p>

<p>Due to the vegetables in the body is reduced vitamin and mineral complex. Belly immediately becomes smaller, because effectively cleans all the deposits on the walls of the intestine.</p>

<p>Diet is over, and we can return to a normal diet. But because it is necessary to exclude:</p>

<ul>
<li>Too salty foods and foods</li>
<li>Sweet soda water.</li>
</ul>


<p>What can you eat? Eat low-fat cheese, no more than 50g a day, bread from wheat flour, no more than 4 slices per day. Also drink water in large quantities and keep the schedule meals. You need not eat more than 4 times a day in small portions at most 250g at a time no later supper seven hours.</p>

<p>The proposed diet is not too &quot;hungry&quot;, but it is quite specific. You do not need to combine diet with exercise, fitness, work in the country and other complex procedures. But on the contrary leave more move, walk, swim, dance - just relax actively.</p>

<h2>Helpful advice</h2>

<p>Ladies, if you know that you can not abandon all kinds of temptations on holiday, it is better to give up this diet once and for all! It is better to learn to enjoy its appearance as it is. If you can not resist the goodies and will be broken, then all your efforts will be in vain. And remember that any woman can be sexy, regardless of the splendor of forms. The main thing - it is a smiling, good spirits and good humor.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[1kg Per Day Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/1kg-per-day-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-04T14:28:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/1kg-per-day-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/1kg-per-day/img.jpg" alt="1kg per day diet">When a person in one day looking in the mirror and finds that his figure needs to be corrected, he goes online and begins to look for ways to lose weight out there. Moreover, a gradual decrease in weight was not satisfied. Man must necessarily lose weight quickly, to ensure a minimum duration period, when it will have to limit yourself to food. Many people tend to lose weight by 1 kg per day, but whether this is real rate of decrease body fat? Diets in which the authors promise such high rates of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/citrus-diet-for-weight-loss-diet-menus-on-citrus-reviews-recipes/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>, there, and now we will discuss the most common ones.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Some women use a day diet allows you to lose 1 kg of weight. Note that minus 1 kg of body mass - is not the same as the minus 1 kg of fat. This one-day diet is often recommended on the Internet, but few mention one of its features. In the early days of any fat diets are extremely reluctant to leave, so the weight is reduced by emptying the intestines and excretion of fluids. At the same time the stomach will become flatter, but the thickness of the subcutaneous fat layer will remain unchanged.</p>

<ol>
<li>Duration - exactly one day.</li>
<li>Diet painted strictly by the hour, can not deviate from it.</li>
<li>Weight loss occurs by reducing the amount of body fluids and faeces in the intestine.</li>
<li>Diet - 8 times per day, so it is advisable to sit on this mini-diet at the weekend, so it does not interfere with the work schedule.</li>
<li>Salt prohibited - this measure will bring the body of liquid without the use of diuretics.</li>
</ol>


<p><em>Diet Menu minus 1 kg for 1 day on the clock:</em></p>

<p>7:00 - unsweetened black tea (0 kcal);
9:00 - boiled egg (80 calories);
11:00 - tablespoon of raisins (25 kcal);
13:00 - 100 grams of boiled chicken (180 calories);
15:00 - a glass of tomato juice (40 calories);
17:00 - boiled egg (80 calories);
21:00 - a cup of yogurt (100 kcal).</p>

<p>Total - 555 <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/" title="calories">calories</a> for the entire day. If you observe a diet all the time, then quickly led to full order of the figure. Another thing is that to sustain this meager menu longer than 1 day, akin to a feat. Surely you will torment hunger. In addition, such a diet can hardly be called healthy and balanced.</p>

<p>Diet minus 1 kg per day - it&rsquo;s an ambulance to your figure. If your body is not too much fat, you will be visually slimmer. This allows you to look better the next day after the diet. It should be understood that the body fat mass will remain unchanged, so you will get only a temporary result. For sustainable weight loss diet should be longer.</p>

<p>There are longer diets are designed for weight loss of 1 kg per day. In general, they are designed for a week. Subsequently diets simply lose their effectiveness. The fact that lose 1 kg of fat per day impossible. Even if you are physically active, and thus did not eat hardly lose a day more than 500 grams of fat. Moreover, even such pitches are possible only in the first few days, and then the body will reduce the metabolic rate to conserve energy in the hungry period.</p>

<p>Diet minus 1 kg per day is only for 7 days, because in this period to achieve weight loss can be achieved by removing the liquid and purgation of faeces. Naturally, when the old food out of the intestines, and the new comes in miniscule amounts, you become easier. Similarly, reduced body weight when the body takes the water. But infinitely away she can not, so the process of so-called &quot;<a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="slimming">slimming</a>&quot; rapidly slowing.</p>

<p>One of the most common schemes power save enable presumably to 1 kg per day, referred to as &quot;favorite diet&quot;. Who loves it, and most importantly - for what, history is silent. Here&rsquo;s her menu on days:</p>

<p>Monday - you can drink anything you want, in any quantity, but can not eat.
Tuesday - you can eat vegetables in any quantity.
Wednesday - you can drink, but you can not have.
Thursday - you can eat only fruit.
Friday - allowed to eat boiled meat and fish low-fat varieties, eggs and seafood.
Saturday - only to drink, but can not eat.
Sunday - the day the menu includes servings of vegetable salad, two eggs, two servings of fruit salad and cup of soup.</p>

<p>This diet is stupid, ineffective, it contains a whole bunch of unnecessary regulations. Perhaps someone once coined it for a joke, and the rest was picked up and distributed over the Internet. You can not reset using this diet 1 kg daily. However, any result you will surely get. Three of the seven days you are not allowed to consume food. It is unlikely that these will be the days of drinking in vain for your figure.</p>

<p>The Internet goes the myth that diet singer Valeria, which is designed for three days, on a daily basis allows a person to lose 1 kg of weight. It is based on the use of buckwheat porridge without fat and salt. Most sources say that buckwheat acquires special fat-burning properties, if you do not cook it in boiling water and leave overnight to infuse in hot water.</p>

<p><em>In the diet of the singer Valeria only two rules:</em></p>

<ol>
<li>There are only buckwheat water, but in any amount.</li>
<li>Water should be drinking at least 2 liters per day.</li>
</ol>


<p>It is not known whether this diet Valery complied with in reality, or is it another tabloids fiction, but a way to lose weight, we do not recommend because of poor performance. Buckwheat - is a product that eating large amounts can not reduce weight, but on the contrary, grow side. But even if you keep yourself from overeating calorie diet buckwheat these three days will be enough low for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="rapid weight loss">rapid weight loss</a>.</p>

<p>Undoubtedly, the top most stupid diets for weight loss led power scheme, which is based on the daily consumption of fruit alone. Here is your menu for 6 days:</p>

<p>Monday - 1 kg of fruit.</p>

<p>While other human diet literally forced to drink the water in high amounts, fruit diet restricts liquid to 500 ml per day. It is obvious that no advantage is not such a diet. But it has drawbacks whole bunch:</p>

<ul>
<li>fruit contained in the composition of organic acids, which stimulate intestinal motility, causing the secretion of digestive juices and hunger provoking;</li>
<li>fruits contain a lot of carbohydrates, including simple sugars, but the protein in them is very small, so the diet is unhealthy and little use for the figure;</li>
<li>people with diseases of the gastrointestinal tract diet is contraindicated due to the possible aggravation of her background of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/gastritis.html" title="gastritis">gastritis</a> or <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/diagnosis-of-peptic-ulcer-disease.html" title="peptic ulcer">peptic ulcer</a>.</li>
</ul>


<p>You may be able to lose weight on a little fruit. But if the pitches are, they are clearly not amount to 1 kg per day. The diet is unhealthy, poorly tolerated and has a very low efficiency. Perhaps these three reasons enough to abandon it.</p>

<p>The most zealous fans of freebies do not want only a few days to fix a figure, but still wish to do so without dieting. The emergence of the desire to contribute to sellers of various additives, belts, bracelets and other rubbish, supposedly allowing lose weight at least 1 per kg per day without dieting and effort. Typically, such a person desire to end waste of money, human expectations and decreased motivation to further weight loss.</p>

<p>&quot;Minus 1 kg a month without dieting&quot; - that should sound like your goal, if you do not want to limit themselves in power. It is likely that you do not need to diet adjustment, if you will exercise the utmost physical activity:</p>

<ul>
<li>always walk, if possible;</li>
<li>perform yoga exercises in the gym under the supervision of a trainer;</li>
<li>active rest, but not in front of the TV.</li>
</ul>


<p>But you have to understand that provide a negative energy balance in the body without the use of diet is extremely difficult. To do this, you must spend a lot of calories. Although theoretically possible weight loss without dieting, weight reduction achieved in real life, keeping the old diet - it is a very difficult task that requires human willpower, discipline and dedication.</p>

<p>Lose 1 kg per day - this is achievable task. But it is feasible only in the case if you follow a diet plan is not more than 1 day. If you are set to lose fat, not water, and feces, such a goal is unrealistic, regardless of the presence or absence of the desire to diet.</p>

<p>Minus 1 kg per day - a task that will take you just a waste of money. You again sell another &quot;miracle pill&quot; for $100, or &quot;fat burning&quot; zone for $500. Set a goal adequate. Lose weight gradually, and then over time you normalize the weight of his body, without harm to health and damage to the purse.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
