<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Weight-loss | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/weight-loss/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-01-08T20:15:09+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Belly Massage for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/belly-massage-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-08T11:18:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/belly-massage-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/belly-massage-for-weight-loss/img.jpg" title="WBelly massage for weight loss" alt="belly massage for weight loss at home"><strong>Massage</strong> - a method that has long been in service with the conventional medicine. It is approved by the Ministry of Health, and is used to treat a huge number of diseases. Of course, as an auxiliary method of therapy. Massage is used in virtually all areas of medicine. He is firmly entrenched in our lives, and probably in the world there is not one person who would never lay on a massage table.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>The effectiveness of massage</h2>

<p>The effectiveness of massage has long been proved. It can help you improve the condition of the patient, regardless of the disease, which he suffers. However, the inability of the placebo-controlled studies leaves some doubt as to the mechanism of its effects. Which factor plays the most important role: the psychological or physiological? What makes a person feel relieved: relaxation and faith in the healing power of massage or mechanical effect on the soft tissues of the body?</p>

<p>This question remains open for the time being. We are interested in, whether it is possible with the help of abdominal massage to lose at least a few kilograms? Agree, it would be great: no need to starve, no strain, just lie down on the table, belly up, and wait for someone skilled hands make short work of your fat. Is it possible? Let&rsquo;s deal.</p>

<p>All the effects of the massage can be divided into psychological and physiological. The first is certainly very useful, but are unlikely to have a specific and predictable effect on the weight of your body. Therefore, it makes no sense to consider them, go directly to the physiological. We will not engage in speculation, use a pseudo-data, for example, on energy currents - too. That&rsquo;s the impact on the human body has a significantly abdominal massage:</p>

<ul>
<li>Warms the skin due to emitted as a result of mechanical friction heat;</li>
<li>Stimulates the microcirculation of the skin by heating;</li>
<li>It stimulates the flow of lymph and venous blood due to mechanical compression of blood vessels;</li>
<li>Relaxes the muscles by mechanical action on them, as well as enhance blood flow.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Belly massage and weight loss</h2>

<p>Which of these mechanisms, in your opinion, can contribute to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>? Let&rsquo;s look at them all in turn.</p>

<p>Obviously, warm skin of the abdomen can not dissolve fat. It does not melt like wax, so the effect of massage is unlikely to reduce the weight of your body. Judge for yourself if the increase in skin temperature contribute to weight loss, for the acquisition of a slim figure you would rather stick a couple of yellow cards in the stomach, or heat it with an ordinary table lamp. From the sea, everything is back to not only rested, but also slim, because the fat left on the beach not only the stomach, but also from the entire body.</p>

<p>The skin temperature increases by touching hand massage, so the blood vessels dilate to give away excess heat. This is one of the mechanisms of thermoregulation, protects the body from overheating. Due to dilation of small blood vessels nutrition improves soft tissues, primarily the skin. Does this mean that fat belly will start to leave? No, otherwise all alcoholics with red faces would not wear belly in his hands, and would look more slender birch. Medicines from the group of proofreaders microcirculation, led by pentoxifylline, have themselves become popular drugs for weight loss.</p>

<p>This effect helps to eliminate stagnant lymph and venous blood. Thus, the massage display allows the liquid that has accumulated in the soft tissues. Perhaps it is this feature made people consider massage as a regular method of losing weight. <strong><em>Firstly</em></strong>, with the fluid leaves the body weight, that causes a person to believe that massage helped him to break down fat. <strong><em>Second</em></strong>, visually stomach becomes more flat. This is due to improvement of the skin and removal of liquid. <strong><em>Third</em></strong>, the possible reduction in waist circumference, again, due to the removal of edema.</p>

<p>At the young age of these effects may not occur at all, or to be mild, but after 40 years, when the body breaks down the balance of hormones, a change in metabolism, fluid accumulates more actively. Accordingly, massage is more effective way to reduce body weight. Of course, the effect of massage is very useful for the figure. But make no mistake, the fat remains in place, leaving only water.</p>

<p>Surprisingly, making the opposite action, a lot of people waiting to get on the output a result. Shaking the press, they are straining the abdominal muscles, hoping to lose weight. Visiting massage people relax the same muscle groups, waiting for an identical effect - weight loss. So what still needs to be done with the muscles? Perhaps, after all, cut, and as often as possible. If muscle relaxation accompanied by weight loss, people have lost weight during the holidays. To enhance the effect, he tried to muscle relaxants and antispasmodics - drugs that reduce muscle tone.</p>

<p>Lose weight with the help of belly massage can be in only one case: if you are doing it yourself. And preferably more than once per day. Massage takes away a lot of strength and energy, so you&rsquo;ll save calories, and with them - the extra weight. But lying on the table and making the masseur knead your stomach, you just get rid of the money that paid for his services. Of excess weight - is unlikely.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Lose Weight at Home?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-05T08:48:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/img.jpg" title="rapid weight loss, how to lose weight fast at home, rope, exercise for weight loss and press" alt="How to lose weight at home?">It&rsquo;s not a secret that proper healthy diet is essential for maintaining the health and control their weight. To overcome the overweight should be, above all, to overcome their bad eating habits, such as overeating, eating before going to sleep, irregular eating, eating unhealthy foods. Remember that the stomach - a hollow muscular organ that easily expands as binge eating, and later - in the normal diet in order to achieve a sense of saturation required to eat large amounts of food, because the stomach is already &quot;accustomed&quot; to be stretched. Consumption while healthy but high-calorie foods in quantities exceeding the energy intake necessary for you daily energy requirement, a sedentary lifestyle, low physical activity also contribute to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>. Therefore, to maintain a slim figure of the ideal need to eat regularly and properly balanced, and exercise more.</p>

<!--more-->


<p><strong>Willpower and mood of success</strong> - your first allies in the difficult task to lose weight. There should be a clear desire to get rid of the extra kilos. Do not give up until you shake the ill-fated arrow on the mechanical balance in the smaller side, or until crawl down the numbers on the display of electronic scales.</p>

<p><strong>Learn to say a firm &quot;no&quot; to temptation</strong> and fast food, but, unfortunately, bad nutrition. Before you succumb to the temptation to buy a pizza, sugary sodas, delicious fries, a double burger with cheese or soft flour cakes, bathed in chocolate - think about the number of calories that are contained in them and imagine how they will be stored in the fat folds of your limp body.</p>

<p>Eat <strong>more foods with dietary fiber</strong>. They give food volume contribute to the rapid filling of the stomach and thus less food will cause a feeling of fullness in the brain. In addition, dietary fiber contribute to the removal of toxic products of metabolism from the gut, serve as a substrate for the intestinal flora, stool form, in part serve as prevention of unpleasant intestinal conditions like <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/constipation.html" title="constipation">constipation</a> and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/diarrhea.html" title="diarrhea">diarrhea</a>. Where to contain dietary fiber? Vegetables, fruits, bran, cereals, wholemeal bread. All of these products can and should be consumed in large quantities under the emergency measures for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> at home.</p>

<p>Wash consumed foods. <strong>Drink plenty of fluids</strong>, because the water speeds up metabolism and promotes breeding and disposal of harmful metabolic products in the urine, feces, evaporation through the surface of the skin (sweating) and lungs. Drinking water reduces hunger and helps <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a>. Remember that an adequate daily fluid intake is the key to the proper functioning of the internal organs of the human body, especially the liver.</p>

<p>Part of the daily routine should be a morning <strong>exercise, stretching, exercises with weights</strong>, and better training on a stationary bike or treadmill - on any simulator that you can install at home. It would be even better to regularly engage in gyms, make daily walks and engage in a variety of active sports.</p>

<p>Remember that any kind of mental pressure lead to the emergence of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a> and even <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/depression.html" title="depression">depression</a>. Stress, in turn, can lead to <strong>emotional overeating</strong>. So try not to be nervous, overexcited and do not take to heart the negative attitudes of other individuals. A good practice would be breathing exercises, such as, for example, deep breaths, different meditation technique, oriental health exercises. Do not forget about the rest. Remember that proper rest (not a computer screen) currently has therapeutic effects on the body. The same applies to bed. You must sleep at least 7 hours a day.</p>

<p>What else can be done at home for a successful weight loss? Remember that <strong>you need not only eat well, but also regularly</strong>. Eat 5 times a day in small portions, rather than 2-3 times larger. Perfect breakfast should be low calorie, low fat and high content of dietary fiber. For lunch, eat anything, the main thing that it was useful and tasty (do not forget to enjoy a healthy meal). Do not wait with dinner. The evening meal should be completed in 2-3 hours before bedtime. Do not forget that the number of calories consumed can be reduced by increasing the content of fruits and vegetables in the diet, but they also contain large amounts of vitamins and minerals.</p>

<p>So remember that your daily energy expenditure in the <strong>form of exercise</strong> must exceed the consumption of food in terms of kilocalories contained therein. Unfortunately, however, the intensity of modern life does not always give us the opportunity to be engaged enough in gyms, leisure or sports outside the home, so why do not we engage in more physical activity where we spend about half of my life - that is the house? But in any case, do not take physical exercise as a burden his duties enthusiastically approach to employment, involve family members, including your favorite TV channel or the necessary music. And finally, here are 9 public exercises which you can do at home without having to buy special equipment or equipment:</p>

<ul>
<li><em>Walks around the house (walking):</em> This is the best kind of exercise, you generally do not need to do this only functioning legs. However, if you live in a cramped home, or if the weather is really very good, you can take the opportunity to walking on the street. Necessarily involve your home for this event. Even banal raising and lowering the stairs leading to tone your muscles.</li>
<li><em>Jumping rope:</em> it is itself energy-intensive way of exercise and an occasion for pleasant childhood memories of girls.</li>
<li><em>Ups:</em> Although this type of exercise is given quite difficult, many people prefer push-ups, because they are well trained muscles in the arms and shoulders.</li>
<li><em>Lifting legs:</em> the perfect exercise to strengthen the muscles of the lower extremities and abdomen. For best results, you want to raise the straight legs, but if you feel that it is very difficult, it is possible to bend them a little.</li>
<li><em>Lift the body to the knees from a prone position on the back:</em> This type of exercise is essential for abdominal exercise. Down with flabby abdominal wall with large accumulations of fat! Long live the &quot;cubes&quot;! Cheers &quot;cubes&quot;! By the way, &quot;blocks&quot; are formed by constrictions tendon rectus abdominis muscle, so you need to train this muscle. Just remember that the cubes can be seen when the fat content in the body is about 10% lower.</li>
<li><em>Sports running:</em> very good exercise to train the cardiovascular and respiratory systems, as well as to optimize the consumption of calories. Everyone can jogging or even brisk walking, while listening to the radio, music or just enjoying nature. The only thing you need - a couple of good shoes, and, of course, a strong belief in getting rid of unnecessary kilograms.</li>
<li><em>Squat:</em> have a striking impact on glutes and leg muscles. Even better would be if you crouch not alone, but in company with two charming brunette - dumbbells and Rosa Clara.</li>
<li><em>Weightlifting:</em> if you are a girl and did not want to spend money to buy glamorous dumbbell, you can start to lift weights that are easy to get at home - a laptop man, iron, grown fat cat, two-liter bottle of Coca-Cola (stop, people dumping kilograms, there should be no sugary sodas in the fridge) and large capacity air-conditioned for the washing machine (it is convenient to do just to lift).</li>
<li><em>Dance:</em> yes, dance - it is also an interesting exercise. They increase the speed of your metabolism and give a sense of overall satisfaction.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gone Month After Weight Loss. How to Restore the Month Following the Diet?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-05T08:35:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/menstruation-after-weight-loss/img.jpg" title="title" alt="alt">This problem is very common among girls, too much carried away by losing weight. Heavy training in the gym, wasting the minimum calorie diet, unbalanced power - all this, acting together, can disrupt the hormonal balance of the female body and lead to amenorrhea - the cessation of menstruation. Their absence is a sign of serious damage to health and can cause other, more terrible consequences. So, if the problem you have encountered, you should take as soon as possible for its decision.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The normal termination of a woman&rsquo;s menstruation should occur only in 45-55 years, when she, because of age, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/menopause.html" title="menopause">menopause</a>. In younger years cycle disorders are a symptom of a more or less serious violations.</p>

<p>Some girls are easy enough to react to the fact that <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/body-wraps-for-weight-loss-belly/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> after they begin the long delays or even complete absence of menstruation. This is probably due to all the well-known myth, if sportswomen month did not happen. However, in reality, only to suffer a similar professional athletes, usually engaged in power sports, and often taking specific means to improve their physical condition, such as steroids. At the same time, they make a conscious choice between sports achievements and his health - in favor of the first, as you may have guessed.</p>

<p>You do not engage in professional sports, but just decided to lose a few pounds, so you should not be like this. Maybe for you, even absence of menstruation seems convenient, but keep in mind that it is able to do a lot of damage to health.</p>

<p>If you are a long time did not receive a sufficient amount of food nutrients, it could contribute to the emergence of anemia, disturbance of the production of sex hormones, changes in metabolism, resulting in a disruption of the normal functioning of the ovaries. At first it is fixable, but then atrophy and other changes in the reproductive system are becoming more stable and may even be irreversible.</p>

<p>Significantly it is not proved, but experts believe that, given the long absence of menstruation due to weight loss, women may develop complications. Moreover, their appearance is possible even if the cycle is still possible to recover. In particular, the likelihood of complications include dishormonal disorders: dysfunctional uterine <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/injuries-and-accidents/bleeding.html" title="bleeding">bleeding</a>, the development of hormone-dependent benign tumors, polycystic ovaries, and cysts. Ultimately, in particularly serious cases, this can lead to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/infertility.html" title="infertility">infertility</a>.</p>

<p>The key point for safe weight loss - it is a slow or moderate speed weight loss. If you are struggling to the results &quot;minus 30 kg per month&quot;, and ready for this fast and torturing your body unbearable load it one way or another will have an effect: someone - a stomach ulcer, someone - violations of the cycle.</p>

<p>The second rule, which will save you from the problems of women&rsquo;s health - is striving for a balanced diet, even against the background diet. In particular, you even in small amounts, but should eat fat-containing animal products, because it is based on <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a>, which you are so afraid, are built molecule hormones. This does not mean that you can not use a mono-diet, or fat-free diet, simply by practice over several days rather than months in a row.</p>

<h2>What should I do to restore menstruation?</h2>

<p>Take action, and fast. Of course, the emergence of amenorrhea on the background of weight loss does not require as much emergency treatment to the doctor, as a traumatic brain injury, or other medical emergency, but to think you should not spend more than a week.</p>

<p>It is desirable to bring to the solution of the problem of a specialist. If you do not understand, which is why it&rsquo;s happened, he will explain the reason for cessation of menstruation, to recommend changes in diet and prescribe drugs for the treatment. It will be hormonal. Do not be afraid of what you prescribe them because now they are needed. Artificial hormones entering the body, will lead to the cyclic operation of the reproductive organs and quickly restore cycle. In a few months you will be able to give them up.</p>

<p>You can also simultaneously - not as a basis, in the form of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/aids.html" title="aids">aids</a>! - To use national treatment. As the herbs that have a positive impact on women&rsquo;s health are known upland uterus, lovage, chamomile, parsley. Their decoctions and infusions is also possible to use if you do not have contraindications to herbal medicine, in particular <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/allergology/allergy.html" title="allergy">allergy</a> to grass.</p>

<p>So, if on the background of intensive weight loss you have gone monthly, restore them as soon as possible. Doing this is through a combination of good nutrition, medication, prescribed by a physician, and, if desired, the use of aids. Even if you have not yet reached their ultimate goal in losing weight, you better time to interrupt this process and pay attention to their health. Let this situation will give you some lessons and will help you understand that you can not scoff at his body with impunity. Hopefully, you will restore your health, and in the future, you will not be so foolish to strive for weight loss.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Body Wraps for Weight Loss Belly]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/body-wraps-for-weight-loss-belly/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-04T17:36:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/body-wraps-for-weight-loss-belly</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/body-wraps-for-weight-loss-belly/body-wraps-for-weight-loss-belly.jpg" title="Body wraps for weight loss belly" alt="Body wraps for weight loss belly">How should look like your belly so you can feel free to wear tight shirts and short tops? Some girls like sports press - absolutely flat stomach with a hint of &quot;cubes&quot;. Others prefer a more feminine option - a combination of a thin waist with a faint soft roundness below the navel; just so perfect tummy looks at the owners figure &quot;hourglass&quot;, and not just in this case, it looks perfectly piercing. Unfortunately, for many people neither one nor the other is not available, and they do not even know how to actually look like their waist, because it is hidden under the more or less visible fat layer. How to lose weight? Some are used for different types of wraps. In this article we will describe some of the most popular body wraps for weight loss belly and talk about their performance.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Vinegar wraps</h2>

<p><strong>As they are made.</strong> Dining room (ie diluted) vinegar moistened cloth, the size suitable for the desired part of the body. Fabric slightly drained, is wrapped in 1-2 layers (depending on the thickness of material) around the waist and leave all approximately 30-40 minutes. On top of the fabric should not be any clothes you need to vinegar is evaporated. After the procedure, the skin is rinsed with water.</p>

<p><strong>Expected effect.</strong> During evaporation means the skin surface to which it is applied, it is cooled; on the same principle based vinegar rubdown in patients with <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/fever.html" title="fever">fever</a>. At the same time, low body temperature contributes to the fact that the body begins to waste energy on heating, spending reserves of calories available.</p>

<p>Comparing these two well-known fact, supporters of vinegar wraps claim if such procedures cause the burning of fat in the body is applied to the vinegar. In addition, it is assumed, if the vitamins, minerals and acids that means a positive effect on the skin and can even reduce the size and depth of stretch marks. Whatever it said, the experts?</p>

<p><strong>The real effect of the procedure.</strong> Unfortunately, the effectiveness of vinegar wraps is greatly exaggerated, their real effect - almost zero. Why? Firstly, during their cooling of the skin is not so much that the body began to actively warmed. Secondly, under the local effect of low temperature energy is drawn not from the area, which is cooled and from the general reserves of fat, that is, there is not a local, and the total weight loss. Third, as a part of vinegar is only dilute acetic acid, other &quot;acids, vitamins and minerals&quot; it there, so that on stretching means will not act.</p>

<p><strong>Conclusion.</strong> Vinegar wraps useless for slimming the abdomen.</p>

<h2>Cold wraps</h2>

<p><strong>As they are made.</strong> For the procedure, you will need two layers of fabric and crushed ice. Pieces of ice should be evenly distributed between the layers of matter and wrap it around your waist. Of course, it is not easy, since the pieces may be shifted and fall out, so they are sometimes used instead of ice water. In this case, as heating the tissue, ie, every 2-3 minutes, remove the cloth, re-soak in water, drained and then wrapped around the waist. The procedure lasts about 30 minutes.</p>

<p><strong>Expected effect.</strong> It uses the same principle as that of acetic wrappings: It is assumed that the cooling body will promote local lipolysis.</p>

<p><strong>The real effect of the procedure.</strong> As already mentioned, the local impacts of low temperature does not contribute to the breakdown of fat in the area of &#8203;&#8203;exposure to the cold. Nevertheless, these wraps are more effective than acetic acid. <strong><em>Firstly</em></strong>, they are used for lower temperatures, and thus the body is still in its warm spends a certain amount of calories. <strong><em>Second</em></strong>, the strong cooling effect on the blood vessels, which increases the drainage of fluid from the problem area and therefore contributes to a small extent visual thinning waist, although quite insignificant and brief.</p>

<p><strong>Conclusion.</strong> Cold wraps are ineffective for weight loss abdomen, but can be used in combination with other treatments aimed at weight reduction.</p>

<h2>Coffee wrap</h2>

<p><strong>As they are made.</strong> From natural ground coffee prepared paste by mixing it with water. The mixture was applied to the waist region, is wrapped on top of it 3-4 times with cling film. Then the abdomen is additionally wrap and lie down for an hour under a warm blanket.</p>

<p><strong>Expected effect.</strong> Coffee is known as an aid to weight loss. It is believed that during the wrapping caffeine penetrates beneath the skin and causes the breakdown of fat in the coating.</p>

<p><strong>The real effect of the procedure.</strong> Alas, even the best components and organic coffee does not penetrate into the subcutaneous fat layer. So its &quot;toning, firming and stimulating&quot; effect can be felt only in respect of the nervous system and for receiving the coffee inside, and not in relation to fat when external use. The only positive effect of wrap is the local application of heat, which dilates blood vessels, improves microcirculation and promotes drainage of fluid in the tissues. All of this does not lead to weight loss, but a little better effect appropriate measures aimed at fighting fat.</p>

<p><strong>Conclusion.</strong> Coffee wraps can be used only against the background of exercise of massage and dieting. With their independent use of weight loss will not happen.</p>

<p>For the effects on the stomach area, and recommended other kinds of wraps: honey (we wrote about it in one of my previous posts), mustard, clay, etc. We do not see much point to describe in detail each of them: in any case, their effect will be largely determined by the application of heat or cold, but not unique influence selected for their active ingredient.</p>

<p><strong>Even the most effective options for existing wraps will help you not just go and get rid of excess fat on the abdomen; the most that you can expect from them - a drainage action, against which will create the appearance of weight loss.</strong> The real effect you watch only when specifically will undertake to improve the figure and will no longer rely on the fact that lose weight, lying under a blanket in plastic wrap.</p>

<p>Study at home or join a gym if you can not discipline themselves; reduce caloric intake or consult a dietitian to recommend you a diet; do massage and wraps the problem area, or make an appropriate cosmetic procedures. The main thing - do it all the time, long and complex. If you really want to achieve, and to see his waist in perfect condition, you will not stop what it will take up to several months of effort, and that it will be accompanied to your constraints and the need to carry physical activity and possibly material costs.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protein for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-04T11:05:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/protein-for-weight-loss/protein-for-weight-loss.jpg" title="Protein for weight loss" alt="weight loss protein">Protein - one of the three main energy substrates required to sustain the human body. Along with carbohydrates and fats, they form the basis of our food. In the intestine, the proteins are broken down into amino acids, which are released into the bloodstream, and can then be consumed as a &quot;fuel&quot;. But if fat and especially carbohydrates energy function is the main, the proteins are spent mainly on the construction of the cells in our body.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Surely you notice that most of today&rsquo;s diets restricted in the first place, the consumption of fats and carbohydrates, while the basis of the diet are just proteins. What is the reason? Obviously, nutritionists believe proteins are less harmful to the figures, so a person is allowed to use them in large quantities. But the splitting of proteins produce as much energy as carbohydrates. That is, their calorie content comparable. What is the secret properties of dietary protein foods?</p>

<p>Secret 1. As already mentioned, only a small portion of protein is used to meet the energy needs of the body. The rest are going to build new cells, enzymes, antibodies, hormones.</p>

<p>Secret 2. Squirrels rarely turn into fat, as this is a complex and energy-intensive process, which, moreover, takes place in two stages. In the process of gluconeogenesis from amino acids derived glucose, which can then be used for the synthesis of triglycerides (fats). Normally, our body is not economical decided on such irrational action.</p>

<p>Secret 3. The process of protein breakdown in the intestines requires large amounts of energy. For example, to 1000 kcal of protein, the body has to expend about 300 calories. To remove the same amount of energy from carbohydrates consumed only 70 kcal.</p>

<p>All protein products, in fact, are dietary. But not only this is the reason for the wide use of proteins in nutrition programs aimed at weight reduction. If the shortage of fats and carbohydrates is only good figure, the lack of protein in the body can turn around serious health problems.</p>

<ol>
<li>It reduces the body&rsquo;s defenses, increased incidence of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/" title="infectious diseases">infectious diseases</a>. Proteins are essential for the maintenance of both cellular and humoral immunity same. Antibodies complement system, interferon, lysozyme, immunoglobulins, leukocytes - to produce all the necessary elements of the immune system proteins.</li>
<li>hormonal imbalance, deterioration of the skin, fatigue, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/depression.html" title="depression">depression</a>, decreased libido, and even cessation of menstruation - can also be caused by protein deficiency.</li>
<li>If there is insufficient protein the body tries to get them from domestic sources, breaking down the body&rsquo;s own tissue. First in the course are the skeletal muscles. Therefore, in the absence of a sufficient amount of food proteins, at some point, muscle mass begins to decline rapidly.</li>
<li>When the amount of albumin in the blood is reduced, the swelling begin to form. The reason for this decrease in oncotic (exerted proteins) plasma pressure. The liquid passes easily from the vessels into the interstitial (intercellular) space, which results in swelling of the soft tissues.</li>
<li>Protein is needed for generation of platelets and clotting factors. Therefore, protein deficiency increases the risk of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/injuries-and-accidents/bleeding.html" title="bleeding">bleeding</a>.</li>
</ol>


<p>The protein does not burn fat, but it promotes weight loss when used instead of fats and carbohydrates. As one of the three main sources of energy, in fact, this nutrient has the lowest calorie. So most popular diets are based on reducing the intake of carbohydrates and fats that are harmful to the figure. Proteins thus, are generally not limited.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
