<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: healthy lifestyle | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com//categories/healthy-lifestyle/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-07-05T13:02:39+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Products debilitating arthritis pain]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/products-debilitating-arthritis-pain/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-05T12:52:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/products-debilitating-arthritis-pain</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/products-debilitating-arthritis-pain/0.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/products-debilitating-arthritis-pain/0.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;arthritis pain, arthritis, diet, ñhondroprotectors, dairy products&rsquo; &lsquo;Products debilitating arthritis pain&rsquo;" >Arthritis &ndash; an inflammatory disease of the joint (or more joints), and among the main causes various infections diseases, injuries, nervous system disorders, allergy, metabolic disorders, vitamin deficiencies. The disease occurs quite often, and do not always get sick elderly people (although they are certainly more often).</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Arthritis &ndash; a set of measures, including medication, mud hirudotherapy, physiotherapy, and, alas, sometimes it comes to surgery. But the disease could have been avoided or at least significantly delay it, if in time, that is, from his youth to think about its prevention. And this, above all, the right diet. But never too late to start, the people who have been diagnosed with arthritis, it is recommended to stick to a certain diet &ndash; in conjunction with the main treatment this will substantially reduce joint pain and slow the progression of the disease.</p>

<h2>Fighting overweight</h2>

<p>There have arthritis your &ldquo;favorites&rdquo;, but rather &ldquo;darling&rdquo; &ndash; is obese women overstepped 50-year milestone. As a rule, most of these ladies are suffering from any disease of the joints &ndash; this arthritis and osteoarthritis and gout, etc. It is important to understand that the further progression of these diseases in a short time can lead to disability and, of course, very spoil the quality of life, and that is why it is now important in combination with other therapeutic measures to think about weight loss. This not only helps to improve the condition of the joints, but also contribute to the overall improvement of the body.</p>

<h2>Priority products</h2>

<p>Is not a secret that vegetarians are significantly less likely to suffer from diseases of the joints than avid meat-eaters. Besides diet, based fresh fruits and vegetables containing fiber, promote rapid weight loss.</p>

<p>For example, people suffering from arthritis, recommended in all kinds of cabbage. It contains sulforaphane &ndash; a substance which prevents the destruction of the cartilage tissue. In this sense, all the good cabbage varieties, but especially broccoli. Cabbage also contains a record number of vitamins, micro and macro, and therefore not only helps prevent joint pain, but also enhances the body&rsquo;s resistance to many diseases. And by the way, the constant use of cabbage effectively helps to cope with the problem of constipation, if any.</p>

<p>Summer must eat cherries. These berries contain a lot of antioxidants (anthocyanins), which due to their anti-inflammatory properties, act as an anesthetic. Arthritis, osteoarthritis and gout even able to retreat before the cherries.</p>

<p><strong>Collagen</strong> is essential for building bone and cartilage, muscles and ligaments. He is in aspic jelly or which are prepared on the basis of bone broth.</p>

<p><strong>Chondroprotectors</strong> &ndash; another substance which promotes the restoration of the cartilaginous tissue and enhances the production of synovial fluid. Pharmacopeia offers a variety of drugs for the treatment of arthritis, based on glucosamine and chondroitin them who belong to the group chondroprotectors. Contains a substance in food gelatin, so do not forget to prepare a more delicious dessert and low-cal like jelly.</p>

<p>It must be treated gently <strong>proteins</strong>, such as red meat is recommended to exclude completely, but that does not mean that you should go to the protein-free diet. Proteins are needed to build new tissue and to restore the cartilage that covers the articular surfaces of bones. &ldquo;Take&rdquo; protein from lean white meat, fish and vegetable of buckwheat and legumes (peas, beans, lentils). By the way, the protein is better absorbed if the meat is cooked for a couple of stewed or boiled. Contribute to the restoration of the joints and dairy products, particularly useful dairy products &ndash; yogurt, fermented baked milk, cottage cheese.</p>

<p>One of the causes of joint diseases is metabolic disorders, so patients with arthritis need fats. It should be fats of vegetable origin, also allowed a small amount of butter.</p>

<p>Body needs B vitamins &ndash; they play an important role in the proper metabolism. A lack of these vitamins in addition to arthritis can appear many other diseases, is caused by impaired metabolism.</p>

<p>Vitamin D &ndash; is another important vitamin, its deficiency leads to excessive deposition of calcium in the articular cartilage to reduce its elasticity. Result &ndash; the cartilage is gradually destroyed. Compensate for the deficiency of this vitamin helps the fish oil &ndash; it requires not only children but also adults.</p>

<p>Drink a lot! Water &ndash; the basis of any diet in the treatment of arthritis. Dehydration is extremely harmful for our joints, and, as they say, do not lead to sin, it is understood that dehydration occurs in the joints long before a person starts to feel thirsty. But the fluid can not be abused &ndash; excess fluid leads to edema, and this disrupts the blood supply and food joints. So drink plenty of fluids, but be careful to avoid edema.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meals centenarians. Secrets of longevity]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/meals-centenarians-secrets-of-longevity/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-28T23:12:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/meals-centenarians-secrets-of-longevity</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/food-centenarians/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/food-centenarians/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Food centenarians, longevity secrets&rsquo; &lsquo;Meals centenarians. Secrets of longevity&rsquo;" > Secrets of centenarians &ndash; in their diet. The greatest Greek physician Hippocrates and teacher, whose name is in our perception is inextricably linked with the famous Hippocratic Oath, rightly considered the &ldquo;father of medicine&rdquo;, claimed that any human disease is due to a breach of food habits and lifestyle.</p>

<p>It belongs to Hippocrates famous phrase: &ldquo;We are what we eat&rdquo;, thus emphasizing the most important role nutrition for human life and health.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Without exception, all people want to live a long time, but have to stay healthy, vigorous, firm in the mind and memory. Scientists around the world are trying to find the answer to the secrets of longevity, carefully study this phenomenon, trying to understand why so few people manage to live so long without the disease, although genetically the human capacity for approximately 150 years of life.</p>

<h2>Power centenarians</h2>

<p>Despite the huge number of hypotheses about the secrets of health and longevity, as well as the fact that all the various centenarians living conditions &ndash; climatic, geographical, social, and views of all scientists in agreement that the power of centenarians is very closely linked with longevity and plays it  For all their differences and peculiarities, long-lived of all regions of the Earth have very similar features and rules for the use of food.</p>

<p>Slightly paraphrasing the famous line of Hippocrates, you can add that person &ndash; it&rsquo;s not only what he eats, but also the fact that he was drinking. All the world&rsquo;s centenarians drink only pure, natural spring water, which is the most important secret of longevity, since the human body is 75% water and therefore it is very important what kind of water it makes its internal reserves. On the crucial role of water in human life, norms of consumption and correct drinking regime for health read the article on our website.</p>

<p>Secrets of centenarians is pretty simple, like all brilliant. Centenarians world eat only those foods that grow in their climate zone without using anything to eat imported and exotic. It is so right that we should consider whether we need, such as bananas, which, undoubtedly, are a storehouse of vitamins, but only if they break and then eat.</p>

<p>However, as is known, bananas have not grow, they rip green, immature and thus are coated with wax and other harmful chemical compounds for prolonged preservation and transportation. So I ask, we need such fruits is not it better to eat an apple? The same question arises about the imported strawberries and watermelons have no taste, no smell, no good. Is not it better to wait for the season to gorge and plenty of delicious and healthy fruits and vegetables that grow in our area?</p>

<p>All centenarians eat very little of the world, never overeat and get up from the table without a sense of satiety. They are no excess weight and obesity, which are known to not add health and longevity. About the dangers of overeating and benefits of short breaks from eating to read this article.</p>

<p>Food in the diet dominated by long-lived low-fat and low-fat, which is very useful for keeping in perfect condition of blood vessels and the prevention of hypertension. The use of low-calorie food that has high biological activity, has long been experimentally proved by many scientists. Well known scientific experiment conducted on rats &ndash; in a subgroup of animals that reduced caloric intake by a quarter, life expectancy increased by 32%. However, where calorie reduced by 50%, the rats lived twice as long.</p>

<p>Food centenarians consume only fresh, it keeps the most of the vitamins and nutrients of food. Naturally, they reject the canned food and other unhealthy foods. No fast food, reheating and yesterday&rsquo;s food out of the fridge, all the half-eaten give cattle.</p>

<p>By the way, according to some studies, this indispensable in the modern kitchen thing as a microwave, just destroys the products have passed the microwave treatment, vitamins, minerals and nutrients. Therefore, whenever possible, should follow the example of centenarians &ndash; cook gruel and then eat it, not a three-day warm up in the microwave soup, which does not have anything useful. Especially do not recommend to warm up food in the microwave for small children.</p>

<p>Power centenarians virtually includes entrees and rich broth and meat on their menu is mainly present in cooked form. On the table there is always a lot of different herbs that help to keep the gut flora in perfect condition. In centenarians Abkhazia and Azerbaijan on the composition of intestinal microflora in general identical to the flora of healthy children, which is achieved by regular consumption of the national dairy products, which are known to be very useful for proper digestion.</p>

<p>An important secret of longevity is also made in the absence of sugar in their diet in its purest form, as well as a variety of jams, chocolates and other sweets today that can trigger the development of diabetes. Sugar they receive in the form of glucose, which is necessary for the body to quickly replenish energy deficit by eating honey, raisins and a variety of sweet fruit. Fruits and vegetables make up a large portion of all food centenarians.</p>

<p>Chinese gerontologists are absolutely sure that the formula found longevity and looks like this &ndash; very low calorie diet, with a minimal amount of fat and animal protein and lots of vegetables and fruits.</p>

<p>As far as this is true, time will tell, but do for yourself useful conclusions and adopt some simple secrets of centenarians in the diet, we just have to. Having started eating right, as do the long-lived all over the world, we will stop gaining weight, get sick, we are in great shape and, therefore, will live longer.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Periodontal disease and bleeding gums]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/periodontal-disease-and-bleeding-gums/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-28T23:10:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/periodontal-disease-and-bleeding-gums</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/periodontal-disease/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/periodontal-disease/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Periodontal disease, bleeding gums, periodontal&rsquo; &lsquo;Periodontal disease and bleeding gums&rsquo;" > Successful treatment of periodontal disease depends on timely access to a doctor. Bleeding gums is the most common symptom of periodontal disease &ndash; a complex of tissues surrounding and holding the teeth in the jaw bone. Despite the fact that by Parodont also include bone around the teeth and muscle ligaments that hold the teeth in the jaw bones, most people are faced with the problem of gum &ndash; regular or occasional bleeding, swelling and inflammation.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Many people mistakenly believe trifling periodontal disease and do not require emergency treatment of symptomatic &ndash; with &ldquo;harmless&rdquo; bleeding gums simply rinse their mouth herbs and do not go to the doctor. However, engaging in self-treatment, they cause serious damage to your health.</p>

<p>Fact that gingivitis (initial stage of periodontitis), the main symptom is bleeding gums, quite successfully (nearly 100%) is treatable if it initiated when the first symptoms.</p>

<p>If the disease takes the form of running, then there is a risk of losing teeth even at a young age. According to the WHO, 80% of children under the age of 10 years, there are already early signs of gingivitis, which is associated with significant physiological stress of the periodontal tissues in a growing body when cutting, shaping and growth of teeth.</p>

<p>For older people, because they have periodontitis tooth loss occurs in 95% of cases. However, there is good news &ndash; if only a few decades ago with the disease periodontitis keep the teeth was considered virtually impossible, the modern development of zubosohranyayuschih technology to successfully stop the destructive process.</p>

<h2>What is periodontal disease and periodontal disease &ndash; what&rsquo;s the difference between them</h2>

<p>Periodontal disease is a relatively rare disease (it accounts for only about 3 &ndash; 4% of the cases of periodontal problems), while periodontitis is &ldquo;honorable&rdquo; second among all dental disease (caries immediately after), and is present to varying degrees in nearly 95.</p>

<h2>Periodontal disease causes and symptoms</h2>

<p>Periodontal disease &ndash; is a non-inflammatory disease of periodontal tissues, which are due to internal disturbances in the body, leading to malnutrition and periodontal tissue perfusion and, as a consequence, to atrophy of the alveolar bone (bone edges of the hole tooth).</p>

<p>As a result of atrophic processes in periodontitis occur sclerotic changes in the bone tissue, reduced interdental septum, and the gums gradually become thinner and the like &ldquo;settle down&rdquo;, resulting in the effect of &ldquo;wedge-shaped teeth&rdquo; with bare roots. In the future, increased sensitivity to chemical and thermal stimuli, changing the color and the enamel is destroyed. Subsequently, as a result of running and complete atrophy, the teeth become loose and fall out much.</p>

<p>Local factors, in particular the impact of micro-organisms essential role in the development of the disease do not play, but serve only unfavorable factor aggravating.</p>

<h2>Periodontal disease symptoms and the stage</h2>

<p>Periodontitis, in contrast to periodontal disease, is an inflammatory nature and manifests the destruction of the connection between the tooth, gum and surrounding tissues, the formation of deep periodontal pockets and the gradual deformation and destruction of the bone hole tooth.</p>

<p>Because periodontal disease most often develops slowly and gradually over the years does not cause discomfort in the early stages it is quite difficult to diagnose. However, it should be noted that there are cases sufficient and rapid development of the disease.</p>

<h2>Step periodontitis</h2>

<p>First, the easy, harmless and effectively treatable stage of periodontal disease (gingivitis) is accompanied by a slight redness, inflammation and bleeding gums, bad breath and the formation of shallow periodontal pockets.</p>

<p>While moderate adds the following symptoms &ndash; a small tooth mobility, the emergence of cracks and gaps between the teeth, on education-and subgingival stones, difficulty in chewing food, deepening periodontal pockets (up to 5 mm) with a small selection of them.</p>

<p>In severe teeth start to hurt badly, offset, in part, loose and fall out, and deepened periodontal pockets and from their cavities are frequent and copious purulent discharge with an unpleasant odor.</p>

<p>Causes periodontal disease are diverse and the main of them are traditionally considered to be a lack of oral hygiene, however, all is not as easy as it might seem. Indeed, the microbes that live in the mouth and form plaque (stones), can affect the periodontal tissues, they cause inflammation and lead to loosening and loss of teeth. Therefore, periodic professional scaling is necessary, but, unfortunately, the lack of means of prevention.</p>

<p>Equally important role in the development of pathology plays the uneven load on the teeth, malocclusion uncorrected, errors prosthetics and jaw injuries. For example, periodontal disease often develops if removed 6th teeth and dentures soon not installed or improperly formed contact between the upper and lower jaws. Adverse effect might wear braces, microtrauma while cutting the thread, the habit of chewing on one side, leading to an overload of a separate part of the jaw, use as toothpicks metal objects, the effect on enamel acid and alkali.</p>

<p>It is important that the seals were installed correctly &ndash; do not protrude over the edge of the tooth, and at the same time, a close fit to it. If the seal is not tight fits, the germs and infections can easily penetrate to the root and destroy it, but if the seal hangs, it prevents the removal of plaque quality, and as a consequence, inflammation of the gum tissue. In case of improper prosthetic disease process develops locally, ie, only in problem areas. In such cases we say about the local gingivitis or periodontitis local.</p>

<p>In addition, the trigger for the development of the disease often appear overall negative factors for the entire body &ndash; lowered immunity, salivary gland diseases, endocrine diseases and malnutrition. In this case, the pathological process is developing in the area of ​​the teeth and is of a generalized (universal) the nature &ndash; of a generalized gingivitis or periodontitis.</p>

<h2>Periodontitis treatment</h2>

<p>Treatment of periodontal disease in the early stages, as mentioned, has a very good prognosis, so it is very important at the first warning signs, consult a dentist. First of all, you should alert the occurrence of bleeding when brushing your teeth and chewing hard food.</p>

<p>First, try replacing your toothbrush at a softer and more use toothpaste and mouthwash with the addition of healing, restorative and antiseptic natural components. If this does not lead to the desired result, you should immediately seek medical attention &ndash; periodontist, as the bleeding can not be ignored.</p>

<p>In the first phase treatment is limited, as a rule, professional cleaning and removal of plaque and use of folk remedies for periodontal disease &ndash; applications of aloe leaves and rinse with infusions and decoctions of medicinal herbs (chamomile, oak bark, sage, plantain). Traditional medicine with bleeding gums are also advised to rub them with sea salt, honey &ndash; Mix 20 g of honey with 5 &ndash; 10 g salt and rub the teeth and gums every day, not leading to injury.</p>

<p>In addition, the presence of periodontal pockets doctor offers them washing with antiseptic solutions &ndash; a process that helps reduce inflammation and swelling of the gums and reduce bleeding. If the teeth lose their stability, showed a temporary or permanent splinting especially strong ribbons &ndash; first on the tooth surfaces make the groove depth of about 0.5 mm, and then placed her in the tape and cover the filling material.</p>

<p>To gain stability, and widely used surgical techniques, in particular patchwork technique, transplantation of bone and soft tissues and artificial guided bone regeneration. Flap operation applies to the case where the gingival pocket too deep (greater than 5 mm) to reduce its depth. To do this, a small incision is made in the gum area and cleared of stones baring at the root. Then align the affected contour of bone and sutured incision.</p>

<p>Transplantation of soft tissue (taken from the sky) is applied at the tooth roots and bared for cosmetic purposes, and bone transplants (of their own bone or synthetic) used in significant destruction of the bone tissue for retaining the tooth, and for regeneration of new bone tissue.</p>

<h3>Treatment of periodontal disease</h3>

<p>Despite the fact that an effective treatment of periodontal disease is currently no exist as physiotherapy and surgical modern technology to recover gums and relieve itching, pain, hypersensitivity and other unpleasant symptoms.</p>

<p>Physical therapy aimed at improving blood circulation and regeneration processes in the periodontium. These include massage gums darsonvalization, vakuumoterapiya, flyuktuorizatsiya, gingival shower, UHF and magnetic-laser therapy. A good massage for the gums and the best prevention of periodontal disease is the chewing of solid plant foods. Abuse of soft refining food leads to exhaustion and bone atrophy, and with regular chewing solid foods, especially raw vegetables and fruit, on the contrary, there is a training vessel gums and natural cleansing of plaque.</p>

<p>Of the surgical treatment of periodontal disease using surgery to remove the periodontal pockets, removal of microabscesses and festering gums, bone grafting, removal of infected overgrown soft tissue closure of exposed roots, raised descended gums. One promising area of ​​treatment of periodontal disease is the use of cellular technologies to stimulate the recovery of their own bone. Similar operations are underway in Moscow.</p>

<h2>Prevention of periodontal disease</h2>

<p>For the prevention of periodontal disease should be serious about the state of their teeth:</p>

<ul>
<li>1 at least once a year to visit the dentist for a professional oral hygiene;</li>
<li>Brushing teeth 2 times a day, and possibly after every meal;</li>
<li>Remove it after eating the remains of the interdental spaces with dental floss;</li>
<li>To choose a toothbrush with rounded and not too coarse bristles;</li>
<li>Eat right. For periodontal health in the menu should be physiologically required amount of protein, carbohydrates, fats, vitamins and trace elements. Do not abuse the sweets and eat more fresh organic fruits and vegetables.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colon cleansing with salt water]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/colon-cleansing-with-salt-water/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-28T23:09:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/colon-cleansing-with-salt-water</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/colon-cleansing-salt-water/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/colon-cleansing-salt-water/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Colon cleansing salt water, salt water purification intestine&rsquo; &lsquo;Colon Cleansing with salt water&rsquo;" > Clear the bowel salt water heals the whole body. Use a regular intestinal cleansing of toxins, toxins and poisons produced because of malnutrition, bad environment and stress, has long been no one in doubt because &ldquo;dirty gut&rdquo; is a favorable environment for the growth of pathogenic spoilage bacteria, which are gradually.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>As a result, in the body there is a lot of issues:</p>

<ul>
<li>There is a deficiency of vitamins and minerals that are synthesized by the beneficial bacteria;</li>
<li>Poisons are absorbed through unprotected rectal wall and the liver, which leads to disruption of the structure and the formation of gall stones in the gallbladder;</li>
<li>Suffers excretory system, causing the skin appears abrasions, acne, inflammation and signs of early aging;</li>
<li>Toxins negative effect on the blood vessels, causing them to spasm, increased blood pressure (hypertension symptoms) and the development of heart attacks and strokes;</li>
<li>Toxins and poisons can be absorbed from the intercellular space in the cell itself, destroying it at the genetic level, and contributing to malignant degeneration.</li>
</ul>


<p>The main features of slagging intestine when it is time to take action &ndash; drowsiness, headache, lethargy, furred tongue plaque, bad breath, heaviness in the abdomen, rumbling and bloating, skin rash, constipation, inflammation of the mucous membranes in the mouth, plaque on teeth  As a rule, people are not too young or not quite leading a healthy lifestyle, there is always more of the signs.</p>

<p>For regular colon cleansing should be a priority for every person who wants to maintain their health and protect against disease.</p>

<h2>Clear the bowel salt water</h2>

<p>The most effective and complete way of cleansing the body is to clean the intestines with salt water, used in the exercises of yoga for centuries. This unique technique is called Shank-Prakshalanoy and allows you to completely clear the gastro-intestinal tract, which can not in any way other than complete starvation.</p>

<p>All other methods, unfortunately, give the illusion of a complete cleaning, because the traditional enemas, and Colon are valid only in the large department. There are cases where people who thought that they clean the intestines after a colon hydrotherapy sessions, when the Shank-Prakshalany surprised to discover in their stool cherry stones, eaten many months ago.</p>

<p>The fact that the digestive tract towards the stomach to the anus extends a large number of food and sphincter valve which is opened and closed, helping to promote it. Methods Shank-Prakshalany except bowel cleansing with salt water, including performing specific exercises that relax the muscles of the valves. Because of this salty water flows freely into the rectum and acts like a lubricant there, softening the stool and freeing it from the traffic jams.</p>

<h2>Contraindications and frequency of execution</h2>

<p>Colon Cleansing salt water by the method of Shank-Prakshalany contraindicated for people with diseases of the stomach ulcer and acute lesions of the digestive tract &ndash; colitis, gastritis, pancreatitis, diarrhea, dysentery, tuberculosis, hemorrhoids and heightened bowel cancer. Also, do not carry it out during menstruation, at elevated temperature or blood pressure, heart attacks, any exacerbation of chronic illnesses and colds, when the body is too weak. Prohibits this method of treatment in pregnancy and immediately after the release of fasting (not earlier than one month).</p>

<p>Carry out the procedure Shank-Prakshalany can be as necessary as a preventive four times a year when the seasons change. For those suffering from chronic constipation, it may be the best means of &ldquo;re-education&rdquo; of the intestine and used in place of enemas &ndash; first two times a week, and then, to the extent of purification, once every two weeks. For best results, it is desirable to clean prepare in advance, that is, relax, moisturize and warm your body. To do this week try to refrain from fatty, fried, spicy and meat dishes every day, take a warm bath every morning and drink fresh juices vegetables &ndash; carrot, apple, beet, cucumber.</p>

<h2>Method bowel cleansing salt water</h2>

<p>Method bowel cleansing salt water is the following &ndash; you need to dissolve 1 tablespoon sea ​​salt in a liter of warm water and drink 1 glass, alternating between drinking a glass of water with the performance of special moves at a fast pace to help relax the sphincter. So it is necessary to repeat 6 times (a glass of water &ndash; exercises) until consumed 6 cups.</p>

<p>Stand with your feet shoulder width apart, arms at the castle over the head with his hands up, breathing free. Slow slopes alternately right and left by 8 times in each direction. These movements open the pylorus, what would the water could get out of it into the duodenum.</p>

<p><strong>Exercise number 2 &ldquo;Circular motion&rdquo;</strong></p>

<p>Pull the right arm forward, press the left chest. Thrusting his right hand, turn right only the upper part of the body. Then the other side. Perform 8 times.</p>

<p>Take the prone position, with emphasis on the elbows, feet shoulder width 40 cm Hold your breath, raise your hands and turn to the right, trying to see his own heel. Return to the starting position and relax. Repeat on the other side. Perform 8 times.</p>

<p><strong>Exercise number 4 &ldquo;Squatting&rdquo;</strong></p>

<p>Squat down so that the distance between the feet was about 30 cm and the heel located on the outside of the thighs, and not under the buttocks. Lower the left knee to the floor, hands on knees. By hand tilt the right foot to the left, tilting the body slightly forward. In this case, try to press down on the right foot stomach. The same is repeated at the left side, 8 times in each direction. This exercise helps to move water into the rectum.</p>

<p>Once the cup 6 is consumed and 6 complexes made should appear urge to defecate. If they are not within 5 mauled again, repeat the full range of motion at first and go to the toilet. If you still do not get emptied, which is unlikely, take a small enema with plain water without salt.</p>

<p>After the first empty again to drink a glass of water, do exercises and go to the bathroom. This cycle must be repeated up until the water comes out clean. The number of repeated treatments depends on individual pollution intestines, but usually requires no more than 10-14 glasses. After the end of the cleansing drink 3 glasses of plain water and pushing the root of the tongue, try to induce vomiting in order to fully clean the stomach and turn off the mechanism of evacuation. If you do not, then within a few hours of time you want to go to the toilet.</p>

<p>Sometimes, after a few glasses of salt water drunk nausea and abdominal fullness, feeling that the water does not pass into the intestine. This indicates that it is not opened the first sphincter. In this case, perform a series of exercises 2-3. Once the nausea will pass, then pass into the stomach and can be opened further to continue the procedure under the scheme.</p>

<p>If you feel that the gas formed in the gut tube and hinders the process of draining, push down on the belly with his hands, make a stand on the blades (birch) and do the set of all four exercises.</p>

<h2>Food and drink after bowel cleansing with salt water</h2>

<p>After the full completion of cleaning rest for half an hour, then be sure to eat, no later than an hour after the last discharge (this is important because you can not keep the stomach empty after salt treatment over an hour). Drink before a meal can not be, despite appeared thirsty, because you support this evacuation, and will continue to go to the toilet.</p>

<p>The first recommended food &ndash; rice cooked in water with butter (about 40 grams), wheat, oats or pasta with grated hard cheese. In the next days you can not consume milk, yogurt, white cheese, fresh vegetables and fruits, acidic foods and alcohol. The bread can be eaten after the second meal, at the end of day return to a normal diet, but meat.</p>

<p>The first bowel movements appear about 24-36 hours after treatment, they are golden-yellow in color and odor, as in infants. The positive effect of cleansing occur at some time in the form of fresh breath, improve the complexion and pure whites of the eyes. In addition, following this procedure, many people get rid of allergies and get excellent absorption of nutrients, resulting in one acquires ideal weight &ndash; thin rid of unhealthy thinness, and those who are overweight, lose weight.</p>

<p>People who intend to seriously address their rehabilitation and purification, may carry Shank-Prakshalanu every month, as it helps to rejuvenate, strengthen immunity, well-being and increased energy?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cleaning vessels folk remedies]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/cleaning-vessels-folk-remedies/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-22T23:19:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/cleaning-vessels-folk-remedies</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/cleaning-vessels-folk-remedies/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/cleaning-vessels-folk-remedies/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Cleaning vessels folk remedies, cleaning vessels from cholesterol&rsquo; &lsquo;After cleaning the vessels are headaches and pressure&rsquo;" > Cleaning of vessels and keeping them in good condition is the key to health and longevity, because healthy blood vessels &ndash; is a guarantee of the normal state of circulatory and cardiovascular system and the prevention of atherosclerosis, hypertension, heart attacks and strokes.</p>

<p>As you know, with age wear vessels &ndash; they gradually thicken, lose their elasticity and become brittle, and their walls are jagged and rough.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>They eventually deposited layer of salt, fat lime, cholesterol, preventing blood flow and form plaques.</p>

<p>Intrigue atherosclerosis is that at first it goes unnoticed and does not provide any clinical symptoms, so such terrible its complications such as heart attack or stroke may suddenly strike is considered quite healthy person. Only by narrowing the blood vessels of more than 50% of the characteristic symptoms begin to appear atherosclerotic lesions.</p>

<p>Here are the main features of the &ldquo;bad&rdquo; blood vessels, which is necessary to pay close attention to and which indicate the need to do their cleaning and consolidation:</p>

<p>If it affects the blood vessels of the brain &ndash; the deterioration of memory and concentration, headaches, dizziness, decreased vision and hearing, loss of performance.</p>

<p>If it affects the blood vessels of the heart &ndash; shortness of breath, angina.</p>

<p>Atherosclerosis extremities &ndash; cramps in the legs, chill the extremities, muscle pain when walking, skin blanching legs.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
