<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Healthy-lifestyle | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/healthy-lifestyle/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-05-26T18:48:11+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Products Raise, and Which Lower Blood Pressure?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/what-products-raise-and-which-lower-blood-pressure/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-11T17:06:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/what-products-raise-and-which-lower-blood-pressure</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/what-products-raise-and-which-lower-blood-pressure/img.jpg" title="What products raise, and which lower blood pressure?" alt="products lowers blood pressure, foods raise blood pressure, products which reduce the pressure reduction">It is no secret that different foods can affect blood pressure - both upward (<a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/cardiology/hypertension.html" title="hypertension">hypertension</a>) and decrease in strontium (hypotension). Both conditions are unfavorable to the body and should therefore be corrected figures of pressure in the direction of their normal values. Chronic elevation of blood pressure often indicate different starting health problems, genetic predisposition to hypertension, and the problems associated with lifestyle. Acute episodes of high blood pressure is usually caused by <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a> and unhealthy diet.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>


<p>Sodium is the main component of salt is a natural mineral that is found in many foods, but most of it gets to us it is in the form of salt - the well-known compounds <em>NaCl</em>, are sure that the label of &quot;white death&quot;. Why is this connection is maintained for such a bad reputation?</p>

<p>The fact is that sodium is the main extracellular ion rights, without which it is impossible to imagine the course of normal metabolic processes. Sodium, making the main contribution to the maintenance of osmotic pressure of the blood, thereby causes fluid retention in the bloodstream, and when excessive amounts causes an increase in blood volume and, consequently, an increase in blood pressure.</p>

<p>Manufacturers often added salt in packaged foods as a preservative which increases their lifespan. Restaurants also added a large amount of salt in prepared foods to improve taste. According to doctors at the <em>Cleveland Clinic</em>, the addition of sodium in foods is often the culprit spikes in blood pressure and, as a consequence, the emergence of hypertensive crises. Some examples of foods that are high in sodium, which contribute to high blood pressure: deli meats, sausage, bacon, ham, instant soups, broths, marinades, sauces, including soy sauce, ketchup, chips, popcorn, salted nuts, salted seafood to beer, and pickled.</p>

<p>According to numerous scientific data reduction of salt in the diet leads to a sustainable reduction in blood pressure. It is recommended to use less than 5 grams (5000 mg) of salt a day, but if you already have any disease of the cardiovascular system, then you are limiting the content of salt in the diet should be at a level of no more than 1500 mg, which is significantly less than in the previous recommendations. For orientation, one teaspoon of salt contains about 2400 milligrams of sodium.</p>

<p>Excessive alcohol consumption blood pressure can rise to dangerous levels. Dr. Sheldon Sheps of the Mayo Clinic says that drinking more than three doses of conventional alcoholic drinks temporarily raises blood pressure, while recurring binges can cause high blood pressure for a long time. Understanding how much alcohol you consume, is already an important step in reducing the habit; per conventional dose of alcohol is considered to be 350 ml beer, 140 ml of wine or 40 ml of the 40-degree vodka.</p>

<p>It was found that people who follow a diet high in fat, have higher blood pressure than vegetarians. In contrast, a study published in April 1987 in the Journal of the Royal Society of Medicine suggests that a diet high in fiber and high in polyunsaturated fats is able to keep blood pressure low. In addition, many fruits and vegetables contain potassium, known for its action for lowering blood pressure.</p>

<p><strong>Here we consider a number of foods that can help lower blood pressure:</strong></p>

<p>Vegetables - provide the body with magnesium, potassium and fiber, which are important nutrients that can reduce blood pressure. Be sure to eat a variety of vegetables daily, including broccoli, potatoes, spinach, cabbage, tomatoes and zucchini. If you consume vegetable juice, make sure it does not have a high sodium content.</p>

<p><em>Fruits</em> - choose a variety of fruits to help meet your needs for magnesium, potassium and fiber. Bananas, apples, berries, melons, peaches, pineapple and citrus fruits are good choices. Eat fruits daily. If you choose a fruit juice, make sure that there is enough plant fiber and low in sugar (ie, preference should be given exactly the juice, not nectar).</p>

<p><em>Dairy Products</em> - it has been shown that calcium is contained in dairy products, it is effective in reducing blood pressure in persons suffering from hypertension. Dairy products are a rich source of calcium, including it relates to milk, cheese and low-fat yoghurt.</p>

<p><em>Whole grains</em> - mainly contain vegetable fiber (cellulose), which can also help reduce blood pressure. Therefore, enter in your diet of brown rice, whole grains, bran cereal, cereal and bread based on barley and oats.</p>

<p><em>Fish</em> - even if the fish is fat, but it contains a lot of omega-3 fatty acids - such as in salmon, it is a very positive effect on the cardiovascular system in general has a definite hypotensive effect. The American Heart Association offers a variety of foods to eat fish twice a week.</p>

<p><em>Nuts</em>, legumes and seeds are a rich source of fiber, energy, protein and magnesium, which also has a hypotensive action. So try to periodically use almonds, hazelnuts, walnuts, peanuts, sunflower seeds or pumpkin.</p>

<p><em>Spices</em> - to eat less food with salt (i.e., less salt food), try to diversify its nutritional quality of a variety of spices to give the food a unique new fragrance.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Not to Eat Before Blood Donation?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/what-not-to-eat-before-blood-donation/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-11T15:03:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/what-not-to-eat-before-blood-donation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/what-not-to-eat-before-blood-donation/img.jpg" title="What not to eat before blood donation?" alt="before the blood test, before the blood test can have, before taking a blood test, eat before the blood test">Dietary restrictions - that&rsquo;s what a lifetime many times faced everyone. Aggravated <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/gastritis.html" title="gastritis">gastritis</a> - you can not eat spices, fried, sweet, salty and fresh fruits and vegetables; performance scales began to &quot;off-scale&quot; higher positions - sit on a diet and generally deprive ourselves of the majority of gastronomic pleasures. Even the blood can not pass so do without taboos&hellip;</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>


<h2>Restrictions before taking blood samples</h2>

<p>Regardless of whether it is for a study you donate blood (for general analysis, sugar, for biochemical research, hormones, infection, etc.), preparation steps for the procedure will always be roughly the same.</p>

<p>In the first place, it will need to come fasting, i.e., not less than 6-8 hours after the last (not tight) meal. In some sources you can find that prior to entering the treatment room you for 12 hours or more in any case can not even look in the direction of the refrigerator. This is not true; the period of voluntary hunger strike for a period of 6-8 hours is enough.</p>

<p>As a rule, the complexities of this preparatory measure does not arise, because usually all the research blood is taken in the morning and after a nap, not every person is experiencing severe famine.</p>

<p>Most people have heard, and that before the analysis can not eat anything, but that their knowledge in preparation for the blood collection procedure usually exhausted. Nevertheless, there are certain restrictions and for the earlier period of the preparation. To analysis showed the most reliable results, for 2 days before the nurse bring to your hand syringe needle, you have to sit on a special diet. You are not recommended to eat:</p>

<ul>
<li>Fatty, fried, smoked foods;</li>
<li>Sweets and confectionery products in large quantities;</li>
</ul>


<p>If donating blood on a general analysis, it can be a bit neglected (that many, by the way, do), but more complex investigations such as biochemical analysis, determination of antibodies to infections, detection of cancer markers, immunogram, etc., require from patients greater diligence.</p>

<p>It is believed that before the blood sugar should be almost a week to refuse the use of carbohydrates in any form. In fact, it will need only a couple of days a sensible diet.</p>

<p>Carbohydrate consumed quickly or stocking up body, transformed into glycogen or fat, so that within a few hours after their use in the blood should not be a trace of &quot;extra&quot; sugar - if the patient is certainly not ill severe diabetes. But for such situations, people usually know in advance, so already receiving treatment and control your diet.</p>

<p>Very often patients confidentially divided among themselves that they have ignored the preparation for a particular study, and they &quot;had nothing&quot;. For this reason, some people are also beginning to question the logic of the requirements of the doctor. There is a thought: &quot;And what will happen if you do not prepare for the analysis?&quot; Of course, it may be that you&rsquo;re lucky and it will not affect the quality of the results. However, excesses of food before a <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/analysis-and-research/blood-test-biochemical.html" title="blood test">blood test</a> can cause false data receipt.</p>

<p>Here&rsquo;s a simple example. After the meal, there is a man called physiologic leukocytosis - cells are white blood cells at a time out of the tissues into the bloodstream, and the amount of blood increases.</p>

<p>If you make a general analysis of the patient, who has recently eaten, this figure could be his inflated, because of what the doctor will suggest the presence of infection in the body and starts up and down to survey the unfortunate patient who is merely frivolous attitude to training&hellip; similar erroneous situations can occur at the time of other analyzes.</p>

<h2>Restrictions before taking blood donation</h2>

<p>But here the situation is different, however, the differences are not so great.</p>

<p>As for the early transition to comply with the above diet, this requirement exists for donors. Eating fatty, fried and other junk food before taking the blood impairs the quality of harvested materials. Incidentally, the &quot;no&quot; in this case, apply also on protein foods - meat, cheese, eggs, cheese, etc., they create a large load on the immune system and human kidney, which are transfused components of your blood.</p>

<p>It is characteristic that, if you do not follow a diet and to the right to take the plasma you immediately incriminate insufficient training. The plasma (blood serum) in patients who are on the eve of fat eaten, a little cloudy, and has a unique, slightly grayish-greenish tint&hellip;</p>

<p>Restrictions before taking blood or plasma donation on more serious than before the tests, but the day of the procedure, the donor is not waiting for the hunger strike, but rather an indulgence in the diet. He can afford a light breakfast (no forbidden foods), best of all, consisting of carbohydrate foods.</p>

<p>Tea or coffee with biscuits, drying, or a pair of candy fit perfectly. Once at the station transfusion his blood examined and the person will give the &quot;green light&quot; for the change, there he asked to drink more tea and biscuits and chocolate. Besides, you do not have to carry a thermos and a bag with a sweet, nice bonus that will be given to you right there.</p>

<p>So, whether you are pursuing your own interests (donates blood for tests) or doing good to others (sacrifice her as a donor), before the procedure of putting in something have to deny yourself a little sit on a diet. Do not let that upset, because in both cases, your goals deserve to suffer some inconvenience for them. Moreover, the dietary restrictions will last very long&hellip;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Should You Run? Benefits and Harms of Running]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/why-should-you-run-benefits-and-harms-of-running/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-08T11:05:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/why-should-you-run-benefits-and-harms-of-running</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/why-should-you-run-benefits-and-harms-of-running/img.jpg" title="Why should you run? Benefits and harms of running" alt="benefits and harms of running">Nowadays, an active and healthy lifestyle is often associated with running. That this exercise has the most popular, and throughout the world. Those who are older will remember the American trend of the 90s, according to which everyone had to run. Everyone is used to talk about the benefits of running, but no one really thinks about its pros and cons. All are accustomed to consider running a useful exercise, but the question is: why? - no answer. We will try to carry out a detailed analysis.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>


<p>First of all, it should be noted the current situation - a large part of the population leads a sedentary lifestyle, that they have observed an increased risk of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/vascular-disease/" title="cardiovascular disease">cardiovascular disease</a>. The argument at the time forced thousands of Americans to get out into the fresh air and to carry out various marathons. Even then began to celebrate the negative consequences of the long run. Look at the Champions marathon, do they look healthy people? Not at all. And it is a professional, not to mention the amateurs that morning wearing a pair of sneakers, running headlong, piously believing in <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> and the benefits of such action.</p>

<p>It was at that time running for the analysis came from many foreign sports institutions. It was found that the most rational way to engage in such aerobics is not more than thirty minutes 4-5 times a week. Less time will not produce the desired effect, as the fat storage will remain untouched, as the metabolic rate. At the same time, longer running session, the body perceives as <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a>, and not a positive one. The adrenal glands begin to secrete hormones in the emergency mode. Of course, the human body is designed for such loads, but your body can not withstand such conditions for a long time.</p>

<p>Speaking on the merits, it is one of the best basic exercises that makes working all the muscles of the body. All limbs are not fixed and do not have support, which in turn loads the muscles excellent stabilizers. But perhaps the biggest advantage of ease of implementation can be considered. Running is suitable for both beginners and advanced fitness.</p>

<p><strong>The general scheme of the positive factors of running is as follows:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Improvement of the cardiovascular system;</li>
<li>Saturation of oxygen (also leads to lipolysis);</li>
<li>Burning of a large number of calories;</li>
<li>Destruction of fat storage (with slow running and interval);</li>
<li>Strengthening the musculoskeletal system;</li>
<li>An increase in heat production, thereby burn fat.</li>
</ul>


<p>Among all the aerobic exercise jogging can &quot;boast&quot; the highest risk of injury. An illiterate training can quite undermine health. It is important to moderate the amount of load, a good rest, and regular exercise. Observance of these three factors in most cases will prevent overtraining and injuries.</p>

<p>It should be noted that when running load on all joints and bones of the person is increased 5-8 times - especially in obese second and third type. Any excess weight puts a ban on small jogging. Your feet are simply not ready for such a huge load. Mindlessly running can completely erase the patellar tendon, and the sport will have to forget. In addition to this common injury is a sprain or a dislocation of the ankle joint. As a rule, this is due to incorrect posture while running. Posture plays a key role, both in daily life and in sports. In terms of its lack of load balance collapses.</p>

<p>The saddest thing for us - women, is the fact that we are exposed to greater risk of injury than men. Nature endowed us a wider pelvis in order to fit it all the organs. As a result, changing the angle of the femur, whereby the knee joint when running gets practically doubled load.</p>

<p>Of course, running has lots of advantages. It is an indispensable exercise for both professionals and amateurs. In addition, it can be used for cardio sessions (intervals or slow), and for the development of strength endurance (short track speed). However, in the meantime, if you have a high percentage of body fat, you need to use this exercise with caution. We encourage you to quick step, since such a motion is not necessary to perform semi-jumping, and as a consequence there is no short-term use of one leg for support. This load sparing joints and bones, ie - It is more acceptable.</p>

<p>In general, feel free to use running, but do not forget to adjust it for yourself. Women tend to be employed in running and cardio training to maintain the overall tone, using a slow tempo or intervals.</p>

<p>It is imperative that the correct heating, ie - Warm-up. Perform stretching all muscle groups. Take this aspect of 5-10 minutes. Next, you need to warm up the muscles of the neck separately, as they are the most vulnerable spot on the body. Many girls while running quite actively rotate the head, eventually received various injuries. Follow the circular movements of the head and side bends. This will cause the blood to go to the scalene muscles, causing the neck to temporarily become stronger.</p>

<p>Running should start slowly, even if you use intervals. You need to provide the muscle gradually increasing the load. Even a car can not dart off in fifth gear. Everything happens in a timely manner. The same can be attributed to the person during the run. Quick Step is gradually transformed into a slow run, after 2-3 minutes the pace increases, etc. up to the level you require.</p>

<p>With regard to the position of the body, the torso should be slightly tilted forward. Back and head should be kept in line. Always follow the arching of the spine, the back should not be circular. The width of the steps depends on your individual characteristics, so that there is no general recommendations. During the run look only forward. Falling Down view discourages and does not allow to keep your back straight.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fitness During Menstruation]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/fitness-during-menstruation/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-06T11:10:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/fitness-during-menstruation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/fitness-during-menstruation/fitness-during-menstruation.jpg" title="fitness, sports, training, yoga during menstruation" alt="Fitness during menstruation">On this point there are different opinions. Most people do not accept the &quot;intermediate&quot; options are the supporters of a categorical &quot;no&quot; or &quot;yes&quot;. The first show that during <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="menstruation">menstruation</a> sports is clearly prohibited, because &quot;these days, even on the physical education free&quot;, while the latter argue that the first - a &quot;freeloader&quot; who are too sorry for yourself and make excuses for their laziness. Ostensibly, they simply do not want to once again rise to the sofa and go to the gym or to the stadium&hellip; <!--more-->In general, the two positions are not supported by any reasonable arguments and certainties - the emotions and own assumptions. Well, we look at how really things, and whether monthly about the &quot;hang&quot; of workouts.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>


<h2>What is menstruation?</h2>

<p>Menstruation - a rejection of the uterine mucosa, which occurs under the influence of hormones. The presence of menstruation - is one of the main signs of &quot;consistency&quot; of the female body.</p>

<p>Each month the uterus prepares for the possible implantation of the embryo, in other words, to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a>. Therefore, it is the mucous membrane (endometrium) grows gradually, becoming more &quot;thick&quot;, it increases the number of vessels. This is necessary in order to ensure that the embryo expected a decent supply of nutrients.</p>

<p>About a week after ovulation (egg release from the ovaries), which accounts for about 10-14 day cycle, the state of the mucous optimal for the development of the ovum. It is 5-6 mm layer of well-perfused epithelial cells.</p>

<p>If pregnancy does not occur, the endometrium thickens. In the end, it becomes a cell so much that the uterine vessels simply lose their ability to feed. Therefore mucous is rejected; The &quot;bursting&quot; vessels, and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/injuries-and-accidents/bleeding.html" title="bleeding">bleeding</a> occurs. Actually, this is menstruation.</p>

<p>Description of the process looks pretty grim and unpleasant, but the first day of the monthly body again &quot;taken up the old&quot; and again starts optimistically preparing for a possible pregnancy. Run active processes of regeneration (recovery), and monthly stop.</p>

<p>All cyclic changes run hormones at the beginning of the cycle (about 2 weeks from the first day of menstruation) in the body increases the content of estrogen in the second half increased levels of progesterone. The fact that all this means - below.</p>

<h2>What happens in the body during menstruation and how it is reflected in the athletic achievements?</h2>

<p>So, during menstruation a woman&rsquo;s body is going through a fairly large-scale changes, which is accompanied by changes in health and response to exercise.</p>

<p><strong><em>Hormonal storm.</em></strong> High blood levels of progesterone is replaced by increase of estrogen levels. Progesterone causes accumulation of fluid in the body, it improves the extensibility of tissue. However, against the background of its high content of muscle relaxation occurs, thereby reducing the physical strength and endurance. For this reason, in the first 1-2 days monthly until little estrogen and progesterone much sprinting and power load perceived by women worse than usual. But stretching exercises, on the contrary, a better work out.</p>

<p>3-4 day weakness caused by hormonal storm reduced. Estrogens are growing, and they are - a kind of hormones, anabolic steroids.</p>

<p><strong><em>Blood loss.</em></strong> Almost all Internet resources assert that during menstruation is a loss of blood, so the woman is reduced hemoglobin levels, which means that tissues receive less oxygen. On this basis, some advise to give up loads or doing gymnastics on the type of &quot;two imbedded - three cotton&quot;.</p>

<p>However, this is not entirely correct. First, the female body is genetically adapted to blood loss. If you&rsquo;ve ever been on blood collection points, then we saw that among donors to faint after giving blood fall mostly men. Second, the blood loss is not as great as it seems. On average, it is 80-100 ml for all time periods. For the body is almost invisible, and hemoglobin almost not reflected.</p>

<p>Another thing, if a woman or heavy menstruation, especially violations of the cycle in which the menstrual period is prolonged. There really need to spare yourself. But in other cases, if the load is well tolerated, it is not a necessity.</p>

<p><strong><em>Bad feeling.</em></strong> Someone feels absolutely adequate at any day of the cycle, but for someone periods become almost a tragedy. Hormonal changes, certain features of the body and the presence of so-called oligomenorrhea (painful menstruation) can provide an unforgettable woman &quot;critical days&quot;.</p>

<p>Some of the girls during the time of menstruation (stronger in the early days) complain of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/neurology/headache.html" title="headache">headaches</a>, nausea, bad mood, severe pain in the abdomen, weakness, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/neurology/dizziness.html" title="dizziness">dizziness</a>. Is all this a contraindication to physical exercise? Of course, yes. If you feel unwell training for the benefit will not go and will only torment.</p>

<p>We hope that the content of the previous section, you realize that there is no single answer, to determine the sports activities during menstruation should be individually.</p>

<p>A woman can not carry the load, or need to schedule them gently if they are accompanied by <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/abdominal-pain.html" title="abdominal pain">abdominal pain</a> and general poor health.</p>

<p>In other cases, you can engage in moderate-intensity workouts, nothing terrible will happen. Professional athletes are never asked to release them from employment and competition if they have the &quot;wrong&quot; days. And nothing&hellip;</p>

<p>Another important point. Many online resources contain information that during menstruation can not practice the exercises on the abs, as it can increase bleeding and abdominal discomfort. If in your case, they are accompanied by &quot;side effects&quot;, they are really better to take time off.</p>

<p>But we would advise you to exercise more to fear on the buttocks and thighs. The fact that the rear of the hip muscles are indirectly connected with the ligaments of the fallopian tubes. Therefore, active walking, running, leads the feet back, deep squat tube tightened and that &quot;disturbs&quot; the uterus and can cause the appearance of spastic abdominal pain and increased bleeding.</p>

<p>Let&rsquo;s hope this post has helped you answer the question: &quot;Can I play sports during menstruation?&quot; Adequately plan the schedule of sports activities, listen to their feelings during and after workouts, choose the &quot;right&quot; exercise, and menstruation does not prevent you keep yourself in the form and lead an active life.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[For What Needed Amino Acids?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-06T10:55:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/for-what-needed-amino-acids/img.jpg" title="For what needed amino acids?" alt="amino acids, how to make amino acids, amino acids for weight loss, essential amino acids, amino acids for muscle growth, what are amino acids">Amino acids - are chemical compounds that comprise proteins. When the human digestive tract gets protein foods, using special enzymes, it is split into amino acids. Only then it can be assimilated. Small-sized molecules penetrate the amino acids from the intestine into the blood, and then the body can use them for their own purposes.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>


<p>Amino acids perform many important functions in the body. They can be divided into plastic and energy. Plastic functions are built from amino acids of the protein molecules that make up all the tissues of our body. Because amino acids are not only bodies, but also biologically active substances: enzymes, certain hormones, neurotransmitters. The energy function is the splitting of the amino acids in order to release energy.</p>

<p>To maintain human life he needed only 20 species of amino acids, although they exist in nature much more. They are divided into three groups:</p>

<ul>
<li>Interchangeable - can be synthesized in the body from chemical compounds having a non-protein origin;</li>
<li>Conditionally replaceable - are synthesized in a limited number;</li>
<li>Essential - are not synthesized in the body.</li>
</ul>


<p>Man receives daily amino acids from food. Most of them are found in meat, fish, eggs, milk and other animal products. The richest vegetable source of protein is soy and other legumes, but they contain less essential amino acids.</p>

<h2>What are amino acids common man?</h2>

<p>Everyone needs amino acids. None of these chemical compounds, we can not synthesize protein. If the amino acids are no longer come from the outside, the body begins to break down its own tissues and organs, to compensate for their deficits. The absence of even one essential amino acid in the human diet leads to severe disease.</p>

<p>The source of these materials were previously only foods. Today amino acids produced by many pharmaceutical companies as supplements or drugs. Some of them are designed for the treatment of certain diseases, others are used by athletes to build muscle. With the purpose of treatment of amino acids into the reception - this is an expensive and inefficient pleasure.</p>

<p>There are many medications on the basis of amino acids, which are used for parenteral nutrition patients. If a person can not eat food alone, he poured the amino acid solutions intravenously. Often because of these drugs the doctors save patient lives, as in the period of severe illness when the body&rsquo;s plastic processes are active, the body needs protein more than usual.</p>

<h2>What are amino acids during training?</h2>

<p>Most athletes who are engaged in bodybuilding, taking protein powders. They use it as an additional source of protein to build muscle mass quickly. Alternatively the protein amino acid solutions are applied. Pharmaceutical companies argue that they are more effective than the protein obtained from food as well as familiar to most athletes protein powders.</p>

<p>True or not? Most companies that produce amino acids for athletes, convince us of the veracity of this information. But their interest is obvious: the amino acids of the protein are much more expensive, so bring more income from sales. For the successful promotion of the product on the market was invented so-called &quot;protein window&quot; or &quot;protein corridor&quot;.</p>

<p>&quot;Protein box&quot; - a period of time after the workout, which is considered optimal for protein <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a>. It is 40-50 minutes. During this period the athlete should learn the most protein to gain muscle growth. If the late bodybuilder, muscles will grow more slowly. But the protein from foods like protein powders, slowly digested, so the athlete has only one chance to catch up to the closing &quot;window of protein&quot;. To do this, take the amino acid solution.</p>

<p>Unlike the protein, amino acids absorbed from the intestine immediately without pretreatment with proteolytic enzymes. Their concentration in the blood rises sharply after 15-20 minutes after taking the supplements. Thus, a person has time to deliver the amino acids in muscle, while &quot;protein window&quot; remains open.</p>

<p>It is quite logical to study the benefits of amino acids in protein loved athletes. Very often in the specialized literature for bodybuilders can find information about the &quot;protein window&quot;. But studies have shown that intake of protein and amino acids provides identical results athletes during training. &quot;Protein window&quot; hardly exists, although the myth about him still wanders from book to book, stimulating the sale of free amino acids.</p>

<p>BCAA - three amino acids, most commonly used in the training. These include isoleucine, valine and leucine. It is these amino acids are part of the majority of sports supplements for bodybuilders. The main effects of BCAA:</p>

<ul>
<li>The accelerated build-up of muscle mass;</li>
<li>Increasing strength athlete;</li>
<li>Reduction of body fat mass.</li>
</ul>


<p>There is no doubt the benefits of BCAA bodybuilder. With them he will reach sports results. They are rapidly absorbed and have high bioavailability, are easy to use. But the lack of supplements based on amino acids BCAA is the price. They are expensive, but a similar result can be obtained by an athlete using whey protein.</p>

<p>Amino BCAA available in different dosage forms. There capsules and solutions, but less likely to take the supplement in powder form. It is recognized that the powder is less convenient to use: it is poorly soluble in the liquid and has a bitter taste. Ready amino acid solutions are tastier, more convenient to use and transport, but are more expensive.</p>

<p>Take BCAA recommended 1 teaspoon (4-5 grams), from 1 to 3 times a day. Amino acids are allowed to be combined with any other sports nutrition. Of course, it makes no sense to take them together with protein, since these additives have the same mechanism of action, although some people do it to save money.</p>

<p>Amino acids - are chemical substances, of which built all the proteins in our body. A person must receive them regularly with food to stay healthy. Athletes who are building up the muscles need additional source of amino acids. Especially important for them leucine, valine, isoleucine, which are abbreviated as BCAA. Supplements containing amino acids, convenient to use and easily digested. However, they are expensive, so as a source of amino acids most athletes use a cheaper but equally effective protein powder.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
