<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: healthy lifestyle | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com//categories/healthy-lifestyle/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-07-23T13:39:09+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to protect from Alzheimer's disease?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-20T12:21:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="/images/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;alzheimer&rsquo;s disease, alzheimer, factors for alzheimer&rsquo;s, cases of alzheimer&rsquo;s, risk of alzheimer&rsquo;s disease&rsquo; &lsquo;How to protect from Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease?&rsquo;" >We&rsquo;ve all heard that stimulate our brain functions, including intellectual could protect us from Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>

<p>Thus, crosswords and all kinds of learning are recommended.</p>

<p>Today, studies suggest that there are other protective factors.
Was even identified risk factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease&hellip; And it appears that we could halve the number of people affected.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Alzheimer&rsquo;s, prevent long as we do not know how to cure</h2>

<p>The research was mobilized for years to develop treatments that will cure Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease. Similarly, researchers are busy around prevention. An analysis of all publications focused on this subject gave particularly interesting results.</p>

<p>In fact, risk factors and protective factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease have been identified.</p>

<p>The good news is that all are modifiable, meaning that acting on each of these factors could reduce by half the number of people affected by Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>

<h2>6 risk factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease</h2>

<ul>
<li>Diabetes;</li>
<li>Excess <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a> in midlife;</li>
<li>Smoking.</li>
</ul>


<p>But another study points 3 other additional risk factors (1)</p>

<ul>
<li>Hypertension;</li>
<li>Obesity;</li>
<li>Depression.</li>
</ul>


<h2>5 of protective factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease</h2>

<ul>
<li>The Mediterranean diet;</li>
<li>The folic acid or vitamin B9;</li>
<li>Low or moderate alcohol consumption;</li>
<li>Cognitive activities;</li>
<li>Physical activity.</li>
</ul>


<p>For example, diabetes increases the risk of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease by 39%. Knowing that 6% of the world population is affected by diabetes, the disease is alone responsible for 2% of cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>

<p>Another example, physical inactivity increases the risk of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease by 82%. If we consider that 18% of the world population is physically inactive, sedentary lifestyle is responsible for 13% of cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>

<p>Smoking increases the risk of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease by 59%. If we consider that 27% of the population smokes, smoking is responsible for 14% of cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>

<p>Finally, knowing that many of these factors are related, act on one of them can simultaneously have a significant impact on others. <strong>For example, by acting only on physical inactivity, can simultaneously reduce the risk of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/cardiology/hypertension.html" title="hypertension">hypertension</a> and diabetes&hellip;</strong></p>

<p><strong>You can see that all these factors are modifiable. In other words, we can all take action and protect us from Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</strong></p>

<p>Thus, nearly half of the cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease could be prevented by modifying these factors.</p>

<p>Recall that in the world, the number of people affected by Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease is estimated at 34 million. In USA, the figure is estimated at nearly 1 million. In the current absence of treatment to cure this disease, prevention is a huge challenge.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anorexia and bulimia]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/anorexia-and-bulimia/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-19T13:15:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/anorexia-and-bulimia</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="/images/anorexia-and-bulimia/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;anorexia, bulimia, eating behavior, eating disorder, eating, restrictions on food, diet&rsquo; &lsquo;Anorexia and bulimia&rsquo;" >Anorexia &ndash; a pathological condition in which there was a complete lack of appetite in the presence of the objective necessity of the body in the diet. Anorexia may occur due to various reasons, such as parasitic infestations and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/" title="infectious diseases">infectious diseases</a>, diseases of the digestive system. Usually considered separately anorexia nervosa.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Anorexia nervosa is an eating disorder in which a person willfully refuses to eat for weight loss purposes. This disease occurs more often in girls. Nevertheless, it can be observed not only in the young, but also in adulthood, both women and men.</p>

<p>Anorexia nervosa is characterized by the occurrence of a pathological desire to lose weight, which is accompanied by the development of intense fear of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>. People suffering from anorexia, there is distortion of the own body, there is a concern about weight gain, even if in reality it is not marked. The causes of anorexia are divided into psychological (internal conflicts, the impact of the family), biological (genetic predisposition) and social (the impact of society &ndash; popular diets imitation idols).</p>

<p>Anorexia is phasing flow &ndash; isolated dismorfomanicheskuyu, anorectic and cachectic stage. The first stage &ndash; dismorfomanicheskaya &ndash; characterized by the emergence of thoughts of inferiority because of imaginary completeness. In this patient develops anxiety, depressed mood, he sees himself in the long mirror. Also at this stage following the first attempt to limit in food.</p>

<p>In the second stage the patient has resorted to a strict diet and grueling physical <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a>. However, he loses much weight, but does not stop fasting, since it can not objectively assess the degree of weight loss. Due to continuous malnutrition occur in the body pathological reactions. There are features such as <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/hair-loss.html" title="hair loss">hair loss</a>, dry skin, decreased sexual desire, syncope, arrhythmia, stomach pain, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/constipation.html" title="constipation">constipation</a>, nausea, and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/depression.html" title="depression">depression</a>. Infertility occurs: women due to amenorrhea (cessation of menstruation), men &ndash; due to the suppression of spermatogenesis.</p>

<p>Body weight of the patient has been steadily declining in the body degenerative changes occur, and there comes a cachectic period. This stage usually develops anorexia after two years of onset. Pathological changes in the body leads to irreversible inhibition of the functions of all organs and systems, and result in death. In connection with this incessant flow and severe consequences, anorexia is a serious disease that requires mandatory treatment.</p>

<h2>Bulimia</h2>

<p>Another uncommon <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/eating-disorders.html" title="eating disorders">eating disorders</a> is <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/bulimia.html" title="bulimia">bulimia</a>. Bulimia occurs due to mental disorders, diseases of the endocrine and central nervous systems. This pathology often leads to obesity.</p>

<p>Bulimia nervosa is characterized by sudden significant increase in appetite, feeling really hungry. Typically, bulimia occurs in the form of attacks or last time. Seizures are characterized by the absorption of huge amounts of food. They can occur suddenly or develop at a certain time (eg at night).</p>

<p>People with bulimia often resorted to the use of laxatives and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/vomiting.html" title="vomiting">vomiting</a> to control weight. However, the use of large amounts of food and the subsequent forced cleaning of the stomach cause severe complications.</p>

<p>Bulimia can develop independently or arise against the background of anorexia nervosa. As people with anorexia and bulimia patients control their weight become the overriding purpose in life. Bulimia, emerged against the background of anorexia nervosa is characterized by periodic episodes of binge eating occurrence that alternate periods of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/starvation.html" title="starvation">starvation</a>. During these episodes the patient will eat huge amounts of food in a short time, while he usually swallows food without chewing. Typically, after a bout of bulimia patient vomits or takes large amounts of diuretics or laxatives, not thinking about the consequences for your health.</p>

<p>Bulimia and anorexia are life-threatening conditions, so people suffering from these diseases, needs appropriate treatment. Unfortunately, patients are often hospitalized for anorexia able drastic depletion, whereas in the early treatment of the disease can be performed on an outpatient basis. It must be remembered that the earlier therapeutic interventions will be carried out, the less the risk of irreversible changes.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crohn's disease: what are symptoms?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/crohns-disease-what-are-symptoms/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-18T10:47:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/crohns-disease-what-are-symptoms</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="/images/crohns-disease-what-are-symptoms/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;crohn&rsquo;s disease, crohn&rsquo;s disease causes, and colon, from anus&rsquo; &lsquo;Crohn&rsquo;s disease: what are symptoms?&rsquo;" ><strong>In USA, there are 120,000 people with Crohn&rsquo;s disease, both men and women.</strong></p>

<blockquote><p>Each year 4-5 new cases per 100,000 are diagnosed.
<strong>Crohn&rsquo;s disease causes chronic inflammation of digestive system. Any segment of the gastrointestinal tract may be affected, from anus esophagus. But more often, it is bowel that is achieved by inflammation: colon, small intestine terminal portion.</strong></p></blockquote>

<!--more-->


<p>Illness progresses in spurts interspersed with remission periods.</p>

<p>Signs are mainly gastrointestinal, but not only, depend on the segments achieved location.</p>

<h2>In Crohn&rsquo;s disease, the symptoms are mostly gastrointestinal</h2>

<p><strong>Crohn&rsquo;s disease causes:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Anal pain (fistulas, abscesses).</li>
<li>An issue of blood or mucus from anus.</li>
<li>Abdominal pain (sometimes very strong up to think appendicitis).</li>
<li>There may be heavy, watery diarrhea.</li>
<li>Nausea, vomiting.</li>
</ul>


<blockquote><p>These digestive symptoms lead to poor general condition: fatigue, loss of appetite, weight loss with faltering growth in children and adolescents, fever, paleness, breathlessness due to a anemia risk and vitamin B12 deficiency.</p></blockquote>

<h2>Other non-digestive signs&hellip;</h2>

<p><strong>Crohn&rsquo;s disease can also cause other symptoms as digestive, including joint, skin and eye.</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Articular rheumatism: ankylosing spondylitis&hellip;</li>
<li>Dermatological disorders: ulcers, erythema nodosum&hellip;</li>
<li>Ocular: uveitis&hellip;</li>
</ul>


<p>It is estimated that these extraintestinal manifestations affect one third of patients during their illness. Knowing they can appear before the gastrointestinal signs, they should be considered as warning signs to get see.</p>

<h2>Crohn&rsquo;s disease Diagnosis and treatment</h2>

<p><strong>Diagnosis is based on examination and in particular on signs, supplemented by:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>A biological balance sheet;</li>
<li>A colonoscopy (rectum and colon examination, terminal portion of small intestine, assessing damage extent);</li>
<li>Upper gastrointestinal endoscopy (to determine the high illness location);</li>
<li>Video capsule ingestion.</li>
</ul>


<p>Other tests may be required or placed under surveillance:</p>

<ul>
<li>MRIs;</li>
<li>Abdominal CT;</li>
<li>Abdominal ultrasound,</li>
<li>Radio.</li>
</ul>


<p>As for treatment, they are based on anti-inflammatory drugs target (5-ASA, corticosteroids, immunomodulators, antibiotics, iron). If unsuccessful, surgery may be necessary. A balanced diet is necessary to risk malnutrition reduce. During severe outbreaks, a restricted diet in fruits and vegetables can not increase gastrointestinal symptoms. Only tobacco should be avoided.</p>

<blockquote><p>Care is multidisciplinary, involving the intervention of various specialists: physician, gastroenterologist, rheumatologist, dietician, doctor or school work, social worker, psychiatrist or psychologist, etc..
It aims to ease outbreaks, prevent relapses, complications and improve life quality.</p></blockquote>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Too much cholesterol: what symptoms?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/too-much-cholesterol-what-symptoms/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-17T10:19:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/too-much-cholesterol-what-symptoms</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="/images/too-much-cholesterol-what-symptoms/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;cholesterol, symptoms, excess cholesterol, calibrate their cholesterol&rsquo; &lsquo;Too much cholesterol : what symptoms? What are the signs?&rsquo;" >Some people wonder if cholesterol is accompanied by symptoms indicative.</p>

<p>If so, then these signs could indicate that it is time to calibrate their cholesterol.</p>

<p>This is unfortunately not the case&hellip;</p>

<!--more-->


<blockquote><p><strong>There are no specific symptoms manifested when an cholesterol excess in the blood.</strong>
We can not rely on any evidence to decide whether to calibrate their cholesterol checked and if all goes well on this side.</p></blockquote>

<p><strong>Excess cholesterol is a silent phenomenon as hypertension.</strong></p>

<h2>Symptoms of cholesterol are those complications</h2>

<p>It was only after years of evolution of symptoms may be too late, because the signs are then those complications of high cholesterol.</p>

<p>Recall that the long, excess cholesterol tends to be deposited in the arteries (plaque), narrowing their diameter and impeding proper blood circulation potentially causing arteritis members lower. This plaque can harden and cause angina. A blood clot can also form and detach, then going to butcher a coronary artery is myocardial or cerebral artery and is the stroke or renal artery is insufficient kidney.</p>

<p><strong>The symptoms of these accidents are well known</strong> (or should be because of the vital urgency):</p>

<p>What are the signs of angina?
Stroke or Heart Attack? Warning symptoms differ!</p>

<p>Overall, all symptoms suggestive of cardiovascular disease involving excess cholesterol are:</p>

<ul>
<li>Calves pain;</li>
<li>Chest pain with tightness;</li>
<li>Nausea, dizziness;</li>
<li>Fever, headache;</li>
<li>Shortness of breath, palpitations;</li>
<li>Feeling cold extremities;</li>
<li>Loss of strength in the face, arms, legs, especially on one side;</li>
<li>Slurred speech;</li>
<li>Blurred vision;</li>
<li>Etc..</li>
</ul>


<h2>So when do calibrate their cholesterol?</h2>

<blockquote><p><strong>The cholesterol assay based on a simple fasting blood test</strong> (after 12 hours without food and drink intake).
We can measure total cholesterol, HDL-cholesterol (&ldquo;bad&rdquo;) and triglycerides, while LDL-cholesterol is calculated from previous values.</p></blockquote>

<p>It is recommended to calibrate their cholesterol once before the age of 30 to screen for familial hypercholesterolemia. Then the pace is every 5 years to 50 years and then every 3 years beyond because the arteries naturally harden with age. In case of diabetes, cholesterol is dose every year at least.</p>

<blockquote><p><strong>Thin also may have too much cholesterol!</strong>
If overweight and obesity increase the risk of having too much bad cholesterol due to an unbalanced diet, thin people can also suffer from high cholesterol and then it is usually a family phenomenon&hellip;</p></blockquote>

<p>In addition to age and diabetes, there are other risk factors that can lead to monitor your cholesterol more closely: family history of premature coronary heart disease, smoking, hypertension, overweight (or obese), waist excessive, etc&hellip;</p>

<p><strong>It is noteworthy that what characterizes excess cholesterol is precisely symptoms absence. This is why regular monitoring is required!</strong></p>

<p><strong>For more information</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Why do an assessment of blood lipids?</li>
<li>What is lipid?</li>
<li>Determination of total cholesterol: manual.</li>
<li>Why and how to HDL and LDL cholesterol balance?</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salt. A real danger to our health]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/salt-a-real-danger-to-our-health/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-13T23:38:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/salt-a-real-danger-to-our-health</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="/images/salt-a-real-danger-to-our-health/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;salt, food, health&rsquo; &lsquo;Salt, a real danger to our health&rsquo;" ><strong>Our diet is too rich in salt.</strong></p>

<p>Now the world specialists of hypertension and cardiovascular disease are unanimous: <strong>excess salt is detrimental to the overall population, regardless of age.</strong></p>

<p>Thus the reduction of salt is one of the leading objectives of national health nutrition.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>The dangers of salt</h2>

<p>A strong link has been established between excessive salt intake and health.</p>

<ul>
<li><p><strong>A diet high in salt is one of the risk factors for hypertension and cardiovascular disease.</strong>
In fact, there is a direct link between excess salt in the diet and high blood pressure because the genes that control blood pressure are also those that regulate salt reabsorption in the kidneys. But cardiovascular disease is the leading cause of death in our country.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Excess salt is also known to promote the gastric cancer.</strong></p></li>
<li><p><strong>Finally, too much salt increases the risk of osteoporosis.</strong>
Knowing that high salt levels in the blood increases calcium excretion in urine, after several years, this may result in a decrease in bone mineral density and increased osteoporosis.</p></li>
</ul>


<h2>The French consume too much salt</h2>

<p>According to the latest expertise of the National Agency for Food Safety (handles), the average salt consumption of French through food is 8.7 g/day in men and 6.7 g/day in women. At these intakes from food consumed, &ldquo;we must add 1 to 2 grams of salt per day, due to salting food and cooking water by the consumer himself&rdquo;.</p>

<p><strong>This is too much and too far from the recommendations of the WHO recommends not exceed 5 g of salt per day.</strong></p>

<p>So much so that health authorities have been forced to set interim target of 8 g per day maturity of 5 years, a reduction of 20% (6.5 g/day for women and children)!</p>

<h2>An imperative: reduce sodium intake in the diet</h2>

<p>Consumers generally know the risks associated with excess salt, but what they often do not know is that over 70% of the salt consumed comes from a group of 6 food:</p>

<ul>
<li>Bread and crackers.</li>
<li>The deli.</li>
<li>Soups.</li>
<li>Cheese.</li>
<li>The dishes.</li>
<li>Pizzas, quiches and savory pastries.</li>
</ul>


<p>To which must be added (because of their high consumption in children):</p>

<ul>
<li>The pastries.</li>
<li>The cereal breakfast.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Solutions they get there?</h2>

<ul>
<li><p>Decrease the salt levels in foods and thus encourage industry to engage in a charter or regulatory changes.
Remember that salt is interesting as a preservative, flavor enhancer and has a assoiffant power (likely to drive up consumption of drinks&hellip;).</p></li>
<li><p>More information for consumers through the labeling of the salt content of industrial products.</p></li>
<li><p>Encourage French to limit their consumption of the most savory and salt additions in the preparation and during the meal.</p></li>
</ul>


<p><strong>On the right track</strong>
These three fields of action have already been more or less established, with the first results in a decrease between 1999 and 2007 of 5.2% of average salt intake in the general population and 20-30% in very heavy users (more than 12 g/day).</p>

<h2>Delete eating habits at risk</h2>

<p><strong>We can all individually control a good part of our sodium intake by eliminating our eating habits at risk:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li><p>No salt available on the table.</p></li>
<li><p>Ban systematic dusting: always taste before adding salt or salt.</p></li>
<li><p>Replace salt with other types of seasonings such as spices, herbs and cooking with garlic, onions, shallots.</p></li>
<li><p>Reduce the amount of salt added to the cooking water.</p></li>
<li><p>Replace crackers, peanuts and chips with vegetables and fruits: cherry tomatoes, radish, melon balls, celery or carrots soaked in yoghurt sauce, etc..</p></li>
<li><p>Avoid too rich mineral waters by comparing the sodium salt contents on the labels.</p></li>
<li><p>Limiting industrial products, often very rich in salt.</p></li>
<li><p>Limit the richest salt foods: meats (salami, prosciutto), broth (vegetable or meat), sauces and condiments, cheeses, pizzas and quiches, pastries, crackers, etc..</p></li>
<li><p>Do not accustom young children to eat too salty because eating habits are set in early childhood and it is difficult to change in adulthood.</p></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
