<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: healthy lifestyle | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/healthy-lifestyle/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-11-19T20:02:59+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Therapeutic exercise for patients with diabetes]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/therapeutic-exercise-for-patients-with-diabetes/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:49:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/therapeutic-exercise-for-patients-with-diabetes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/exercise-therapy-for-patients-with-diabetes/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/exercise-therapy-for-patients-with-diabetes/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Exercise therapy for patients with diabetes&rsquo; &lsquo;Therapeutic exercise for patients with diabetes&rsquo;" > Exercise therapy for patients with diabetes helps to offset the disease. Exercise therapy (physical therapy) for patients with diabetes, along with other essential elements of treatment (insulin therapy, medication drugs, diet and self-control), plays a critical role in the compensation of the disease and has a beneficial effect on the patient, helping to maintain good health and performance.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>The role of physical therapy for patients with diabetes</h2>

<p>The violation of protein and fat metabolism in the body accumulates toxins and it is poisoning products of incomplete combustion of fats. In addition, disturbance of lipid metabolism leads to the fact that blood fat filled, it increases bad cholesterol, thereby repeatedly increased risk of atherosclerosis and other cardiovascular diseases.</p>

<p>Exercise therapy is shown not only in all types of diabetes (except for depleted due to untreated or poorly the treatment of diabetes patients), but also when prediabetnom condition. Modern research shows that, if we strictly adhere to the prescribed diet, exercise and give up bad habits &ndash; overeating, smoking and alcohol, then go into pre-diabetes mellitus can be avoided.</p>

<p>According to currently available data, the most common occurrence and development of diabetes contributes to overeating. That is why a person full-bodied and with disturbances in metabolism, need to understand that once in a painful exchange process will involve carbohydrate metabolism, inevitably develop diabetes.</p>

<p>In connection with this, people with excess body weight, being at risk of diabetes, must periodically tested for the presence of sugar in the blood and urine, to detect the first time the symptoms of the disease and to begin treatment. In addition to weight loss, you should pay attention to the following common symptoms of incipient diabetes &ndash; long nezazhivlenie wounds, abrasions resistant to treatment, itching, bleeding gums, loosening of teeth, impotence.</p>

<h2>Features of physical therapy for patients with diabetes</h2>

<p>The main objectives of physical therapy for patients with diabetes:</p>

<p>Improving cardiovascular and respiratory systems;
Improving patients' health;
Reducing hyperglycaemia in non-insulin (type 2 diabetes) and the potentiation of insulin in patients with insulin-dependent (type 1 diabetes);
Opposition to the development of micro-and macrovascular.</p>

<p>In diabetes, insulin deficiency addition, broken oxidative processes in the muscle due to which they can not utilize glucose. At the same physical stress oxidative enzyme activity is significantly enhanced in the blood are increased alkaline reserves, thereby increasing the uptake and consumption of glucose by muscles, decreases hyperglycemia and increased tolerance of the organism in carbohydrates. In addition, exercise in combination with insulin increase the therapeutic effect of insulin, strengthen the nervous and cardiovascular system of the patient, increase the body&rsquo;s resistance and prevent the development of atherosclerosis.</p>

<p>The distinctive feature of LFC in diabetes is that the recommended exercises should be performed in a moderate (Slower) rate, as well as muscular effort. In the anaerobic organism not occur and oxidation processes that contribute to the increase of glucose by muscles.</p>

<p>Classes begin physiotherapy is recommended to elementary exercises for the muscles of the legs, arms and torso with no encumbrances, combining with breathing exercises.  In addition to physical therapy, are useful dosed walking, rowing, cycling, swimming pool, skiing, gardening, light physical work.</p>

<p>When doing physical therapy you need to carefully monitor their well-being &ndash; if after playing the feeling of weakness or fatigue, the load must be reduced. If training were to shake hands, there was a strong feeling of hunger and weakness, you need to eat 1 to 2 pieces of sugar and immediately stop training. Resuming workout just a day after the disappearance of the symptoms of hypoglycemia, while reducing the dosage. Patients with diabetes who are on insulin therapy, in the days of long and intense physical activities recommended to reduce the dose of insulin (after consultation with the attending physician).</p>

<p>LFC need to conduct studies in a well-ventilated room or outdoors, breathing in this case should be free and rhythmic, through your nose and exhale longer inspiratory time. Physical exercise is necessary to alternate the different muscle groups and perform with a large amplitude in the joints.</p>

<p>Repeat each exercise should be 5-6 times in the future, to the extent of fitness, you can enhance the load by reducing breaks, increasing the rate and number of repetitions. Age is not a barrier to practice physical therapy, monitoring the patient&rsquo;s state of health is the only changes and hyperglycemia and weight.</p>

<p>Since the blood sugar level rises patient after a night&rsquo;s sleep, (which partly explains quiet sleep) are most useful gymnastics, and light walking exercise in the morning, as they not only lower blood glucose, but also promote the release of insulin in a more  But, if possible, try to exercise and in the evening (for 1.5 &ndash; 2 hours before bedtime) to secure an equivalent exercise for the day.</p>

<h2>Complex physiotherapy for patients with diabetes</h2>

<p>Starting position &ndash; the main counter. Set aside the leg back, put your hands up &ndash; inhale, return to the initial position &ndash; Exhale. Repeat 4-5 times.</p>

<p>Within 2-4 minutes walk alternately with high lifting hips, with the movements of the arms up and to the side, with the attacks. Breathe freely.</p>

<p>Stand up straight, hands behind head, elbows pinch the face. On the 1-2 dissolve in hand, inhale. On the 3-4 return to the starting position, tilt your head forward, exhale.</p>

<p>Feet shoulder width apart. Spread your arms out to the side, turn the body all the way to the left, the right hand should be in front of the chest. Then turn to the full right (left arm in front of chest, right assigned to the side). Lean forward to the left leg, pulling the sock right hand. Repeat on the other hand.</p>

<p>Starting position &ndash; arms out, legs apart. Make 3 springy lean to the left (right leg bent, left arm behind his back, right arm is raised up).</p>

<p>Mahi legs, pulling his hands in front summarized hands.</p>

<p>Starting position &ndash; the main counter. Lean forward, trying to get his hands floor without bending your legs. Then fall to focus on her knees, feet alternately move back please stop lying. Without bending your arms and legs and moving them from place, lift the hips higher by tilting forward, lower your head between hands. Lower the pelvis, taking the emphasis lying. Then alternate movement of the feet take forward the emphasis on his knees, lift your pelvis up, straighten your legs and arms.</p>

<p>Emphasis sitting, fingers pull back. Cave in to stop lying behind. Without moving your heels and hands with room, sit down to the heels of the bent leg, then without removing your hands from the floor, straighten your legs and put them apart. Connect and bend your legs and then straighten (without moving from the place of the heel), and return to starting position. Repeat 6-8 times.</p>

<p>Lie on your back, bend your arms at chest (forearms parallel to the one above the other). Lift them up, without straightening and does not disconnect (inhalation) and lower into place (exhale).</p>

<p>Lie on your stomach, hands under shoulders. Arms out to the sides (palms down on the floor), bend your back, and then straighten them and cave in, off the floor straight legs and hands, his head laid back. Hold this position for a few seconds, re-dissolve and bring feet back to its original position.</p>

<p>Lie on your back, raise your legs vertically. At the 1 &ndash; 2 dilute and bring your feet on the 3-4 bend and straighten. Repeat 4-6 times, not holding my breath.</p>

<p>Starting position &ndash; the main counter. Lift your arms to the shoulders (inspiration), and then relaxed &ldquo;drop&rdquo; them, head down, shoulders rounded off with.</p>

<p>Perform a peaceful walk for 2 minutes.</p>

<p>At the end of lessons useful to take a cool shower, bath or sponging, as well as water treatment activate the oxidative processes in the body. Start to cool off with a towel soaked in water at room temperature (not below), gradually lowering the temperature of water by one degree in a few days. Motion for a rubdown should be directed from the periphery to the heart.</p>

<p>Despite the fact that diabetes is a life-long illness, with good self-control and respect for all the doctor&rsquo;s appointments, diabetics can keep working and socially useful life on a par with healthy and live to a ripe old age.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Therapeutic exercises in spinal osteochondrosis]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/therapeutic-exercises-in-spinal-osteochondrosis/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:48:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/therapeutic-exercises-in-spinal-osteochondrosis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/physical-therapy-in-spinal-osteochondrosis/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/physical-therapy-in-spinal-osteochondrosis/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Physical therapy in spinal osteochondrosis&rsquo; &lsquo;Therapeutic exercises in spinal osteochondrosis&rsquo;" > Physical therapy reduces stress on the joints and helps the deposition of salts. Many people who have the first symptoms of joint disease &ndash; the crunch and clicks, believe that they have a &ldquo;simple&rdquo; salt deposits &ndash; a trifle, which is observed in almost all and therefore do not require treatment. However, the deposition of salt, as it is popularly called low back pain, the disease is not as harmless as it may seem at first glance.</p>

<p>The fact that the starting salt deposited only at inappropriate salt metabolism in the body. A healthy body can absorb salts only as much as is necessary for normal functioning, and the excess output.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>If you violate a salt exchange surpluses are deposited in various parts of the body, causing certain diseases, often low back pain, gout, kidney stones and gall stones.</p>

<p>For osteochondrosis deferrable salt are often formed in sharp spikes that compress the nerves and cause severe pain with movement, causing a person is suffering, can not turn his head, torso, and the robot has to move, protecting yourself from the pain. In addition, osteochondrosis of the cervical spine may be accompanied by severe headaches, and in the period of acute lumbar degenerative disc disease and sciatica people and is completely bedridden.</p>

<p>Due to the fact that the joints begin to undergo similar changes already 20 years old, everyone should regularly engage in the prevention of salt deposits, which includes the cleaning of joints, proper diet (read the article diet for gout, osteochondrosis and salt deposits in the joints), and clear the joints folk remedies, such as using rice or bay leaf, carried out in order to prevent a year and gives a good effect. Therapeutic diet should be organized to remove excess weight, which is an additional burden on joints and provide the body with all the necessary vitamins and trace elements, especially calcium for strong bones and cartilage.</p>

<h2>Physical therapy in spinal osteochondrosis</h2>

<p>Gymnastics spinal osteochondrosis plays a major role, as well strengthens and tones the muscles of the back. With weak muscles of the body burden is &ldquo;hanging&rdquo; on one spine, flattening and deforming discs. If the muscles of the back and loins are well fortified, as they would create an additional corset and take on the weight of the body.</p>

<p>In addition, therapeutic exercises in spinal osteochondrosis helps get rid of extra salt, because if you exercise the bone and muscle tissue using them to compensate for the physiological loss. Finally, regular active movements, with which physiotherapy is the deposition of salts, gradually, as it were &ldquo;polished&rdquo; salt spikes, making them less sharp and painful.</p>

<p>Physical therapy will be effective only if it is done regularly, every day for 10-15 minutes. The following is a universal set of exercises that will suit everyone. We need to start small, gradually complicating every move &ndash; increasing the number of repetitions, strength and amplitude of slopes and turns. To enhance the effect of the exercises you can use a stick, holding her elbows behind his back. The first four are preparatory exercises complex and prepare the cardiovascular system to the load, and four of the latter, on the contrary, contribute to bringing the body to a calm state after a workout.</p>

<h2>Versatile set of exercises with osteochondrosis</h2>

<h3>Preparatory exercises</h3>

<p>Raise your hands, stretch up (breath), and then lower down, returning to the starting position (exhale).</p>

<p>Grasp the support and rise from heel to toe.</p>

<p>Stand with your feet shoulder width apart, hands on his belt. Move the arms back, reducing the maximum blade (inhalation). Bring elbows to the first starting position and then forward as far as you can (exhale).</p>

<p>Tread on the spot, raising his knees.</p>

<p>Stand erect with your feet shoulder width apart. The maximum stretch up, raising his hands (breath), then lean forward (exhale).</p>

<h3>Arms down at your sides</h3>

<p>Stand erect. Turn around in different directions, arms relaxed at the same time and how would overwhelm the body.</p>

<p>Circular rotation to the right and left lower part of the body.</p>

<p>The circular rotation of hands alternately in different directions.</p>

<p>Stand erect, hands on waist, feet shoulder width apart. Take your right hand back, looking at her (inspiration), go back (exhalation). Similarly, perform the other hand.</p>

<p>Standing upright or sitting in a chair doing Reclining head turns to the right, left, back and forth, then a circular motion.</p>

<p>Sit on a chair and slowly slide your feet on the floor back and forth alternately.</p>

<p>Stand up straight, stretch up with your hands (inhalation), scroll down (exhale).</p>

<p>By the universal set of exercises with osteochondrosis can be added to the selection of specific additional exercises for the cervical, thoracic or lumbar spine, as well as for large joints most affected by the deposition of salts &ndash; shoulder, hip, and knee.</p>

<h3>Exercises for the cervical spine</h3>

<p>Starting position &ndash; lying on his stomach, head turned to the side. Lift up on the hands, throwing his head back (inspiration), go back (exhale).</p>

<p>Tilt your head back, touching the back. Draw your shoulders vertically.</p>

<p>Tilt your head forward and touching his chest, chin slide up and down, simulating the movement of birds to clean the feathers.</p>

<h3>Exercises to help relieve the chest department</h3>

<p>Sit in a chair, hands behind his head rewound (inhalation), cave as possible back, shoulders touching the chair back (exhale).</p>

<p>Get on all fours, cave in the back, keep your head straight, stay in this position for a few seconds, then return to starting position.</p>

<p>Exercise &ldquo;Boat&rdquo;. Lie on your stomach, arms along the body. Cave in &ldquo;boat&rdquo;, taking his head and legs as high as possible off the floor.</p>

<h3>Exercise for the lumbar spine</h3>

<p>Lie on your back, press down bent knees as close to your chest.</p>

<p>Lying on his stomach, rest on the floor bent arms. Straightening your arms, push-ups on the floor, keeping the legs.</p>

<p>Get on your knees, resting his hands on the floor straight. Maximum Flex the back up, then return to starting position.</p>

<p>Stand with your feet shoulder width apart. Lean down, trying to get the floor with his hands. Then stand up straight, raise your arms above your head cave in and make the most.</p>

<p>Exercise &ldquo;cat&rdquo; perfectly relieves tension from the back. Get on all fours, leaning on his knees and hands. Arms and back should be straight, do not tilt your head, look forward. Tilt your head back down and forecasting arc up like a cat, stay in this position for 10 seconds, then go back and relax.</p>

<p>It is also useful to hang out at every opportunity on the bar for 1-2 minutes.</p>

<h3>Exercises for the shoulder joints</h3>

<p>Sit on a chair, put his hands on his belt and spread to the sides. Slowly lift your shoulders up to the stop and gently lowered down slightly pulling down.</p>

<p>Sit on a chair, a push to the back, hands on his waist, elbows divorced. Follow the movement of the shoulders gently back and forth.</p>

<p>In the same starting position alternately follow the circular movement of the shoulders.</p>

<p>Sit on a chair and slide as far back as the patient&rsquo;s hand, healthy, grabbed her wrist and pull toward your buttocks until the pain. Stay in this position for 10 seconds and strain the patient&rsquo;s hand. Then relax and try to move it a few more inches to the onset of pain. Repeat 3-5 times.</p>

<p>Get a hands behind his back and locked in a castle. Then pull in different directions, as if trying to break the lock. Alternately, drag them to the right and to the left, not disengaging.</p>

<p>Stand erect, flattened behind the castle as his hands slowly allot up and back, trying to take as much as possible, but without sharp pain. In this case, the patient remains passive hand.</p>

<h3>Exercises for the hip joints</h3>

<p>Lie on your side with your right leg at the knee and remove the floor in front of him. Then do the same with the other hand.</p>

<p>Lie on your stomach. Bend your right leg, pull it to the side and push the knee to the floor, as if crawling &ldquo;on their bellies.&rdquo; Then do the same with the left hand.</p>

<p>Lying on his stomach, focusing on the bent arm. Then straighten your arms and sit on your heels.</p>

<p>Sit on the floor cross-legged with his legs crossed. Swing your body back and forth.</p>

<h3>Exercises for the knee</h3>

<p>Movement &ldquo;Bicycle&rdquo;. Lying on his back, legs mimic the movement while riding a bike, do not touch the floor.</p>

<p>Lie on your stomach. Without lifting your hips off the floor, bend your legs alternately, trying to touch their buttocks. If there are no sharp pains, you can perform up to 50 times.</p>

<p>Lying on your stomach, bend your leg at the knee at 90 degrees with respect to the body and hold a few seconds. Follow by turns both feet until you get tired (you can up to 50 times).</p>

<p>Sitting on the floor and holding exactly back, dangling his feet at a moderate speed. This exercise is useful to carry out during the day for a lot of times.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Total bilirubin in the blood]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/total-bilirubin-in-the-blood/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:43:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/total-bilirubin-in-the-blood</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-lower-bilirubin/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-lower-bilirubin/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Direct bilirubin, indirect bilirubin, elevated bilirubin, how to lower bilirubin&rsquo; &lsquo;Total bilirubin in the blood, direct, indirect&rsquo;" > Increased bilirubin &ndash; a source of dangerous intoxication of the brain. Bilirubin &ndash; the pigment saturated yellow-brown color, is produced in many organs and tissues and is the end product of the breakdown of hemoglobin and other proteins heme-containing in the cells of the liver, bone marrow and spleen.</p>

<p>The physiological role of bilirubin is not completely understood, but according to recent research, it is necessary not only for the disposal of hemoglobin, as previously thought, but is also a powerful natural antioxidant that gives great promise for the discovery of new treatments for cancer, cardiology and many other diseases.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Bilirubin direct, indirect and total</h2>

<p>In the human body bilirubin is present in two forms &ndash; direct (related) and indirect (Free). Total bilirubin in its pure form does not exist, and is defined as the sum of direct and indirect, and, normally, direct bilirubin should be 75% of the total. Every day, the body is made of about 250 &ndash; 350 mg of bilirubin, wherein, about 80% erythrocytes formed during decomposition (1 gram of hemoglobin &ndash; about 36 grams bilirubin).</p>

<p>It is known that human blood is a rapidly renewing connective tissue composed of plasma cells and uniform elements: erythrocytes (provide tissues with oxygen), white blood cells (responsible for the immune system and fight infections) and platelets (responsible for blood clotting).</p>

<p>The erythrocytes, or red blood cells &ndash; the most numerous of the blood cells. They live in an average of about 120 days, after which decompose, releasing the hemoglobin contained in them. Hemoglobin, after complex chemical reactions, originally converted into a free or indirect bilirubin is insoluble in water and is extremely poisonous. It is concentrated in the liver by gripping it from the blood of liver cells.</p>

<p>Unconjugated bilirubin in the liver as a &ldquo;neutralized&rdquo; &ndash; under the influence of special enzymes, it connects to the glucuronide and get involved. Due to the effect of glucuronic acid, direct bilirubin, in contrast to indirect becomes soluble and less toxic &ndash; easily soluble in bile, it falls along with it in the intestine and then removed from the body naturally with faeces, giving it a brown color.</p>

<h2>Increased bilirubin in the blood causes and symptoms</h2>

<p>In the normal metabolism of bilirubin in the blood gets very little direct bilirubin. However, under pathological failure, it can significantly increase the concentration in blood (hyperbilirubinemia) and urine (bilirubinuria) penetrating into the surrounding tissue and causing yellowing of the skin, sclera eyes and mucous membranes. In addition, frequent signs of the disease &ndash; nausea, weakness, vomiting, bitter belching, heaviness in the right upper quadrant, bleached almost white feces, urine, beer color and itchy skin.</p>

<p>Primary cause of bilirubin metabolism:</p>

<p>Diseases of the blood in which there is a sharp increase in the number of non-viable red blood cells (anemia), the immune aggression toward normal red blood cells (hemolytic disease of the newborn rhesus &ndash; conflict with the child&rsquo;s mother), and exposure to toxic chemicals and blood cells.</p>

<p>Liver disease (viral, bacterial, autoimmune, toxic and drug hepatitis, jaundice), striking or destroy liver cells. When severe jaundice yellowing not only the skin and the sclera eyes, but also saliva, sweat, tears, breast milk, and all the internal organs.</p>

<p>Violation of the free passage of bile on biliary pathways &ndash; gallstones, gallbladder dyskinesia, pakreatit, the presence of tumors, scars or enlarged lymph nodes in close proximity to bile ways.</p>

<p>Poisoning by alcohol, chemicals and medicines.
A lack of vitamin B12.
Hereditary lack of liver enzyme &ndash; Gilbert&rsquo;s syndrome.
Physiological neonatal jaundice.</p>

<h2>Normal bilirubin in children and adults</h2>

<p>Determining the level of bilirubin in the blood is an important tool for the diagnosis of many diseases, especially of the liver, biliary tract and the hematopoietic system, and is one of the key indicators of the biochemical analysis of blood. Refferentnye values ​​of normal levels of total, direct and indirect bilirubin levels for adults and children are shown in the table below</p>

<h3>In adults and children older than 1 month</h3>

<p>Birth 51-60 mmol/l, with 2 days to the end of the first week may increase to 256 mmol/l by indirect (preterm and 170 pmol/l).</p>

<p>3 By the end of the week approaches the indicator for vzroslyhNepryamoydo 15.4 mmol/l (75% of the total) in the peak period of not less than 90% of the obschegoPryamoydo 5.1 mmol/l (25% of the total) in the peak period of not more than 10%.</p>

<h2>Physiological neonatal jaundice</h2>

<p>Increased bilirubin in neonates is not a disease and in most cases takes place independently and does not require treatment. This phenomenon is called physiologic jaundice (jaundice) in infants and children is associated with the adaptation of the organism to changing environmental conditions.</p>

<p>Fact that blood first days of life of children comprises a so-called fetal hemoglobin (formed in utero) which differs in composition from adult human hemoglobin and is active replacement for the first month of life.</p>

<p>Due to the fact that the replacement of a significant amount of released hemoglobin degradation products of erythrocytes, and the liver and biliary system infant has not yet fully operational, approximately 3 &ndash; 4 days of age his skin and mucous membranes may be colored yellow. Afraid of this state do not have to &ndash; as soon as the enzyme system of the child is fully working, skin color changes to pale &ndash; pink, this is usually a 7 &ndash; 8 day of life.</p>

<p>A slightly longer and expression can occur in rhesus jaundice &ndash; conflict (Rh negative mother and an infant positive) or in the presence of mothers in the first group of blood, and the child&rsquo;s second (sometimes third). At the same time children become overly drowsy and need to wake up for feedings.</p>

<p>To reduce the toxicity effects of high levels of bilirubin and accelerate its excretion in feces and urine, modern medicine is widely used method of light therapy (phototherapy). Infant is placed under a special lamp, close your eyes and cover the bandage, if possible, on both sides. Typically, after the 4 &ndash; day fotolecheniya, jaundice symptoms completely disappear.</p>

<p>The positive effect of the treatment has zheltushki breastfeeding and earlier attachment baby to the breast &ndash; it promotes more rapid discharge of meconium and reduces the likelihood of complications. In more severe cases, with severe jaundice may require donor blood transfusion, allowing the nervous system and save a child&rsquo;s life from the toxic effects.</p>

<h2>How to lower bilirubin?</h2>

<p>To reduce the bilirubin in the blood, it is first necessary to establish the root cause of its increase. Otherwise, it will continue to rise since hyperbilirubinemia is not a separate disease but a symptom of a disease.</p>

<p>In particular, if the fault stagnation of bile, sufficient to remove the obstacle, for example, remove the stone in the gall bladder or a course of treatment with drugs that improve bile secretion. In viral hepatitis need antiviral treatment, hemolytic anemia &ndash; a means to warn increased breakdown of red blood cells. If the reason is due to intoxication of the body, will help welcome the adsorbents bind toxic substances and getaprotektorov, which serve to protect the liver.</p>

<p>In addition, to reduce the rate of the enzyme in blood, it is necessary to unload the liver and gallbladder, changing his diet toward healthy diet. From the menu to exclude acute, smoked and fried foods, carbonated drinks, alcohol, strong tea, sweets. Choose more fresh, boiled and baked foods, especially vegetables &ndash; this will help to eliminate the causes of constipation, restore useful microflora and provide quick removal of toxins from the intestines.</p>

<p>In order not to disturb the functioning of the digestive tract, eat often, but little by little, do not overeat and avoid long breaks between meals. In addition, during the acute banned starvation diets for weight loss, showing compliance with therapeutic diet for gallstones.</p>

<p>For the correct diagnosis needs to know how to properly prepare for the tests. Blood is drawn from a vein in the morning on an empty stomach is not recommended to eat and drink coffee (caffeine reduces bilirubin levels) for 8 hours before the procedure, otherwise the results may be unreliable.</p>

<p>In previous blood donation day give up fatty foods (not to overload the liver) and from excessive exercise, provoking pain in the right upper quadrant. To obtain accurate figures, sometimes requires the prior cancellation (within 2 weeks), certain drugs, in particular vitamin C and anti-epileptic drugs.</p>

<p>If the research is carried out correctly and showed enzyme levels significantly below normal, it also should be alerted. Causes of low bilirubin insufficiently studied, because, more often than not, people are suffering from high enzyme content, not low. However, according to some medical studies, a direct link between between its reduced level of disease and coronary heart disease, that is, the risk of heart attack and stroke is much lower at high bilirubin than at low.</p>

<p>Finally, we note that high levels of bilirubin requires careful and rigorous, as it is highly toxic to the central nervous system and causes a variety of ailments &ndash; persistent headaches, fatigue, slowing of heart rate (bradycardia). Therefore, the best way to avoid poisoning the brain and body &ndash; at the first symptoms to seek medical attention.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
