<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Healthy-lifestyle | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/healthy-lifestyle/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-01-06T11:56:07+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Reduce the Acidity of the Stomach?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-04T17:20:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach.jpg" title="How to reduce the acidity of the stomach?" alt="How to reduce the acidity of the stomach">Even healthy people a few times a year are faced with situations where they suddenly starts to bother nausea, heaviness in the abdomen or stomach pain. The reasons for this may be many - from the use of poor-quality food to the side effects from taking aspirin. In some cases, listed complaints arising from the increased acidity of gastric juice, which can contribute to the development of some diseases in the first place, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/gastritis.html" title="gastritis">gastritis</a> and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/diagnosis-of-peptic-ulcer-disease.html" title="peptic ulcer">peptic ulcer</a> disease. So if you think you have such a breach, you should pay more attention to their own health.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Currently, in various diseases of the stomach is quite rarely do the analysis on acidity, because it has been proven that the prospects of treatment depend on this factor only to a small extent (a much more significant role played by the nature of the disease, its severity, and others.). And if the person has no serious pathologies and considers himself generally healthy, such a diagnostic procedure the more meaningless - and, moreover, very unpleasant. However, it should be remembered that increased acidity in the body can create an environment in which to easily develop disease processes; In addition, it brings a man some discomfort. So what to do to prove its existence?</p>

<p>Just listen to yourself, and your <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/" title="symptoms">symptoms</a> you may use a fairly high probability to determine if there is a violation of you or not. If you are concerned about the &quot;acidic&quot; belching, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/heartburn.html" title="heartburn">heartburn</a>, pain in the upper abdomen (especially after eating foods that enhance the secretion of gastric juice), then it is possible that you have increased the acidity. Your guess is finally confirmed when you experiment with food and other methods to reduce it, and they will give results. So what to do to help themselves?</p>

<p>It can be said, the cornerstone of your efforts - without the normal power supply to solve the problem fail. The first thing is to give up all the foods and beverages that contribute to enhanced secretion of digestive juices. When acidity organism too responsive to food stimuli, whereby the stomach is filled with &quot;excess&quot; of hydrochloric acid, which irritates its wall.</p>

<p>Now, remember, <strong>you should not eat (especially on an empty stomach and/or in large quantities), the following products:</strong> coffee, chocolate, soft drinks, sour berries and fruit (currants, some varieties of apples), citrus, undiluted fruit juice, spices, canned food, meats, hearty soups and broths, pickles, fried foods. It contains so-called extractive substances, which greatly increase secretion. Also, do not get involved in a very cold food and drinks.</p>

<p>Instead of all this is to increase the content in the diet of boiled, baked and stewed vegetables and meat, milk and dairy products, sweet fruit. Lower acidity and protect the stomach wall against possible damage to help jelly, mucous soups and soups, porridge. If you suffer from symptoms of hyperacidity, do not recommend to stick to strict diets to lose weight: eat small portions you need, but fractionally, from 4 to 6 times a day. Fasting is also strictly contraindicated.</p>

<p>Do not forget that food should moderate amounts include fats, animal and especially plant to help recover the mucosa and create on it a thin protective film. Although, of course, it is important not to overdo it: a piece of fatty mutton will your stomach into complete confusion and provoke hypersecretion of hydrochloric acid, which will cause you to regret his shortsightedness.</p>

<p><strong>Bad habits and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a>: how they affect the acidity?</strong></p>

<p>Bad! And you probably heard about it is great. It is no secret that the lady&rsquo;s finger greater among those who are often nervous - hence, the stress increases the acidity of gastric juice. In addition, the experience contribute to disruption of the activity of certain hormones local action and reduce the blood supply to the mucosa. Also, a state of nervous tension inhibits the work of the cells that produce the protective mucus and bicarbonate, which in the normal digestive enzymes do not dissolve the stomach itself.</p>

<p>Smoking and alcohol also significantly impaired digestion, so it is better to give them. It is believed that a cigarette after a meal is not so much effect on gastric secretion as smoked on an empty stomach, but with frequent smoking effect of nicotine becomes a constant that does not relieve us from the consequences.</p>

<p><strong>Folk remedies for reducing the acidity</strong></p>

<p>There are many variations of recipes that supposedly help solve problems associated with acidity. But the really significant action you can expect only on the rice or oat broth that protect the stomach from acid, and even recommended by doctors as a therapeutic agent for patients with gastritis or ulcer.</p>

<p>To reliably reduce gastric acidity, should be performed at any one, but all these suggestions. Controlling diet and avoiding bad habits and stress, you are literally within 2-3 weeks will achieve a result. If this does not happen, and you will still be something to disturb refer to a gastroenterologist: <strong>persistent symptoms can talk about already developed the disease, which will make you friends not only with the &quot;right&quot; food, but also with medications that reduce the acidity.</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Soybeans: Benefits and Harms, Doctor Review]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-04T15:52:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review.jpg" title="Black soybeans: benefits and harms, doctor review" alt="Black soybeans">Black soybean - a product that is used in traditional Chinese medicine. It is considered a source of balance. Therapeutic effects: replenishes blood levels, nourishing yin, expels wind, strengthens weakened, normalizes the activity of the channels of stomach and spleen. In Russia, black soybeans also find healing, but its effect is usually described using different terminology, more understandable to our man.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Black soybean useful in exactly the same extent that and soy white or yellow. This is a common legume has a high protein content and insoluble dietary fiber. There is hardly any sense to use it as a medicine. Black soybean much more suitable for use in food. Nevertheless, she decided to attribute the following useful properties:</p>

<ul>
<li>Normalizes nervous activity;</li>
<li>Cures cancer (probably not in the world of plants, which it does not cure, according to admirers of traditional medicine);</li>
<li>To protect people from the harmful effects of the environment;</li>
<li>Reduces the level of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a> in the blood;</li>
<li>Promotes weight loss.</li>
</ul>


<p>All these inventions. This can be read on virtually any product of plant origin. Perhaps black soy and healthy if its systematic use in food, but cancer or diabetes, it is certainly not cures.</p>

<p>Black soybean contains no toxic compounds for the organism. The damage is only possible with overeating or the presence of diseases of the digestive system. Disadvantages of the product:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>High calorie</strong> - do not pass at a weight problem;</li>
<li><strong>High fiber content</strong> - possible bloating, changes in the frequency and stool consistency;</li>
<li><strong>Small size, dense texture, slippery edge</strong> - a man with a deficit of intelligence can strangle if Bob gets into the respiratory tract.</li>
</ul>


<p>People with normal mental development and good health black soybeans can not hurt anything. Eat without fear for their health.</p>

<p>On the Internet a lot of popularity gained supplement for weight loss called &quot;black soybeans&quot;. The advertisement says that it is delivered directly from Japan. It is not clear why they are doing, because it is a good idea in Russia is growing.</p>

<p>At sells website reported that the secret of longevity of the Japanese, finally revealed! It turns out the high life expectancy - a consequence of regular consumption of black soya.</p>

<p>Take supplements you offer for the following purposes:</p>

<p><strong>1. Weight Loss.</strong> The main purpose of black soya. Weight reduction is due to increasing the activity of fat cells. Those allegedly begin to burn fat, regardless of the amount of food consumed by you, including, if you have no physical activity. In addition, thanks to soy protein, according to advertising, the muscles grow without any training.
<strong>2. Improvement by saturating the body with useful substances.</strong> The site Product asserts that certain vitamins, minerals and amino acids are contained only in black soybeans. Nowhere in nature, they are no more. I wonder what kind of minerals are? If you would like Mendeleev heard, he probably would have got out of the coffin to burn his table of chemical elements.
<strong>3. Rejuvenation.</strong> It is due to dietary fiber (which, incidentally, are in any plant food). The body is rejuvenated as a result of lightning elimination of toxins under the influence of black soy from Japan. After that, according to the suppliers of goods, there is a surge of energy forces in the cell, and you feel much better.</p>

<p>Due to what effect this wonder-drug that reduces weight and rejuvenate the body? If you believe the official site, as part contains the following components:</p>

<p><strong>Proteins.</strong> Present in any food products. They are a source of calories. Promote weight loss, but only if used in place of fatty and sugary foods, not in addition to it.</p>

<p><strong>Vitamins A and E.</strong> So these vitamins, which are found nowhere else in nature, except for black soy! Or is there? Yes, still there. Vitamin A is full in carrots and other yellow vegetables, and vitamin E in abundance found in vegetable oils. Both components are useful for health, weight loss but not in any way contribute.</p>

<p><strong>B vitamins</strong> are present in many other foods. Good for your health, but they do not lose weight and look younger.</p>

<p><strong>Alimentary fiber.</strong> In fact contribute to weight loss. But only if the abundance of dietary fiber in the diet causes decrease in consumption of other foods. By themselves, they do not burn fat.</p>

<p><strong>Amino acids.</strong> This protein structural components, so that in fact when transferring the composition manufacturer repeats the same material twice. As mentioned above, from the proteins do not lose weight if they are a supplement, not a substitute for the usual ration.</p>

<p><strong>Trace elements.</strong> What kind of minerals are in the black soybeans - the manufacturer is not recognized. Given that nowhere in other products do not, in general, these micronutrients to mankind is not known, to evaluate their real impact on the shape and health is very difficult.</p>

<p>Black soybean are sold as a concentrate. You will receive a jar of powder. It must be diluted in a glass of water and drink before each meal, three times a den.Takoe use of black soya will help in weight loss, as it will reduce appetite.</p>

<p>Of course, this will not happen because of the presence of this plant amazing fat-burning properties. Hunger subsides as the day before the meal in the stomach will be less space. As a result, you eat less. If this happens regularly for at least several months, you will eventually be able to normalize the figures.</p>

<p>Black soybeans - is one of hundreds or thousands of useless goods for figure and health that is actively circulating on the Internet. It pacifiers in a beautiful package. They are sold on the colorfully decorated sites and skillfully advertised, but because demand. Nevertheless, the man who would be able to lose weight and rejuvenate with the help of black soybean, the world does not know.</p>

<p>This product is recommended to buy the people:</p>

<ul>
<li>The rich - who do not consider $ 40 money, worthy of attention;</li>
<li>Curious - who are used to check for yourself;</li>
<li>Stupid - who believed in a bright, but not the most convincing and reasoned advertising;</li>
<li>Desperate - who wants nothing to do with his own figure and wants to clear his conscience, allegedly fighting <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a> even with the help of useless supplements.</li>
</ul>


<p>The rest of the people recommended to use other methods of weight loss. There are supplements better. However, keep in mind that without the support of the diet and increase physical activity, no medication is not going to work.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Appetite Before Menstruation. Why Before Menstruation I Want to Eat a Lot?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/appetite-before-menstruation-why-before-menstruation-i-want-to-eat-a-lot/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-03T18:02:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/appetite-before-menstruation-why-before-menstruation-i-want-to-eat-a-lot</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/appetite-before-menstruation-why-before-menstruation-i-want-to-eat-a-lot/appetite-before-menstruation-why-before-menstruation-i-want-to-eat-a-lot.jpg" title="Appetite before menstruation" alt="Appetite before menstruation. Why before menstruation I want to eat a lot">What would you no longer want to eat - yogurt, a chocolate bar or a hamburger? At any other time, you will be thinking, but if at the moment your new cycle is nearing completion, the answer is obvious: &quot;All and more!&quot;. Among other <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/" title="symptoms">symptoms</a> of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/premenstrual-syndrome.html" title="premenstrual syndrome">premenstrual syndrome</a>, sometimes women overcomes increased appetite, due to which all the household food reserves are disappearing at a high rate and must be constantly replenished. What is happening and how to deal with it?</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>A brief excursion into the female physiology</h2>

<p>Some girls have every reason to be jealous of men with hormonal virtually flat. In the weak half of humanity it is not so: in women occur every 28-32 days cyclical changes, and during each cycle, they have a certain time can be observed patterns change in health. To make it easier to understand the causes of their increased appetite, to remind you of some of the physiological characteristics of your body.</p>

<p>The menstrual cycle is divided into two approximately equal length phases. The first phase in the body gradually increases the level of hormones, estrogen (estradiol, estriol, estrone). This promotes the maturation of the egg; during this phase the woman feels great, different optimal performance and on what does not complain.</p>

<p>At the peak of the concentration of estrogen ovulation - out egg from the ovary into the fallopian tube where it is ready to be fertilized. From that moment so much estrogen the body is already unnecessary: &#8203;&#8203;their level is gradually reduced, but increasing performance of the hormone progesterone. It prepares the body for a possible <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a>, and creates the conditions to safely settled alleged embryo in the uterus.</p>

<p>All anything, but with the growth of the level of this hormone often start various &quot;tricks&quot; to health. Irritability, lethargy, drowsiness, edema, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/acne.html" title="acne">acne</a> and, of course, a great desire always something to chew&hellip; And how progesterone affects your appetite?</p>

<h2>Mechanisms of appearance of increased appetite</h2>

<p>There are several common explanations for increase appetite during the premenstrual period.</p>

<p>Someone says that estrogen somehow affect the selection into the body of the hormone of happiness, serotonin. Once the second phase of the cycle the estrogen level decreases, it means that the body does not have enough of this &quot;happiness&quot; that makes women look for his other sources, for example, chocolate&hellip;</p>

<p>This is too simplistic an explanation. Firstly, hormones - not only to affect serotonin, and secondly, it promotes the synthesis of not only chocolate but also milk, bananas and other products. Third, before menstruation women pulls not only sweet but also in meat, bakery, etc.</p>

<p>There is still a belief that shortly before the onset of menstruation activates the metabolism, which leads to increased consumption of nutrient and calorie needs increase. This is not so: the metabolic processes are most active when a lot of estrogen in the body (the first phase of the cycle, if you remember the previous section). And with the prevalence of the metabolism of progesterone, on the contrary, a few slowed down.</p>

<p>Other statement does is from the category of &quot;popular&quot;, is that a woman&rsquo;s body prepares for the &quot;cleansing&quot; in the form of monthly, so the pre-stored nutrients to restore torn away the endometrium and blood volume replacement. This is not true! So what&rsquo;s the deal?</p>

<p>But the fact that a woman&rsquo;s body each month naive &quot;hopes&quot; that she finally will assume the obligations imposed on it by nature, and decides to become a mother. So he is not preparing for cleansing, but rather for pregnancy. Under the influence of certain hormones changing composition of the activity of some brain structures (limbic system, reticular formation, hypothalamus). Among other things, the activation of the hunger center; also observed increased secretion of the glands of the digestive tract and other metamorphoses.</p>

<p>In general, the specific reason for your hunger there; blame him - the complex interaction of hormones that influence the changes of the central nervous system, digestive tract and other organs. Act on all this is impossible&hellip; And mediated cause increased appetite is a weakness, irritability and general malaise before menstruation, against which you want to console himself tasty.</p>

<h2>All you are experiencing increased appetite before menstruation?</h2>

<p>As you obviously already knew in their observations, not all women respond to hormonal surges desire to cry, aggression towards others or the desire to absorb the entire contents of the refrigerator. Most just live a normal life, without feeling any particular signs of the end of the cycle.</p>

<p>There are those who have known premenstrual syndrome is not accompanied by increased appetite, but on the contrary, it proceeds with an aversion to food, nausea and even <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/vomiting.html" title="vomiting">vomiting</a>. All individually. So, if you regularly eats before menstruation, do not consider yourself the most miserable creature in the world: Believe me, there are far more options unpleasant condition known as PMS.</p>

<p>You may have noticed on offer, write a few lines above: that the changes in the body that lead to increased feelings of hunger, do not depend on the will of a woman and are not controlled. This is true; You can not make your ovaries change operation&hellip; But no, you can, there is one way.</p>

<p>According to the research, hormonal contraceptives can reduce or eliminate the symptoms of premenstrual syndrome, including increased appetite and. Against the background of hormonal balance is more equalized, and it allows women to feel better.</p>

<p>Other ways to fight hunger are ineffective; We have to rely only on his will and not the means that somehow it will reduce. It is recommended to comply with a reasonable diet, eat more fruits, whole grains, vegetables, chocolate and flour to replace the dried fruit and other more benign figures for sweets. All this will help to eat less, but will only because you themselves will control myself. Another good idea helps something to occupy themselves: loads before menstruation work, school, or anything else, and it will make you think less about hunger.</p>

<p>And in general, why you are so worried about increased appetite? Practice shows that the food eaten during this period, usually fully consumed by the body and does not cause the actual weight gain, unless your condition is not close to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/bulimia.html" title="bulimia">bulimia</a>. Try to get on the scales after a couple of days after the month - and you most likely will not see any changes. So it is not worth much to blame themselves and experience; just try to limit the amount eaten, and your monthly &quot;attacks&quot; will not affect the figure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strength Training for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/strength-training-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-02T14:16:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/strength-training-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/strength-training-for-weight-loss/strength-training-for-weight-loss.jpg" title="Strength training for weight loss" alt="Strength training for weight loss">How to lose weight? The first thing that comes to mind for most people - you need to go on a diet and running every day. But not only cardio training, such as jogging or swimming, contribute to weight loss. One of the methods to reduce body fat - it is strength training. It is to lose weight used by both men and women. It is advisable to work out in the gym, where there are all necessary: &#8203;&#8203;shells, trainers, coaches, moral support and competent advice. But at home to lose weight using weight training is also possible, although the results will be worse.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>The mechanism of action of strength training</h2>

<p>Strength training affects the body fat mass by means of several mechanisms:</p>

<ol>
<li><em>Energy consumption during the workout</em>. Rising iron or doing other exercise, you expend calories. Spend an extra 400-500 calories per day, you will lose weight faster.</li>
<li><em>Accelerate metabolism</em>. Surely you&rsquo;ve noticed that even after 1-2 hours after exercise, you still feel like you are out of the heat. This is a consequence of accelerated metabolism. Increased heat indicates an increased calorie consumption per unit time. That is, even in a state of rest after returning from the gym, you lose weight.</li>
<li><em>Build muscle</em>. Regular classes are usually weightlifting increases muscle mass man. The higher it is, the greater will be the average daily calorie consumption.</li>
</ol>


<p>We should not suppose that only one sport can give yourself a great figure. If your body a lot of fat, in addition to strength training diet is necessary. Classes burn an average of 500 kcal per day in addition to the primary energy consumption. At the same time with the diet can be reduced energy input into the body to 1000 kcal per day and more.</p>

<p>The diet is more effective for weight loss than weight training. But these methods of weight loss can not be opposed to each other. You will achieve maximum results, combining them. Combining sport, proper nutrition, supplementation, adjusting lifestyle, you will lose weight more quickly, and this process will become more natural.</p>

<p>Men are much more likely to engage in weight training than women. This is quite a natural phenomenon, because the stronger sex to have a good figure, should have developed musculature. At the same time big biceps women scare men rather than attract, so the girls better to lose weight with the help of kardionagruzok.</p>

<p>Strength training for men may include:</p>

<ul>
<li>Training with a barbell: bench press, deadlift, wide grip pull-up to his chest, curl with reverse grip barbell bench press standing because of the head;</li>
<li>Training with dumbbells: lunges, squats, curl with dumbbells standing on a bench, dumbbells swings to the side lying, divorce dumbbells;</li>
<li>Exercises using own weight: twisting, pulling on the bar, push-ups, sit-ups.</li>
</ul>


<p>It is advisable to go to the gym and worked under the guidance of coach as weight training require specific knowledge and skills. They help to achieve higher sports results while avoiding overtraining, injury and loss of motivation. Although the house is also possible to lose weight and be sure to purchase this post with a bench and dumbbells.</p>

<p>Women can also be used for weight loss weight training. It should be remembered that too much muscle hypertrophy, especially in the back and arms, will not make the figure more beautiful. Therefore, exercise must be carried out primarily at strengthening the muscles of the legs, buttocks, abdomen, chest.</p>

<p>Women weight training can achieve the following results:</p>

<ul>
<li>Make the legs more slender;</li>
<li>Become more confident, get rid of complexes.</li>
</ul>


<p>For successful weight loss is recommended for women to alternate weight training and cardio training. Catching weightlifting, girls can not build muscle as well as men. This prevents both hormones, and differences in the structure of the muscle fibers. Women have less endurance-they are not able to exercise for one to burn as many calories as men.</p>

<p>Optimum training schedule for weight loss:</p>

<ul>
<li>1-2 times a week - trip to the gym and doing exercises with dumbbells and barbell;</li>
<li>2-3 times a week - cardio training (bike, running, skating);</li>
<li>Every day - walking 30 minutes or more.</li>
</ul>


<p>Be aware of the need for dieting. Training usually increase the appetite, so you have to control your diet conscious.</p>

<p>Strength training may be used as a method of weight loss. It allows you to spend a lot of energy during exercise, temporarily speeds up the metabolism, it helps to build muscle mass. As a method of weight loss, strength training are more suited to men than to women, because the beauty of their figures is largely dependent on the amount of muscle. In addition, they have more stamina for regular and sustained exercise. Women desirable to combine strength training with cardio: running, training on a stationary bike, swimming, skating, aerobics.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Government Is Struggling With Obesity Among Lesbians]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/the-us-government-is-struggling-with-obesity-among-lesbians/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-14T21:44:06+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/the-us-government-is-struggling-with-obesity-among-lesbians</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>According to studies by the National Institutes of Health, three-quarters of lesbians in the United States are overweight. As noted in the publication of Daily Mail, the Institute for research and study of the relationship between <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a> and sexual orientation of the patient from the US budget allocated about half a million dollars.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The grant, the award of the National Institute of Health noted that the study of the issue of obesity among lesbian women, compared with gay men is crucial for health.</p>

<p>The researchers emphasize that previously none of the scientists did not address the issue. However, they managed to find out that women with a different sexual orientation are disproportionately affected by the epidemic of obesity that will allow physicians not only to study the problem and find a way out of it.</p>

<p>The entire project is designed for five years, but the first findings are expected to receive within three years, they have developed a strategy to include the fight against obesity among women or lesbians.</p>

<p>Who led the study will be the director of the medical center, and a professor at Harvard Medical University, Bryn Austin.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
