<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Healthy-lifestyle | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/healthy-lifestyle/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-01-02T16:21:57+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Government Is Struggling With Obesity Among Lesbians]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/the-us-government-is-struggling-with-obesity-among-lesbians/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-14T21:44:06+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/the-us-government-is-struggling-with-obesity-among-lesbians</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>According to studies by the National Institutes of Health, three-quarters of lesbians in the United States are overweight. As noted in the publication of Daily Mail, the Institute for research and study of the relationship between <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a> and sexual orientation of the patient from the US budget allocated about half a million dollars.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The grant, the award of the National Institute of Health noted that the study of the issue of obesity among lesbian women, compared with gay men is crucial for health.</p>

<p>The researchers emphasize that previously none of the scientists did not address the issue. However, they managed to find out that women with a different sexual orientation are disproportionately affected by the epidemic of obesity that will allow physicians not only to study the problem and find a way out of it.</p>

<p>The entire project is designed for five years, but the first findings are expected to receive within three years, they have developed a strategy to include the fight against obesity among women or lesbians.</p>

<p>Who led the study will be the director of the medical center, and a professor at Harvard Medical University, Bryn Austin.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Scientists Named Apricot Most Valuable in the World of Fruit]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/scchinese-scientists-named-apricot-most-valuable-in-the-world-of-fruit/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-14T21:40:26+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/scchinese-scientists-named-apricot-most-valuable-in-the-world-of-fruit</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Researchers in China conducted a large-scale testing of different fruits with the aim to find out which of them is not only delicious, but also the most useful and vitamins. The first contest took place in the apricot.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>This fragrant and sweet fruit has a very positive effect on the cardiovascular system and helps the human heart. In addition, the regular use of apricot help in the prevention of many diseases. The fact is that the apricot contains large amounts of potassium and potassium, is known to play a crucial role in the healthy functioning of the cardiovascular system. In addition, potassium helps rid the body of harmful toxins, and normalizes blood pressure in the arteries.</p>

<p>Scientists have noted that most needed potassium and iron, which are contained in apricots and dried apricots, during <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a> and lactation. Eating a little bit of dried apricots every day, pregnant or nursing mother fill the lack of mineral salts in the body, improve metabolism and make bones strong.</p>

<p>It is also recommended to regularly feast on fresh apricots people who suffer from diseases of the cardiovascular system. Dried apricots also help with poor circulation, reduced cardiac arrhythmia and eventually are an excellent preventive measure against heart attack.</p>

<p>Apricots contains vitamins and <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/solar-capsules-beta-carotene-to-better-tan/" title="beta-carotene">beta-carotene</a>, which help fight <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/" title="infectious diseases">infectious diseases</a> and even cancer diseases. So include in your diet apricots, moreover, that during Lent she will help the body to get enough vitamins and not to succumb to the spring beriberi.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alcohol and Energy Drinks: Bad Combination]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/alcohol-and-energy-drinks-bad-combination/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-27T14:57:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/alcohol-and-energy-drinks-bad-combination</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/alcohol-and-energy-drinks-bad-combination/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="alcohol energy drinks" alt="Alcohol and energy drinks: bad combination"><strong>This is not the first time that energy drinks are singled out, especially in alcoholic evenings.</strong></p>




<p>A new Australian study confirms these fears of dangerous liaisons&hellip;</p>




<!--more-->




<h2>Overconsumption of alcohol</h2>




<p>For the purposes of the study, seventy five young people aged 18 to 30 were invited to drink cocktails in the context of a party held in a laboratory: they received either 60 ml of a mixture Vodka &ndash; Red Bull, 60 ml of a mixture Vodka &ndash; carbonated water, plus 200 ml of a fruit drink in each of these mixtures. Nobody knew what he received as a beverage, but people with the habit of consuming energy drinks have easily recognized. Young also had to take a test and complete questionnaires on which researchers have relied.</p>




<p><strong>It is clear from this experience that those receiving alcohol cocktail with energy drinks were also those who were more inclined to continue to drink alcohol.</strong></p>




<p>However, all is not taken action, some arriving to reason&hellip;</p>




<h2>A trap for the most vulnerable?</h2>




<p>The fact that all those who received the alcohol cocktails and energy drinks, have not drank more than others even if they had more desire can reassure this proves that it is always possible not to succumb! However, proving that the desire to drink alcohol is increased by energy drinks, this study suggests also fear that the most vulnerable to alcohol people have trouble resisting. Indeed, we are not equal face the risk of addiction. And vulnerable people often have trouble recognizing they have a problem with alcohol, because they may very well do without alcohol for several days in a row. This is true, but can not help but consume much always in identical circumstances (such as partying with friends) shows that there is already a problem and it is time to talk to his doctor!</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[1.5 Million Died of AIDS in 2013: A Figure Much Lower]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/1-dot-5-million-died-of-aids-in-2013-a-figure-much-lower/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-25T10:59:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/1-dot-5-million-died-of-aids-in-2013-a-figure-much-lower</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/15-million-died-of-aids-in-2013-a-figure-much-lower/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="AIDS deaths" alt="1.5 million died of AIDS in 2013: a figure much lower"><strong>According to the 2013 report on the <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/aids.html" title="AIDS">AIDS</a> epidemic recently published UNAIDS, the number of deaths due to AIDS for the first time dropped significantly.</strong></p>




<p><strong>However, the number of people living with HIV has increased slightly.</strong></p>




<!--more-->




<h2>Very sharp decrease in the number of people who died of AIDS in 2013</h2>




<p>The results of UNAIDS published in July 2014 indicates that 1.5 million people died of AIDS in 2013, against 1.7 million in 2012, a decrease of 11.8% in a year, the highest drop recorded since the peak of the epidemic in 2005.</p>




<p><strong>In total, ten years, deaths from AIDS have declined by 35%.</strong></p>




<p>Regarding people worldwide with HIV, their number increased slightly, rising to 35 million today, against 34.6 million the previous year. That said, since 2005, there has been a decrease of 33%.</p>




<h2>New infections also fall</h2>




<p><strong>The number of people newly infected each year with HIV continues to fall:</strong> 2.1 million in 2013, against 2.2 million in 2012. But since 2001, new HIV infections have fallen by 38%.</p>




<p><strong>Children born with the AIDS virus are also decreasing:</strong> 240,000 in 2013 against 270,000 in 2012, a decrease of 27.6% since 2005.</p>




<p><strong>The most affected region is sub-Saharan Africa</strong> (South Africa and Nigeria in particular): 70.8% of those affected and still predominantly women (58%). In this part of the world totalling 1.1 million people died of AIDS, 24.7 million people living with HIV, including 2.9 million children.</p>




<p>To this day still, 22 million people have no access to treatment. 38% of adults have, against 24% of children.</p>




<p>Finally, $19.1 billion (14 billion euros) were made available in 2013, against 18.9 million in 2012 and $4.6 billion 10 years ago.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect From Alzheimer's Disease?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-20T12:21:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-protect-from-alzheimers-disease/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="s disease" alt="How to protect from Alzheimer">We&rsquo;ve all heard that stimulate our brain functions, including intellectual could protect us from Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>




<p>Thus, crosswords and all kinds of learning are recommended.</p>




<p>Today, studies suggest that there are other protective factors.
Was even identified risk factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease&hellip; And it appears that we could halve the number of people affected.</p>




<!--more-->




<h2>Alzheimer&rsquo;s, prevent long as we do not know how to cure</h2>




<p>The research was mobilized for years to develop treatments that will cure Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease. Similarly, researchers are busy around prevention. An analysis of all publications focused on this subject gave particularly interesting results.</p>




<p>In fact, risk factors and protective factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease have been identified.</p>




<p>The good news is that all are modifiable, meaning that acting on each of these factors could reduce by half the number of people affected by Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>




<h2>6 risk factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease</h2>




<ul>
<li>Diabetes;</li>
<li>Excess <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a> in midlife;</li>
<li>Smoking.</li>
</ul>




<p>But another study points 3 other additional risk factors (1)</p>




<ul>
<li>Hypertension;</li>
<li>Obesity;</li>
<li>Depression.</li>
</ul>




<h2>5 of protective factors for Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease</h2>




<ul>
<li>The Mediterranean diet;</li>
<li>The folic acid or vitamin B9;</li>
<li>Low or moderate alcohol consumption;</li>
<li>Cognitive activities;</li>
<li>Physical activity.</li>
</ul>




<p>For example, diabetes increases the risk of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease by 39%. Knowing that 6% of the world population is affected by diabetes, the disease is alone responsible for 2% of cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>




<p>Another example, physical inactivity increases the risk of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease by 82%. If we consider that 18% of the world population is physically inactive, sedentary lifestyle is responsible for 13% of cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>




<p>Smoking increases the risk of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease by 59%. If we consider that 27% of the population smokes, smoking is responsible for 14% of cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>




<p>Finally, knowing that many of these factors are related, act on one of them can simultaneously have a significant impact on others. <strong>For example, by acting only on physical inactivity, can simultaneously reduce the risk of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>, <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/cardiology/hypertension.html" title="hypertension">hypertension</a> and diabetes&hellip;</strong></p>




<p><strong>You can see that all these factors are modifiable. In other words, we can all take action and protect us from Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</strong></p>




<p>Thus, nearly half of the cases of Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease could be prevented by modifying these factors.</p>




<p>Recall that in the world, the number of people affected by Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease is estimated at 34 million. In USA, the figure is estimated at nearly 1 million. In the current absence of treatment to cure this disease, prevention is a huge challenge.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
