<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Healthy-lifestyle | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/healthy-lifestyle/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-01-02T20:38:39+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strength Training for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/strength-training-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-02T14:16:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/strength-training-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/strength-training-for-weight-loss/strength-training-for-weight-loss.jpg" title="Strength training for weight loss" alt="Strength training for weight loss">How to lose weight? The first thing that comes to mind for most people - you need to go on a diet and running every day. But not only cardio training, such as jogging or swimming, contribute to weight loss. One of the methods to reduce body fat - it is strength training. It is to lose weight used by both men and women. It is advisable to work out in the gym, where there are all necessary: &#8203;&#8203;shells, trainers, coaches, moral support and competent advice. But at home to lose weight using weight training is also possible, although the results will be worse.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>The mechanism of action of strength training</h2>

<p>Strength training affects the body fat mass by means of several mechanisms:</p>

<ol>
<li><em>Energy consumption during the workout</em>. Rising iron or doing other exercise, you expend calories. Spend an extra 400-500 calories per day, you will lose weight faster.</li>
<li><em>Accelerate metabolism</em>. Surely you&rsquo;ve noticed that even after 1-2 hours after exercise, you still feel like you are out of the heat. This is a consequence of accelerated metabolism. Increased heat indicates an increased calorie consumption per unit time. That is, even in a state of rest after returning from the gym, you lose weight.</li>
<li><em>Build muscle</em>. Regular classes are usually weightlifting increases muscle mass man. The higher it is, the greater will be the average daily calorie consumption.</li>
</ol>


<p>We should not suppose that only one sport can give yourself a great figure. If your body a lot of fat, in addition to strength training diet is necessary. Classes burn an average of 500 kcal per day in addition to the primary energy consumption. At the same time with the diet can be reduced energy input into the body to 1000 kcal per day and more.</p>

<p>The diet is more effective for weight loss than weight training. But these methods of weight loss can not be opposed to each other. You will achieve maximum results, combining them. Combining sport, proper nutrition, supplementation, adjusting lifestyle, you will lose weight more quickly, and this process will become more natural.</p>

<p>Men are much more likely to engage in weight training than women. This is quite a natural phenomenon, because the stronger sex to have a good figure, should have developed musculature. At the same time big biceps women scare men rather than attract, so the girls better to lose weight with the help of kardionagruzok.</p>

<p>Strength training for men may include:</p>

<ul>
<li>Training with a barbell: bench press, deadlift, wide grip pull-up to his chest, curl with reverse grip barbell bench press standing because of the head;</li>
<li>Training with dumbbells: lunges, squats, curl with dumbbells standing on a bench, dumbbells swings to the side lying, divorce dumbbells;</li>
<li>Exercises using own weight: twisting, pulling on the bar, push-ups, sit-ups.</li>
</ul>


<p>It is advisable to go to the gym and worked under the guidance of coach as weight training require specific knowledge and skills. They help to achieve higher sports results while avoiding overtraining, injury and loss of motivation. Although the house is also possible to lose weight and be sure to purchase this post with a bench and dumbbells.</p>

<p>Women can also be used for weight loss weight training. It should be remembered that too much muscle hypertrophy, especially in the back and arms, will not make the figure more beautiful. Therefore, exercise must be carried out primarily at strengthening the muscles of the legs, buttocks, abdomen, chest.</p>

<p>Women weight training can achieve the following results:</p>

<ul>
<li>Make the legs more slender;</li>
<li>Become more confident, get rid of complexes.</li>
</ul>


<p>For successful weight loss is recommended for women to alternate weight training and cardio training. Catching weightlifting, girls can not build muscle as well as men. This prevents both hormones, and differences in the structure of the muscle fibers. Women have less endurance-they are not able to exercise for one to burn as many calories as men.</p>

<p>Optimum training schedule for weight loss:</p>

<ul>
<li>1-2 times a week - trip to the gym and doing exercises with dumbbells and barbell;</li>
<li>2-3 times a week - cardio training (bike, running, skating);</li>
<li>Every day - walking 30 minutes or more.</li>
</ul>


<p>Be aware of the need for dieting. Training usually increase the appetite, so you have to control your diet conscious.</p>

<p>Strength training may be used as a method of weight loss. It allows you to spend a lot of energy during exercise, temporarily speeds up the metabolism, it helps to build muscle mass. As a method of weight loss, strength training are more suited to men than to women, because the beauty of their figures is largely dependent on the amount of muscle. In addition, they have more stamina for regular and sustained exercise. Women desirable to combine strength training with cardio: running, training on a stationary bike, swimming, skating, aerobics.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Government Is Struggling With Obesity Among Lesbians]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/the-us-government-is-struggling-with-obesity-among-lesbians/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-14T21:44:06+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/the-us-government-is-struggling-with-obesity-among-lesbians</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>According to studies by the National Institutes of Health, three-quarters of lesbians in the United States are overweight. As noted in the publication of Daily Mail, the Institute for research and study of the relationship between <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a> and sexual orientation of the patient from the US budget allocated about half a million dollars.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The grant, the award of the National Institute of Health noted that the study of the issue of obesity among lesbian women, compared with gay men is crucial for health.</p>

<p>The researchers emphasize that previously none of the scientists did not address the issue. However, they managed to find out that women with a different sexual orientation are disproportionately affected by the epidemic of obesity that will allow physicians not only to study the problem and find a way out of it.</p>

<p>The entire project is designed for five years, but the first findings are expected to receive within three years, they have developed a strategy to include the fight against obesity among women or lesbians.</p>

<p>Who led the study will be the director of the medical center, and a professor at Harvard Medical University, Bryn Austin.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Scientists Named Apricot Most Valuable in the World of Fruit]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/scchinese-scientists-named-apricot-most-valuable-in-the-world-of-fruit/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-14T21:40:26+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/scchinese-scientists-named-apricot-most-valuable-in-the-world-of-fruit</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Researchers in China conducted a large-scale testing of different fruits with the aim to find out which of them is not only delicious, but also the most useful and vitamins. The first contest took place in the apricot.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>This fragrant and sweet fruit has a very positive effect on the cardiovascular system and helps the human heart. In addition, the regular use of apricot help in the prevention of many diseases. The fact is that the apricot contains large amounts of potassium and potassium, is known to play a crucial role in the healthy functioning of the cardiovascular system. In addition, potassium helps rid the body of harmful toxins, and normalizes blood pressure in the arteries.</p>

<p>Scientists have noted that most needed potassium and iron, which are contained in apricots and dried apricots, during <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gynecology/pregnancy.html" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a> and lactation. Eating a little bit of dried apricots every day, pregnant or nursing mother fill the lack of mineral salts in the body, improve metabolism and make bones strong.</p>

<p>It is also recommended to regularly feast on fresh apricots people who suffer from diseases of the cardiovascular system. Dried apricots also help with poor circulation, reduced cardiac arrhythmia and eventually are an excellent preventive measure against heart attack.</p>

<p>Apricots contains vitamins and <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/solar-capsules-beta-carotene-to-better-tan/" title="beta-carotene">beta-carotene</a>, which help fight <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/" title="infectious diseases">infectious diseases</a> and even cancer diseases. So include in your diet apricots, moreover, that during Lent she will help the body to get enough vitamins and not to succumb to the spring beriberi.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alcohol and Energy Drinks: Bad Combination]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/alcohol-and-energy-drinks-bad-combination/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-27T14:57:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/alcohol-and-energy-drinks-bad-combination</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/alcohol-and-energy-drinks-bad-combination/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="alcohol energy drinks" alt="Alcohol and energy drinks: bad combination"><strong>This is not the first time that energy drinks are singled out, especially in alcoholic evenings.</strong></p>




<p>A new Australian study confirms these fears of dangerous liaisons&hellip;</p>




<!--more-->




<h2>Overconsumption of alcohol</h2>




<p>For the purposes of the study, seventy five young people aged 18 to 30 were invited to drink cocktails in the context of a party held in a laboratory: they received either 60 ml of a mixture Vodka &ndash; Red Bull, 60 ml of a mixture Vodka &ndash; carbonated water, plus 200 ml of a fruit drink in each of these mixtures. Nobody knew what he received as a beverage, but people with the habit of consuming energy drinks have easily recognized. Young also had to take a test and complete questionnaires on which researchers have relied.</p>




<p><strong>It is clear from this experience that those receiving alcohol cocktail with energy drinks were also those who were more inclined to continue to drink alcohol.</strong></p>




<p>However, all is not taken action, some arriving to reason&hellip;</p>




<h2>A trap for the most vulnerable?</h2>




<p>The fact that all those who received the alcohol cocktails and energy drinks, have not drank more than others even if they had more desire can reassure this proves that it is always possible not to succumb! However, proving that the desire to drink alcohol is increased by energy drinks, this study suggests also fear that the most vulnerable to alcohol people have trouble resisting. Indeed, we are not equal face the risk of addiction. And vulnerable people often have trouble recognizing they have a problem with alcohol, because they may very well do without alcohol for several days in a row. This is true, but can not help but consume much always in identical circumstances (such as partying with friends) shows that there is already a problem and it is time to talk to his doctor!</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[1.5 Million Died of AIDS in 2013: A Figure Much Lower]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/1-dot-5-million-died-of-aids-in-2013-a-figure-much-lower/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-25T10:59:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/1-dot-5-million-died-of-aids-in-2013-a-figure-much-lower</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/15-million-died-of-aids-in-2013-a-figure-much-lower/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="AIDS deaths" alt="1.5 million died of AIDS in 2013: a figure much lower"><strong>According to the 2013 report on the <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/infectious-diseases/aids.html" title="AIDS">AIDS</a> epidemic recently published UNAIDS, the number of deaths due to AIDS for the first time dropped significantly.</strong></p>




<p><strong>However, the number of people living with HIV has increased slightly.</strong></p>




<!--more-->




<h2>Very sharp decrease in the number of people who died of AIDS in 2013</h2>




<p>The results of UNAIDS published in July 2014 indicates that 1.5 million people died of AIDS in 2013, against 1.7 million in 2012, a decrease of 11.8% in a year, the highest drop recorded since the peak of the epidemic in 2005.</p>




<p><strong>In total, ten years, deaths from AIDS have declined by 35%.</strong></p>




<p>Regarding people worldwide with HIV, their number increased slightly, rising to 35 million today, against 34.6 million the previous year. That said, since 2005, there has been a decrease of 33%.</p>




<h2>New infections also fall</h2>




<p><strong>The number of people newly infected each year with HIV continues to fall:</strong> 2.1 million in 2013, against 2.2 million in 2012. But since 2001, new HIV infections have fallen by 38%.</p>




<p><strong>Children born with the AIDS virus are also decreasing:</strong> 240,000 in 2013 against 270,000 in 2012, a decrease of 27.6% since 2005.</p>




<p><strong>The most affected region is sub-Saharan Africa</strong> (South Africa and Nigeria in particular): 70.8% of those affected and still predominantly women (58%). In this part of the world totalling 1.1 million people died of AIDS, 24.7 million people living with HIV, including 2.9 million children.</p>




<p>To this day still, 22 million people have no access to treatment. 38% of adults have, against 24% of children.</p>




<p>Finally, $19.1 billion (14 billion euros) were made available in 2013, against 18.9 million in 2012 and $4.6 billion 10 years ago.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
