<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Proctology | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/proctology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2017-03-13T17:16:21+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Sit on the Toilet Correctly? Causes of Constipation and Hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-sit-on-the-toilet-correctly-causes-of-constipation-and-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2017-03-13T16:30:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-sit-on-the-toilet-correctly-causes-of-constipation-and-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-sit-on-the-toilet-correctly-causes-of-constipation-and-hemorrhoids/img.jpg" alt="How to sit on the toilet correctly? Causes of constipation and hemorrhoids">&quot;How do we sit on the toilet?&quot; - once asked the author of the book &quot;Charming Bowel&quot;, at that time a student of the medical faculty, a neighbor in the apartment. The result of the answer to the question was the chapter in the book, which helped many people to take a fresh look at the process of defecation and get rid of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/constipation.html" title="constipation">constipation</a> caused by psychological causes and wrong posture in the toilet.</p>

<!--more-->




<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>The process of defecation is the result of well-coordinated work, in particular, two nervous systems. For this purpose, special adaptations and tricks have been developed by nature in our body.</p>

<p>It all starts with an incredibly well-designed system of locking mechanisms (or sphincters). Almost everyone is familiar only with the external locking mechanism, which by means of conscious impulses opens and closes. A similar locking mechanism is located a few centimeters above - it is beyond our control.</p>

<p>Once the brain decides about the disadvantage of the moment for going to the toilet, the outer locking mechanism obeys and closes as tightly as it can. The work of the internal locking mechanism is regulated <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/injuries-and-accidents/unconscious.html" title="unconsciously">unconsciously</a>. Aunt Berthe likes to fart or not, he is of little interest. Its priority is to maintain comfortable conditions inside the body. Gasses accumulate, which are pressed? All negative factors, the internal locking mechanism is inclined to lead out of the body as quickly as possible.</p>

<h2>How does it feel like to go to the toilet?</h2>

<p>Both locking mechanisms work hand in hand. When the waste of our <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a> approaches the internal locking mechanism, it opens up reflexively. Before all the contents are sent to the side of the external sphincter, the process of its testing takes place. In the space between the two locking mechanisms, a large number of sensitive cells are located, which analyze the information about the incoming contents: it is gaseous or solid in nature, and the information is sent to the brain. At this point, the brain forms a need like &quot;I want to go to the toilet&quot; or &quot;I want to fart&quot;.</p>

<p>Now the brain begins to converse with its consciousness: it is guided by what is happening around us at the moment, collecting and analyzing the information of our sight, hearing and already existing experience. In just a few seconds the brain has a complete picture and sends the data to the external locking device: &quot;I looked, we are here with Aunt Bertha in the living room. Fart still possible, but only if quietly. But to go to the toilet for a big need, perhaps, it is not necessary &hellip; not now&quot;.</p>

<p>The external locking mechanism takes received information and contracts even more tightly than before. The internal sphincter respects the decision taken by the colleague, and by joint decision the test sample is sent to the withdrawal queue.</p>

<p>After some time, the internal locking mechanism sends the test sample again to the evaluation. At this time we are already sitting at home, sitting comfortably on the couch: now you can!</p>

<h2>The cause of constipation is the containment of defecation</h2>

<p>Our inner locking mechanism is a stubborn comrade! His main postulate: &quot;What should come out, will be brought out&quot;. The external locking mechanism is in continuous contact with the outside world and constantly assesses: &quot;Will it be convenient to use another&rsquo;s toilet, or is it better not? If I do not go to the toilet now, I can do it only later in the evening, which means I&rsquo;ll have to feel uncomfortable all day long!&quot;.</p>

<p>If we keep ourselves from going to the toilet, suppressing the urge for the urge, then we oppress the work of the internal locking mechanism and as a result we can even damage it. The internal sphincter is in constant subordination to the external locking mechanism. And the more the external sphincter commands the inner sphincter, the higher the risk of development of problems and the appearance of constipation.</p>

<p>Conscious suppression of the natural processes occurring in the body should not be frequent, do not allow this to become a habit.</p>

<h2>How to sit on the toilet correctly?</h2>

<p>From time to time it is useful to review your habits and ask questions: &quot;Is the path to the stop I&rsquo;m going by is the shortest? Do I look more beautiful and modern when I comb my hair with a bald head? Or even this: &quot;Am I sitting right on the toilet?&quot;.</p>

<p>The last question is extremely difficult to get a clear, unambiguous answer. But, experimenting with yourself, you can bring some kind of novelty to the established process. The same opinion was shared by the Israeli doctor Dov Zikirov.</p>

<p>As part of his experiment, he observed an experienced group of 28 people who visited the toilet daily, taking one of the three poses:</p>

<ul>
<li>relaxing on a normal sized toilet bowl;</li>
<li>the same way, but sitting on a very small size toilet;</li>
<li>literally crouched or squatting, like in nature under a bush.</li>
</ul>


<p>At the same time the defecation time was recorded using a stopwatch, after which the questionnaires were filled.</p>

<p>The results were as follows: the act of defecation of the &quot;on nature&quot; type took an average of 50 seconds, the subjects after emptying in such a pose described their condition as &quot;a feeling of complete emptying&quot;. Sitting in the usual pose, the process lasted for an average of 130 seconds and subjective sensations lagged behind the first group of subjects.</p>

<h2>Why the posture &quot;under the bush&quot; is better for defecation</h2>

<p>The fact is that our locking device is designed in such a way that when we are in a sitting position, it can not open completely. There is a muscle that covers the rectum with a loop like a lasso, when we are in a sitting or standing position, as a result of this action, a bend is formed. Such a mechanism is complementary to existing muscular blocking devices. You can draw an analogy with the bend of the hose for irrigation. If you quickly spread the formed inflection, after a few seconds the water starts to beat again with a key.</p>

<p>Due to the blocking bend in the rectum, the locking sphincters, when we are in a standing and sitting position, exert less effort to contain the movement of fecal masses within the body. As soon as the muscle changes position and ceases to affect the intestine, it is eliminated by the hall, and the path is free.</p>

<p>The squatting position is an evolutionary, natural position of our body in the process of defecation.</p>

<p>The modern position of sitting became a habit with the appearance of toilet bowls in the premises at the end of the XVIII century. But the explanation of the type &quot;caveman is always &hellip;&quot; is a somewhat problematic argument for physicians. Who said that in the squatting position, the muscles relax in such a way that unobstructed movement along the intestine is ensured? And here the Japanese scientists to study this issue gave the group of subjects, along with food, substrates containing labeled substances, and during the defecation in various positions, they were followed by X-ray equipment.</p>

<ul>
<li>Conclusion No. 1. Indeed, in the squat position, the intestinal canal accepts a straight trajectory and there is an unobstructed rapid emptying of the rectal cavity.</li>
<li>Conclusion No. 2. Yet there are altruists who friendlyly agreed to absorb labeled substrates and allowed to lead the observation during such a delicate matter as defecation!</li>
</ul>


<h2>Constipation, hemorrhoids and pose in the toilet</h2>

<p><a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/factors-of-hemorrhoids/" title="hemorrhoids">Hemorrhoids</a>, intestinal pathologies and constipation are phenomena prevalent mainly in countries where bowel evacuation occurs as a &quot;sitting on a chair&quot; type. The reason for this, especially in young people, is not weak musculature, but just increased pressure on the intestines. The development of hemorrhoids, which are prominent from the cavity of the rectum, is one of the mechanisms of compensating for increased internal pressure in the abdominal cavity.</p>

<p>1.2 billion people, accustomed to cope with the need of squatting, do not suffer from hemorrhoids of the intestine. The more developed part of mankind, tiring every day, sooner or later faces problems, for the solution of which it is sent to a specialist. Is it really the payoff for a comfortable seat on the toilet seat instead of coping with an unusual way of sitting-squatting? But if only that!</p>

<p>Physicians are unanimous in the opinion that frequent tension of the abdominal wall and stiffness in the toilet are one of the reasons for the development of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/vascular-disease/varicose-veins.html" title="varicose veins">varicose veins</a>. In addition, the risk of developing <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/neurology/stroke.html" title="stroke">strokes</a> increases and even there are cases of loss of consciousness during defecation.</p>

<p>One day from a friend who was vacationing in France, I received a text message: &quot;The French have gone mad! Someone was stealing the toilet bowls right along three parking lots!&quot;. At first I laughed, because I thought that he was not serious. And then I remembered my first visit to France and how, for the first time, when I saw the toilet without a seat, I was thinking to myself with a longing for the hole in the floor: &quot;Excuse me, please, why I should squat when it would be more logical to put an ordinary toilet bowl&quot;.</p>

<p>In case of difficulty in the process of defecation, it is recommended to create a convenient angle for the sphincters of sphincters - to accept the squatting position.</p>

<p>In most of the Asian countries, countries of Africa and South America, people are in need of the pose of a weightlifter lifting a barbell or a skier at the next turn. We, on the contrary, spend time blissfully on the toilet, while simultaneously reading the newspaper, folding origami from toilet paper or just patiently looking at the opposite wall.</p>

<p>When I read this text to my home, I watched the confused glances in which I saw: &quot;And what now, to refuse the faience flasks, to make a hole in the floor and to put the need there?&quot;. Of course not! It turns out that you can change the position of the muscle and sitting on the toilet in the usual way. The following recommendation is especially useful if the relief of the need is carried out with varying difficulties. That&rsquo;s what you need to do: the upper part of the body slightly tilts forward, under the feet we put a low stand - and voila! - the right angle is found. Now you can read the newspaper with a calm heart, play toilet paper or look at the surrounding objects!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meaning Barium Enema in the Diagnosis of Diseases of the Large Intestine]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/meaning-barium-enema-in-the-diagnosis-of-diseases-of-the-large-intestine/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-22T23:56:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/meaning-barium-enema-in-the-diagnosis-of-diseases-of-the-large-intestine</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/meaning-barium-enema-in-the-diagnosis-of-diseases-of-the-large-intestine/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="s colitis, tumor, polyp" alt="Meaning barium enema in the diagnosis of diseases of the large intestine">Irrigoscopy &ndash; one of radiological methods of investigation of the colon using a radiopaque substance. Barium enema is performed after the introduction into the rectum of barium sulfate (contrast material) or barium suspension in combination with air (double contrast method).</p>




<p>Double contrast reveals the small size of the tumor, particularly polyps and mucosal changes that occur in the early stages of inflammatory diseases of the large intestine.</p>




<!--more-->




<p>With the barium enema can be visualized colon almost an entire length, but for the most effective research rectosigmoid zone applies sigmoidoscopy.</p>




<p>Irrigoscopy not performed after radiographic contrast studies of the upper gastrointestinal tract. Used with barium is excreted within a few days, and the remnants of this substance may distort the results irrigoscopy.</p>




<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>




<h2>The information that can be accessed by barium enema</h2>




<p>During the barium enema doctor receives the following information about the patient&rsquo;s colon:</p>




<ul>
<li>The location, shape and diameter of the colon;</li>
<li>The degree of extensibility and flexibility of the intestinal wall;</li>
<li>Define the function bauginievoy flap. Bauginievaya flap &ndash; is a fold, which is located between the ileum and colon. Normally bauginievaya damper must pass the intestinal contents in only one direction (from the small intestine into the large), but there may be a violation of the intestinal contents throw in the opposite direction. Movement in contrast barium enema shows clearly whether there are irregularities in the bauginievoy flap;</li>
<li>Relief mucosa of the colon walls. This indicator is particularly important in the diagnosis of ulcerative lesions of the bowel, fistulas, tumors, diverticulosis, scars and congenital malformations;</li>
<li>Functional state departments of large intestine.</li>
</ul>




<h2>Why is it important to conduct irrigoscopy?</h2>




<p>As a rule, barium enema is used to confirm the diagnosis in suspected those or other diseases of the colon. Barium enema is often decisive diagnostic method for tumors and colon diverticula.</p>




<p>During the barium enema using the technique of double -contrast study diagnostic capabilities are significantly increased. With barium enema can indirectly confirm the presence of diseases such as colitis and tuberculosis.</p>




<h2>Which diseases carried irrigoscopy?</h2>




<p>When irrigoscopy estimated rate of change of the intestinal mucosa in ulcerative colitis, Crohn&rsquo;s disease, as well as visualized tumors, fistulas, malformations and diverticula.</p>




<p>Unlike colonoscopy, barium enema and less traumatic and less likely to cause complications. Furthermore, barium enema is possible to investigate with the &ldquo;blind&rdquo; to the field of colonoscopy, for example, portions in the folds of the mucosa, and also bends in the colon and the sigmoid colon.</p>




<p>Application irrigoscopy shown if the patient following symptoms:</p>




<ul>
<li>Bleeding from the rectum;</li>
<li>Mucous or purulent discharge from the intestines;</li>
<li>Pain in the anus and in the course of the colon;</li>
<li>Chronic disorder stool (constipation or diarrhea).</li>
</ul>




<h2>How is barium enema?</h2>




<p>Barium enema is performed in a specially equipped medical facility office. A few days before the scheduled study patient should prepare for barium enema. Must be made within 3-4 days follow a special cleansing diet and the use of additional methods for bowel cleansing. This patient doctor tells in detail.</p>




<p>Before the study, the patient is laid down on the couch on its side. In the anus enema tip is introduced, which contains a radiopaque substance. In the future, under fluoroscopy intestines filled contrast agents and conduct a series of reviews and sighting shots in different positions of the patient.</p>




<p>After emptying of barium mixture is produced as air filling bowel under fluoroscopy. So can investigate the organic and functional disorders of the intestinal wall.</p>




<p>Duration of the procedure is a few minutes. During double contrast examination may take 30 to 40 minutes.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Factors of Hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/factors-of-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-15T00:03:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/factors-of-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/factors-of-hemorrhoids/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="factors of hemorrhoids, causes of hemorrhoids, hemorrhoid treatment, proctology, Venapro" alt="Factors of Hemorrhoids">Hemorrhoids &ndash; an inflammatory disease that may affect the pathological expansion of hemorrhoidal veins and the formation of knots. According to medical statistics, hemorrhoids often occurs in people older than 45 years.</p>




<p>The exact cause of hemorrhoids is still not established. The main possible causes of the disease, modern medicine treats vascular pathology (dysfunction between the blood flow through the arteries and the flow of blood through the cavernous veins) and disruption of the muscular system, retaining hemorrhoids.</p>




<!-- more -->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>




<h2>Factors of hemorrhoids</h2>




<p>Promote the development of hemorrhoids are many factors among which are:</p>




<ul>
<li><strong>Genetic predisposition</strong>. Some people venous network in the anus has a very dense plexus, which complicates the flow of blood through the vessels. In case of violation of vascular permeability develops blood stagnation that contributes to the inflammatory process.</li>
<li><strong>Pregnancy and childbirth</strong>. During pregnancy the uterus increases in size, which leads to a displacement of the movable upward while the rectum is pressed against the pelvis. Thus, the clamped venous blood vessels, which leads to an overflow of the cavernous bodies.</li>
<li><strong>Physical inactivity</strong>. Sedentary lifestyle contributes to the development of venous insufficiency, in particular to the development of stagnation in the pelvic organs. Reduce the chance of developing hemorrhoids is possible if regularly moderate exercise.</li>
<li><strong>Failure to comply with the rules of hygiene</strong>. When excessive hygiene anus, as well as the use of low-quality toilet paper mucosa irritated anus, thereby increasing the probability of acute hemorrhoids.</li>
<li><strong>Bad habits</strong>. Smoking worsens the condition of vessels, including hemorrhoidal veins. Also, smoking increases the severity of bleeding. As for alcoholic beverages, the alcohol helps dilate blood vessels, which in turn leads to stagnation of blood in the hemorrhoids.</li>
<li><strong>Malnutrition</strong>. Excessive consumption of hot and spicy food, as well as lack of fiber is a significant negative factor in the development of inflammatory processes in the rectum.</li>
<li><strong>Chronic constipation</strong>. Disturbances of feces leads to frequent constipation. Solid stool, lingering in the intestines, put pressure on the choroid plexus of the rectum, thereby helping to expand the hemorrhoidal veins. Also promotes the development of hemorrhoids during defecation habit to push.</li>
<li><strong>Hypothermia</strong>. Hypothermia leads to circulatory problems that can cause the development of inflammation in the rectal area. In particular, avoid hypothermia lower body (not sit on a cold surface, dress appropriately to weather conditions).</li>
<li><strong>Physical activity</strong>. Excessive exercise (weightlifting, bodybuilding, etc.) is likely to disrupt the tone of the muscular apparatus of the anus. Muscle weakness contributes anus prolapsed hemorrhoid. Furthermore, physical overload cause delay of blood in the veins, which increases the likelihood of developing hemorrhoids.</li>
</ul>




<h2>Hemorrhoid Treatment</h2>




<p>Any disease is always easier to prevent than to cure. At elimination of negative factors likely to develop hemorrhoids is minimal. Even hereditary predisposition to hemorrhoids may not materialize if lead a healthy lifestyle and eat right.</p>




<p>If the hemorrhoids are still developed, it is necessary as soon as possible to begin treatment. Depending on severity of the disease may be used as a conservative and surgical treatment.</p>




<p>Medication hemorrhoids includes use of anti- inflammatory, analgesic and hemostatic (if bleeding) drugs.</p>




<p>The most effective use of local products in the form of rectal suppositories. One such drug is Venapro. This combination drug, which includes an anti-inflammatory bufexamac, wound healing agent and bismuth subgallate anesthetic lidocaine component.</p>




<p>Venapro hemorrhoids is useful for a 1-2 stages, as well as diseases such as proctologic anal fissure, proctitis, anal eczema and other.</p>




<p>Available <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7">Venapro</span> in rectal suppositories, which makes it very convenient to use. The likelihood of side effects from the drug is extremely low.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[He Does Not Like Hemorrhoids?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/he-does-not-like-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-02T23:05:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/he-does-not-like-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/he-does-not-like-hemorrhoids/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="aggravation, contraindication factor, hypothermia, lack of exercise, physical activity, dietary fiber" alt="He does not like hemorrhoids?">Follow the advice of doctors and avoid the negative factors contributing to aggravate hemorrhoids.</p>




<!-- more -->




<h2>Why do I get hemorrhoids?</h2>




<p>Doctors say that lately hemorrhoids much &ldquo;younger&rdquo;. Most likely, the reason for that are the negative factors contributing to the development of the disease with which modern man often encountered. These factors include:</p>




<ul>
<li>pregnancy and childbirth;</li>
<li>heredity;</li>
<li>sedentary lifestyle;</li>
<li>unhealthy diet;</li>
<li>poor hygiene;</li>
<li>hypothermia;</li>
<li>chronic gastrointestinal disorder;</li>
<li>excessive exercise.</li>
</ul>




<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>




<p>The combination of these factors leads to the development of pathological enlargement of hemorrhoidal veins and implementation of disease. At the first symptoms should immediately contact a doctor, mainly because hemorrhoids characterized by chronic course with periodic exacerbations. In order to reduce the appearance of the disease and minimize the likelihood of an exacerbation, the patient must be aware of what not to do with hemorrhoids. Especially effective prevention of hemorrhoids is the first stage of the disease when the disease symptoms have not yet pronounced.</p>




<h2>Contraindications for hemorrhoids</h2>




<p><strong>Food contraindications</strong></p>




<p>When hemorrhoids diet is very important. As a preventive measure, doctors recommend eating foods containing large amounts of fiber. Such food will reduce the number of exacerbations and the severity of hemorrhoids. When varicose veins hemorrhoids may want to limit the consumption of these foods and dishes:</p>




<ul>
<li>fried foods;</li>
<li>hot and spicy dishes, irritating;</li>
<li>semolina;</li>
<li>mashed potatoes;</li>
<li>eggs;</li>
<li>jelly;</li>
<li>alcohol;</li>
<li>black tea, coffee.</li>
</ul>




<p><strong>Hypodynamy</strong></p>




<p>Sedentary lifestyle contributes to stagnation in the pelvic organs, which only aggravates the disease. At risk are people who have to be for a long time without moving (office workers, drivers). Try as much as possible to do a little workout. On the way to and from work, try to walk more. And best of all to engage in moderate exercise regularly. Jogging, swimming, walking trails and many other kinds of physical activity will only benefit.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bleeding Internal Hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/bleeding-internal-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-30T07:07:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/bleeding-internal-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/bleeding-internal-hemorrhoids/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="Bleeding internal hemorrhoids" alt="Bleeding internal hemorrhoids"><strong>Hemorrhoids.</strong> One of the main symptoms of this disease is the hemorrhoidal bleeding.</p>




<p>Literature data of recent years have pointed out that the cause of hemorrhoids is a violation of the outflow of blood from the venules of the cavernous bodies, which are located in the wall of the rectum (the largest cluster of notes on 3-7-11 hours on the dial) and is a substrate haemorrhoid. <!-- more -->Therefore, if the wall of the cavernous bodies, which is filled with blood directly from the arterial bed is damaged, the stands out of scarlet, oxygen saturation arterial blood.</p>




<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Bleeding at internal hemorrhoids characterized in that the blood volume, wherein is of a few drops to 100-200 ml per day and with frequent hemorrhage causes the development of anemia. In some cases, hemorrhage may be inkjet and pulsating.</p>




<p><strong>Diagnosis.</strong> Under gentle disclosure of the edges of the anus hemorrhoids are defined as swollen formations bluish color, soft-elastic consistency, covered with a mucous membrane. Necessarily carry out the finger, mirroring studies and sigmoidoscopy. Soft hemorrhoids are rarely detected by digital examination, but this study is an important method for the differential diagnosis. When the mirror examination may reveal the bleeding internal hemorrhoids.</p>




<p><strong>Treatment.</strong> We must remember that the causes of intestinal bleeding may be tumors (benign and malignant) of rectum and colon. Only after exclusion of these diseases should begin to targeted <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7">treatment of hemorrhoidal bleeding</span>.</p>




<p>In chronic hemorrhoids, which manifests itself only bleeding internal hemorrhoids without a loss of knots, in the absence of common anorectal thrombosis recommends a hemostatic therapy with Venapro. 10 percent calcium chloride, 5 percent solution of aminocaproic acid as well as with the use of adrenaline suppositories by recipe.</p>




<p>In the absence of contraindications is possible to use an injection of sclerosing agents.</p>




<p>Contraindications to this kind of treatment are diseases of the prostate and hypertension, in which if there is no severe anemia, such  bleeding is as would damping. At presence of infectious diseases, inflammatory changes in the walls of the anal canal and rectal mucosa injection of sclerosing agents is contraindicated. Relative contraindications for sclerotherapy are loss of internal hemorrhoids and frequent exacerbation of chronic hemorrhoids, because the presence of these complications are indications for surgical treatment.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
