<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: proctology | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/proctology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-11-12T19:15:40+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 7 conditions for victory over hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/top-7-conditions-for-victory-over-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-10T19:22:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/top-7-conditions-for-victory-over-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/top-hemorrhoid-treatment/3.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/top-hemorrhoid-treatment/3.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Top hemorrhoid treatment&rsquo; &lsquo;Top 7 conditions for victory over hemorrhoids&rsquo;" > Medical experts from the Office of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), the United States, called the 7 rules that will help prevent and cure hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Do not read in the bathroom. The study showed that 35% of Americans take with them into the toilet Ipad.
Use the special napkins during a visit to the toilet or wet toilet paper. This protects the sore from too much stimulation sites. Avoid paper and napkins with an aromatic fragrance and alcohol.
Be aware of hygiene: take a warm bath and then take care of the dryness of the anus to avoid friction sensitive tissues.
Go to the toilet every time when you feel the urge to defecate. Delay chair helps increase pressure on the weakened veins, ie, worsening of hemorrhoids.
Avoid constipation: Drink plenty of water, eat foods rich in fiber.
Move more. Activity helps to reduce the pressure on the veins, as well as get rid of the excess weight that contributes to hemorrhoids.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to treat hemorrhoids at home?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-treat-hemorrhoids-at-home/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-10T18:57:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-treat-hemorrhoids-at-home</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/home-cure-for-hemorrhoids/2.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/home-cure-for-hemorrhoids/2.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Home cure for hemorrhoids&rsquo; &lsquo;How to treat hemorrhoids at home?&rsquo;" > For home cure for hemorrhoids treatment include the use of warm baths, medicinal herbal preparations, ointments, creams and suppositories. So how to treat hemorrhoids at home?</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Sitz baths</h2>

<p>Warm water relaxes the sphincter muscles, it can also help soothe the pain associated with hemorrhoids speaking.</p>

<p><strong>Usage:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Fill the tub to the third warm water.</li>
<li>Do not add anything to the water.</li>
<li>Sit in the bath for 15 minutes.</li>
<li>Repeat the procedure several times a day.</li>
</ul>


<p>When the hemorrhoid pain, hip bath &ndash; it&rsquo;s the best and easiest way to get quick relief.</p>

<h2>Using petrolatum or zinc oxide</h2>

<p>Studies have shown that petroleum jelly and/or zinc oxide works best for hemorrhoids than any other expensive creams. To reduce the pain and swelling of hemorrhoids, you can use both tools at the same time.</p>

<p><strong>Usage:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>After cleaning the skin of the anal region, apply a small amount of petroleum jelly or zinc oxide deposited on a cotton swab to the swollen places.</li>
</ul>


<p>Another popular recipe. In order to &ldquo;get rid&rdquo; of hemorrhoids enough to buy at the pharmacy vial zinc ointment, put a little more in the plastic cover and then add five drops of tincture of peppermint and as much butter. Components mixed for several hours and put in the freezer. After a while you need to get the mixture from the refrigerator and cut into slices, in the form of suppositories to be inserted into the anal canal at night. For the treatment usually lasts 2-4 caps.</p>

<ul>
<li>Keep the swollen area clean and dry. Do not use scented toilet paper, soap or gel for the body, containing chemicals clinically proven that they are harmful to irritated skin.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Herbal home cure for hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>The most frequent cause of hemorrhoids is a low fiber content, resulting in constipation, whereby chair hardens, and it is difficult to pass through the large intestine. Psyllium, or psyllium seeds, are high in fiber, which essentially helps make stools soft, and easily passable. Psyllium seeds help prevent hemorrhoids and also to make bowel movements less painful. Those interested in how to treat hemorrhoids at home, it is recommended that the seed husks have become a part of your daily diet. Plantain seeds can be easily found in most pharmacies.</p>

<p><strong>Usage:</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Start taking a teaspoon of psyllium with a glass of water in the morning as part of your breakfast for a week.</li>
<li>During the second week, add another glass of seeds to your dinner.</li>
<li>Slowly and carefully enter the third glass of the third week, and make the adoption of psyllium three times a day, your longstanding habit.</li>
<li>When you have begun to take psyllium seed at 3 times a day, you do not need to take any &ndash; or other add-ons. Make sure that you drink plenty of water when taking psyllium or any other type of fiber because fiber softens the stool by absorbing water. It is recommended to drink 50 grams of water per kilogram of your body weight in a day.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Avoid sweat and strain</h3>

<p>Do not try to make a bowel movement, if you do not feel like doing it. And do not spend a lot of time on the toilet than is required for a bowel movement without straining. Once your intestines freed sufficiently, and do not exert yourself.</p>

<h3>Try different positions</h3>

<p>It has been suggested that squatting in the toilet during a bowel movement is a more natural position than sitting on the toilet. Some people believe that maintaining feet on a small foot, and stretching the knees toward the chest, good help for those interested in how to treat hemorrhoids at home.</p>

<h3>Heed the call of nature</h3>

<p>On the other hand, do not wait too long.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How long to cure hemorrhoids?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-long-to-cure-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-10T18:49:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-long-to-cure-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/how-long-to-cure-hemorrhoids/1.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/how-long-to-cure-hemorrhoids/1.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;How long do hemorrhoids last&rsquo; &lsquo;How long to cure hemorrhoids?&rsquo;" > Many of the people in connection with their professional activities or old age are sedentary throughout the day. That&rsquo;s just the body that is not beneficial. The most annoying thing that can undermine your health in this case, it is hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>After the hemorrhoid formation raises the question: how long do hemorrhoids last? As is the case with any other illness, duration of treatment depends on the stage of the disease and the method by which you will be treated. In no case did not begin treatment on their own. Only a doctor can determine the extent of the disease and will take just a decision about treatment. Hemorrhoids tend to move in the acute form, without any warning, even if you initially tried to treat the most simple form of it.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>In the early stages it is possible to shoot down the pain and itching. In this case, the ice will latch to the anal area or compress the warm water. After defecation is best for 15 minutes to apply a warm bath. But do not overdo it with the temperature as excessively warm water can cause burns to the anal area. A few days is to stay at home and keep bed rest. It is recommended to sleep belly down, placing a pillow under your hips. During defecation should not strain the anus.</p>

<p>How long do hemorrhoids last, if he does not retreat? In the following steps should refer to the drugs that the doctor prescribed. Here each drug in accordance with its capabilities involves different durations of treatment. It may be medications that will reduce the outflow of blood and clots (hemorrhoidal formations), in addition to that, they will function as pain relief. Various creams and ointments should be applied to the anal area with a massage at the same time. Massage also performed with the introduction of candles into the anus for hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>Advanced stages of hemorrhoids are treated with surgery. Such methods resort after medication has no effect. External hemorrhoids are removed only if they are too large scale. The most popular surgical procedure with the appearance of internal hemorrhoids. After removal of the clot will take some time to adapt and overcome the pain in the anal area. It is necessary to strictly follow the diet, not eating spicy and fatty foods, and alcohol.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homeopatic treatment of diseases. Hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/homeopatic-treatment-of-diseases-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-10T17:57:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/homeopatic-treatment-of-diseases-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/homeopathic-remedies-for-hemorrhoids/index.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/homeopathic-remedies-for-hemorrhoids/index.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Homeopathic remedies for hemorrhoids&rsquo; &lsquo;Homeopatic treatment of diseases. Hemorrhoids&rsquo;" > Hemorrhoid is an inflammation of veins in the rectum, where they expand, so that nodes are formed.</p>

<p>Those at risk for the disease hemorrhoids include obese people, lovers of spicy foods and alcohol, people who are on duty have little move and sit constantly, constantly bearing the weight people (such as housewives), pregnant and nursing mothers, as well as suffering from constipation several distinct stages of the disease.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Stages of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>In the first stage of development and the severity of patients experience itching in the rectum, frequent constipation. Stronger feelings are after weight lifting, spicy food and drinking alcohol.</p>

<p>The second stage is characterized by the appearance of bleeding hemorrhoids fall out, the pain is getting stronger and more.</p>

<p>Sign of the next stage of hemorrhoids &ndash; hemorrhoids do not reduce a, resulting in an thrombosis or necrosis of the veins of the rectum.</p>

<h2>Symptoms of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>The first striking symptom of hemorrhoids &ndash; is bleeding during each act of defecation. Also, patients notice a prolapsed hemorrhoid, a burning sensation and pain in the anus, feeling the presence of a foreign object into the anus and the severity of the groin.</p>

<p>Immediately, we note that emit sharp and chronic hemorrhoids. In acute discomfort of the disease is stronger and brighter, whereas in chronic long can not be felt and gain strength only in certain periods of life. Among the symptoms of acute hemorrhoids also present perianal swelling.</p>

<p>Next, hemorrhoids noted mucus from the anus, and finally, pain hemorrhoids.</p>

<h2>Hemorrhoid treatment drugs classical medicine</h2>

<p>As with any other disease, hemorrhoids are much easier to treat in the early stages. It was in the early periods of the disease can take advantage of non-surgical treatments. When hemorrhoids are very important the correct way of life that takes into account both traditional medicine and homeopathy.</p>

<h2>Lifestyle hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>The first and most important thing for hemorrhoids &ndash; to begin to move more, will be useful not too heavy physical activities, including swimming. From large loads should be avoided, as with alcohol and spicy food.</p>

<p>Do not forget about hygiene. Need to take a shower after each act of defecation on the toilet paper it is desirable to give up.</p>

<p>Diet plays a huge role in the treatment of hemorrhoids. As mentioned above, you need to stop eating bad foods in the diet and increase the number of fruits and vegetables.</p>

<h2>Treatment of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Proper treatment of hemorrhoids in classical medicine depends on what stage of development is a disease. For example, in the early stages to achieve the result by using the drug, but the drugs are aimed primarily at reducing the discomfort, rather than knocking causes disease. They decrease pain, improve blood flow and reduce inflammation. There are local medications such as ointments and candles, and there are those that are taken orally, such as tablets and injections.</p>

<p>As soon as a thrombosis, as indicated by increased pain and discomfort in the anal area, ointments prescribed blood-thinning. The point of this is to not allow the blood to clot. In the case of very heavy bleeding from hemorrhoids begin receiving hemostatic drugs.</p>

<p>Also recommended medications that strengthen the walls of veins, in particular often used Venapro.</p>

<h3>The treatment of hemorrhoids without surgery</h3>

<p>We should also say about treatments for hemorrhoids without surgery, which, like medication, are good only at the initial stages. Today, sclerotherapy is used (in hemorrhoids introduced special substances to fill the lumen and wall adhesion), infrared coagulation (blocking the blood supply to the hemorrhoidal nodes), proximal ligation (ligation of the arteries) and ligation (ligation latex rings). The latter procedure is good even in the third stage of hemorrhoids.</p>

<h3>Surgery for hemorrhoids</h3>

<p>If the disease has gone too far and the application of the methods described above will not give proper result, it is necessary to resort to surgery. Unlike conventional medicine, homeopathic remedies can cure hemorrhoids without surgery, even at the last stage of its development.</p>

<h3>Hemorrhoid Treatment drugs homeopathy</h3>

<p>Many homeopathic remedies for hemorrhoids have been used successfully in the treatment. Tell you about the most common ones.
If the disease worsened, that is passed into the last stage, it should be administered Atsidum muriatikum or hydrochloric acid in the sixth, twelfth and thirtieth dilution.
If hemorrhoids are accompanied by itching and burning, it will help Venapro or capsicum in the third, sixth and twelfth dilution.</p>

<p>When the disease is characterized by a sense of gravity, then appoint Sokotrina aloe or aloes in the third decimal, third and sixth dilution.</p>

<p>When hemorrhoids, accompanied by bleeding, or helps Hamamelis Virginika hamamelis virginiana third decimal, third and sixth dilution, as well as ointments and oils.</p>

<p>In general, the following are recommended for hemorrhoids homeopathic remedies:  Venapro drug combines these medications well.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hemorrhoid home treatment]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoid-home-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T23:36:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoid-home-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When we say the word &ldquo;hemorrhoid&rdquo;, many are experiencing negative, sometimes reaching up to phobias, feelings. However, this disease is not so bad, especially in the early stages. It occurs due to poor nutrition, physical inactivity and sedentary lifestyle. It may be provoke a heredity.</p>

<p>In order to answer the question of how to treat hemorrhoids, you need to give it a clear definition. Hemorrhoids are vascular cavernous body. These are formed in the rectum (in the lower part). Nodes can be internal or external. Simultaneously, at the patient may be present both species, in this case will help only complex treatment.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Characteristically reluctance of a large number of patients to see a doctor in the early stages of this disease. They do not ask how to cure hemorrhoids and how to pick a remedy for hemorrhoids, even experiencing pain and discomfort. However, the need to go to a specialist as soon as possible. It is better to hemorrhoid home treatment, than to resort to complex surgery, which in some cases does not bring the proper favor and alleviate suffering.</p>

<p><strong>In the U.S., 80% of persons with hemorrhoids, the doctor did not address</strong></p>

<p>There are four stages of this disease:</p>

<ol>
<li>The formation hemorrhoid nodes inside the rectum (internal hemorrhoids);</li>
<li>There is a loss of nodes of the rectum after a bowel movement, they themselves reduce a back;</li>
<li>The nodes do not reduce a own but it can still be done with your fingers;</li>
<li>Impossible to reduce fallen nodes (external hemorrhoids).</li>
</ol>


<p>Effective hemorrhoid home treatment is possible only on the first and second stages. On the third and fourth often have to resort to surgery.</p>

<p>In spite of the obvious symptoms of many ill in no hurry to seek medical help. They will not go to the doctor, as a result, they develop hemorrhoids third and fourth stage. For some reason, some people think hemorrhoids are something shameful. They hide their illness from others. This trend is not exclusive to the United States, but also in many European countries. However it is better to learn from experts how to treat hemorrhoids, rather than later hospital treatment needed or, worse, in the outpatient and dispensary observation.</p>

<p>Today, a large amount of useful information on how to cure hemorrhoids, can also find on the Internet. In a network there are enough sites on which there is information about the problem of the disease, the mechanisms of its development, prevention methods and hemorrhoid home treatment.</p>

<h2>How to treat hemorrhoids. The main methods</h2>

<ol>
<li>Non-medical impact. Effective only in the early stages, is to change the lifestyle and diet, increasing physical activity.</li>
<li>Drug therapeutic impact.</li>
<li>Reducing the pressure in the anal canal (the means for doing so are drug «Venapro» and ointments such as Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Locoid etc.).</li>
<li>Non-surgical methods of influence.</li>
<li>Surgical treatment.</li>
</ol>


<p>In the early stages of the disease and as a prophylactic course after surgical treatment is <strong>very effective natural product «Venapro»</strong>.</p>

<p>Identify hemorrhoids simply by the following symptoms:
&ndash; Bleeding during bowel movements, blood in faeces.
&ndash; The occurrence of burning and itching in the anal area.
&ndash; Pain when sitting, walking, bowel movements.
&ndash; The emergence of a sense of gravity or presence of a foreign body in the rectum.
&ndash; Inflammation of hemorrhoid nodes. They be palpated, this gives rise to pain.
&ndash; Occurs loss of nodes of the rectum.</p>

<p>It should, as soon as possible, seek medical attention if these symptoms.</p>

<h2>Hemorrhoid home treatment. Traditional methods</h2>

<p>The use drug treatment is usually only gives a relief of symptoms of the disease in the third and fourth stages. To effectively deal with hemorrhoids, you need to use an integrated approach.</p>

<p>Modern medicine offers to hemorrhoid home treatment is not only tablets but also in other ways. In the early stages helps to get rid of the pain and reduce inflammation of the nodes special diet. Of the food exclude alcohol, spicy and fatty foods, condiments and spices. A diet enriched with plant-based diet high fiber content. Recommended for early hemorrhoids long walks, special exercises, including squats, press load, tilts, etc. It is necessary to make a thorough hygiene of the anus after defecation.</p>

<p>However, the disease exacerbation of those measures will not be enough. In the acute form of hemorrhoid home treatment will require the use of anal suppositories, ointments, and cold lotions. When it is impossible to stop the periodic occurrence of venous bleedings knots injected sclerosing solutions.</p>

<p>By resorting to surgery only in cases where there are prolonged and severe bleeding, constantly drop nodes, at a jamming. All the same any form of treatment is useless if you do not aimed at removing underlying causes of the disease. They only temporarily make easier the patient&rsquo;s condition, reduce pain and symptoms.</p>

<p>In the complex treatment of hemorrhoids is to include products «Venapro &ndash; Hemorrhoid formula». It is especially effective in the early stages of the disease.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
