<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: proctology | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/proctology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-12-10T22:07:58+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thrombosis - Thrombosed hemorrhoid]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/thrombosis-thrombosed-hemorrhoid/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-10T22:06:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/thrombosis-thrombosed-hemorrhoid</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-hemorrhoid/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-hemorrhoid/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Thrombosed hemorrhoid&rsquo; &lsquo;Thrombosis &ndash; Thrombosed hemorrhoid&rsquo;" > <strong>Thrombosed hemorrhoid</strong>, also called acute hemorrhoids &ndash; a disease which occurs in almost 10% of all adults. This is a problem that everyone knows, but prefer not to talk, because it&rsquo;s embarrassing. And meanwhile, it is the patients reluctance seeking medical attention leads to what the disease becomes chronic late stage.</p>

<p>The cause of the disease are blood clots of external or internal hemorrhoids that drop out. If you look, the blood clot is a hematoma near the anus, which brings a man a lot of inconvenience and pain.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Simultaneous thrombosis of external and internal nodes is fairly rare. It can spread to all anus around (in this case it is called the circular), or to be on only one side, covering the anus of a semicircle.</p>

<h2>Causes and symptoms of Thrombosed hemorrhoid</h2>

<p>Reasons for the formation of blood clots in hemorrhoids diverse. It can be physical exertion &ndash; weight lifting, pregnancy or childbirth, as well as diarrhea, constipation, hypothermia and even alcohol abuse. In addition, for unpleasant consequences can result sedentary lifestyle work-related (pilots and drivers), or some sports &ndash; weightlifting, cycling, horseback riding.</p>

<p>Any stress, leading to a rush of blood to the pelvis can cause rupture of the vessel in the perianal region and lead to thrombosed external hemorrhoid. In this case, the thrombus begins to put pressure on the vessel wall from within, irritating nerve endings and causing pain. It is these symptoms of hemorrhoids cause a &ldquo;duck&rdquo; gait of patients.</p>

<p>Most often in the early stages, the disease is accompanied by itching, burning and secretions from anus. Patients rarely turn to doctors with such complaints, because they consider them uncritical, or just shy of his problem. Most often they are accompanied by still bleeding. First, rare and meager &ndash; only a few drops during stool, and then they become regular. And when there is a prolapsed hemorrhoid and the pain becomes unbearable and avoid a visit to a specialist is can not.</p>

<h2>Thrombosed hemorrhoid treatment</h2>

<p>The easiest and fastest way to treat hemorrhoids &ndash; is surgery. It is performed under local anesthesia and takes only a few minutes. During the operation, the doctor-proctologist makes minimal incision (up to 5 mm) and through it removes the blood clot from the node, after which the pain immediately goes away. Sometimes, to achieve a cosmetic effect, thrombus excised together with the node. After these operations, the man does not lose the ability to work, and the wound is healing on-site intervention is less than a week.</p>

<p>The only drawback to this method is that the operation &ndash; not a radical cure for hemorrhoids. A blood clot will not appear on the site was operated, but could come close. Therefore, this method of treatment is used to advanced stages of the disease as a means of emergency medicine, as soon as possible to save people from pain.</p>

<p>In all other cases, and at the unwillingness of the patient subjected to surgery, treatment is carried out with the use of medication ointments, rectal suppositories and warm baths. This method gives the effect only after a month and in the future does not preclude the emergence of a blood clot in the same place. Therefore, in order to avoid undesirable effects during treatment should follow a diet, eliminating alcohol and spicy foods, as well as limit physical exertion and less walking.</p>

<p>Speaking of non-surgical treatment of hemorrhoids can not pay attention to the drug Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula, which has proved its effectiveness in the fight against this disease. This drug is made from natural ingredients and with proper treatment recovery comes faster than with other drugs. It is particularly effective in the early stages of hemorrhoids when hemorrhoid nodes have not fallen out. Its also worth taking after recovery as prophylaxis to prevent any re-occurrence of a blood clot.</p>

<p>Remember, <strong>thrombosed hemorrhoid</strong> is always easier to cure in the early stages, and delayed treatment or lack of it at all can lead to complications.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acute hemorrhoids - Thrombosed external hemorrhoid]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/acute-hemorrhoids-thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-09T22:50:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/acute-hemorrhoids-thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Thrombosed external hemorrhoid&rsquo; &lsquo;Acute hemorrhoids &ndash; Thrombosed external hemorrhoid&rsquo;" > A patient with <strong>thrombosed external hemorrhoid</strong> can be found on the &ldquo;duck gait&rdquo; with which they come into the doctor&rsquo;s office. Asked to sit down on a chair, meet the &ldquo;thank you I&rsquo;ll stand by foot&rdquo;. Why is that? Because concerned about pain in the anal area, at whom are moderate, at whom expressed.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>The cause of acute hemorrhoids is different: constipation, diarrhea, hypothermia, weight lifting, alcohol, pregnancy, childbirth, anal sex, etc. With an increase in intra-abdominal pressure occurs powerful rush of blood to pelvis, because of what could &ldquo;explode&rdquo; vein in the perianal area and formed <strong>thrombosed external hemorrhoid</strong>. In fact, this hematoma, which is located under the skin gives a lot of pain and discomfort. This occurs because blood clot presses on the inner tissues thereby stretching the nerve endings, followed by pain. Many people ask this hematoma can get to the heart? No description of a single case of getting thrombosed blood clot (hematoma) of the haemorrhoid in the heart.</p>

<p>Thrombosed external hemorrhoid is more often a unit, can occur immediately 2-3 thrombosed node and can be circular when the swells all perianal area. As well found thrombosis of internal hemorrhoids. This occurs against the background of already existing hemorrhoids during stool internal nodes drop out further as a consequence of the sphincter spasm nodes are infringed, there is an infringement of outflow of blood, swelling knotswith subsequent thrombosis. With such an aggravation of internal hemorrhoids pain for so many severe that patients can not &ldquo;neither sit nor stand up&rdquo; and some call the &ldquo;911&rdquo;. What to do if diagnosed acute hemorrhoids?</p>

<h2>How to treat thrombosed external hemorrhoid</h2>

<p>Treatment hemorrhoid thrombosis. Usually in such cases, you need to limit yourself to walking, exercise, spicy foods, alcohol. Appointed by warm baths and heating pads 2-3 times a day for 20-30 minutes (due to the heat accelerates the resorption of blood clots). When the external manifestations of thrombosis knots rectal suppositories are ineffective. The good effect of acute hemorrhoids gives a natural product such as «Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula». Locally thrombosed knots must be lubricated with ointments Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Hytone, Locoid Lipocream, Locoid, Westcort, that also helps to speed up the resorption process thrombosed clots. All the foregoing conservative therapy will surely give effect, it should be noted that in the conservative treatment process of resorption may take 1-1.5 months. After the complete disappearance of the phenomenon of acute hemorrhoids, on the site of the thrombosed knot almost always remains so-called fringe anal hemorrhoidal.It should be noted that in the future, at the same location, under the influence of any factor may again appear thrombosis node.</p>

<p>Now the information for those who do not like long to be treated. The most rapid and effective treatment of thrombosis, it is certainly a thrombectomy (forced removal of thrombus from the knot). Under anesthesia thrombosed clots are removed from the cut of up to 0.5 cm. Node decreases and the pain immediately stoped. The procedure takes about 1-2 minutes. At the site of thrombectomy wound remains (0.5 cm) that heals for an average of 4 days. In this case, the need for rectal suppositories, ointments, warm baths already not. However, it is recommended prophylactic course of Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula (1 month). After 15 minutes of thrombectomy and recommendations of the patient to go home. Ability to work after the procedure is not lost. Frequently offer remove thrombosed clots together with the node in this case addition to the rapid relief of pain is achieved cosmetic effect. Already at this point there is no thrombotic conditions, but in other places around the circumference of the anus can appear. Why? Because thrombectomy and removal of a thrombosed external hemorrhoid is not a radical operation.</p>

<p>In some cases, when exacerbation passes at available hemorrhoids II-IV stage, radical surgery is acceptable for time reasons. After this operation is a complete cure patients from hemorrhoidal disease and the appearance thrombosed external hemorrhoid of this place for many decades (may appear elsewhere). Risks and complications at radical surgery for time reasons do not exceed those for planned interventions.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to cure hemorrhoids. Hemorrhoid home treatment]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-cure-hemorrhoids-hemorrhoid-home-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-08T21:58:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-cure-hemorrhoids-hemorrhoid-home-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoid-home-treatment/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoid-home-treatment/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Hemorrhoid home treatment&rsquo; &lsquo;How to cure hemorrhoids. Hemorrhoid home treatment&rsquo;" > When we say the word &ldquo;hemorrhoid&rdquo;, many are experiencing negative, sometimes reaching up to phobias, feelings. However, this disease is not so bad, especially in the early stages. It occurs due to poor nutrition, physical inactivity and sedentary lifestyle. It may be provoke a heredity.</p>

<p>In order to answer the question of how to treat hemorrhoids, you need to give it a clear definition. Hemorrhoids are vascular cavernous body. These are formed in the rectum (in the lower part). Nodes can be internal or external. Simultaneously, at the patient may be present both species, in this case will help only complex treatment.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Characteristically reluctance of a large number of patients to see a doctor in the early stages of this disease. They do not ask how to cure hemorrhoids and how to pick a remedy for hemorrhoids, even experiencing pain and discomfort. However, the need to go to a specialist as soon as possible. It is better to hemorrhoid home treatment, than to resort to complex surgery, which in some cases does not bring the proper favor and alleviate suffering.</p>

<p>There are four stages of this disease:</p>

<ol>
<li>The formation hemorrhoid nodes inside the rectum (internal hemorrhoids);</li>
<li>There is a loss of nodes of the rectum after a bowel movement, they themselves reduce a back;</li>
<li>The nodes do not reduce a own but it can still be done with your fingers;</li>
<li>Impossible to reduce fallen nodes (external hemorrhoids).</li>
</ol>


<p>Effective hemorrhoid home treatment is possible only on the first and second stages. On the third and fourth often have to resort to surgery.</p>

<p>In spite of the obvious symptoms of many ill in no hurry to seek medical help. They will not go to the doctor, as a result, they develop hemorrhoids third and fourth stage. For some reason, some people think hemorrhoids are something shameful. They hide their illness from others. This trend is not exclusive to the United States, but also in many European countries. However it is better to learn from experts how to treat hemorrhoids, rather than later hospital treatment needed or, worse, in the outpatient and dispensary observation.</p>

<p>Today, a large amount of useful information on how to cure hemorrhoids, can also find on the Internet. In a network there are enough sites on which there is information about the problem of the disease, the mechanisms of its development, prevention methods and hemorrhoid home treatment.</p>

<h2>How to treat hemorrhoids. The main methods</h2>

<ol>
<li>Non-medical impact. Effective only in the early stages, is to change the lifestyle and diet, increasing physical activity.</li>
<li>Drug therapeutic impact.</li>
<li>Reducing the pressure in the anal canal (the means for doing so are drug «Venapro» and ointments such as Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Locoid etc.).</li>
<li>Non-surgical methods of influence.</li>
<li>Surgical treatment.</li>
</ol>


<p>In the early stages of the disease and as a prophylactic course after surgical treatment is <strong>very effective natural product «Venapro»</strong>.</p>

<p>Identify hemorrhoids simply by the following symptoms:
&ndash; Bleeding during bowel movements, blood in faeces.
&ndash; The occurrence of burning and itching in the anal area.
&ndash; Pain when sitting, walking, bowel movements.
&ndash; The emergence of a sense of gravity or presence of a foreign body in the rectum.
&ndash; Inflammation of hemorrhoid nodes. They be palpated, this gives rise to pain.
&ndash; Occurs loss of nodes of the rectum.</p>

<p>It should, as soon as possible, seek medical attention if these symptoms.</p>

<h2>Hemorrhoid home treatment. Traditional methods</h2>

<p>The use drug treatment is usually only gives a relief of symptoms of the disease in the third and fourth stages. To effectively deal with hemorrhoids, you need to use an integrated approach.</p>

<p>Modern medicine offers to hemorrhoid home treatment is not only tablets but also in other ways. In the early stages helps to get rid of the pain and reduce inflammation of the nodes special diet. Of the food exclude alcohol, spicy and fatty foods, condiments and spices. A diet enriched with plant-based diet high fiber content. Recommended for early hemorrhoids long walks, special exercises, including squats, press load, tilts, etc. It is necessary to make a thorough hygiene of the anus after defecation.</p>

<p>However, the disease exacerbation of those measures will not be enough. In the acute form of hemorrhoid home treatment will require the use of anal suppositories, ointments, and cold lotions. When it is impossible to stop the periodic occurrence of venous bleedings knots injected sclerosing solutions.</p>

<p>By resorting to surgery only in cases where there are prolonged and severe bleeding, constantly drop nodes, at a jamming. All the same any form of treatment is useless if you do not aimed at removing underlying causes of the disease. They only temporarily make easier the patient&rsquo;s condition, reduce pain and symptoms.</p>

<p>In the complex treatment of hemorrhoids is to include products «Venapro &ndash; Hemorrhoid formula». It is especially effective in the early stages of the disease.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thrombosed hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/thrombosed-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-08T21:56:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/thrombosed-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-hemorrhoids/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-hemorrhoids/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Thrombosed hemorrhoids&rsquo; &lsquo;Thrombosed hemorrhoids&rsquo;" > Thrombosed hemorrhoids usually occurs when you straining during bowel movements due to swelling of the dropped out nodes. Sphincter of the rectum spasm  increases the swelling, leads to stagnation of blood in the lower rectal plexus and thrombosed of external hemorrhoids. The patient complained of pain, swelling, discharge from the rectum with an unpleasant odor and difficulties at defecation. At survey are determined dropped out not reduce a edematous internal hemorrhoids, often with fibrinous coating.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>In 70-80% of cases,  complicated by inflammation of the transition to subcutaneous tissue and the anal area. In this case drugs are being used in combination with a water soluble ointments having potent anti-inflammatory action. These include Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Hytone, Locoid Lipocream, Locoid, Westcort.</p>

<p>In acute hemorrhoids and the early stages of chronic hemorrhoids hold conservative treatment. Its main purpose &ndash; relieve pain and inflammation, normalize blood circulation in the rectal area, adjust the digestion. Thrombosed hemorrhoids is an indication for the use of anticoagulants local action. This group of medications include ointments Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Hytone, Locoid Lipocream, Locoid, Westcort. As a preparation for the topical treatment of hemorrhoids established itself particularly Anusol HC. As an agent for the prevention and treatment of hemorrhoids of its in the early stages established itself a natural product Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula. Each component of the drug exerts its beneficial effects in thrombosed hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>Conservative treatment is common: increasing venous tone tablets, improve blood flow in small vessels and cavernous veins (for example Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula); and local: wound healing, pain relievers and antipruritic ointments, suppositories, microclysters and baths. At the same time is appointed antihemorrhoidal diet: vegetables, fruits, bran, and that&rsquo;s about spices, spicy food and alcohol have to forget.</p>

<p>In surgical treatment under local anesthesia, produce diaplasis dropped nodes, and then perform ligation of the internal nodes latex rings and thrombectomy of the radial incisions at accompanying acute thrombosis of external hemorrhoids. The intervention is performed on an outpatient basis. Short-and long-term results are good. Thrombosis, complicated hemorrhoids stage IV requires urgent hemorrhoidectomy.</p>

<p>Thrombectomy &ndash; removal of thrombus (venous blood clot). Thrombectomy represents a thrombosed node dissection and removal of a blood clot. Thrombectomy is assigned to the nodes are large and cause severe discomfort to the patient, and conservative therapy is ineffective or may take too time. This procedure does not require hospitalization. After thrombectomy is rapid a relief, hemorrhoid, after a while, collapses.
Excision of external hemorrhoid: a procedure which can eliminate the root cause of thrombosis &ndash; an external hemorrhoid. This is the most effective method for the treatment of external thrombosed hemorrhoids, as it allows get rid in a subsequent of the recurring exacerbations. Excision of the outdoor knot assigned when acute thrombosis, when conservative therapy is ineffective, or thrombosed knot brings strong discomfort. In most cases this procedure is performed on an outpatient basis under local anesthesia and does not require hospitalization. Excision of external hemorrhoid can be done with a scalpel conventional or a high-frequency electro-scalpel.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The effectiveness of the hemorrhoid creams proven practices]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/the-effectiveness-of-the-hemorrhoid-creams-proven-practices/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-07T23:53:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/the-effectiveness-of-the-hemorrhoid-creams-proven-practices</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoid-creams/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoid-creams/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Hemorrhoid creams&rsquo; &lsquo;The effectiveness of the hemorrhoid creams proven practices&rsquo;" > In the hemorrhoid treatment efficient are not only suppositories and ointment, creams but also.  The basic doctors precept in the hemorrhoids treatment is precisely the use of these drug form.</p>

<p>The superiority of the <strong>hemorrhoid creams</strong> to the ointment lies in the fact that it is more easily absorbed and short term relieves symptoms such as itching, burning and pain. In addition, the creams can also have long-term effect: relieve inflammation, restore the elasticity of blood vessels, eliminates congestion, tone up your rectum, have a cosmetic effect, heal anus wounds and cracks, have antibacterial properties and hemostatic.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>The advantage of hemorrhoid creams before rectal suppositories is that with external hemorrhoids suppositories is not effective, while an internal hemorrhoid they penetrate too deep into the rectum and does not facilitate patient suffering. But creams often are effective for external and internal hemorrhoids, removing the symptoms and eliminating the cause of the disease. They help in the treatment of anal fissures and the lower portion of the rectum, anal itching eliminate, and erosive changes in the structure of organs and tissues.</p>

<p>Nitroglycerin-based cream is used to relieve pain from hemorrhoids and relieves spasm of the sphincter.</p>

<p>The structure of the <strong>hemorrhoid creams</strong> typically include substances such as petroleum jelly, beeswax, purified sulfur, lanolin, extracts of raspberry, chestnut, oak bark, black poplar, essential oils of lemon and cypress. Also there may be present alcohols, organic acids, vitamins. These drugs provide short-term local anesthesia. Some components have astringent properties to help stop bleeding. Essential oils and plant extracts prevent complications, strengthen blood vessels walls, reduce hemorrhoids, facilitate defecation. This component as phenylephrine hydrochloride, promotes constrict blood vessels of the anus, the normalization of blood circulation, relieves swelling, eliminates the presence of serous discharge, effectively treats itching, reduces the production of exudate. Have a softening effect and other vegetable oils &ndash; such as corn, as well as mineral oil and glycerin.</p>

<p>Always together with creams should take the drug Venapro, which greatly enhances the effectiveness of treatment. Venapro also should be taken as a prevention for some time after recovery (preferably drink away monthly course of medication), as well as people who are prone to hemorrhoidal disease (sedentary lifestyle, heredity, etc.).</p>

<p>Hemorrhoid creams may have some contraindications. Thus, their use is not recommended for people who have an increased sensitivity to drug components, to children under the age of 12 years, as well as the propensity to thromboembolism and granulocytopenia (drugs often lead to an increase in blood clotting). The cream can cause a side effects such as dermatitis and allergic reactions.</p>

<p>Not recommended to use hemorrhoid creams patients who are taking medications such groups as antidepressants, antihypertensive drugs, monoamine oxidase inhibitors. In such situations, the appointment is only possible under strict medical indications. Pregnant and lactating women appoint hemorrhoid creams is only entitled to an experienced and qualified specialist this area. Use of the drug in such cases should be maximum careful to avoid the possibility of putting even a the slightest harm to the child or fetus.</p>

<p>As a rule, cream is used in the morning and evening, and after defecation. However, it should be remembered that it is not recommended to use the drug more than four times a day. Before applying the medication necessary to fulfill the hygienic cleansing of corresponding area. The cream is applied on the area around the anus and into the anus. The approximate duration of treatment &ndash; 1 week. If after this period to facilitate does not come, should urgently to see a specialist.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
