<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: proctology | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/proctology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-12-02T00:01:59+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surgical treatment of hemorrhoids: the cost of surgery to remove nodes]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/surgical-treatment-of-hemorrhoids-the-cost-of-surgery-to-remove-nodes/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:22:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/surgical-treatment-of-hemorrhoids-the-cost-of-surgery-to-remove-nodes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoids-surgery-cost/14.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoids-surgery-cost/14.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;hemorrhoids surgery cost&rsquo; &lsquo;Surgical treatment of hemorrhoids: the cost of surgery to remove nodes&rsquo;" > If a man appeared for the first time in the life of hemorrhoids, he usually tries to take all measures to get rid of the unpleasant symptoms. If the patient in time refers to the proctologist, complaining of discomfort during bowel movements, itching, cracking or bleeding from hemorrhoids, you can quickly get rid of the early stages. However, the disease often becomes extremely sleazy. Almost all patients go to the doctor already after conservative treatment of hemorrhoids is no longer effective. In this case, the doctor carefully examines the patient and determines the future strategy of the treatment of the disease. Often, the final stage of this process is the surgical treatment of hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>If doctors detect external hemorrhoids requiring mechanical removal, to begin the patient is usually prescribed minimally invasive techniques that do not require surgical intervention. However, they are not suitable for all patients, so a large percentage of people suffering from hemorrhoids, gets on the operating table.</p>

<p>Do I need surgery if you have hemorrhoids? As mentioned above, the doctors try to minimize the chances of radical treatments. If there is a chance to eliminate the disease conservative or non-surgical method, the doctor uses all techniques that can have an effect. Most often, the operation shall be appointed, if a person is present hemorrhoids grade 3 complications. If the disease is the first or second step, the patient may help non-surgical hemorrhoid sclerotherapy.</p>

<h2>How do the surgery and what to choose?</h2>

<p>Today in medicine there are two main types of surgery to remove hemorrhoids. First &ndash; this is a hemorrhoidectomy for Milligan-Morgan. Second &ndash; gemorroidopeksiya by Longo. Longo operation differs from the operation of Milligan-Morgan. With this procedure, the hosts themselves are not deleted, but removes part of the rectum. By removing a portion of mucosal blood flow is disturbed nodes, whereupon they atrophy. The intervention on the Milligan-Morgan exterior and interior nodes are excised and then sewn sutures.</p>

<p>How much surgery? Data close to the end of the article. On the appropriateness of the procedure you can tell your doctor. As for the criteria for the appointment of each of the types of intervention, they can be represented as a simple table.</p>

<h2>Do I need to prepare?</h2>

<p>Preparation for surgery is performed in both cases. Both types of procedures performed in a hospital, so patients necessarily prepared for anesthesia and the surgery in advance. Hemorrhoidectomy and operation Longo require prior hospitalization. As for anesthesia, then the operation can Longo local anesthesia, although most often it is performed under general intravenous anesthesia. Hemorrhoidectomy for Milligan-Morgan performed only under intravenous anesthesia. Also, the patient can make epidural anesthesia. Local anesthesia is hardly found. Preparing for Surgery Hemorrhoids usually are not too durable, but you can not avoid this step.</p>

<h2>How long is the surgery?</h2>

<p>Another criterion &ndash; the duration of the procedure. The operation to Milligan-Morgan takes about half an hour, and the operation Longo lasts no more than twenty minutes. Tolerated both procedures are equally good, but after the surgery the patient requires medical supervision. Treatment after surgery includes preventive tools for toning the veins.</p>

<h2>Stay in a hospital</h2>

<p>After the surgery, the patient remains Longo in hospital under observation for 2-3 days. When hemorrhoidectomy hospital stay may increase up to a week. Deserve special attention, patients who develop complications of thrombosed hemorrhoids: surgery in this case should only start after the relief of the inflammatory process. Do not put the patient on the operating table during an exacerbation. It should be noted that the cost of surgery to remove hemorrhoids almost never include the cost of hospital stays. If you are being treated at a private clinic, check in advance how much are the day following hospital treatment.</p>

<h2>Terms of rehabilitation</h2>

<p>In contrast to the non-invasive techniques, after which the patient can go to work the next day, after surgical treatment of hemorrhoids patient must comply with bed rest to a week. Temporary disability after intervention by Milligan-Morgan can reach months, and after the operation is issued weekly Longo hospital.</p>

<h2>Pain</h2>

<p>How to be a painful operation? This question is asked all the patients who were prescribed surgical excision or removal of nodes of the rectal mucosa. According to experts, in operation Longo pain is negligible. In the case of the operation for Milligan-Morgan pain observed in the postoperative period in almost all patients. This procedure is a significant drawback, however, this does not diminish its effectiveness. While the patient is in the hospital, doctors removed the pain with the help of powerful analgesics. Absolutely painless surgical removal of hemorrhoids does not exist. The only option &ndash; a minimally invasive procedure. With their help, you will get a low-cost and rapid treatment of hemorrhoids &ndash; the prices of these procedures are low. However, many advanced cases surgery is the only curative treatment of the disease.</p>

<p>It should be noted also that the operation Longo is assigned only when an internal hemorrhoid. If you are running outside or combined hemorrhoids, then applied to eliminate the disease hemorrhoidectomy by Milligan-Morgan.</p>

<h2>Contra</h2>

<p>Advantage Longo operation is that it is practically no contraindications. It is quite easy to carry, even if the patient is suffering from a serious illness. With this method it is possible to eliminate even postpartum hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>As for the Milligan-Morgan, then to her, there are a range of contraindications. Among them are the following:</p>

<ul>
<li>HIV;</li>
<li>Crohn&rsquo;s Disease;</li>
<li>Pregnancy and lactation</li>
<li>Cancer;</li>
<li>The aggravation of chronic diseases;</li>
<li>Acute inflammation in the body.</li>
</ul>


<h2>How much is hemorrhoid surgery?</h2>

<p>Both methods require a certain investment, but the Milligan-Morgan different low cost, unlike the method Longo, since the latter requires expensive equipment surgeons.</p>

<p>The average price for an operation to remove hemorrhoids is:</p>

<ul>
<li>The method of Longo &ndash; the cost of surgery is about $ 1,200;</li>
<li>The method of Milligan-Morgan &ndash; 650 &ndash; $ 800</li>
</ul>


<h2>Complications</h2>

<p>As with any surgical procedure, surgery to treat hemorrhoids can be followed by subsequent complications. The most common complications</p>

<ul>
<li>Bleeding</li>
<li>Rectal and vaginal fistula</li>
<li>An infectious infestation of the affected tissues</li>
<li>An inflammatory process</li>
</ul>


<p>Doctors tend to avoid complications, and for which there is a post-operative hospital.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suppository for Hemorrhoids - what is best for treatment?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/suppository-for-hemorrhoids-what-is-best-for-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:21:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/suppository-for-hemorrhoids-what-is-best-for-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/suppository-for-hemorrhoids/13.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/suppository-for-hemorrhoids/13.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Suppository for hemorrhoids&rsquo; &lsquo;Suppository for Hemorrhoids &ndash; what is best for treatment?&rsquo;" > Suppository from hemorrhoids are a conservative method of getting rid of the disease. Therefore, they can not always be used in the treatment of this disease. Apply suppository should be started only after having been accurately diagnosed. In this paper we describe in general what the existing market more efficient suppository, how best to use them, by treating the condition. To know the specific list of suppository for hemorrhoids with a description of their properties and recommendations &ndash; click on a link (you can open a new tab if you first want to finish reading this article).</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>It is important to understand &ndash; to the question &ldquo;what is better spark&rdquo; in a particular case, the answer can only be a specialist conducting the diagnosis of your condition. In drugstores are very different &ndash; they differ among themselves on the nature of the action. Some are designed to reduce the pain that causes the disease. Other suppositories have a healing effect. This means that these suppository for hemorrhoids help wounds heal faster and existing cracks in the rectum and anus. Still others &ndash; these are the best suppository for hemorrhoids bleeding. They are able to stop the flow of blood for couples of improving its clotting.</p>

<h2>What are the suppository from hemorrhoids to choose?</h2>

<p>Sold suppository for hemorrhoids and fissures, from internal and external forms of the disease vary in price. But this is often an indication that cheap suppository worse than their more expensive counterparts. Usually cures for hemorrhoids local production cost less than importations, imported. Price consists of several parameters. In the case of foreign drugs, their price increases due to shipping costs, customs duties, and so on</p>

<p>What suppository for hemorrhoids, you choose yourself. It all depends on your financial capabilities. Somebody&rsquo;s power to obtain the most effective suppository imported at a high enough price. And someone can buy only cheap, chinese.</p>

<h2>What are the suppository and their composition?</h2>

<p>Pain suppository with hemorrhoids. Their main purpose is to reduce the pain that causes the disease of the rectum. They consist of novocaine or anestezina. These chemical elements are very well remove all the existing discomfort, itching and pain. However, the use of anesthetics has a number of contraindications. First, they are very much increase blood pressure. Therefore, these suppository can not be used in the treatment of patients with hypertension disease. Also avoid the use of suppositories in the elderly, when increased pressure is normal because of age-related changes in the human body.
Hemostatic suppository. The composition of these suppository are such components as Dicynone, menadione, calcium chloride. All of these chemical elements increase blood clotting. This is a very important fact in the treatment of bleeding hemorrhoids. Blood loss, if not stop, can cause anemia. This disease is not only dangerous to human health, but also for his life.
Anti-hemorrhoids suppository. The composition of the suppository includes various components which have a bactericidal effect. The best preparations of this group contain sea buckthorn oil. It not only helps speed the healing of wounds and fractures in the rectum and anus, but also kills bacteria, germs and other microorganisms that caused the inflammation. Have a similar effect and such components of vegetable appointment as propolis, tea tree oil, an extract of St. John&rsquo;s wort, yarrow, and so on</p>

<h2>Suppository for hemorrhoids treatment &ndash; how to use?</h2>

<p>Of course, suppository today are effective in the treatment of the disease, along with pills. However, even the best of them will not have the desired effect if they are not properly used. It is important to know what you need suppository, how to insert them when it is best to carry out medical procedures and how many times.</p>

<p>Suppository for hemorrhoids need to put in the evening before you are going to go to bed. Well, if the procedure before you empty the bowel. After the act of defecation is necessary to make water treatments. The anal opening must be clean prior to treatment. The suppository is necessary to open and remove the protective cover. This should be done as early as fully finished state, so you can directly enter into the anus of a candle. Otherwise, it will start to melt. After the candle was introduced into the rectum, you should immediately lie down on your back and lie down so at least thirty minutes. This is usually sufficient to ensure that the drug has melted and fell into the bloodstream. More specific nuances about the use of suppository for hemorrhoids can be read in the instructions that came with a particular drug.</p>

<p>Recommend suppository may only your doctor who knows the specific features of the disease. Even if you have a whole list of these drugs, it does not guarantee that they will help you. Only your doctor is aware of your particular state of diseases of the rectum and can choose the right treatment.</p>

<p>Hemorrhoid Treatment folk remedies possible. But any recipe before you start using it, must be approved by your doctor. Most methods of folk medicine used in combination with traditional therapies, help accelerate recovery person.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Constipation and hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/constipation-and-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:20:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/constipation-and-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoids-and-constipation/12.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoids-and-constipation/12.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Hemorrhoids and constipation&rsquo; &lsquo;Constipation and hemorrhoids&rsquo;" > Chronic constipation and hemorrhoids, is the most frequent combination, and related hemorrhoids condition. Sometimes impossible to determine the priority of hemorrhoids and constipation secondary and vice versa. Hemorrhoids without constipation is rare, while those suffering from chronic constipation, almost without exception, noted bleeding during bowel movements, pain, itching in the anus and in the long history, prolapsed hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>If the hemorrhoids in a certain number of cases can occur quite early in young adults (usually a family history of hereditary), the constipation often develop later in connection with chronic jetlag nutrition and diets desired composition.
Constipation greatly exacerbate the development of hemorrhoids, accelerate the emergence of its clinical manifestations. The complaints are typical of hemorrhoids, there are patients, usually after a period of difficulty chair, and one of the biggest complaints &ndash; constipation themselves. Thus, the struggle with constipation at any stage of manifestation of hemorrhoids and even before any of its manifestations in patients with identified during routine inspections hemorrhoid symptoms (asymptomatic stage) is the most important conservative measure of prevention and treatment of this disease.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, some of the doctors to whom falls sick hemorrhoids, do not pay sufficient attention to the treatment of constipation in this population, which largely negates the efforts of conservative therapy and have a negative impact on the outcomes of operations for hemorrhoids. With all of the many facilities offered by the treatment of hemorrhoids, including the application of sclerosing injections and surgical interventions, relapse is likely unless the patient will or encounter constipation. So treat constipation in patients with hemorrhoids is necessary, regardless of the underlying cause.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First aid for hemorrhoids and its exacerbation or bleeding]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/first-aid-for-hemorrhoids-and-its-exacerbation-or-bleeding/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:19:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/first-aid-for-hemorrhoids-and-its-exacerbation-or-bleeding</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-help-hemorrhoids/11.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/how-to-help-hemorrhoids/11.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;How to help hemorrhoids&rsquo; &lsquo;First aid for hemorrhoids and its exacerbation or bleeding&rsquo;" > Normally the development of hemorrhoids is gradual, but there are cases when the disease suddenly catches. The aggravation of hemorrhoids, accompanied by bleeding, may be triggered by excessive physical work and heavy lifting, often &ndash; poor diet and processes such as childbirth in women. In such cases, first aid for hemorrhoids need no less than any other disease.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Bleeding, sharp pain in the anus, stool problems, constipation &ndash; all manifestations of an exacerbation of the disease. Typically, the cause of bleeding is hard stool that their sharp edges damage pile. After the damage of blood hemorrhoids and is accompanied by a sharp pain, itching.</p>

<h2>First Aid with acute hemorrhoids &ndash; what to do</h2>

<p>Despite the fact that in most cases with acute hemorrhoids is no serious threat to the organism does not occur at the sight of blood patients begin to panic and often exacerbate the situation by their own actions. Also not to be confused with hemorrhoids prolapse of the rectum.</p>

<p>Here are the basic steps for first aid in case of aggravation of hemorrhoids:</p>

<ul>
<li>Remain calm and do not in any way straining with constipation, try to get rid of the remnants of feces. This way, you can avoid additional damage and reduce the bleeding sites.</li>
<li>Change the position of the body of standing or sitting on the escalation try to lie more &ldquo;face up&rdquo; by removing the stress on the muscles of the anus.</li>
<li>To avoid getting an infection in the body &ndash; most often use the bath with cool (room temperature) water. On the road or on a business trip or cleaning the help cool off. It will also reduce the pain manifestations.</li>
<li>Make an enema &ndash; it will download the intestines and promotes the healing of wounds aggravated.</li>
<li>Immediate start a diet, eating prunes and fiber, the exclusion from the diet of &ldquo;heavy&rdquo; foods, alcohol and starchy foods will lead to the fact that the next time the process of defecation is not constipation, hemorrhoids will not be damaged and begin to heal.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Folk remedies to help</h2>

<p>Since the constant aggravation help coming stool, damaged areas simply do not have time to heal, then in such cases it is recommended to use special herbal teas. For example, the infusion of herbs pochechuynoy has a strong laxative and hemostatic effect.</p>

<p>Will be able to help with bleeding following extracts: yarrow, cranberry bark, bloodroot goose. It is also recommended to take sea buckthorn oil. Use oil can be both inside and outside. Lubrication of the anus, and the use of enemas with oils will help reduce pain, heal hemorrhoids.</p>

<h2>Surgical treatment of acute hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>The first and most necessary condition for successful treatment &ndash; a distinction hemorrhoids from rectal prolapse. At home, perform this procedure, you can not do, so you should consult a doctor in the shortest possible time. During the examination, the doctor will determine the state of the anal area, and the presence of hemorrhoids dropped.</p>

<p>Following the procedure of collecting the necessary data, the doctor will prescribe a treatment. In cases where conservative treatment is ineffective, surgical intervention. The goal of this therapy will be to excision of hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>Even this operation can not always guarantee 100% results. It all depends on the many features of the disease. In this case, complications may give the late stages of developing hemorrhoids, pathological features of the structure of the rectum and anus.</p>

<h2>Treatment of bleeding hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>The main symptom of hemorrhoids &ndash; a bright red color of blood. Color blood indicates that the blood flows from the injured arteries. To stop the bleeding often use enemas.</p>

<p>Enemas sodium tannin promote partial coagulation of proteins and form a protective film. Due to this, there is a reduction of pain and narrowed blood vessels of the rectum. Also possible enema 3% hydrogen peroxide. The time an enema is 2 &ndash; 3 days.</p>

<p>In the event of prolonged bleeding continued urgent need to see a doctor who will prescribe the necessary examination.</p>

<h2>Lifestyle hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Hemorrhoids &ndash; this is not a death sentence. When the first symptoms of the disease is urgently think about changing lifestyles. Very often acute hemorrhoids catches people pursuing &ldquo;sedentary&rdquo; lifestyle. Under these conditions increases the risk of congestion in the rectal area. Avoid similar situations and bleeding will help: swimming, running, frequent walking, dancing.</p>

<p>Do not neglect the rules of personal hygiene. When hemorrhoids after each toilet visit, it is recommended to wash the perineum with cool water. The use of toilet paper may enhance the already strong pain.</p>

<p>It is also worth diet. In the treatment of hemorrhoids is necessary to settle a chair, because it should not be hard. It is recommended to eat fruits and vegetables that contain a sufficient amount of fiber. Dietary fiber in this case will help to improve the formation of stools. It is necessary to limit the use of sharp and salty foods.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which specialist to seek help with hemorrhoids?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/which-specialist-to-seek-help-with-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-13T21:18:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/which-specialist-to-seek-help-with-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoids-specialist/10.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoids-specialist/10.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Hemorrhoids specialist&rsquo; &lsquo;Which specialist to seek help with hemorrhoids?&rsquo;" > Presumably, you have hemorrhoids: which doctor to go? How can he be able to help you? Consider these questions in this section. It happens that people like and would love to go to a medical professional, but to what exactly &ndash; do not know&hellip; It complexes: ask for advice from someone ashamed and bear &ndash; strength is not enough. It is a vicious circle, a chain which we now will help you break!</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>If you want to help was the most complete, you&rsquo;ll like this doctor: treating hemorrhoids quickly and at a professional level that it has experience in this specialization. And, most importantly, who is not ashamed to apply, since for him the disease from the category of ordinary! As many have already guessed, this is a proctologist.</p>

<p>It coloproctologist treats hemorrhoids any stage. He examines, if necessary, appoint additional surveys, analyzing the situation, and eventually prescribe effective treatment.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
