<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: proctology | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com//categories/proctology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-18T17:04:04+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meaning barium enema in the diagnosis of diseases of the large intestine]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/meaning-barium-enema-in-the-diagnosis-of-diseases-of-the-large-intestine/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-22T23:56:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/meaning-barium-enema-in-the-diagnosis-of-diseases-of-the-large-intestine</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="/images/meaning-barium-enema-in-the-diagnosis-of-diseases-of-the-large-intestine/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Barium enema, bowel, barium sulfate, X-rays, contrast, disease, Crohn&rsquo;s colitis, tumor, polyp&rsquo; &lsquo;Meaning barium enema in the diagnosis of diseases of the large intestine&rsquo;" >Irrigoscopy &ndash; one of radiological methods of investigation of the colon using a radiopaque substance. Barium enema is performed after the introduction into the rectum of barium sulfate (contrast material) or barium suspension in combination with air (double contrast method).</p>

<p>Double contrast reveals the small size of the tumor, particularly polyps and mucosal changes that occur in the early stages of inflammatory diseases of the large intestine.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>With the barium enema can be visualized colon almost an entire length, but for the most effective research rectosigmoid zone applies sigmoidoscopy.</p>

<p>Irrigoscopy not performed after radiographic contrast studies of the upper gastrointestinal tract. Used with barium is excreted within a few days, and the remnants of this substance may distort the results irrigoscopy.</p>

<h2>The information that can be accessed by barium enema</h2>

<p>During the barium enema doctor receives the following information about the patient&rsquo;s colon:</p>

<ul>
<li>The location, shape and diameter of the colon;</li>
<li>The degree of extensibility and flexibility of the intestinal wall;</li>
<li>Define the function bauginievoy flap. Bauginievaya flap &ndash; is a fold, which is located between the ileum and colon. Normally bauginievaya damper must pass the intestinal contents in only one direction (from the small intestine into the large), but there may be a violation of the intestinal contents throw in the opposite direction. Movement in contrast barium enema shows clearly whether there are irregularities in the bauginievoy flap;</li>
<li>Relief mucosa of the colon walls. This indicator is particularly important in the diagnosis of ulcerative lesions of the bowel, fistulas, tumors, diverticulosis, scars and congenital malformations;</li>
<li>Functional state departments of large intestine.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Why is it important to conduct irrigoscopy?</h2>

<p>As a rule, barium enema is used to confirm the diagnosis in suspected those or other diseases of the colon. Barium enema is often decisive diagnostic method for tumors and colon diverticula.</p>

<p>During the barium enema using the technique of double -contrast study diagnostic capabilities are significantly increased. With barium enema can indirectly confirm the presence of diseases such as colitis and tuberculosis.</p>

<h2>Which diseases carried irrigoscopy?</h2>

<p>When irrigoscopy estimated rate of change of the intestinal mucosa in ulcerative colitis, Crohn&rsquo;s disease, as well as visualized tumors, fistulas, malformations and diverticula.</p>

<p>Unlike colonoscopy, barium enema and less traumatic and less likely to cause complications. Furthermore, barium enema is possible to investigate with the &ldquo;blind&rdquo; to the field of colonoscopy, for example, portions in the folds of the mucosa, and also bends in the colon and the sigmoid colon.</p>

<p>Application irrigoscopy shown if the patient following symptoms:</p>

<ul>
<li>Bleeding from the rectum;</li>
<li>Mucous or purulent discharge from the intestines;</li>
<li>Pain in the anus and in the course of the colon;</li>
<li>Chronic disorder stool (constipation or diarrhea).</li>
</ul>


<h2>How is barium enema?</h2>

<p>Barium enema is performed in a specially equipped medical facility office. A few days before the scheduled study patient should prepare for barium enema. Must be made within 3-4 days follow a special cleansing diet and the use of additional methods for bowel cleansing. This patient doctor tells in detail.</p>

<p>Before the study, the patient is laid down on the couch on its side. In the anus enema tip is introduced, which contains a radiopaque substance. In the future, under fluoroscopy intestines filled contrast agents and conduct a series of reviews and sighting shots in different positions of the patient.</p>

<p>After emptying of barium mixture is produced as air filling bowel under fluoroscopy. So can investigate the organic and functional disorders of the intestinal wall.</p>

<p>Duration of the procedure is a few minutes. During double contrast examination may take 30 to 40 minutes.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Factors of hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/factors-of-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-15T00:03:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/factors-of-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="/images/factors-of-hemorrhoids/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;factors of hemorrhoids, causes of hemorrhoids, hemorrhoid treatment, proctology, Venapro&rsquo; &lsquo;Factors of Hemorrhoids&rsquo;" > <p data-jbox-image-white=""></p><p data-jbox-image=""></p>Hemorrhoids &ndash; an inflammatory disease that may affect the pathological expansion of hemorrhoidal veins and the formation of knots. According to medical statistics, hemorrhoids often occurs in people older than 45 years.</p>

<p>The exact cause of hemorrhoids is still not established. The main possible causes of the disease, modern medicine treats vascular pathology (dysfunction between the blood flow through the arteries and the flow of blood through the cavernous veins) and disruption of the muscular system, retaining hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Factors of hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Promote the development of hemorrhoids are many factors among which are:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>Genetic predisposition</strong>. Some people venous network in the anus has a very dense plexus, which complicates the flow of blood through the vessels. In case of violation of vascular permeability develops blood stagnation that contributes to the inflammatory process.</li>
<li><strong>Pregnancy and childbirth</strong>. During pregnancy the uterus increases in size, which leads to a displacement of the movable upward while the rectum is pressed against the pelvis. Thus, the clamped venous blood vessels, which leads to an overflow of the cavernous bodies.</li>
<li><strong>Physical inactivity</strong>. Sedentary lifestyle contributes to the development of venous insufficiency, in particular to the development of stagnation in the pelvic organs. Reduce the chance of developing hemorrhoids is possible if regularly moderate exercise.</li>
<li><strong>Failure to comply with the rules of hygiene</strong>. When excessive hygiene anus, as well as the use of low-quality toilet paper mucosa irritated anus, thereby increasing the probability of acute hemorrhoids.</li>
<li><strong>Bad habits</strong>. Smoking worsens the condition of vessels, including hemorrhoidal veins. Also, smoking increases the severity of bleeding. As for alcoholic beverages, the alcohol helps dilate blood vessels, which in turn leads to stagnation of blood in the hemorrhoids.</li>
<li><strong>Malnutrition</strong>. Excessive consumption of hot and spicy food, as well as lack of fiber is a significant negative factor in the development of inflammatory processes in the rectum.</li>
<li><strong>Chronic constipation</strong>. Disturbances of feces leads to frequent constipation. Solid stool, lingering in the intestines, put pressure on the choroid plexus of the rectum, thereby helping to expand the hemorrhoidal veins. Also promotes the development of hemorrhoids during defecation habit to push.</li>
<li><strong>Hypothermia</strong>. Hypothermia leads to circulatory problems that can cause the development of inflammation in the rectal area. In particular, avoid hypothermia lower body (not sit on a cold surface, dress appropriately to weather conditions).</li>
<li><strong>Physical activity</strong>. Excessive exercise (weightlifting, bodybuilding, etc.) is likely to disrupt the tone of the muscular apparatus of the anus. Muscle weakness contributes anus prolapsed hemorrhoid. Furthermore, physical overload cause delay of blood in the veins, which increases the likelihood of developing hemorrhoids.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Hemorrhoid Treatment</h2>

<p>Any disease is always easier to prevent than to cure. At elimination of negative factors likely to develop hemorrhoids is minimal. Even hereditary predisposition to hemorrhoids may not materialize if lead a healthy lifestyle and eat right.</p>

<p>If the hemorrhoids are still developed, it is necessary as soon as possible to begin treatment. Depending on severity of the disease may be used as a conservative and surgical treatment.</p>

<p>Medication hemorrhoids includes use of anti- inflammatory, analgesic and hemostatic (if bleeding) drugs.</p>

<p>The most effective use of local products in the form of rectal suppositories. One such drug is Venapro. This combination drug, which includes an anti-inflammatory bufexamac, wound healing agent and bismuth subgallate anesthetic lidocaine component.</p>

<p>Venapro hemorrhoids is useful for a 1-2 stages, as well as diseases such as proctologic anal fissure, proctitis, anal eczema and other.</p>

<p>Available <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7" onclick="banner = ban.venapro">Venapro</span> in rectal suppositories, which makes it very convenient to use. The likelihood of side effects from the drug is extremely low.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[He does not like hemorrhoids?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/he-does-not-like-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-02T23:05:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/he-does-not-like-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/he-does-not-like-hemorrhoids/0.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/he-does-not-like-hemorrhoids/0.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;aggravation, contraindication factor, hypothermia, lack of exercise, physical activity, dietary fiber&rsquo; &lsquo;He does not like hemorrhoids?&rsquo;" >Follow the advice of doctors and avoid the negative factors contributing to aggravate hemorrhoids.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Why do I get hemorrhoids?</h2>

<p>Doctors say that lately hemorrhoids much &ldquo;younger&rdquo;. Most likely, the reason for that are the negative factors contributing to the development of the disease with which modern man often encountered. These factors include:</p>

<ul>
<li>pregnancy and childbirth;</li>
<li>heredity;</li>
<li>sedentary lifestyle;</li>
<li>unhealthy diet;</li>
<li>poor hygiene;</li>
<li>hypothermia;</li>
<li>chronic gastrointestinal disorder;</li>
<li>excessive exercise.</li>
</ul>


<p>The combination of these factors leads to the development of pathological enlargement of hemorrhoidal veins and implementation of disease. At the first symptoms should immediately contact a doctor, mainly because hemorrhoids characterized by chronic course with periodic exacerbations. In order to reduce the appearance of the disease and minimize the likelihood of an exacerbation, the patient must be aware of what not to do with hemorrhoids. Especially effective prevention of hemorrhoids is the first stage of the disease when the disease symptoms have not yet pronounced.</p>

<h2>Contraindications for hemorrhoids</h2>

<p><strong>Food contraindications</strong></p>

<p>When hemorrhoids diet is very important. As a preventive measure, doctors recommend eating foods containing large amounts of fiber. Such food will reduce the number of exacerbations and the severity of hemorrhoids. When varicose veins hemorrhoids may want to limit the consumption of these foods and dishes:</p>

<ul>
<li>fried foods;</li>
<li>hot and spicy dishes, irritating;</li>
<li>semolina;</li>
<li>mashed potatoes;</li>
<li>eggs;</li>
<li>jelly;</li>
<li>alcohol;</li>
<li>black tea, coffee.</li>
</ul>


<p><strong>Hypodynamy</strong></p>

<p>Sedentary lifestyle contributes to stagnation in the pelvic organs, which only aggravates the disease. At risk are people who have to be for a long time without moving (office workers, drivers). Try as much as possible to do a little workout. On the way to and from work, try to walk more. And best of all to engage in moderate exercise regularly. Jogging, swimming, walking trails and many other kinds of physical activity will only benefit.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bleeding internal hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/bleeding-internal-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-30T07:07:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/bleeding-internal-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/bleeding-internal-hemorrhoids/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/bleeding-internal-hemorrhoids/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Bleeding internal hemorrhoids&rsquo; &lsquo;Bleeding internal hemorrhoids&rsquo;" > <p data-jbox-image-white=""></p><p data-jbox-image=""></p><strong>Hemorrhoids.</strong> One of the main symptoms of this disease is the hemorrhoidal bleeding.</p>

<p>Literature data of recent years have pointed out that the cause of hemorrhoids is a violation of the outflow of blood from the venules of the cavernous bodies, which are located in the wall of the rectum (the largest cluster of notes on 3-7-11 hours on the dial) and is a substrate haemorrhoid. <!-- more -->Therefore, if the wall of the cavernous bodies, which is filled with blood directly from the arterial bed is damaged, the stands out of scarlet, oxygen saturation arterial blood.</p>

<p>Bleeding at internal hemorrhoids characterized in that the blood volume, wherein is of a few drops to 100-200 ml per day and with frequent hemorrhage causes the development of anemia. In some cases, hemorrhage may be inkjet and pulsating.</p>

<p><strong>Diagnosis.</strong> Under gentle disclosure of the edges of the anus hemorrhoids are defined as swollen formations bluish color, soft-elastic consistency, covered with a mucous membrane. Necessarily carry out the finger, mirroring studies and sigmoidoscopy. Soft hemorrhoids are rarely detected by digital examination, but this study is an important method for the differential diagnosis. When the mirror examination may reveal the bleeding internal hemorrhoids.</p>

<p><strong>Treatment.</strong> We must remember that the causes of intestinal bleeding may be tumors (benign and malignant) of rectum and colon. Only after exclusion of these diseases should begin to targeted <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7" onclick="banner = ban.venapro">treatment of hemorrhoidal bleeding</span>.</p>

<p>In chronic hemorrhoids, which manifests itself only bleeding internal hemorrhoids without a loss of knots, in the absence of common anorectal thrombosis recommends a hemostatic therapy with Venapro. 10 percent calcium chloride, 5 percent solution of aminocaproic acid as well as with the use of adrenaline suppositories by recipe.</p>

<p>In the absence of contraindications is possible to use an injection of sclerosing agents.</p>

<p>Contraindications to this kind of treatment are diseases of the prostate and hypertension, in which if there is no severe anemia, such  bleeding is as would damping. At presence of infectious diseases, inflammatory changes in the walls of the anal canal and rectal mucosa injection of sclerosing agents is contraindicated. Relative contraindications for sclerotherapy are loss of internal hemorrhoids and frequent exacerbation of chronic hemorrhoids, because the presence of these complications are indications for surgical treatment.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[External hemorrhoid. Thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/external-hemorrhoid-thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-11T19:56:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/external-hemorrhoid-thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid-treatment/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid-treatment/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment&rsquo; &lsquo;External hemorrhoid. Thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment&rsquo;" > As the most common disease of the rectum, hemorrhoids can proceed in different forms. Depending on where the knots are located, allocate hemorrhoids external, internal and combined. All these forms are equally common, delivered to the patient a lot of discomfort.</p>

<p>The disease has been well studied, and in the modern medical literature contains enough information how to manifested the external hemorrhoids and how to treat this pathology.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Characteristic for external hemorrhoids is that the knots are located always outside around the anus and without exacerbation absolutely not bother man. They may have different sizes and formed by extending and hemorrhoidal plexus, which is normally located under the skin of the perineum near the anus.</p>

<p>What causes this disease? What are the symptoms it is manifested? And how to get rid of external hemorrhoids?</p>

<h2>What are the causes of external hemorrhoids?</h2>

<p>To the formation of external hemorrhoids predisposes congenital weakness of the venous wall, however protrude knots only under certain conditions:</p>

<p>If a person moves a little, but mostly sits or stands.
If there is a problem with a stools, trouble with constipation, and defecation is accompanied by long waiting or straining.
If a person is forced by type of activity to lift weights, or engaged in power sports.
If the patient&rsquo;s favorite food &ndash; meat dishes flavored with a good dose of hot spices and alcohol.
In women often arises external hemorrhoids during pregnancy and after birth, especially repeated.</p>

<p>Under the action of all these factors, overflow occurs veins of the pelvis and perineum of blood, that the weakness of the vein wall leads to its stretching and protrusion, that is, to the formation of knots, and can be formed as external hemorrhoids and the internal simultaneously.</p>

<h2>What are the symptoms external hemorrhoids?</h2>

<p>Often, the first symptoms of the disease appear even before the significant increase of knots:</p>

<p>Itching and discomfort in the anal area. If herewith to comb the skin, there arises yet irritation.
Traces of blood on the toilet paper. Bleedings is usually not characteristic for external hemorrhoids, especially if the knots of small size. But with their increasing dense stool can injure the skin with the release of a small amount of blood. In addition, when there are external hemorrhoids &ndash; bleeding at a defecation can arise from anal fissures, that often accompany this form of the disease.
In the event of aggravation, when the knots are inflamed, swell, appears one more symptom &ndash; the pain during stool, but in a calm state, with remission of this symptom is not.
And, of course, bumps around the anus, which can have different sizes, and which the patient gropes fingers.
As a rule, external hemorrhoids &ndash; symptoms which are not so are numerous &ndash; begins to disturb human at an exacerbation of the disease and in remission no specific complaints.</p>

<h2>Complications of external hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Sometimes external hemorrhoids can be complicated by thrombosis of the knot. In this case appears typical clinic with acute symptoms. Therefore thrombosed external hemorrhoids attributed to the acute forms of the disease.</p>

<p>Thrombosis unit develops through prolonged of stagnation of blood, which leads to its condensation and the thrombus formation. A blood clot inside knot expands causing severe pain, aggravated by movement, coughing, sneezing.</p>

<p>The knot itself with a bluish color, edematous, tense and sharply painful when touched.
Acute external hemorrhoids may be accompanied by inflammation. Then, on a background of intense pain in humans raises of temperature, and local redness of the skin appears around the knot, and soft tissue swelling.</p>

<p>If the inflammation extends to the subcutaneous tissue, then the redness and swelling captures all area of the perineum, and pains become more intense and felt not only in the knot itself, but also around it.</p>

<p>If in time and competently did not handle this situation, process may result in purulent paraproctitis or fistula adrectal formation. Therefore, thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment, especially with inflammation, should be initiated as early as possible.</p>

<p>The diagnosis of external hemorrhoids usually straightforward because the knots are located outside, and they can be seen even with a simple inspection of the anal area.</p>

<h2>Treatment of external hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment are usually directed to ensure that remove the inflammation in the knot and remove associated with it edema and pain. Used for this purpose are different anti-hemorrhoidal drugs.
External hemorrhoids treatment folk remedies can also be quite effective, but on condition that the knots are small, and no thrombosis.</p>

<p>In order to remedy to cure of external hemorrhoids had the desired action, it must be properly chosen according to with those processes that are taking place in the knot.</p>

<p>Local therapy can be carried out and candles and ointments. All modern anti-hemorrhoidal ointments and candles from external hemorrhoids include several components. First, there is some hormonal substance with powerful anti-inflammatory, anti-edematous and antipruritic effect. Secondly &ndash; a local anesthetic, which gives analgesic effect. And, thirdly, the component blood thinner and prevents thrombosis, or resorptional have already a blood clot. Most often, this substance is heparin.</p>

<p>Some suppositories and liniments contain other components, for example, accelerating the healing process and has an antibacterial effect. Simply apply ointment on the external knots, therefore preference is given it her rather than suppositories.</p>

<p>If there is no thrombosis of knot possibly external hemorrhoid treatment at home. Of folk remedies are used steam and hip baths, natural-based ointments and various lotions.
Hip baths can be done with cold water, with hot water and anti-inflammatory herbal concoctions (chamomile, calendula, series), propolis, garlic, onion skins. No less popular and such folk remedies for external hemorrhoids as steam baths onion and garlic, as well as bath with alum</p>

<p>If arises a thrombosed external hemorrhoid &ndash; treatment should be started immediately, and treat should only proctologist. Pursuing a self-medication, especially folk remedies, you can lose valuable time, that is fraught with serious consequences. Because any natural cure for external hemorrhoids acts more gently and not so fast as pharmaceuticals, and thrombosis knot, especially with inflammation, every minute counts.</p>

<p>In addition to local means when external hemorrhoid thrombosing &ndash; treatment may include the ingestion of non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs and and venotonic medications. In addition, there are anti-inflammatory drugs of natural origin, the ingredients of which are natural and have vegetable nature. One of these drugs &ndash; Venapro, is the most efficient of its kind. It includes witch hazel, horse chestnut, st.mary &rsquo;s thistle, krameria mapato, arnica montana, fluoride of lime. Furthermore that the drug very is effective against external hemorrhoids, especially in the early stages of the disease, its merits can be attributed more ease of use (available as tablets and spray), and the harmlessness of its components can take it during pregnancy and during breast-feeding her baby.</p>

<p>If the spent therapy when the patient&rsquo;s condition does not improve or, on the contrary is compounded resort to knot dissection and removal of the thrombus. It is therefore very important that the patient, who appeared thrombosed external hemorrhoid, treatment received under the supervision of a doctor. This allows enough time to apply radical measures and avoid serious consequences.</p>

<p>Generally, when in a patient is external hemorrhoids &ndash; treatment methods envisage only two approaches &ndash; conservative and surgical, with removal of external hemorrhoids is made in the case, when conservative measures fail, and the aggravation is saved practically constant.</p>

<p>Extra care must external hemorrhoids treatment during pregnancy, and in fact need to remove symptoms, and the child no harm. Therefore all means as medicinal as well as folk can recommend a doctor. This condition must respected in the event that, when there is external hemorrhoids after childbirth, and a woman is breastfeeding.</p>

<p>How to thrombosed external hemorrhoid treat once and for all? You can remove already formed knots. But if a person&rsquo;s life are all the precipitating factors, then after a time in another place will be new. So the main thing condition, which will help to prevent both internal and external hemorrhoids &ndash; is a lifestyle change and parting with the habits and the factors that lead to disease.</p>

<p>If you want to know what it looks like external hemorrhoids, on the our website has a page with photos of the disease. There you will see different pictures of external hemorrhoids. Some of them will help you understand what is uncomplicated external hemorrhoids and  photos of thrombosed and inflamed knots will provide insight on how to appear complications of the disease.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
