<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: proctology | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/proctology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-12-14T21:56:26+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[External hemorrhoid. Thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/external-hemorrhoid-thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-11T19:56:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/external-hemorrhoid-thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid-treatment/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid-treatment/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment&rsquo; &lsquo;External hemorrhoid. Thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment&rsquo;" > As the most common disease of the rectum, íemorrhoids can proceed in different forms. Depending on where the knots are located, allocate hemorrhoids external, internal and combined. All these forms are equally common, delivered to the patient a lot of discomfort.</p>

<p>The disease has been well studied, and in the modern medical literature contains enough information how to manifested the external hemorrhoids and how to treat this pathology.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Characteristic for external hemorrhoids is that the knots are located always outside around the anus and without exacerbation absolutely not bother man. They may have different sizes and formed by extending and hemorrhoidal plexus, which is normally located under the skin of the perineum near the anus.</p>

<p>What causes this disease? What are the symptoms it is manifested? And how to get rid of external hemorrhoids?</p>

<h2>What are the causes of external hemorrhoids?</h2>

<p>To the formation of external hemorrhoids predisposes congenital weakness of the venous wall, however protrude knots only under certain conditions:</p>

<p>If a person moves a little, but mostly sits or stands.
If there is a problem with a stools, trouble with constipation, and defecation is accompanied by long waiting or straining.
If a person is forced by type of activity to lift weights, or engaged in power sports.
If the patient&rsquo;s favorite food &ndash; meat dishes flavored with a good dose of hot spices and alcohol.
In women often arises external hemorrhoids during pregnancy and after birth, especially repeated.</p>

<p>Under the action of all these factors, overflow occurs veins of the pelvis and perineum of blood, that the weakness of the vein wall leads to its stretching and protrusion, that is, to the formation of knots, and can be formed as external hemorrhoids and the internal simultaneously.</p>

<h2>What are the symptoms external hemorrhoids?</h2>

<p>Often, the first symptoms of the disease appear even before the significant increase of knots:</p>

<p>Itching and discomfort in the anal area. If herewith to comb the skin, there arises yet irritation.
Traces of blood on the toilet paper. Bleedings is usually not characteristic for external hemorrhoids, especially if the knots of small size. But with their increasing dense stool can injure the skin with the release of a small amount of blood. In addition, when there are external hemorrhoids &ndash; bleeding at a defecation can arise from anal fissures, that often accompany this form of the disease.
In the event of aggravation, when the knots are inflamed, swell, appears one more symptom &ndash; the pain during stool, but in a calm state, with remission of this symptom is not.
And, of course, bumps around the anus, which can have different sizes, and which the patient gropes fingers.
As a rule, external hemorrhoids &ndash; symptoms which are not so are numerous &ndash; begins to disturb human at an exacerbation of the disease and in remission no specific complaints.</p>

<h2>Complications of external hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Sometimes external hemorrhoids can be complicated by thrombosis of the knot. In this case appears typical clinic with acute symptoms. Therefore thrombosed external hemorrhoids attributed to the acute forms of the disease.</p>

<p>Thrombosis unit develops through prolonged of stagnation of blood, which leads to its condensation and the thrombus formation. A blood clot inside knot expands causing severe pain, aggravated by movement, coughing, sneezing.</p>

<p>The knot itself with a bluish color, edematous, tense and sharply painful when touched.
Acute external hemorrhoids may be accompanied by inflammation. Then, on a background of intense pain in humans raises of temperature, and local redness of the skin appears around the knot, and soft tissue swelling.</p>

<p>If the inflammation extends to the subcutaneous tissue, then the redness and swelling captures all area of the perineum, and pains become more intense and felt not only in the knot itself, but also around it.</p>

<p>If in time and competently did not handle this situation, process may result in purulent paraproctitis or fistula adrectal formation. Therefore, thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment, especially with inflammation, should be initiated as early as possible.</p>

<p>The diagnosis of external hemorrhoids usually straightforward because the knots are located outside, and they can be seen even with a simple inspection of the anal area.</p>

<h2>Treatment of external hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Thrombosed external hemorrhoid treatment are usually directed to ensure that remove the inflammation in the knot and remove associated with it edema and pain. Used for this purpose are different anti-hemorrhoidal drugs.
External hemorrhoids treatment folk remedies can also be quite effective, but on condition that the knots are small, and no thrombosis.</p>

<p>In order to remedy to cure of external hemorrhoids had the desired action, it must be properly chosen according to with those processes that are taking place in the knot.</p>

<p>Local therapy can be carried out and candles and ointments. All modern anti-hemorrhoidal ointments and candles from external hemorrhoids include several components. First, there is some hormonal substance with powerful anti-inflammatory, anti-edematous and antipruritic effect. Secondly &ndash; a local anesthetic, which gives analgesic effect. And, thirdly, the component blood thinner and prevents thrombosis, or resorptional have already a blood clot. Most often, this substance is heparin.</p>

<p>Some suppositories and liniments contain other components, for example, accelerating the healing process and has an antibacterial effect. Simply apply ointment on the external knots, therefore preference is given it her rather than suppositories.</p>

<p>If there is no thrombosis of knot possibly external hemorrhoid treatment at home. Of folk remedies are used steam and hip baths, natural-based ointments and various lotions.
Hip baths can be done with cold water, with hot water and anti-inflammatory herbal concoctions (chamomile, calendula, series), propolis, garlic, onion skins. No less popular and such folk remedies for external hemorrhoids as steam baths onion and garlic, as well as bath with alum</p>

<p>If arises a thrombosed external hemorrhoid &ndash; treatment should be started immediately, and treat should only proctologist. Pursuing a self-medication, especially folk remedies, you can lose valuable time, that is fraught with serious consequences. Because any natural cure for external hemorrhoids acts more gently and not so fast as pharmaceuticals, and thrombosis knot, especially with inflammation, every minute counts.</p>

<p>In addition to local means when external hemorrhoid thrombosing &ndash; treatment may include the ingestion of non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs and and venotonic medications. In addition, there are anti-inflammatory drugs of natural origin, the ingredients of which are natural and have vegetable nature. One of these drugs &ndash; Venapro, is the most efficient of its kind. It includes witch hazel, horse chestnut, st.mary &rsquo;s thistle, krameria mapato, arnica montana, fluoride of lime. Furthermore that the drug very is effective against external hemorrhoids, especially in the early stages of the disease, its merits can be attributed more ease of use (available as tablets and spray), and the harmlessness of its components can take it during pregnancy and during breast-feeding her baby.</p>

<p>If the spent therapy when the patient&rsquo;s condition does not improve or, on the contrary is compounded resort to knot dissection and removal of the thrombus. It is therefore very important that the patient, who appeared thrombosed external hemorrhoid, treatment received under the supervision of a doctor. This allows enough time to apply radical measures and avoid serious consequences.</p>

<p>Generally, when in a patient is external hemorrhoids &ndash; treatment methods envisage only two approaches &ndash; conservative and surgical, with removal of external hemorrhoids is made in the case, when conservative measures fail, and the aggravation is saved practically constant.</p>

<p>Extra care must external hemorrhoids treatment during pregnancy, and in fact need to remove symptoms, and the child no harm. Therefore all means as medicinal as well as folk can recommend a doctor. This condition must respected in the event that, when there is external hemorrhoids after childbirth, and a woman is breastfeeding.</p>

<p>How to thrombosed external hemorrhoid treat once and for all? You can remove already formed knots. But if a person&rsquo;s life are all the precipitating factors, then after a time in another place will be new. So the main thing condition, which will help to prevent both internal and external hemorrhoids &ndash; is a lifestyle change and parting with the habits and the factors that lead to disease.</p>

<p>If you want to know what it looks like external hemorrhoids, on the our website has a page with photos of the disease. There you will see different pictures of external hemorrhoids. Some of them will help you understand what is uncomplicated external hemorrhoids and  photos of thrombosed and inflamed knots will provide insight on how to appear complications of the disease.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thrombosis - Thrombosed hemorrhoid]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/thrombosis-thrombosed-hemorrhoid/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-10T22:06:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/thrombosis-thrombosed-hemorrhoid</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-hemorrhoid/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-hemorrhoid/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Thrombosed hemorrhoid&rsquo; &lsquo;Thrombosis &ndash; Thrombosed hemorrhoid&rsquo;" > <strong>Thrombosed hemorrhoid</strong>, also called acute hemorrhoids &ndash; a disease which occurs in almost 10% of all adults. This is a problem that everyone knows, but prefer not to talk, because it&rsquo;s embarrassing. And meanwhile, it is the patients reluctance seeking medical attention leads to what the disease becomes chronic late stage.</p>

<p>The cause of the disease are blood clots of external or internal hemorrhoids that drop out. If you look, the blood clot is a hematoma near the anus, which brings a man a lot of inconvenience and pain.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Simultaneous thrombosis of external and internal nodes is fairly rare. It can spread to all anus around (in this case it is called the circular), or to be on only one side, covering the anus of a semicircle.</p>

<h2>Causes and symptoms of Thrombosed hemorrhoid</h2>

<p>Reasons for the formation of blood clots in hemorrhoids diverse. It can be physical exertion &ndash; weight lifting, pregnancy or childbirth, as well as diarrhea, constipation, hypothermia and even alcohol abuse. In addition, for unpleasant consequences can result sedentary lifestyle work-related (pilots and drivers), or some sports &ndash; weightlifting, cycling, horseback riding.</p>

<p>Any stress, leading to a rush of blood to the pelvis can cause rupture of the vessel in the perianal region and lead to thrombosed external hemorrhoid. In this case, the thrombus begins to put pressure on the vessel wall from within, irritating nerve endings and causing pain. It is these symptoms of hemorrhoids cause a &ldquo;duck&rdquo; gait of patients.</p>

<p>Most often in the early stages, the disease is accompanied by itching, burning and secretions from anus. Patients rarely turn to doctors with such complaints, because they consider them uncritical, or just shy of his problem. Most often they are accompanied by still bleeding. First, rare and meager &ndash; only a few drops during stool, and then they become regular. And when there is a prolapsed hemorrhoid and the pain becomes unbearable and avoid a visit to a specialist is can not.</p>

<h2>Thrombosed hemorrhoid treatment</h2>

<p>The easiest and fastest way to treat hemorrhoids &ndash; is surgery. It is performed under local anesthesia and takes only a few minutes. During the operation, the doctor-proctologist makes minimal incision (up to 5 mm) and through it removes the blood clot from the node, after which the pain immediately goes away. Sometimes, to achieve a cosmetic effect, thrombus excised together with the node. After these operations, the man does not lose the ability to work, and the wound is healing on-site intervention is less than a week.</p>

<p>The only drawback to this method is that the operation &ndash; not a radical cure for hemorrhoids. A blood clot will not appear on the site was operated, but could come close. Therefore, this method of treatment is used to advanced stages of the disease as a means of emergency medicine, as soon as possible to save people from pain.</p>

<p>In all other cases, and at the unwillingness of the patient subjected to surgery, treatment is carried out with the use of medication ointments, rectal suppositories and warm baths. This method gives the effect only after a month and in the future does not preclude the emergence of a blood clot in the same place. Therefore, in order to avoid undesirable effects during treatment should follow a diet, eliminating alcohol and spicy foods, as well as limit physical exertion and less walking.</p>

<p>Speaking of non-surgical treatment of hemorrhoids can not pay attention to the drug Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula, which has proved its effectiveness in the fight against this disease. This drug is made from natural ingredients and with proper treatment recovery comes faster than with other drugs. It is particularly effective in the early stages of hemorrhoids when hemorrhoid nodes have not fallen out. Its also worth taking after recovery as prophylaxis to prevent any re-occurrence of a blood clot.</p>

<p>Remember, <strong>thrombosed hemorrhoid</strong> is always easier to cure in the early stages, and delayed treatment or lack of it at all can lead to complications.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acute hemorrhoids - Thrombosed external hemorrhoid]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/acute-hemorrhoids-thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-09T22:50:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/acute-hemorrhoids-thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-external-hemorrhoid/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Thrombosed external hemorrhoid&rsquo; &lsquo;Acute hemorrhoids &ndash; Thrombosed external hemorrhoid&rsquo;" > A patient with <strong>thrombosed external hemorrhoid</strong> can be found on the &ldquo;duck gait&rdquo; with which they come into the doctor&rsquo;s office. Asked to sit down on a chair, meet the &ldquo;thank you I&rsquo;ll stand by foot&rdquo;. Why is that? Because concerned about pain in the anal area, at whom are moderate, at whom expressed.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>The cause of acute hemorrhoids is different: constipation, diarrhea, hypothermia, weight lifting, alcohol, pregnancy, childbirth, anal sex, etc. With an increase in intra-abdominal pressure occurs powerful rush of blood to pelvis, because of what could &ldquo;explode&rdquo; vein in the perianal area and formed <strong>thrombosed external hemorrhoid</strong>. In fact, this hematoma, which is located under the skin gives a lot of pain and discomfort. This occurs because blood clot presses on the inner tissues thereby stretching the nerve endings, followed by pain. Many people ask this hematoma can get to the heart? No description of a single case of getting thrombosed blood clot (hematoma) of the haemorrhoid in the heart.</p>

<p>Thrombosed external hemorrhoid is more often a unit, can occur immediately 2-3 thrombosed node and can be circular when the swells all perianal area. As well found thrombosis of internal hemorrhoids. This occurs against the background of already existing hemorrhoids during stool internal nodes drop out further as a consequence of the sphincter spasm nodes are infringed, there is an infringement of outflow of blood, swelling knotswith subsequent thrombosis. With such an aggravation of internal hemorrhoids pain for so many severe that patients can not &ldquo;neither sit nor stand up&rdquo; and some call the &ldquo;911&rdquo;. What to do if diagnosed acute hemorrhoids?</p>

<h2>How to treat thrombosed external hemorrhoid</h2>

<p>Treatment hemorrhoid thrombosis. Usually in such cases, you need to limit yourself to walking, exercise, spicy foods, alcohol. Appointed by warm baths and heating pads 2-3 times a day for 20-30 minutes (due to the heat accelerates the resorption of blood clots). When the external manifestations of thrombosis knots rectal suppositories are ineffective. The good effect of acute hemorrhoids gives a natural product such as «Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula». Locally thrombosed knots must be lubricated with ointments Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Hytone, Locoid Lipocream, Locoid, Westcort, that also helps to speed up the resorption process thrombosed clots. All the foregoing conservative therapy will surely give effect, it should be noted that in the conservative treatment process of resorption may take 1-1.5 months. After the complete disappearance of the phenomenon of acute hemorrhoids, on the site of the thrombosed knot almost always remains so-called fringe anal hemorrhoidal.It should be noted that in the future, at the same location, under the influence of any factor may again appear thrombosis node.</p>

<p>Now the information for those who do not like long to be treated. The most rapid and effective treatment of thrombosis, it is certainly a thrombectomy (forced removal of thrombus from the knot). Under anesthesia thrombosed clots are removed from the cut of up to 0.5 cm. Node decreases and the pain immediately stoped. The procedure takes about 1-2 minutes. At the site of thrombectomy wound remains (0.5 cm) that heals for an average of 4 days. In this case, the need for rectal suppositories, ointments, warm baths already not. However, it is recommended prophylactic course of Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula (1 month). After 15 minutes of thrombectomy and recommendations of the patient to go home. Ability to work after the procedure is not lost. Frequently offer remove thrombosed clots together with the node in this case addition to the rapid relief of pain is achieved cosmetic effect. Already at this point there is no thrombotic conditions, but in other places around the circumference of the anus can appear. Why? Because thrombectomy and removal of a thrombosed external hemorrhoid is not a radical operation.</p>

<p>In some cases, when exacerbation passes at available hemorrhoids II-IV stage, radical surgery is acceptable for time reasons. After this operation is a complete cure patients from hemorrhoidal disease and the appearance thrombosed external hemorrhoid of this place for many decades (may appear elsewhere). Risks and complications at radical surgery for time reasons do not exceed those for planned interventions.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to cure hemorrhoids. Hemorrhoid home treatment]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-cure-hemorrhoids-hemorrhoid-home-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-08T21:58:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-cure-hemorrhoids-hemorrhoid-home-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoid-home-treatment/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/hemorrhoid-home-treatment/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Hemorrhoid home treatment&rsquo; &lsquo;How to cure hemorrhoids. Hemorrhoid home treatment&rsquo;" > When we say the word &ldquo;hemorrhoid&rdquo;, many are experiencing negative, sometimes reaching up to phobias, feelings. However, this disease is not so bad, especially in the early stages. It occurs due to poor nutrition, physical inactivity and sedentary lifestyle. It may be provoke a heredity.</p>

<p>In order to answer the question of how to treat hemorrhoids, you need to give it a clear definition. Hemorrhoids are vascular cavernous body. These are formed in the rectum (in the lower part). Nodes can be internal or external. Simultaneously, at the patient may be present both species, in this case will help only complex treatment.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Characteristically reluctance of a large number of patients to see a doctor in the early stages of this disease. They do not ask how to cure hemorrhoids and how to pick a remedy for hemorrhoids, even experiencing pain and discomfort. However, the need to go to a specialist as soon as possible. It is better to hemorrhoid home treatment, than to resort to complex surgery, which in some cases does not bring the proper favor and alleviate suffering.</p>

<p>There are four stages of this disease:</p>

<ol>
<li>The formation hemorrhoid nodes inside the rectum (internal hemorrhoids);</li>
<li>There is a loss of nodes of the rectum after a bowel movement, they themselves reduce a back;</li>
<li>The nodes do not reduce a own but it can still be done with your fingers;</li>
<li>Impossible to reduce fallen nodes (external hemorrhoids).</li>
</ol>


<p>Effective hemorrhoid home treatment is possible only on the first and second stages. On the third and fourth often have to resort to surgery.</p>

<p>In spite of the obvious symptoms of many ill in no hurry to seek medical help. They will not go to the doctor, as a result, they develop hemorrhoids third and fourth stage. For some reason, some people think hemorrhoids are something shameful. They hide their illness from others. This trend is not exclusive to the United States, but also in many European countries. However it is better to learn from experts how to treat hemorrhoids, rather than later hospital treatment needed or, worse, in the outpatient and dispensary observation.</p>

<p>Today, a large amount of useful information on how to cure hemorrhoids, can also find on the Internet. In a network there are enough sites on which there is information about the problem of the disease, the mechanisms of its development, prevention methods and hemorrhoid home treatment.</p>

<h2>How to treat hemorrhoids. The main methods</h2>

<ol>
<li>Non-medical impact. Effective only in the early stages, is to change the lifestyle and diet, increasing physical activity.</li>
<li>Drug therapeutic impact.</li>
<li>Reducing the pressure in the anal canal (the means for doing so are drug «Venapro» and ointments such as Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Locoid etc.).</li>
<li>Non-surgical methods of influence.</li>
<li>Surgical treatment.</li>
</ol>


<p>In the early stages of the disease and as a prophylactic course after surgical treatment is <strong>very effective natural product «Venapro»</strong>.</p>

<p>Identify hemorrhoids simply by the following symptoms:
&ndash; Bleeding during bowel movements, blood in faeces.
&ndash; The occurrence of burning and itching in the anal area.
&ndash; Pain when sitting, walking, bowel movements.
&ndash; The emergence of a sense of gravity or presence of a foreign body in the rectum.
&ndash; Inflammation of hemorrhoid nodes. They be palpated, this gives rise to pain.
&ndash; Occurs loss of nodes of the rectum.</p>

<p>It should, as soon as possible, seek medical attention if these symptoms.</p>

<h2>Hemorrhoid home treatment. Traditional methods</h2>

<p>The use drug treatment is usually only gives a relief of symptoms of the disease in the third and fourth stages. To effectively deal with hemorrhoids, you need to use an integrated approach.</p>

<p>Modern medicine offers to hemorrhoid home treatment is not only tablets but also in other ways. In the early stages helps to get rid of the pain and reduce inflammation of the nodes special diet. Of the food exclude alcohol, spicy and fatty foods, condiments and spices. A diet enriched with plant-based diet high fiber content. Recommended for early hemorrhoids long walks, special exercises, including squats, press load, tilts, etc. It is necessary to make a thorough hygiene of the anus after defecation.</p>

<p>However, the disease exacerbation of those measures will not be enough. In the acute form of hemorrhoid home treatment will require the use of anal suppositories, ointments, and cold lotions. When it is impossible to stop the periodic occurrence of venous bleedings knots injected sclerosing solutions.</p>

<p>By resorting to surgery only in cases where there are prolonged and severe bleeding, constantly drop nodes, at a jamming. All the same any form of treatment is useless if you do not aimed at removing underlying causes of the disease. They only temporarily make easier the patient&rsquo;s condition, reduce pain and symptoms.</p>

<p>In the complex treatment of hemorrhoids is to include products «Venapro &ndash; Hemorrhoid formula». It is especially effective in the early stages of the disease.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thrombosed hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/thrombosed-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-08T21:56:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/thrombosed-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-hemorrhoids/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/thrombosed-hemorrhoids/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Thrombosed hemorrhoids&rsquo; &lsquo;Thrombosed hemorrhoids&rsquo;" > Thrombosed hemorrhoids usually occurs when you straining during bowel movements due to swelling of the dropped out nodes. Sphincter of the rectum spasm  increases the swelling, leads to stagnation of blood in the lower rectal plexus and thrombosed of external hemorrhoids. The patient complained of pain, swelling, discharge from the rectum with an unpleasant odor and difficulties at defecation. At survey are determined dropped out not reduce a edematous internal hemorrhoids, often with fibrinous coating.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>In 70-80% of cases,  complicated by inflammation of the transition to subcutaneous tissue and the anal area. In this case drugs are being used in combination with a water soluble ointments having potent anti-inflammatory action. These include Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Hytone, Locoid Lipocream, Locoid, Westcort.</p>

<p>In acute hemorrhoids and the early stages of chronic hemorrhoids hold conservative treatment. Its main purpose &ndash; relieve pain and inflammation, normalize blood circulation in the rectal area, adjust the digestion. Thrombosed hemorrhoids is an indication for the use of anticoagulants local action. This group of medications include ointments Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Hytone, Locoid Lipocream, Locoid, Westcort. As a preparation for the topical treatment of hemorrhoids established itself particularly Anusol HC. As an agent for the prevention and treatment of hemorrhoids of its in the early stages established itself a natural product Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula. Each component of the drug exerts its beneficial effects in thrombosed hemorrhoids.</p>

<p>Conservative treatment is common: increasing venous tone tablets, improve blood flow in small vessels and cavernous veins (for example Venapro-Hemorrhoid Formula); and local: wound healing, pain relievers and antipruritic ointments, suppositories, microclysters and baths. At the same time is appointed antihemorrhoidal diet: vegetables, fruits, bran, and that&rsquo;s about spices, spicy food and alcohol have to forget.</p>

<p>In surgical treatment under local anesthesia, produce diaplasis dropped nodes, and then perform ligation of the internal nodes latex rings and thrombectomy of the radial incisions at accompanying acute thrombosis of external hemorrhoids. The intervention is performed on an outpatient basis. Short-and long-term results are good. Thrombosis, complicated hemorrhoids stage IV requires urgent hemorrhoidectomy.</p>

<p>Thrombectomy &ndash; removal of thrombus (venous blood clot). Thrombectomy represents a thrombosed node dissection and removal of a blood clot. Thrombectomy is assigned to the nodes are large and cause severe discomfort to the patient, and conservative therapy is ineffective or may take too time. This procedure does not require hospitalization. After thrombectomy is rapid a relief, hemorrhoid, after a while, collapses.
Excision of external hemorrhoid: a procedure which can eliminate the root cause of thrombosis &ndash; an external hemorrhoid. This is the most effective method for the treatment of external thrombosed hemorrhoids, as it allows get rid in a subsequent of the recurring exacerbations. Excision of the outdoor knot assigned when acute thrombosis, when conservative therapy is ineffective, or thrombosed knot brings strong discomfort. In most cases this procedure is performed on an outpatient basis under local anesthesia and does not require hospitalization. Excision of external hemorrhoid can be done with a scalpel conventional or a high-frequency electro-scalpel.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
