<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: proctology | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/proctology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-10-31T19:10:37+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hemorrhoid home treatment]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoid-home-treatment/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T23:36:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoid-home-treatment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When we say the word &ldquo;hemorrhoid&rdquo;, many are experiencing negative, sometimes reaching up to phobias, feelings. However, this disease is not so bad, especially in the early stages. It occurs due to poor nutrition, physical inactivity and sedentary lifestyle. It may be provoke a heredity.</p>

<p>In order to answer the question of how to treat hemorrhoids, you need to give it a clear definition. Hemorrhoids are vascular cavernous body. These are formed in the rectum (in the lower part). Nodes can be internal or external. Simultaneously, at the patient may be present both species, in this case will help only complex treatment.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Characteristically reluctance of a large number of patients to see a doctor in the early stages of this disease. They do not ask how to cure hemorrhoids and how to pick a remedy for hemorrhoids, even experiencing pain and discomfort. However, the need to go to a specialist as soon as possible. It is better to hemorrhoid home treatment, than to resort to complex surgery, which in some cases does not bring the proper favor and alleviate suffering.</p>

<p><strong>In the U.S., 80% of persons with hemorrhoids, the doctor did not address</strong></p>

<p>There are four stages of this disease:</p>

<ol>
<li>The formation hemorrhoid nodes inside the rectum (internal hemorrhoids);</li>
<li>There is a loss of nodes of the rectum after a bowel movement, they themselves reduce a back;</li>
<li>The nodes do not reduce a own but it can still be done with your fingers;</li>
<li>Impossible to reduce fallen nodes (external hemorrhoids).</li>
</ol>


<p>Effective hemorrhoid home treatment is possible only on the first and second stages. On the third and fourth often have to resort to surgery.</p>

<p>In spite of the obvious symptoms of many ill in no hurry to seek medical help. They will not go to the doctor, as a result, they develop hemorrhoids third and fourth stage. For some reason, some people think hemorrhoids are something shameful. They hide their illness from others. This trend is not exclusive to the United States, but also in many European countries. However it is better to learn from experts how to treat hemorrhoids, rather than later hospital treatment needed or, worse, in the outpatient and dispensary observation.</p>

<p>Today, a large amount of useful information on how to cure hemorrhoids, can also find on the Internet. In a network there are enough sites on which there is information about the problem of the disease, the mechanisms of its development, prevention methods and hemorrhoid home treatment.</p>

<h2>How to treat hemorrhoids. The main methods</h2>

<ol>
<li>Non-medical impact. Effective only in the early stages, is to change the lifestyle and diet, increasing physical activity.</li>
<li>Drug therapeutic impact.</li>
<li>Reducing the pressure in the anal canal (the means for doing so are drug «Venapro» and ointments such as Anusol HC, Carmol HC, Hydrocortisone, Locoid etc.).</li>
<li>Non-surgical methods of influence.</li>
<li>Surgical treatment.</li>
</ol>


<p>In the early stages of the disease and as a prophylactic course after surgical treatment is <strong>very effective natural product «Venapro»</strong>.</p>

<p>Identify hemorrhoids simply by the following symptoms:
&ndash; Bleeding during bowel movements, blood in faeces.
&ndash; The occurrence of burning and itching in the anal area.
&ndash; Pain when sitting, walking, bowel movements.
&ndash; The emergence of a sense of gravity or presence of a foreign body in the rectum.
&ndash; Inflammation of hemorrhoid nodes. They be palpated, this gives rise to pain.
&ndash; Occurs loss of nodes of the rectum.</p>

<p>It should, as soon as possible, seek medical attention if these symptoms.</p>

<h2>Hemorrhoid home treatment. Traditional methods</h2>

<p>The use drug treatment is usually only gives a relief of symptoms of the disease in the third and fourth stages. To effectively deal with hemorrhoids, you need to use an integrated approach.</p>

<p>Modern medicine offers to hemorrhoid home treatment is not only tablets but also in other ways. In the early stages helps to get rid of the pain and reduce inflammation of the nodes special diet. Of the food exclude alcohol, spicy and fatty foods, condiments and spices. A diet enriched with plant-based diet high fiber content. Recommended for early hemorrhoids long walks, special exercises, including squats, press load, tilts, etc. It is necessary to make a thorough hygiene of the anus after defecation.</p>

<p>However, the disease exacerbation of those measures will not be enough. In the acute form of hemorrhoid home treatment will require the use of anal suppositories, ointments, and cold lotions. When it is impossible to stop the periodic occurrence of venous bleedings knots injected sclerosing solutions.</p>

<p>By resorting to surgery only in cases where there are prolonged and severe bleeding, constantly drop nodes, at a jamming. All the same any form of treatment is useless if you do not aimed at removing underlying causes of the disease. They only temporarily make easier the patient&rsquo;s condition, reduce pain and symptoms.</p>

<p>In the complex treatment of hemorrhoids is to include products «Venapro &ndash; Hemorrhoid formula». It is especially effective in the early stages of the disease.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hemorrhoids. Natural remedy for hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoids-natural-remedy-for-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T23:28:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/hemorrhoids-natural-remedy-for-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Along with balms, ointments and compresses, which can be used for hemorrhoids, there are tablets and capsules. You do not need a prescription to obtain them. You can order these products via the Internet, or buy them at your local health food store, or through distributors, that deal with Chinese medicinal substances.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Understand that surgery should not be the only opportunity. There are many safe and effective, organic and natural remedy for hemorrhoids, you should try, before you decide to go under the knife. If the Chinese can not suffer from hemorrhoids, why can not you too? Here I will describe those drugs with which I had to read, and the use of which, I quickly went to the amendment. By the treatment of hemorrhoids must be approached comprehensively. In these natural medicines, it is natural! Instead of synthetic, with which the market is oversaturated, contain active components that promote rapid healing of hemorrhoids wall units and. Let&rsquo;s get started!</p>

<p><strong>Hemorrhoid Quick Peace Tablet</strong>. This product is used for both internal and external hemorrhoids. Stops bleeding and pain, reduces swelling, as well as weakens the bowel movements. It contains: root ampelopsisa, Sophora flower, sumac, black beans and pig bile. Dosage &ndash; 4 pills 3 times a day.</p>

<p><strong>Notoginseng Hemorrhoids-Transforming Pill</strong>. This product also stops the bleeding and swelling of both types of hemorrhoids. Dosage &ndash; 3 grams, 2 to 3 times a day. It contains: Notoginseng, the imperative and groundsel.</p>

<p><strong>Venapro</strong> relieves the symptoms of hemorrhoids; contains ingredients vitamin E, zinc oxide, L-Argine, horse chestnut, oat straw, Plaintain, Cascara Sagrada, blueberries, mullein, cayenne pepper. Please note that Venapro is not only intended for temporary relief, and can be used to eliminate the causes of hemorrhoids.</p>

<p><strong>Avatrol</strong> educes the severity of symptoms, as well as a reduced risk of the disease returning. Contains: buckeye, arginine, oat straw, Cascara Sagrada, blueberries, butcher&rsquo;s broom, mullein, cayenne pepper, and zinc. Perfect for the relief of symptom.</p>

<p><strong>Hem-Relief</strong> natural product that helps reduce swelling and inflammation. Contains: horse chestnut leaves and roots of ginger.</p>

<p><strong>Hemorrease</strong> is a powerful anti-inflammatory agent, used to reduce the symptoms of hemorrhoids, with ingredients such as: White oak bark, butcher&rsquo;s broom, witch hazel, Pipa.</p>

<p>As you can see, most of these natural remedy for hemorrhoids are very popular ingredients that promote healing. The use of these drugs &ndash; one of the ways to deal with hemorrhoids. Typically, a doctor writes a prescription rather strong medications that have a number of side effects, because contain a synthetic material comprising.</p>

<p>All of these products, as you can see, assist in the elimination of the symptoms of hemorrhoids. Remember, only natural remedy are able to cure and eliminate the cause of hemorrhoids, be sure to read them. The fact that commonly prescribed doctors only, which is advantageous since get kickbacks from pharmacies as a percentage of sales. Should not be the subjects in this dirty business. Think how much money you&rsquo;ll save!</p>

<p>Remember, hemorrhoids can come back! In spite of all natural products, or recipes that you use, you need to make changes in your diet and lifestyle, if you want to get rid of him once and for all. Many have already done so, now it&rsquo;s your turn!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Herbal remedies for hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/herbal-remedies-for-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T23:24:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/herbal-remedies-for-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hemorrhoids &ndash; a common disease that affects more than half of the population. While hemorrhoids are not yet entered the stage when conservative methods do not work, need to focus on such a method of treatment to avoid injury.</p>

<p>Hemorrhoids can be internal and external. Internal hemorrhoids &ndash; is modified vessels, hemorrhoids, which are located inside the rectum and are not visible from the anus. External hemorrhoids – are nodes that fall out, you can find with your fingers, and their doctors see perfectly without any instruments.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>For the treatment of internal and external hemorrhoids is quite widely used tablet form, giving good results. Tablets from hemorrhoids often include natural ingredients that are safe for pregnant women and older people. In times of acute illness and cracks can be used painkillers for hemorrhoids. Consider the most famous and effective pill for hemorrhoids, as in the treatment of hemorrhoids tablets also have a major role.</p>

<p>Venapro – fitodrug, comes in tablet form and as a spray. The structure of this drug include herbal extracts, which strengthen the walls of blood vessels. Venapro stop bleeding, anti-inflammatory action. With these pills improves sensation during defecation &ndash; out voltage disappears itching and burning sensation in the anal area. Thus Venapro pills help the digestive process and the actual. The drug should be used within three weeks &ndash; then it will be the first results. Consistent effect can be achieved in about 3-6 months of reception these pills.</p>

<p>If hemorrhoids are fairly long and progressive, it requires preparation with a wide spectrum of action, which would get rid of the multiple symptoms of hemorrhoids immediately. It is a drug Pilex. Its components have anti-inflammatory, analgesic and hemostatic effect. As part of Pilex tablet natural herbal ingredients that have a beneficial effect on the vascular wall. Increasing the turgor of capillaries, respectively, and reduced the number of swollen.</p>

<p>Tablets with hemorrhoids have several indisputable advantages. First, they can be used anytime and anywhere. Secondly, the tablet is more convenient in terms of use. Often it happens that sitting at work there is a need to take a pill. After all, why would you go to the toilet every day, several times to lubricate the anus and remove itching. Therefore, blisters of pills are very comfortable &ndash; they are always on hand, can only take a pill in case of aggravation.</p>

<p>Tablets of hemorrhoids include not only chemical substances, but also useful natural components, by which healing is much faster and more efficient. Pill is easier to use for older single people who can not serve themselves qualitatively. However, it is important to remember that the tablets of the hemorrhoid doctor should prescribe that the data collected survey makes the choice to certain drugs. In any case, do not despair &ndash; among all the different products you can always find exactly the pill that will relieve you from hemorrhoids permanently.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consequences of birth: ruptures and hemorrhoids]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/consequences-of-birth-ruptures-and-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T23:20:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/consequences-of-birth-ruptures-and-hemorrhoids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Unfortunately, not all women after childbirth fine. There are some side effects to deal with that would not like anyone, but often still have to. Of course all of this vremennoya phenomenon, but it has to be properly experienced.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>The three most common problems are:</p>

<ul>
<li>Perineum dissection,</li>
<li>Ruptures soft tissue crotch,</li>
<li>Hemorrhoids.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Perineum dissection and ruptures</h2>

<p>It often happens that in the process of childbirth maternity make a neat incision or does it turn out breaks. At these places later stitches.</p>

<p>If you stitches, then you should know how to look after them:</p>

<ul>
<li>Joints must be kept clean and dry. Bowl gasket change, and even better throw a &ldquo;ventilation&rdquo;;</li>
<li>When taking a shower, watch the water would not fall into the vagina;</li>
<li>Outer seams are very well cleaned chamomile, calendula;</li>
<li>The first two months of getting out of bed very carefully and do not make any sudden movements;</li>
<li>If the outer seams &ndash; the first two weeks is not recommended to sit;</li>
<li>Does not in any way lift heavy;</li>
<li>Breastfeed better lying down;</li>
</ul>


<p>During the healing you can feel the pain slack, but if you suddenly become joint pain fester and worsen, immediately consult a gynecologist. If the scars are large and hard to soften the suit light massage with the infusion of herbs. Just do Kegel exercises, they will help restore elasticity of the skin.</p>

<h2>Hemorrhoids</h2>

<p>Hemorrhoids &ndash; varicose veins in the form of a nodule in the anus. This problem can affect you during pregnancy and during labor, and after them. If you are faced with such a sensitive issue, do not despair. Of course, you need to see a doctor.</p>

<p>In addition to expert advice will help you:</p>

<ul>
<li>Take a warm bath with herbal infusions in a sitting position. However, it can be done only after the post-partum end up in isolation.</li>
<li>Apply directly to the trouble spot fitoled.</li>
<li>As well help herbal compresses.</li>
<li>Avoid constipation. Include in your diet: beets, baked apples, sea cabbage, cereals.</li>
<li>Avoid strenuous exercise.</li>
<li>Perform Kegel exercises.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get rid of hemorrhoids for good]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-get-rid-of-hemorrhoids-for-good/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T23:16:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-get-rid-of-hemorrhoids-for-good</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How to get rid of hemorrhoids at home, so do not bother hemorrhoids bumps and could sit comfortably. All patients with hemorrhoids like this, but not all in this endeavor. Hemorrhoids insidious disease and calls for a serious approach. The systematic application of the treatment and the combination of its different variants and persistence will help get rid of hemorrhoids for good.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>How to get rid of hemorrhoids at home for good</h2>

<p>When a sedentary job or lifestyle, diet does not promote healing. Here we have to solve each: what is more important &ndash; the health or human weakness.
Traditional medicine is armed with a lot of good recipes from hemorrhoids. They all help to eliminate the bleeding, reduce inflammation cones. Unfortunately, a family history of venous varicose vein walls and fine win easy, but you can.</p>

<h2>How to get rid of hemorrhoids for good, old-fashioned recipe:</h2>

<p>This is an old recipe to effectively treat hemorrhoids. To get rid of the disease must be made within 40 days without missing a single day, drink 1 tbsp 2 times a day for an hour before eating corn oil.</p>

<h2>How to get rid of hemorrhoids for good with a normal garlic:</h2>

<p>Get the great big clove of garlic, mash it in a frog, add a little boiling water and this fluid lubricate the anus outside and inside. Very much will burn, but for 2-3 hours you get rid of hemorrhoids for good.</p>

<p>After dinner, at eight o'clock in the evening, and can be a little early to take a pack of black pepper powder (20 g), pour into a glass and pour warm, room temperature water to the brim. Interfere with a teaspoon, until a homogeneous mass and drink all at once. You will burn in your mouth as if you ate the soup with pepper, and then, while you&rsquo;re watching TV &ndash; will be held.
But then nothing can neither eat nor drink. Go to bed in the morning, when you go to the toilet a lot, you will have to tweak the anus &ndash; is good, your hemorrhoids will disappear forever.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
