<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Dietology | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/dietology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-06-05T13:02:34+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nine-day Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-05T12:26:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/nine-day-diet/img.jpg" alt="Nine-day diet">Want to quickly bring your body in good shape before the long-awaited vacation? Nothing could be easier. Nine-day diet will help you deal with this problem in a few days.</p>

<p>And why is it always? All year flies by, but we did not have time to enroll in a gym, in the shaping or dance, we eat what we want, and grabs his head only when the time is almost gone. And as always in the holiday expectations we stand before the mirror and realize that all night snacks, salted potato chips and crisps, beer and cocktails are our figure does not help, but rather spoiled her beyond recognition. <!--more-->Looking in the mirror, we realize that with such a body to appear in a bikini on the beach - it&rsquo;s a crime. An urgent need to do something!</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
First of all you need to tune in to the fact that, following the right diet of this diet, you will lose weight in a day 0.5-1kg. This is certainly a serious <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a> to the body, so before starting the diet is better to consult a doctor. This diet is not suitable for those who have stomach ulcers, diseases of the cardiovascular system, or even the uncommon cold.</p>

<p>Next, you should understand that no diet compliance, a periodic &quot;jumping from diet&quot;, etc. It leads to the fact that all is well kilos gone back to his place, and maybe even &quot;friends&quot; with a lead. Began to lose weight - grow thin, you do not want to lose weight - do not sit on a diet. To fix the result, it is necessary to understand that after the diet need to eat moderately and wisely.</p>

<h2>Menu diet for 9 days:</h2>

<p>This diet consists of three phases.</p>

<p><strong>The first stage</strong> - three days to eat only rice, honey and drink the water.</p>

<p>On the day we take 250g long grain white rice, 2-2.5 liters of mineral water without gas, and 3 teaspoons of honey spoon.</p>

<p>On the night of rice soaked with cold water. In the morning, wash the rice in a colander to wash most of the cereal starch. Further boil in a saucepan for 15 minutes, adding rice and water in a ratio of 1:2, respectively.</p>

<p>Cooked rice divide into 5 equal portions and we eat it all day long, trying to avoid the strong feelings of hunger. Last time you can eat no later than eight o'clock in the evening. In between meals and after-meal drink water, distributing evenly. In the evening, lean on the liquid is not worth it. Also included in the diet of honey which eat in parallel with rice and water during the day. Honey is not spread on bread or cookies, eat a teaspoon with water.</p>

<p>Why this diet is effective? Figure acts as enterosorbent he cleans accumulated for a long time, toxins from the gastrointestinal tract, which actually promotes <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/1kg-per-day-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>.</p>

<p><strong>The second stage</strong> - the next 3 days, you can eat chicken or fish, water and honey.</p>

<p>On the day we need 1.2-1.3kg chicken or lean fish 700-800g, as well as water (2-2.5 l) and three teaspoons of honey.</p>

<p>Chicken or lean fish cook in a double boiler. In the morning we drink a glass of water, and then proceed to the meal.</p>

<p>If you chose the chicken, then it is necessary to remove the peel, then eat a whole piece of the leg and the back, that is where a fifth part of the carcass. Then carve the chicken, separating the meat from the bones, mix white and red meat, divide into equal portions and eat up during the remainder of the day. Last time we eat no later than seven o'clock in the evening.</p>

<p>If you <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="choose">choose</a> the fish, it should be divided into 5-6 pieces and eat as well as chicken, for a whole day in equal portions, trying to avoid feeling hungry. To fish was delicious, you can add a little greenery and lemon juice.</p>

<p>You can alternate days fish and chicken to the diet was not too bothersome. As in the early days of drinking water, and we eat the honey.</p>

<p>Why do we lose weight? Receipt of protein contributes to the fact that fat cells break up fat, which contributes to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="rapid weight loss">rapid weight loss</a>.</p>

<p><strong>The third stage</strong> - the next 3 days, we eat only vegetables, water and honey.</p>

<p>Take a day 1 kg of vegetables, 2-2.5l mineral water without gas, and 3 teaspoons of honey spoon.</p>

<p>It is better to give preference to white, and green vegetables such as cabbage, zucchini, onions, etc. But also do not forget about beets, tomatoes and carrots, but take them to a lesser extent. Please take a pound of vegetables, finely chopped, and simmer, remaining vegetables, we are preparing a salad brush.</p>

<p>What do you need? Raw beet, raw carrots, some cabbage, fresh herbs, a few drops of lemon juice, a teaspoon of olive oil, tablespoon water.</p>

<p><strong>How to cook?</strong> Clean the vegetables and rub on a coarse grater or chop finely. Add the olive oil, lemon juice and water for juiciness.</p>

<p>Then we share the steamed vegetables into three parts and a salad as a brush into three equal parts. It is necessary to alternate the meals throughout the day.</p>

<p>Due to the vegetables in the body is reduced vitamin and mineral complex. Belly immediately becomes smaller, because effectively cleans all the deposits on the walls of the intestine.</p>

<p>Diet is over, and we can return to a normal diet. But because it is necessary to exclude:</p>

<ul>
<li>Too salty foods and foods</li>
<li>Sweet soda water.</li>
</ul>


<p>What can you eat? Eat low-fat cheese, no more than 50g a day, bread from wheat flour, no more than 4 slices per day. Also drink water in large quantities and keep the schedule meals. You need not eat more than 4 times a day in small portions at most 250g at a time no later supper seven hours.</p>

<p>The proposed diet is not too &quot;hungry&quot;, but it is quite specific. You do not need to combine diet with exercise, fitness, work in the country and other complex procedures. But on the contrary leave more move, walk, swim, dance - just relax actively.</p>

<h2>Helpful advice</h2>

<p>Ladies, if you know that you can not abandon all kinds of temptations on holiday, it is better to give up this diet once and for all! It is better to learn to enjoy its appearance as it is. If you can not resist the goodies and will be broken, then all your efforts will be in vain. And remember that any woman can be sexy, regardless of the splendor of forms. The main thing - it is a smiling, good spirits and good humor.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[1kg Per Day Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/1kg-per-day-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-04T14:28:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/1kg-per-day-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/1kg-per-day/img.jpg" alt="1kg per day diet">When a person in one day looking in the mirror and finds that his figure needs to be corrected, he goes online and begins to look for ways to lose weight out there. Moreover, a gradual decrease in weight was not satisfied. Man must necessarily lose weight quickly, to ensure a minimum duration period, when it will have to limit yourself to food. Many people tend to lose weight by 1 kg per day, but whether this is real rate of decrease body fat? Diets in which the authors promise such high rates of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/citrus-diet-for-weight-loss-diet-menus-on-citrus-reviews-recipes/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>, there, and now we will discuss the most common ones.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Some women use a day diet allows you to lose 1 kg of weight. Note that minus 1 kg of body mass - is not the same as the minus 1 kg of fat. This one-day diet is often recommended on the Internet, but few mention one of its features. In the early days of any fat diets are extremely reluctant to leave, so the weight is reduced by emptying the intestines and excretion of fluids. At the same time the stomach will become flatter, but the thickness of the subcutaneous fat layer will remain unchanged.</p>

<ol>
<li>Duration - exactly one day.</li>
<li>Diet painted strictly by the hour, can not deviate from it.</li>
<li>Weight loss occurs by reducing the amount of body fluids and faeces in the intestine.</li>
<li>Diet - 8 times per day, so it is advisable to sit on this mini-diet at the weekend, so it does not interfere with the work schedule.</li>
<li>Salt prohibited - this measure will bring the body of liquid without the use of diuretics.</li>
</ol>


<p><em>Diet Menu minus 1 kg for 1 day on the clock:</em></p>

<p>7:00 - unsweetened black tea (0 kcal);
9:00 - boiled egg (80 calories);
11:00 - tablespoon of raisins (25 kcal);
13:00 - 100 grams of boiled chicken (180 calories);
15:00 - a glass of tomato juice (40 calories);
17:00 - boiled egg (80 calories);
21:00 - a cup of yogurt (100 kcal).</p>

<p>Total - 555 <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/" title="calories">calories</a> for the entire day. If you observe a diet all the time, then quickly led to full order of the figure. Another thing is that to sustain this meager menu longer than 1 day, akin to a feat. Surely you will torment hunger. In addition, such a diet can hardly be called healthy and balanced.</p>

<p>Diet minus 1 kg per day - it&rsquo;s an ambulance to your figure. If your body is not too much fat, you will be visually slimmer. This allows you to look better the next day after the diet. It should be understood that the body fat mass will remain unchanged, so you will get only a temporary result. For sustainable weight loss diet should be longer.</p>

<p>There are longer diets are designed for weight loss of 1 kg per day. In general, they are designed for a week. Subsequently diets simply lose their effectiveness. The fact that lose 1 kg of fat per day impossible. Even if you are physically active, and thus did not eat hardly lose a day more than 500 grams of fat. Moreover, even such pitches are possible only in the first few days, and then the body will reduce the metabolic rate to conserve energy in the hungry period.</p>

<p>Diet minus 1 kg per day is only for 7 days, because in this period to achieve weight loss can be achieved by removing the liquid and purgation of faeces. Naturally, when the old food out of the intestines, and the new comes in miniscule amounts, you become easier. Similarly, reduced body weight when the body takes the water. But infinitely away she can not, so the process of so-called &quot;<a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="slimming">slimming</a>&quot; rapidly slowing.</p>

<p>One of the most common schemes power save enable presumably to 1 kg per day, referred to as &quot;favorite diet&quot;. Who loves it, and most importantly - for what, history is silent. Here&rsquo;s her menu on days:</p>

<p>Monday - you can drink anything you want, in any quantity, but can not eat.
Tuesday - you can eat vegetables in any quantity.
Wednesday - you can drink, but you can not have.
Thursday - you can eat only fruit.
Friday - allowed to eat boiled meat and fish low-fat varieties, eggs and seafood.
Saturday - only to drink, but can not eat.
Sunday - the day the menu includes servings of vegetable salad, two eggs, two servings of fruit salad and cup of soup.</p>

<p>This diet is stupid, ineffective, it contains a whole bunch of unnecessary regulations. Perhaps someone once coined it for a joke, and the rest was picked up and distributed over the Internet. You can not reset using this diet 1 kg daily. However, any result you will surely get. Three of the seven days you are not allowed to consume food. It is unlikely that these will be the days of drinking in vain for your figure.</p>

<p>The Internet goes the myth that diet singer Valeria, which is designed for three days, on a daily basis allows a person to lose 1 kg of weight. It is based on the use of buckwheat porridge without fat and salt. Most sources say that buckwheat acquires special fat-burning properties, if you do not cook it in boiling water and leave overnight to infuse in hot water.</p>

<p><em>In the diet of the singer Valeria only two rules:</em></p>

<ol>
<li>There are only buckwheat water, but in any amount.</li>
<li>Water should be drinking at least 2 liters per day.</li>
</ol>


<p>It is not known whether this diet Valery complied with in reality, or is it another tabloids fiction, but a way to lose weight, we do not recommend because of poor performance. Buckwheat - is a product that eating large amounts can not reduce weight, but on the contrary, grow side. But even if you keep yourself from overeating calorie diet buckwheat these three days will be enough low for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="rapid weight loss">rapid weight loss</a>.</p>

<p>Undoubtedly, the top most stupid diets for weight loss led power scheme, which is based on the daily consumption of fruit alone. Here is your menu for 6 days:</p>

<p>Monday - 1 kg of fruit.</p>

<p>While other human diet literally forced to drink the water in high amounts, fruit diet restricts liquid to 500 ml per day. It is obvious that no advantage is not such a diet. But it has drawbacks whole bunch:</p>

<ul>
<li>fruit contained in the composition of organic acids, which stimulate intestinal motility, causing the secretion of digestive juices and hunger provoking;</li>
<li>fruits contain a lot of carbohydrates, including simple sugars, but the protein in them is very small, so the diet is unhealthy and little use for the figure;</li>
<li>people with diseases of the gastrointestinal tract diet is contraindicated due to the possible aggravation of her background of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/gastritis.html" title="gastritis">gastritis</a> or <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/gastroenterology/diagnosis-of-peptic-ulcer-disease.html" title="peptic ulcer">peptic ulcer</a>.</li>
</ul>


<p>You may be able to lose weight on a little fruit. But if the pitches are, they are clearly not amount to 1 kg per day. The diet is unhealthy, poorly tolerated and has a very low efficiency. Perhaps these three reasons enough to abandon it.</p>

<p>The most zealous fans of freebies do not want only a few days to fix a figure, but still wish to do so without dieting. The emergence of the desire to contribute to sellers of various additives, belts, bracelets and other rubbish, supposedly allowing lose weight at least 1 per kg per day without dieting and effort. Typically, such a person desire to end waste of money, human expectations and decreased motivation to further weight loss.</p>

<p>&quot;Minus 1 kg a month without dieting&quot; - that should sound like your goal, if you do not want to limit themselves in power. It is likely that you do not need to diet adjustment, if you will exercise the utmost physical activity:</p>

<ul>
<li>always walk, if possible;</li>
<li>perform yoga exercises in the gym under the supervision of a trainer;</li>
<li>active rest, but not in front of the TV.</li>
</ul>


<p>But you have to understand that provide a negative energy balance in the body without the use of diet is extremely difficult. To do this, you must spend a lot of calories. Although theoretically possible weight loss without dieting, weight reduction achieved in real life, keeping the old diet - it is a very difficult task that requires human willpower, discipline and dedication.</p>

<p>Lose 1 kg per day - this is achievable task. But it is feasible only in the case if you follow a diet plan is not more than 1 day. If you are set to lose fat, not water, and feces, such a goal is unrealistic, regardless of the presence or absence of the desire to diet.</p>

<p>Minus 1 kg per day - a task that will take you just a waste of money. You again sell another &quot;miracle pill&quot; for $100, or &quot;fat burning&quot; zone for $500. Set a goal adequate. Lose weight gradually, and then over time you normalize the weight of his body, without harm to health and damage to the purse.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Persimmon Nutrition for Weight Loss. Persimmon Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/persimmon-nutrition-for-weight-loss-persimmon-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-07T07:31:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/persimmon-nutrition-for-weight-loss-persimmon-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/persimmon-nutrition-for-weight-loss-persimmon-diet/img.jpg" alt="Persimmon nutrition for weight loss.  Persimmon diet">For those who love sweets on persimmon diet works best: it allows you to quickly get rid of a few extra kilos and is very useful for health.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Persimmon nutrition: the benefits, the essence, advantages and disadvantages</h2>

<p>Calorie 100 g of fruit varies from 60 to 70 calories, so many people is not in question, can I use persimmon diet.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
This miracle fruit contains a large amount of nutrients has a positive impact on the human body:</p>

<ul>
<li>Vitamins;</li>
<li>Minerals;</li>
<li>Proteins;</li>
<li>Organic acids;</li>
<li>Fiber;</li>
<li>Tannin and pectin.</li>
</ul>


<p>The essence of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> on a persimmon nutrition is that a person uses a small amount of calories, due to which the weight starts to drop. Thus, the shortage of energy the body has to produce its own, breaking down existing fat deposits.</p>

<h3>Pros and cons of persimmon nutrition</h3>

<p>Slimming with persimmon has a lot of advantages:</p>

<ul>
<li>This fruit prevents kidney disease, is useful in nervous disorders and <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/vascular-disease/" title="cardiovascular diseases">cardiovascular diseases</a>;</li>
<li>With this technique, you can quickly lose kilograms;</li>
<li>If all the rules harm health is not possible;</li>
<li>Dried persimmon and diet - the concept is almost incompatible, since it contains 274 kcal per 100 g It can be only replace meal - for example, dinner - and then will lose weight.</li>
</ul>


<p>Contraindicated eat persimmons people with diabetes and problems with the digestive tract, but during <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="pregnancy">pregnancy</a> it is recommended by many doctors because of the fact that it has the most necessary elements for the normal development of the fetus.</p>

<h3>How much can you lose on a persimmon nutrition</h3>

<p>It is difficult to imagine a more <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7">effective product for weight loss</span> than the persimmon, and her diet helps to reduce the weight by 1 kg per day, if you are using strict menus, and up to 500 grams for the same period - if it is just to eat dinner instead.</p>

<p>Is the volume on the go with persimmon diet as well as weight? Of course, with the disposal of kilograms after some time it can be seen that the waist and hips become less than a few centimeters in volume, and remained the same breast.</p>

<p>Calorie diet on a persimmon depends on the menu, but it is usually possible to consume per day to 1,500 Kcal.</p>

<p>What products may be diet:</p>

<ul>
<li>Vegetables;</li>
<li>Fruit;</li>
<li>Fermented beverages;</li>
<li>Porridge;</li>
<li>Lean meat and fish;</li>
<li>Greenery;</li>
<li>Boiled eggs;</li>
<li>Hard cheese;</li>
<li>Cottage cheese.</li>
</ul>


<p>As in any other weight loss method, it is strictly forbidden to eat any high-calorie and sweet dishes, and if the menu is limited to just one product - to use once it is resolved.</p>

<p>The effectiveness of the persimmon nutrition is achieved precisely because throughout it has to restrict itself slightly in the food, but soon you can be sure that such restrictions are not in vain.</p>

<h2>Persimmon nutrition: diet menus, recipes, rules</h2>

<p><em>Slimming rules using persimmon:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Persimmon can eat in the usual form, or to cook from her salad when not using mono-diet;</li>
<li>To quickly clear the body and lose weight, you need every day to drink 1.5 liters of clean water without gas;</li>
<li>When used in foods only for 1-2 days it is recommended to refrain from strenuous exercise.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Strict persimmon diet: a menu for 3 days</h3>

<p><em>The most rigid diet is not designed for more than 3 days:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Eat up to 2 kg of persimmon;</li>
<li>Drink water, herbal or green tea.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Persimmon nutrition and yogurt</h3>

<p><em>A further embodiment can also be used not more than three days:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>We eat for the whole day, no more than 6 fruits;</li>
<li>We drink a maximum of 1.5 liters of nonfat yogurt.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Persimmon nutrition and apples</h3>

<p><em>You can replace the yogurt to apples, using this strict diet:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>We drink for 1-3 days 1 kg of apples and persimmons;</li>
<li>As for drinks, leaving only green tea and water.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet and persimmon bran</h3>

<p><em>It is known that bran well cleanse the body and strengthen the immune system and eating salad, cooked them and persimmon, you can lose a couple of extra kilos:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Persimmon grind, mix with a third cup of dry bran, pour all the fat yogurt;</li>
<li>We eat a dish for lunch, and on all other meals ready-made meals from the authorized products.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet persimmon and honey</h3>

<p><em>For weight loss per month for 7-10 kg can be used and this menu:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>We eat any food allowed;</li>
<li>For dinner, we eat a persimmon and 1 ch. L. honey.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Persimmon nutrition and rice</h3>

<p><em>Mono-diet, which lasts up to 7 days, to successfully get rid of 5-7 kg of excess weight:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>We eat only boiled rice without salt (500 g per day);</li>
<li>Eat up to 1 kg of persimmon.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Valerie Diet persimmon</h3>

<p><em>Singer periodically uses this 7-day diet to keep fit:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Breakfast porridge, cooked with water;</li>
<li>Lunch vegetable soup, and a steam cutlet;</li>
<li>Supper persimmons and glass of kefir.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Persimmon nutrition for pregnant persimmon</h3>

<p><em>During childbearing eating persimmon great benefit: eliminating the edema, strengthens the nervous system, removes excess fluid from the body, saturating it with potassium. To get rid of the astringency of the fruit, you can use one of the methods:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Keeping persimmon in warm water 12 hours;</li>
<li>Frozen and then thawed fruit;</li>
<li>Give the fruit ripen on the windowsill, if it is not fully ripened.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Recipes for a diet with persimmons</h3>

<p><em>Recipe salad of persimmons:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Clear the persimmons, cut it into circles;</li>
<li>Cut slices mozzarella cheese;</li>
<li>We spread the cheese on the persimmon, alternating with each other circles;</li>
<li>Sprinkle with pepper and pour olive oil.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Recipe soup with persimmon:</h3>

<ul>
<li>Cut into cubes of onion, sweet pepper and persimmon;</li>
<li>Fry the onion in vegetable oil, add the tomato paste and paprika, simmer on low heat for 5 minutes;</li>
<li>Add to the pan and persimmon pepper, simmer for 7 minutes;</li>
<li>Place the vegetables in a pre-cooked vegetable broth, boil, salt and pepper;</li>
<li>Before serving, sprinkle with herbs.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Recipe dessert with persimmon:</h3>

<ul>
<li>Pour boiling water over prunes, give him shall be melted;</li>
<li>Clean up and cut a persimmon;</li>
<li>We spread in a glass dessert first layer of low-fat cottage cheese, and more - prune and persimmons;</li>
<li>Finally, dressed with yogurt and sprinkle with cinnamon.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avocado Diet for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/avocado-diet-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-01T09:38:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/avocado-diet-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/avocado-diet-for-weight-loss/img.jpg" width="200" height="150" alt="Avocado diet: reviews of lost weight">For those who love sweetish fruit ripe avocado, there is a special diet that allows you to quickly get rid of excess weight.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>A diet with avocado: the essence, the benefits, advantages and disadvantages</h2>

<p>Due to the fact that oily taste the fruit is quite high in calories - 208 kilocalories per 100 grams, many question arises: is it possible to use the avocado diet?</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
It is worth bearing in mind that he quickly satisfies hunger, because to comply with the usual diet will need no more than 5 fruits per day and thus be able to eat no more than 1,100 kcal - this is a very small figure.</p>

<p>The essence of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> on a diet of avocados is precisely to reduce calorie intake, as well as its useful functions for the body:</p>

<ul>
<li>Avocados have no <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a> and it contains monounsaturated fatty acids perfectly clean vessels, eliminate cholesterol plaques and removal of residues;</li>
<li>Turning to your diet avocados contribute to a speedy cure digestive diseases, thyroid and stabilization in <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/cardiology/hypertension.html" title="hypertension">hypertension</a>, as well as skin rejuvenation.</li>
</ul>


<p>It is because of these useful properties of avocado diet is especially appreciated by physicians: they believe that this product is the best suited to make a slim figure.</p>

<h3>Pros and cons of diet with avocado</h3>

<p>In <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7">weight loss</span> with avocado has a number of advantages:</p>

<ul>
<li>The very diet transferred easily, because the ripe juicy fruit reduce appetite and quickly satisfy hunger;</li>
<li>Methods suitable for all, except for pregnant women, children and the elderly;</li>
<li>Many other products on the menu, if it is not strictly mono version.</li>
</ul>


<p>Use avocado diet has a small disadvantage: only one fruit can not be eaten for a long time, as this may lead to metabolic disorders.</p>

<h3>How much can you lose on a diet with avocado</h3>

<p>Calorie diet on the avocado, regardless of its particular species is never higher than 1500 kcal, which allows for 1 day to get rid of 800-900 g weight.</p>

<p>Many people wonder whether the volumes with avocado diet goes, and in this case it is important to know that weight loss always involves a reduction in its volume - in particular, hips and waist.</p>

<h3>Avocado and diet: what foods can be eaten</h3>

<p>During maintenance diet following products may be used in menu:</p>

<ul>
<li>Cereal porridge;</li>
<li>Fruits and vegetables;</li>
<li>Lean meat and fish;</li>
<li>Greenery;</li>
<li>Fermented beverages.</li>
</ul>


<p>Under the ban are all sweet, fatty, smoked or salted food, as they reduce the effectiveness of the diet on the avocado.</p>

<h2>Diet avocado diet menus, recipes, rules</h2>

<p><em>Diet rules with the help of an avocado:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>The fruit should be just ripe, and before use should be cut into two pieces, and remove pits;</li>
<li>Eat must be at least 4 times a day in small portions, and be sure to drink 2 liters of water daily.</li>
</ul>


<h3>A strict diet for avocados: Menu</h3>

<p>To lose up to 4 kilos, you need to follow this menu for the 3 days:</p>

<ul>
<li>Every day, we eat 5 fruit avocado, dividing them into several portions;</li>
<li>2 liters of drinking water, and more.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Avocado diet and yogurt</h3>

<p>A softer version of the three-day diet includes the following:</p>

<ul>
<li>Also, we eat at 5 avocados;</li>
<li>To drink 1 liter of nonfat yogurt.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Avocado diet avocado and cottage cheese</h3>

<p>For 5 days using this menu, you can lose weight by 5 kg:</p>

<ul>
<li>In the morning we eat half an avocado and 50 g of fat-free yogurt;</li>
<li>For lunch we eat a salad with cucumber, green onions, &frac12; avocado and egg;</li>
<li>Supper 100 g of boiled beef, a half avocado and boiled egg.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Avocado diet with ginger</h3>

<p>During the month of application of such a diet turns to throw up to 10 kg:</p>

<ul>
<li>We eat any food from the list of permitted;</li>
<li>For dinner, we eat 40 grams of avocado and drink tea with ginger.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet avocado puree</h3>

<p>This diet is suitable for fasting days:</p>

<ul>
<li>We eat up to 700 grams of mashed avocado pulp;</li>
<li>For breakfast, we eat, and further 100 g of cottage cheese.</li>
</ul>


<h3>A diet with avocado Julia Roberts</h3>

<p>The technique is designed for 28 days, during which the need to eat on the menu the following example:</p>

<ul>
<li>Steam have breakfast omelette and avocado;</li>
<li>For lunch drink fruit juice;</li>
<li>Lunch baked fish and vegetable salad;</li>
<li>Afternoon snack low-fat yogurt;</li>
<li>We have supper of boiled fish and 100 g of fruit.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet blueberry avocado and ginger</h3>

<p>According to the well-known TV presenter, there is the easiest way to lose weight with the help of three products:</p>

<ul>
<li>Avocado: eliminate fat;</li>
<li>Ginger: relieves bloating;</li>
<li>Blueberries: it reduces appetite and has anti-inflammatory effects.</li>
</ul>


<p>All three ingredients must be present in the diet, which is equal to the caloric content of 1500 kcal, while you can eat anything you want, adhering to the specified limit.</p>

<h3>Recipes for a diet with avocado</h3>

<p><em>Recipe mashed avocado:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Clear the number of fruit, remove them from the brush;</li>
<li>Pulp transform into a puree using a blender or corolla.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Recipe salad with avocado:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Boil chicken breast, cut into cubes it together with tomato, cucumber and avocado;</li>
<li>Mix, sprinkle with herbs and pour the lemon juice.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Recipe soup with avocado:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Boil potatoes, peeled avocado and zucchini;</li>
<li>Add salt and pepper;</li>
<li>Beat blender;</li>
<li>Before serving, add a little lemon juice.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Protein, Fat and Carbohydrates You Need in a Day to Lose Weight?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-much-protein-fat-and-carbohydrates-you-need-in-a-day-to-lose-weight/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-23T11:46:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-much-protein-fat-and-carbohydrates-you-need-in-a-day-to-lose-weight</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-much-protein-fat-and-carbohydrates-you-need-in-a-day-to-lose-weight/img.jpg" title="How much protein, fat and carbohydrates you need in a day to lose weight" alt="proteins as needed daily, as needed fat per day">Proteins, fats and carbohydrates <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="every day">every day</a> we get from food, and they are vital to us. These substances in a given amount contains almost any food and are called macronutrients. And why do we need them?</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Proteins - building blocks for all body cells. They are composed of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids/" title="amino acids">amino acids</a>, which are divided into essential and nonessential. Interchangeable can be synthesized in humans only essential to reach a food composition. Proteins are necessary for growth, development, and in general for any physiological process; thus, they are absolutely safe in terms of possible accumulation of excess weight. The sources of protein are meat, fish, dairy products and legumes.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Fats - are made up of fatty acids, which are divided into saturated, monounsaturated and polyunsaturated. Today at all on hearing beneficial omega-3 and omega-6 acids, belonging to the group of polyunsaturated and can lower <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a>. It is also necessary for the absorption of fats, vitamins, synthesis of a number of hormones, the normal operation of many systems of the body. They are contained in both animal food (meat, fish, dairy products) and plant (nuts, seeds, vegetable oil) origin. Excessive consumption of fat - a way to lose the harmony.</p>

<p>Carbohydrates - the main source of energy. They can be simple (glucose, sucrose, etc.) and complex (cellulose, glycogen). Splitting of carbohydrates gives the body energy, the unspent portion of which can be converted into body fat. The main sources of carbohydrates - fruits, vegetables, cereals and sweets.</p>

<p>The diet of an adult to maintain its health and permanent weight gain there should be a certain ratio of these nutrients. Thus, our daily menu should contain:</p>

<p>Once in the digestive system, proteins, fats and carbohydrates are exposed cleavage with release of energy necessary for vital processes. The resulting energy is measured in units - kilocalories (kcal), which, for brevity, often referred to as calories.</p>

<p>Energy value of macronutrients varies. 1 gram of carbohydrate and protein is cleaved to release 4 kcal, 1 gram of fat - 9 kcal.</p>

<h2>Caloric intake and the ratio of macronutrients for weight loss</h2>

<p>Weight person depends on how many calories enters the body, and how much is consumed. If these amounts are approximately equal, the mass remains stable. If it receives more calories than consumed energy postponed &quot;in reserve&quot; in the form of fat.</p>

<p>Accordingly, to reduce weight, it is necessary to spend more calories than is consumed with food.</p>

<p>To calculate daily calorie your diet and calculate the necessary amount of proteins, fats and carbohydrates, using a few simple formulas. Try to make the calculations for yourself using these formulas and examples.</p>

<p><strong><em>1. First you need to calculate your basal metabolism.</em></strong></p>

<p>For women: 655 + (9,6 x weight in kg) + (height x 1,8 cm) - (4,7 x age);</p>

<p>For men: 66 + (13.7 x weight in kg) + (5 x height in cm) - (6.76 x age).</p>

<p>For example, take a woman 30 years Height 165 cm and weight 65 kg.</p>

<p>Its main exchange will be equal to: 655 + (9.6 x 65) + (1.8 x 165) - (4.7 x 30) = 655 + 624 + 297 - 141 = 1435 kcal/day.</p>

<p><strong><em>2. Next you need to determine your level of activity, as measured by the coefficient of activity:</em></strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Inactive (complete absence or rare sports activity) - 1.2;</li>
<li>Sedentary (light load 1-3 times a week) - 1,375;</li>
<li>Medium (load average 3-5 days a week) - 1.55;</li>
<li>Very active (full load 6-7 days a week) - 1,725;</li>
<li>Hyperactive (very high physical activity and physical work 7 days a week) - 1.9.</li>
</ul>


<p>For example, our woman working in the office, mostly sedentary work, to which she gets in transport. However, it is housekeeping, she loves to go shopping and sometimes wanders into a fitness club. So, its activity coefficient - 1.375.</p>

<p><strong><em>3. Now you need to determine daily intake of calories by the formula:</em></strong></p>

<p>The main metabolic activity coefficient x.</p>

<p>In our example, it is 1435 kcal/day x 1.375 = 1973 kcal/day.</p>

<p><strong><em>4. By subtracting from the resulting figure of 500 kcal, we get the amount of calories that we need to consume to lose weight.</em></strong></p>

<p><strong><em>5. In order not to drive themselves in such rigid framework, calculate the so-called &quot;corridor calories&quot; by the formulas:</em></strong></p>

<p>Energy intake for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> - 250 = lower limit</p>

<p>Kalorazh <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="slimming">slimming</a> +100 = upper limit.</p>

<p>That is, our women to lose weight, you need to keep your calorie daily diet within the 1223 - 1573 kcal/day.</p>

<p>In these calculations, it is important to remember that the daily calorie intake for women should not be lower than 1200 kcal. Calories less than this figure have a negative impact on health. 1200 calories a day - it is also very small, so it is better to consume more calories. Keeping within the corridor of calories, you will still lose weight.</p>

<p>To do this, go back to their energy capacity and percentage in the daily diet - 10-25% protein, 20-35% fat and 45-65% carbohydrates. And calculate what proportion they should take, given the upper and lower limit of the corridor calories.</p>

<p>For our example, it will have the following meanings:</p>

<p>So, to lose weight, a woman from the example should be consumed in a day 30.5 - 98 g protein, 27 - 61 grams of fat and 137.5 - 256 grams of carbohydrates.</p>

<p>Of course, this is a rough estimate, and these amounts are not necessarily comply with the accuracy of a tenth of a unit.</p>

<h2>Another obstacle on the road to weight loss</h2>

<p>We hope you have successfully reached the end of the calculations, and now in front of you is a piece of the figures, which you will need to make your diet. And how to be? Here begins the next portion of the complexities. In light of almost no foods which comprise only proteins, but only fats or carbohydrates - all products are mixed with a predominance of certain compounds. So 100 grams of meat is not equivalent to 100 grams of protein. And try to lead your diet in perfect match with the results of your arithmetic exercises you do not succeed.</p>

<p>The daily diet of a person must be present all the major macronutrients. Refusal or severely restricting some of them have a negative impact on your health and well-being. On the other hand, every person is different, and the need for those or other substances may also differ.</p>

<p>Counting the number of proteins, fats and carbohydrates - only one of many ways to achieve harmony and health. However, while one of the most difficult to execute. So it is not necessarily strictly follow it. You will achieve no less results if just eat varied, trying to eat less animal fat and sweets. And freed from the complex calculations time you can spend more usefully: first - on a visit to the gym, and then - to update the wardrobe&hellip;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
