<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Dietology | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/dietology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-05-01T17:38:43+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avocado Diet for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/avocado-diet-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-01T09:38:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/avocado-diet-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/avocado-diet-for-weight-loss/img.jpg" width="200" height="150" alt="Avocado diet: reviews of lost weight">For those who love sweetish fruit ripe avocado, there is a special diet that allows you to quickly get rid of excess weight.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>A diet with avocado: the essence, the benefits, advantages and disadvantages</h2>

<p>Due to the fact that oily taste the fruit is quite high in calories - 208 kilocalories per 100 grams, many question arises: is it possible to use the avocado diet?</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
It is worth bearing in mind that he quickly satisfies hunger, because to comply with the usual diet will need no more than 5 fruits per day and thus be able to eat no more than 1,100 kcal - this is a very small figure.</p>

<p>The essence of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> on a diet of avocados is precisely to reduce calorie intake, as well as its useful functions for the body:</p>

<ul>
<li>Avocados have no <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a> and it contains monounsaturated fatty acids perfectly clean vessels, eliminate cholesterol plaques and removal of residues;</li>
<li>Turning to your diet avocados contribute to a speedy cure digestive diseases, thyroid and stabilization in <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/cardiology/hypertension.html" title="hypertension">hypertension</a>, as well as skin rejuvenation.</li>
</ul>


<p>It is because of these useful properties of avocado diet is especially appreciated by physicians: they believe that this product is the best suited to make a slim figure.</p>

<h3>Pros and cons of diet with avocado</h3>

<p>In <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7">weight loss</span> with avocado has a number of advantages:</p>

<ul>
<li>The very diet transferred easily, because the ripe juicy fruit reduce appetite and quickly satisfy hunger;</li>
<li>Methods suitable for all, except for pregnant women, children and the elderly;</li>
<li>Many other products on the menu, if it is not strictly mono version.</li>
</ul>


<p>Use avocado diet has a small disadvantage: only one fruit can not be eaten for a long time, as this may lead to metabolic disorders.</p>

<h3>How much can you lose on a diet with avocado</h3>

<p>Calorie diet on the avocado, regardless of its particular species is never higher than 1500 kcal, which allows for 1 day to get rid of 800-900 g weight.</p>

<p>Many people wonder whether the volumes with avocado diet goes, and in this case it is important to know that weight loss always involves a reduction in its volume - in particular, hips and waist.</p>

<h3>Avocado and diet: what foods can be eaten</h3>

<p>During maintenance diet following products may be used in menu:</p>

<ul>
<li>Cereal porridge;</li>
<li>Fruits and vegetables;</li>
<li>Lean meat and fish;</li>
<li>Greenery;</li>
<li>Fermented beverages.</li>
</ul>


<p>Under the ban are all sweet, fatty, smoked or salted food, as they reduce the effectiveness of the diet on the avocado.</p>

<h2>Diet avocado diet menus, recipes, rules</h2>

<p><em>Diet rules with the help of an avocado:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>The fruit should be just ripe, and before use should be cut into two pieces, and remove pits;</li>
<li>Eat must be at least 4 times a day in small portions, and be sure to drink 2 liters of water daily.</li>
</ul>


<h3>A strict diet for avocados: Menu</h3>

<p>To lose up to 4 kilos, you need to follow this menu for the 3 days:</p>

<ul>
<li>Every day, we eat 5 fruit avocado, dividing them into several portions;</li>
<li>2 liters of drinking water, and more.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Avocado diet and yogurt</h3>

<p>A softer version of the three-day diet includes the following:</p>

<ul>
<li>Also, we eat at 5 avocados;</li>
<li>To drink 1 liter of nonfat yogurt.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Avocado diet avocado and cottage cheese</h3>

<p>For 5 days using this menu, you can lose weight by 5 kg:</p>

<ul>
<li>In the morning we eat half an avocado and 50 g of fat-free yogurt;</li>
<li>For lunch we eat a salad with cucumber, green onions, &frac12; avocado and egg;</li>
<li>Supper 100 g of boiled beef, a half avocado and boiled egg.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Avocado diet with ginger</h3>

<p>During the month of application of such a diet turns to throw up to 10 kg:</p>

<ul>
<li>We eat any food from the list of permitted;</li>
<li>For dinner, we eat 40 grams of avocado and drink tea with ginger.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet avocado puree</h3>

<p>This diet is suitable for fasting days:</p>

<ul>
<li>We eat up to 700 grams of mashed avocado pulp;</li>
<li>For breakfast, we eat, and further 100 g of cottage cheese.</li>
</ul>


<h3>A diet with avocado Julia Roberts</h3>

<p>The technique is designed for 28 days, during which the need to eat on the menu the following example:</p>

<ul>
<li>Steam have breakfast omelette and avocado;</li>
<li>For lunch drink fruit juice;</li>
<li>Lunch baked fish and vegetable salad;</li>
<li>Afternoon snack low-fat yogurt;</li>
<li>We have supper of boiled fish and 100 g of fruit.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Diet blueberry avocado and ginger</h3>

<p>According to the well-known TV presenter, there is the easiest way to lose weight with the help of three products:</p>

<ul>
<li>Avocado: eliminate fat;</li>
<li>Ginger: relieves bloating;</li>
<li>Blueberries: it reduces appetite and has anti-inflammatory effects.</li>
</ul>


<p>All three ingredients must be present in the diet, which is equal to the caloric content of 1500 kcal, while you can eat anything you want, adhering to the specified limit.</p>

<h3>Recipes for a diet with avocado</h3>

<p><em>Recipe mashed avocado:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Clear the number of fruit, remove them from the brush;</li>
<li>Pulp transform into a puree using a blender or corolla.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Recipe salad with avocado:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Boil chicken breast, cut into cubes it together with tomato, cucumber and avocado;</li>
<li>Mix, sprinkle with herbs and pour the lemon juice.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Recipe soup with avocado:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Boil potatoes, peeled avocado and zucchini;</li>
<li>Add salt and pepper;</li>
<li>Beat blender;</li>
<li>Before serving, add a little lemon juice.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Protein, Fat and Carbohydrates You Need in a Day to Lose Weight?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-much-protein-fat-and-carbohydrates-you-need-in-a-day-to-lose-weight/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-23T11:46:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/how-much-protein-fat-and-carbohydrates-you-need-in-a-day-to-lose-weight</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/how-much-protein-fat-and-carbohydrates-you-need-in-a-day-to-lose-weight/img.jpg" title="How much protein, fat and carbohydrates you need in a day to lose weight" alt="proteins as needed daily, as needed fat per day">Proteins, fats and carbohydrates <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="every day">every day</a> we get from food, and they are vital to us. These substances in a given amount contains almost any food and are called macronutrients. And why do we need them?</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Proteins - building blocks for all body cells. They are composed of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids/" title="amino acids">amino acids</a>, which are divided into essential and nonessential. Interchangeable can be synthesized in humans only essential to reach a food composition. Proteins are necessary for growth, development, and in general for any physiological process; thus, they are absolutely safe in terms of possible accumulation of excess weight. The sources of protein are meat, fish, dairy products and legumes.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Fats - are made up of fatty acids, which are divided into saturated, monounsaturated and polyunsaturated. Today at all on hearing beneficial omega-3 and omega-6 acids, belonging to the group of polyunsaturated and can lower <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a>. It is also necessary for the absorption of fats, vitamins, synthesis of a number of hormones, the normal operation of many systems of the body. They are contained in both animal food (meat, fish, dairy products) and plant (nuts, seeds, vegetable oil) origin. Excessive consumption of fat - a way to lose the harmony.</p>

<p>Carbohydrates - the main source of energy. They can be simple (glucose, sucrose, etc.) and complex (cellulose, glycogen). Splitting of carbohydrates gives the body energy, the unspent portion of which can be converted into body fat. The main sources of carbohydrates - fruits, vegetables, cereals and sweets.</p>

<p>The diet of an adult to maintain its health and permanent weight gain there should be a certain ratio of these nutrients. Thus, our daily menu should contain:</p>

<p>Once in the digestive system, proteins, fats and carbohydrates are exposed cleavage with release of energy necessary for vital processes. The resulting energy is measured in units - kilocalories (kcal), which, for brevity, often referred to as calories.</p>

<p>Energy value of macronutrients varies. 1 gram of carbohydrate and protein is cleaved to release 4 kcal, 1 gram of fat - 9 kcal.</p>

<h2>Caloric intake and the ratio of macronutrients for weight loss</h2>

<p>Weight person depends on how many calories enters the body, and how much is consumed. If these amounts are approximately equal, the mass remains stable. If it receives more calories than consumed energy postponed &quot;in reserve&quot; in the form of fat.</p>

<p>Accordingly, to reduce weight, it is necessary to spend more calories than is consumed with food.</p>

<p>To calculate daily calorie your diet and calculate the necessary amount of proteins, fats and carbohydrates, using a few simple formulas. Try to make the calculations for yourself using these formulas and examples.</p>

<p><strong><em>1. First you need to calculate your basal metabolism.</em></strong></p>

<p>For women: 655 + (9,6 x weight in kg) + (height x 1,8 cm) - (4,7 x age);</p>

<p>For men: 66 + (13.7 x weight in kg) + (5 x height in cm) - (6.76 x age).</p>

<p>For example, take a woman 30 years Height 165 cm and weight 65 kg.</p>

<p>Its main exchange will be equal to: 655 + (9.6 x 65) + (1.8 x 165) - (4.7 x 30) = 655 + 624 + 297 - 141 = 1435 kcal/day.</p>

<p><strong><em>2. Next you need to determine your level of activity, as measured by the coefficient of activity:</em></strong></p>

<ul>
<li>Inactive (complete absence or rare sports activity) - 1.2;</li>
<li>Sedentary (light load 1-3 times a week) - 1,375;</li>
<li>Medium (load average 3-5 days a week) - 1.55;</li>
<li>Very active (full load 6-7 days a week) - 1,725;</li>
<li>Hyperactive (very high physical activity and physical work 7 days a week) - 1.9.</li>
</ul>


<p>For example, our woman working in the office, mostly sedentary work, to which she gets in transport. However, it is housekeeping, she loves to go shopping and sometimes wanders into a fitness club. So, its activity coefficient - 1.375.</p>

<p><strong><em>3. Now you need to determine daily intake of calories by the formula:</em></strong></p>

<p>The main metabolic activity coefficient x.</p>

<p>In our example, it is 1435 kcal/day x 1.375 = 1973 kcal/day.</p>

<p><strong><em>4. By subtracting from the resulting figure of 500 kcal, we get the amount of calories that we need to consume to lose weight.</em></strong></p>

<p><strong><em>5. In order not to drive themselves in such rigid framework, calculate the so-called &quot;corridor calories&quot; by the formulas:</em></strong></p>

<p>Energy intake for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> - 250 = lower limit</p>

<p>Kalorazh <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="slimming">slimming</a> +100 = upper limit.</p>

<p>That is, our women to lose weight, you need to keep your calorie daily diet within the 1223 - 1573 kcal/day.</p>

<p>In these calculations, it is important to remember that the daily calorie intake for women should not be lower than 1200 kcal. Calories less than this figure have a negative impact on health. 1200 calories a day - it is also very small, so it is better to consume more calories. Keeping within the corridor of calories, you will still lose weight.</p>

<p>To do this, go back to their energy capacity and percentage in the daily diet - 10-25% protein, 20-35% fat and 45-65% carbohydrates. And calculate what proportion they should take, given the upper and lower limit of the corridor calories.</p>

<p>For our example, it will have the following meanings:</p>

<p>So, to lose weight, a woman from the example should be consumed in a day 30.5 - 98 g protein, 27 - 61 grams of fat and 137.5 - 256 grams of carbohydrates.</p>

<p>Of course, this is a rough estimate, and these amounts are not necessarily comply with the accuracy of a tenth of a unit.</p>

<h2>Another obstacle on the road to weight loss</h2>

<p>We hope you have successfully reached the end of the calculations, and now in front of you is a piece of the figures, which you will need to make your diet. And how to be? Here begins the next portion of the complexities. In light of almost no foods which comprise only proteins, but only fats or carbohydrates - all products are mixed with a predominance of certain compounds. So 100 grams of meat is not equivalent to 100 grams of protein. And try to lead your diet in perfect match with the results of your arithmetic exercises you do not succeed.</p>

<p>The daily diet of a person must be present all the major macronutrients. Refusal or severely restricting some of them have a negative impact on your health and well-being. On the other hand, every person is different, and the need for those or other substances may also differ.</p>

<p>Counting the number of proteins, fats and carbohydrates - only one of many ways to achieve harmony and health. However, while one of the most difficult to execute. So it is not necessarily strictly follow it. You will achieve no less results if just eat varied, trying to eat less animal fat and sweets. And freed from the complex calculations time you can spend more usefully: first - on a visit to the gym, and then - to update the wardrobe&hellip;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cottage Cheese Diet Maggie. Menu Curd Diet Maggi]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/cottage-cheese-diet-maggie-menu-curd-diet-maggi/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-21T16:55:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/cottage-cheese-diet-maggie-menu-curd-diet-maggi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/cottage-cheese-diet-maggie-menu-curd-diet-maggi/img.jpg" title="Cottage cheese diet Maggie. Menu curd diet Maggi" alt="cottage cheese diet maggi menu">Diet Maggi and its variety - egg and cheese - has been repeatedly mentioned earlier. About the egg we discussed in great detail, the time came to light the principles cheese Maggi, which enjoys enough popular among people who want to lose weight.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>It can be described as: a low-calorie, low-fat, low-carb, high-protein. At first glance, perfect, containing no food components, is converted into fat, and includes only the necessary nutrients for life. In general, this diet is really very effective and, importantly, not &quot;hungry&quot;, but it has its drawbacks, which we will touch upon later.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Diet lasts 4 weeks, and during this time you need to follow a well-defined menu, which occupies a central place cottage cheese. Excesses and going beyond the list of approved products is prohibited; not recommended even pick up food analogues suggested, for example, replace the chicken. If the menu designated fruit or vegetables, among the first need not <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/choosing-a-anti-stretch-marks-cream-after-giving-birth/" title="choose">choose</a> sweet (grape, melon, dried fruit, bananas), and among the second preference amyloid (especially potatoes).</p>

<p>Be sure to drink at least two liters of fluid per day; it can be tea, coffee, mineral water. Sweetening drinks, of course, impossible.</p>

<p>Creator warned that the slightest deviation from the prescribed diet - and diet does not work, stop ubavka weight, kilograms and then come back, so that any failure of supposedly required to start a diet again. We can not say that this statement seems to be true; This is likely just some measure of deterrence, which raises awareness at losing weight and motivates them to the strict implementation of the rules of cottage cheese diet Maggie. But in fact, rare and small errors in the menu do not carry such harm, as promised harsh author so casually allowing freedom in the diet, it is not necessary to return to the menu, the first day of the diet and then resign ourselves to a month of severe deprivation. This is not only pointless, but for some people may not be useful, given the kind of load on the body creates a <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="protein diet">high-protein diet</a> either.</p>

<h2>Menu curd diet Maggi</h2>

<p>It is not particularly different from the egg option, the biggest difference is that instead of eggs is recommended to use low-fat cottage cheese.</p>

<p><strong>Day 1.</strong> Morning: fruit, 200 g of cottage cheese. Day: any fruit. Evening: a little bit of beef, vegetable salad.</p>

<p><strong>Day 2.</strong> Morning: Same Day 1. Day: boiled chicken breast. Evening: fish, vegetable salad, 1 slice of the dried bread, 1 grapefruit or orange.</p>

<p><strong>Day 3.</strong> Morning: Same Day 1. Day: low-fat cheese or cottage cheese, 1 slice of the dried bread, tomatoes. Evening: meat, vegetables.</p>

<p><strong>Day 4.</strong> Morning: the same. Day: any fruit. Evening: meat, vegetables.</p>

<p><strong>Day 5.</strong> Morning: as the day 1. Day: 2 eggs, vegetables. Evening: fish, vegetables, 1 orange or a grapefruit.</p>

<p><strong>Day 6.</strong> Morning: as the day 1. Day: any fruit. Evening: meat, vegetables.</p>

<p><strong>Day 7.</strong> Morning: as the day 1. Day: chicken, cooked vegetables, tomatoes, 1 grapefruit or orange. Evening: boiled vegetables.</p>

<p><strong>Day 1.</strong> Morning: The same as in the first week. Day: cottage cheese and vegetables. Evening: fish, vegetables, grapefruit or orange.</p>

<p><strong>Day 4.</strong> Morning: the same. Day of cheese or cottage cheese, plus any vegetables. Evening: meat or fish, vegetables.</p>

<p><strong>Day 5.</strong> Morning: the same. Day: fish (shrimp), vegetables. Evening: fruit, cottage cheese.</p>

<p><strong>Day 6.</strong> Morning: the same. Day: meat, grapefruit or orange tomatoes. Evening: any fruit.</p>

<p><strong>Day 7.</strong> Morning: the same. Day: chicken, tomatoes, boiled vegetables, grapefruit or orange. Evening: the same as during the day.</p>

<p>In the third and fourth week of the list of products provided for the whole day, the products are distributed on the meals yourself.</p>

<p><strong>Day 3.</strong> Boiled vegetables, fresh vegetables, fresh fruit.</p>

<p><strong>Day 1.</strong> A little meat or chicken (200 g), 2 cucumbers, 3 tomatoes, fruit, 1 slice of bread, the dried, Bank of canned tuna without oil.</p>

<p><strong>Day 2.</strong> Similarly, only without the chicken (you can meat) and tuna.</p>

<p><strong>Day 3.</strong> 400 grams of cottage cheese, a piece of boiled vegetables, 2 tomato and cucumber 1 slice of bread, fruit.</p>

<p><strong>Day 4.</strong> Chicken 500 g, 3 tomatoes, 1 cucumber, 1 slice of bread, the dried fruit.</p>

<p><strong>Day 6.</strong> The hen, a little cheese or cottage cheese, 1 slice of bread, 2 cucumbers and tomatoes, fruit, yogurt.</p>

<p><strong>Day 7.</strong> 400 g of cottage cheese, a portion of boiled vegetables, cans of tuna, 2 tomato and cucumber, the dried slice of bread, fruit.</p>

<p>This diet is over, however, limit caloric intake to maintain the progress achieved is to comply in the future. Furthermore, the transition to its regular diet recommended gradually for about a week.</p>

<h2>Reviews and Results</h2>

<p>As already mentioned, the diet is in great demand - first of all, because it allows us to achieve significant results. On average, it can help people manage to lose 5 to 10 kilos, depending on the amount of food eaten (<a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="at home">at home</a> several days a number of foods you can eat all you want, but it is a great temptation), and level of physical activity.</p>

<p>Against the background of fitness rate of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/gone-month-after-weight-loss-how-to-restore-the-month-following-the-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>, as might be expected, increases, but many note that due to the low power energy value of their sporting achievements largely affected: fatigue sets in more quickly, decreasing resistance to <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/psychology/stress.html" title="stress">stress</a>. If it appears moderately and fatigue does not apply to daily activities, do not pay attention to it: a little lack of energy against the backdrop of high-protein food is natural and expected. That it brings you as little as possible of experiences, choose those kinds of loads, which are easier for you, such as <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/why-should-you-run-benefits-and-harms-of-running/" title="jogging">jogging</a> or swimming breaststroke instead of strength training.</p>

<h2>Contraindications and precautions</h2>

<p>A person with good health can go without losing much required 4 weeks curd diet Maggi, but the presence of certain diseases such change of the composition of food can be dangerous. It is contraindicated for people suffering from <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/constipation.html" title="constipation">constipation</a>, exacerbation of diseases of the gastrointestinal tract (any!), To patients with liver disease, and especially with kidney disease, accompanied by violation of their functions. These people attempt to lose weight through diet Maggie can end is not particularly impressive. At best, they just have to interrupt their efforts and left with nothing, and at worst it leads to hospitalization.</p>

<p>To diet have harmed before its compliance costs to make sure that your health will not fail. If there is any doubt on this score, not too lazy to visit their primary care physician and nutritionist, both professionals and ask the same question as in your case it is advisable to observance of cheese diet. Do not worry if you advise to choose some other method of weight loss, even if he will not be as efficient and fast. The main thing that should interest you - it does not desire to put on as soon as possible is that little dress or jeans, and the ability to safely lose weight by following a diet that you can enjoy life and its &quot;new&quot; figure, and not to pass long-term treatment of its consequences.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[For What Needed Amino Acids?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-06T10:55:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/for-what-needed-amino-acids/img.jpg" title="For what needed amino acids?" alt="amino acids, how to make amino acids, amino acids for weight loss, essential amino acids, amino acids for muscle growth, what are amino acids">Amino acids - are chemical compounds that comprise proteins. When the human digestive tract gets protein foods, using special enzymes, it is split into amino acids. Only then it can be assimilated. Small-sized molecules penetrate the amino acids from the intestine into the blood, and then the body can use them for their own purposes.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>


<p>Amino acids perform many important functions in the body. They can be divided into plastic and energy. Plastic functions are built from amino acids of the protein molecules that make up all the tissues of our body. Because amino acids are not only bodies, but also biologically active substances: enzymes, certain hormones, neurotransmitters. The energy function is the splitting of the amino acids in order to release energy.</p>

<p>To maintain human life he needed only 20 species of amino acids, although they exist in nature much more. They are divided into three groups:</p>

<ul>
<li>Interchangeable - can be synthesized in the body from chemical compounds having a non-protein origin;</li>
<li>Conditionally replaceable - are synthesized in a limited number;</li>
<li>Essential - are not synthesized in the body.</li>
</ul>


<p>Man receives daily amino acids from food. Most of them are found in meat, fish, eggs, milk and other animal products. The richest vegetable source of protein is soy and other legumes, but they contain less essential amino acids.</p>

<h2>What are amino acids common man?</h2>

<p>Everyone needs amino acids. None of these chemical compounds, we can not synthesize protein. If the amino acids are no longer come from the outside, the body begins to break down its own tissues and organs, to compensate for their deficits. The absence of even one essential amino acid in the human diet leads to severe disease.</p>

<p>The source of these materials were previously only foods. Today amino acids produced by many pharmaceutical companies as supplements or drugs. Some of them are designed for the treatment of certain diseases, others are used by athletes to build muscle. With the purpose of treatment of amino acids into the reception - this is an expensive and inefficient pleasure.</p>

<p>There are many medications on the basis of amino acids, which are used for parenteral nutrition patients. If a person can not eat food alone, he poured the amino acid solutions intravenously. Often because of these drugs the doctors save patient lives, as in the period of severe illness when the body&rsquo;s plastic processes are active, the body needs protein more than usual.</p>

<h2>What are amino acids during training?</h2>

<p>Most athletes who are engaged in bodybuilding, taking protein powders. They use it as an additional source of protein to build muscle mass quickly. Alternatively the protein amino acid solutions are applied. Pharmaceutical companies argue that they are more effective than the protein obtained from food as well as familiar to most athletes protein powders.</p>

<p>True or not? Most companies that produce amino acids for athletes, convince us of the veracity of this information. But their interest is obvious: the amino acids of the protein are much more expensive, so bring more income from sales. For the successful promotion of the product on the market was invented so-called &quot;protein window&quot; or &quot;protein corridor&quot;.</p>

<p>&quot;Protein box&quot; - a period of time after the workout, which is considered optimal for protein <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a>. It is 40-50 minutes. During this period the athlete should learn the most protein to gain muscle growth. If the late bodybuilder, muscles will grow more slowly. But the protein from foods like protein powders, slowly digested, so the athlete has only one chance to catch up to the closing &quot;window of protein&quot;. To do this, take the amino acid solution.</p>

<p>Unlike the protein, amino acids absorbed from the intestine immediately without pretreatment with proteolytic enzymes. Their concentration in the blood rises sharply after 15-20 minutes after taking the supplements. Thus, a person has time to deliver the amino acids in muscle, while &quot;protein window&quot; remains open.</p>

<p>It is quite logical to study the benefits of amino acids in protein loved athletes. Very often in the specialized literature for bodybuilders can find information about the &quot;protein window&quot;. But studies have shown that intake of protein and amino acids provides identical results athletes during training. &quot;Protein window&quot; hardly exists, although the myth about him still wanders from book to book, stimulating the sale of free amino acids.</p>

<p>BCAA - three amino acids, most commonly used in the training. These include isoleucine, valine and leucine. It is these amino acids are part of the majority of sports supplements for bodybuilders. The main effects of BCAA:</p>

<ul>
<li>The accelerated build-up of muscle mass;</li>
<li>Increasing strength athlete;</li>
<li>Reduction of body fat mass.</li>
</ul>


<p>There is no doubt the benefits of BCAA bodybuilder. With them he will reach sports results. They are rapidly absorbed and have high bioavailability, are easy to use. But the lack of supplements based on amino acids BCAA is the price. They are expensive, but a similar result can be obtained by an athlete using whey protein.</p>

<p>Amino BCAA available in different dosage forms. There capsules and solutions, but less likely to take the supplement in powder form. It is recognized that the powder is less convenient to use: it is poorly soluble in the liquid and has a bitter taste. Ready amino acid solutions are tastier, more convenient to use and transport, but are more expensive.</p>

<p>Take BCAA recommended 1 teaspoon (4-5 grams), from 1 to 3 times a day. Amino acids are allowed to be combined with any other sports nutrition. Of course, it makes no sense to take them together with protein, since these additives have the same mechanism of action, although some people do it to save money.</p>

<p>Amino acids - are chemical substances, of which built all the proteins in our body. A person must receive them regularly with food to stay healthy. Athletes who are building up the muscles need additional source of amino acids. Especially important for them leucine, valine, isoleucine, which are abbreviated as BCAA. Supplements containing amino acids, convenient to use and easily digested. However, they are expensive, so as a source of amino acids most athletes use a cheaper but equally effective protein powder.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Soybeans: Benefits and Harms, Doctor Review]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-04T15:52:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review.jpg" title="Black soybeans: benefits and harms, doctor review" alt="Black soybeans">Black soybean - a product that is used in traditional Chinese medicine. It is considered a source of balance. Therapeutic effects: replenishes blood levels, nourishing yin, expels wind, strengthens weakened, normalizes the activity of the channels of stomach and spleen. In Russia, black soybeans also find healing, but its effect is usually described using different terminology, more understandable to our man.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>


<p>Black soybean useful in exactly the same extent that and soy white or yellow. This is a common legume has a high protein content and insoluble dietary fiber. There is hardly any sense to use it as a medicine. Black soybean much more suitable for use in food. Nevertheless, she decided to attribute the following useful properties:</p>

<ul>
<li>Normalizes nervous activity;</li>
<li>Cures cancer (probably not in the world of plants, which it does not cure, according to admirers of traditional medicine);</li>
<li>To protect people from the harmful effects of the environment;</li>
<li>Reduces the level of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a> in the blood;</li>
<li>Promotes weight loss.</li>
</ul>


<p>All these inventions. This can be read on virtually any product of plant origin. Perhaps black soy and healthy if its systematic use in food, but cancer or diabetes, it is certainly not cures.</p>

<p>Black soybean contains no toxic compounds for the organism. The damage is only possible with overeating or the presence of diseases of the digestive system. Disadvantages of the product:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>High calorie</strong> - do not pass at a weight problem;</li>
<li><strong>High fiber content</strong> - possible bloating, changes in the frequency and stool consistency;</li>
<li><strong>Small size, dense texture, slippery edge</strong> - a man with a deficit of intelligence can strangle if Bob gets into the respiratory tract.</li>
</ul>


<p>People with normal mental development and good health black soybeans can not hurt anything. Eat without fear for their health.</p>

<p>On the Internet a lot of popularity gained supplement for weight loss called &quot;black soybeans&quot;. The advertisement says that it is delivered directly from Japan. It is not clear why they are doing, because it is a good idea in Russia is growing.</p>

<p>At sells website reported that the secret of longevity of the Japanese, finally revealed! It turns out the high life expectancy - a consequence of regular consumption of black soya.</p>

<p>Take supplements you offer for the following purposes:</p>

<p><strong>1. Weight Loss.</strong> The main purpose of black soya. Weight reduction is due to increasing the activity of fat cells. Those allegedly begin to burn fat, regardless of the amount of food consumed by you, including, if you have no physical activity. In addition, thanks to soy protein, according to advertising, the muscles grow without any training.
<strong>2. Improvement by saturating the body with useful substances.</strong> The site Product asserts that certain vitamins, minerals and amino acids are contained only in black soybeans. Nowhere in nature, they are no more. I wonder what kind of minerals are? If you would like Mendeleev heard, he probably would have got out of the coffin to burn his table of chemical elements.
<strong>3. Rejuvenation.</strong> It is due to dietary fiber (which, incidentally, are in any plant food). The body is rejuvenated as a result of lightning elimination of toxins under the influence of black soy from Japan. After that, according to the suppliers of goods, there is a surge of energy forces in the cell, and you feel much better.</p>

<p>Due to what effect this wonder-drug that reduces weight and rejuvenate the body? If you believe the official site, as part contains the following components:</p>

<p><strong>Proteins.</strong> Present in any food products. They are a source of calories. Promote weight loss, but only if used in place of fatty and sugary foods, not in addition to it.</p>

<p><strong>Vitamins A and E.</strong> So these vitamins, which are found nowhere else in nature, except for black soy! Or is there? Yes, still there. Vitamin A is full in carrots and other yellow vegetables, and vitamin E in abundance found in vegetable oils. Both components are useful for health, weight loss but not in any way contribute.</p>

<p><strong>B vitamins</strong> are present in many other foods. Good for your health, but they do not lose weight and look younger.</p>

<p><strong>Alimentary fiber.</strong> In fact contribute to weight loss. But only if the abundance of dietary fiber in the diet causes decrease in consumption of other foods. By themselves, they do not burn fat.</p>

<p><strong>Amino acids.</strong> This protein structural components, so that in fact when transferring the composition manufacturer repeats the same material twice. As mentioned above, from the proteins do not lose weight if they are a supplement, not a substitute for the usual ration.</p>

<p><strong>Trace elements.</strong> What kind of minerals are in the black soybeans - the manufacturer is not recognized. Given that nowhere in other products do not, in general, these micronutrients to mankind is not known, to evaluate their real impact on the shape and health is very difficult.</p>

<p>Black soybean are sold as a concentrate. You will receive a jar of powder. It must be diluted in a glass of water and drink before each meal, three times a den.Takoe use of black soya will help in weight loss, as it will reduce appetite.</p>

<p>Of course, this will not happen because of the presence of this plant amazing fat-burning properties. Hunger subsides as the day before the meal in the stomach will be less space. As a result, you eat less. If this happens regularly for at least several months, you will eventually be able to normalize the figures.</p>

<p>Black soybeans - is one of hundreds or thousands of useless goods for figure and health that is actively circulating on the Internet. It pacifiers in a beautiful package. They are sold on the colorfully decorated sites and skillfully advertised, but because demand. Nevertheless, the man who would be able to lose weight and rejuvenate with the help of black soybean, the world does not know.</p>

<p>This product is recommended to buy the people:</p>

<ul>
<li>The rich - who do not consider $ 40 money, worthy of attention;</li>
<li>Curious - who are used to check for yourself;</li>
<li>Stupid - who believed in a bright, but not the most convincing and reasoned advertising;</li>
<li>Desperate - who wants nothing to do with his own figure and wants to clear his conscience, allegedly fighting <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a> even with the help of useless supplements.</li>
</ul>


<p>The rest of the people recommended to use other methods of weight loss. There are supplements better. However, keep in mind that without the support of the diet and increase physical activity, no medication is not going to work.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
