<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: dietology | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/dietology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-12-02T20:59:08+06:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diet products for varicose blood thinning and foods that thin blood]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-products-for-varicose-blood-thinning-and-foods-that-thin-blood/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-02T20:50:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-products-for-varicose-blood-thinning-and-foods-that-thin-blood</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/foods-that-thin-blood/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/foods-that-thin-blood/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Diet for varicose veins, blood thinning products, foods that thin blood, varicose veins diet&rsquo; &lsquo;Diet products for varicose blood thinning and foods that thin blood&rsquo;" > Diet for varicose thins the blood and improves venous blood flow. Proper nutrition and therapeutic diet for varicose plays a huge role in the treatment and prevention of disease, as it allows not only to reduce excess weight, thereby significantly reducing the burden on travmatiruyuschuyu diseased veins, but also by good selection of food, thin out the blood and significantly improve.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>For the prevention of varicose veins is first necessary to eliminate the risk factors that create additional pressure on the venous system, the most damaging of which are the extra pounds. The more overweight a person is thicker than the subcutaneous layer of fat, the greater the pressure exerted on the blood vessel wall that is not made of concrete.</p>

<p>This is why people who are overweight, even without overt signs of varicose veins is strictly forbidden to lift weights over 5 pounds, as an additional burden on the lifted weight greatly increases the pressure on the blood vessels and worsens their condition until critical.</p>

<h2>Diet for varicose veins</h2>

<p>Diet for varicose veins is designed to restore proper nutrition, promotes the normalization of weight and transpose blood clotting &ndash; a major risk of varicose veins.</p>

<p>As you know, in varicose veins the blood becomes thick and viscous, causing blood particles &ldquo;stick together&rdquo; to form clots in various parts of the body, usually in the groin, behind the knees and calves, which is a very dangerous condition. The high viscosity of the blood increases the risk of blood clots in the blood vessels and the heart, so the task of thinning it is of paramount importance.</p>

<p>Hemodilution contributes not only diet but also enough drinking regime, as blood is 90% of the water. According to doctors, all vascular patients drink too little of plain water, but for them it is a matter of life and death, especially in the heat. It was in the heat dramatically increases the number of heart attacks and strokes &ndash; a person sweats, loses a lot of moisture, and the vessels are much narrower and the blood thickens.</p>

<p>Therefore, to make the body physiological costs and ensure the usefulness of metabolic processes, you need to drink daily for at least 2 &ndash; 2.5 liters of good quality water &ndash; this is the first natural remedy for thinning the blood, which is always at hand. When used as a dirty, chlorinated water or unstructured body expends a lot of energy at the intracellular level, to transform it.</p>

<p>In addition to water, you can drink green or mint tea and natural fruit and vegetable juices. Especially useful for varicose veins are considered juice from red grapes, lemon, orange, tomato, cranberry and any sour grapes. From beer and alcohol should be avoided, as they are diuretic foods that contribute to dehydration and thickening of blood.</p>

<p>This thickened blood thinners for its active physicians prescribe drugs aspirin because it contains salicylic acid (vitamin C), according to research scientists, not only substantially reduces the viscosity of the blood, but also reduces the workload on the heart muscle and reduces the risk of cardiac and  But all is not rosy as it might seem at first glance. Permissible safe therapeutic dose of aspirin should not exceed 75-100 mg per day, and the excess of it, not only negates the positive effect, but also leads to the opposite result &ndash; the incessant nosebleeds to fatal internal blood loss.</p>

<p>Increasing the dose of aspirin leads to sweatshops effect and blood clots. Therefore, independent, without a doctor&rsquo;s prescription, taking aspirin for the &ldquo;prevention&rdquo; rather than sin in recent years, many people, eating handfuls of it, is totally unacceptable. In addition, it should be noted that aspirin, even intravenous use, very aggressive effect on the digestive tract and cause erosion and ulcers in the stomach wall.</p>

<h2>Foods that thin blood</h2>

<p>Forming the diet menu for varicose veins, you know that there are natural products that contribute to thinning the blood better than aspirin &ndash; they who must always be present on your desktop. For example, a few spoonfuls of raspberry jam, in its effect replace aspirin. And vice versa &ndash; the foods that thin blood, should be possible to eliminate from your diet.</p>

<p>Of vascular doctors generally advise patients to hang in a prominent place in the kitchen are two lists &ndash; the &ldquo;white&rdquo; list of foods and blood thinners &ldquo;black&rdquo; list of banned products, which it is concentrated and strictly check with them their food. After all, our health, by and large, had read it to the dinner table and each product has its own power supply &ldquo;chemistry&rdquo;.</p>

<p>Diet for varicose veins should primarily be aimed at improving the work of the liver, as in all patients varices, deviations in its work. Do not forget that the liver is called the chemical laboratory of the body &ndash; it is responsible for all metabolic processes and generates the necessary substances that prevent blood clots. If the liver is healthy, then the formation of clots in blood vessels, in principle, impossible. But, unfortunately, poor environment, poor diet, alcohol, drugs and an abundance of forcing her to work at full capacity.</p>

<p>Therefore, proper nutrition with varicose veins should be as restrictive of the liver, you need to limit fats, meats, pickles, preserves, sausages, meat broth, jelly, cream and white bread. In addition to the &ldquo;black list&rdquo; of foods that thin blood, are bananas, mango, rose, lentils, walnuts, chokeberry, aronia juice and pomegranate.</p>

<p>A list of useful products, blood thinners, big enough &ndash; flaxseed and olive oil, fish and fish oil, tomato juice, apple cider vinegar, lemons, grapefruit, sunflower seeds, chocolate, cocoa, beets, berries (raspberries, cranberries, blueberries, strawberries,  Regular use of garlic in food, according to research by scientists, is capable of existing clots sucked in half, so try to regularly introduce garlic to your diet.</p>

<p>Additionally, the menu should include products containing magnesium, which inhibits the formation of blood clots. A lot of magnesium is found in oatmeal, oat flour, oatmeal and ginger.</p>

<p>As for herbs, patients with varicose veins should be taken to use them with great caution, as the grass &ndash; it is a serious drug that courses need to be used under medical supervision. For example, the most popular herbs in the people, have the ability to thicken the blood, and therefore contraindicated in patients with vascular &ndash; nettle, St. John&rsquo;s wort, yarrow, corn silk, valerian, mountaineer pochechuyny.</p>

<p>Of useful herbs that promote the resorption of blood clots and do not allow adhesion of red blood cells, can be called hazel, Bees, chicory, meadowsweet (meadowsweet), and wormwood. Chicory leaves useful in cutting lettuce, Bees and add meadowsweet tea and hazelnuts consumed in all kinds.</p>

<p>Typically, the ordering of food and proper diet, soon there is a significant improvement in the disease course. Many doctors argue that without surgery can cure any containers (not only vessels of the lower limbs) &ndash; if the time to cleanse the body of toxins, regular use in food products and blood thinning seek the help of natural remedies.</p>

<p>If you already have thrombophlebitis, very useful to regularly eat a mixture of onions, garlic, honey and lemon. Mix 200 g onions, garlic, 100 grams, 50 grams and 100 grams of lemon honey. and take 3 times a day for 1 tsp</p>

<p>To solve the problem of varicose veins, then revise their bad habits as alcohol, smoking and drugs (especially birth control, hormone and diuretics) significantly increase the viscosity of the blood. You also need to protect themselves from possible stress and engage in moderate exercise, since the inactivity red blood cells literally &ldquo;stick&rdquo; to the walls of blood vessels. A set of special physical exercises to help stop the development of varicose veins and prevent its progression, discussed in detail in the article on our website.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diet for blood type 3 and blood type 4 diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-for-blood-type-3-and-blood-type-4-diet/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-02T20:48:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-for-blood-type-3-and-blood-type-4-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/diet-for-blood-type-3-4/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/diet-for-blood-type-3-4/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Blood type diet, diet for blood type 3, diet for blood type 4&rsquo; &lsquo;Diet for blood type 3, and blood type 4 diet&rsquo;" > Blood type diet is simple, effective and useful. Blood type diet by Dr. Peter D'Adamo has gained immense popularity all over the world, because it is very simple, effective and useful. Ease of it is that, when it is not necessary to calculate the compliance scores, indexes, calories and grams, as in other diet programs.</p>

<p>The efficiency of the power system is that it is very natural and offers catering exclusively products that are genetically adapted to the digestive tract of a particular person, that provides a great metabolism.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>In addition, the blood type diet is healthy as eating the recommended &ldquo;proper&rdquo; food, people not only lose weight, but at the same time heals. According to Dr. D'Adamo, useful products act in the body as the most effective medicine, neutral &ndash; provide its power and energy, and harmful &ndash; poison, destroy and old.</p>

<p>The previous was described in detail the essence of the diet for blood type, classification and evolution of blood types in the world, as well as recommendations for the preparation of the menu for the first and second types.</p>

<h2>Diet for blood type 3 (type B)</h2>

<p>Diet for blood type is the third mixed and balanced, as &ldquo;nomads&rdquo; are omnivorous and equally well with a meat, dairy products and plant foods. People of this type generally have a strong immune, nervous system, strong and well adapted to changes in the diet and environment. But, despite this, unbalanced diet may be an autoimmune disease and a rare virus and are at risk for multiple sclerosis, chronic fatigue syndrome and diabetes type 1.</p>

<p>Diet for weight loss in type people should avoid to the maximum foods that are high in sugar, fat, fried and smoked food, as the latter contribute to weight gain and adversely affect the liver. At the time, it is recommended to eat a diet low interest milk and milk products, vegetables (except tomatoes, pumpkins and olives), fruits, legumes, eggs and cereals (except buckwheat and wheat).</p>

<p>Of the preferred meat lamb, beef and turkey, pork should be excluded because of the high fat content, and a chicken because of its long digestion in people with the third type of blood. Should also be avoided during weight loss contribute to weight gain buckwheat, corn and peanuts, which reduce insulin production, slowing the body&rsquo;s metabolism and contribute to water retention. Give up sodas, and tomato juice, drink plenty of water, green tea and juices &ndash; cranberry, grape, pineapple, cabbage.</p>

<p>People with the third type of blood lose weight is relatively easy compared to other types, as they for weight loss, the exclusion from the diet of fatty foods, meats, fried foods and limit the use of &ldquo;binding&rdquo; fruit &ndash; persimmon, coconut, pomegranate, peanuts. Therefore, they can recommend any protein or carbohydrate diet &ndash; perfect rice, oats, kefir or any other mono-diet (except buckwheat), and the results of weight loss usually appear very quickly after the start of its implementation. In humans type suitable even &ldquo;chocolate diet&rdquo;, provided that the chocolate is black and no sugar added.</p>

<h2>Diet for blood type 4 (type AB)</h2>

<p>The fourth type is the young blood and rare (about 5% of the population), and its owners are sensitive and delicate digestive tract and the immune system is very vulnerable, are not resistant to microbes and cons of having both types &ndash; A and B. People of this type often suffer reduced hemoglobin, and also have a predisposition to heart disease and cancer.</p>

<p>Due to the combinations of types A and B in the preparation of a diet frequently occur since the same person can be reduced gastric acidity (type A) while adapting to the meat (Type B). In this case, although the programming of meat consumption, for its digestion lacks gastric juice, which ultimately leads to the deposition of fat. With this option, you need to limit the amount of meat consumed and increase the intake of vegetables and tofu, which is a great source of protein for both type A and type B for</p>

<p>The same problem often occurs when using buckwheat, corn and beans, as for type A, they are the perfect products recommended, and in type to the slow metabolism and promote weight gain. Therefore, for type AB should avoid these products, as well as products made from wheat because it contains gluten, contributing to weight gain.</p>

<p><strong>Special dietary recommendations for type AB:</strong></p>

<p>Useful low-fat meat products &ndash; turkey, lamb, rabbit, pork is prohibited, fatty lamb, goose, duck.
Recommended dairy products &ndash; yogurt, low-fat cheese and sour cream; eliminated whole milk, and butter.
Useful to use olive oil, but from sunflower and corn should be avoided.
Bread and cereals.
Of bakery products and cereals can be eaten bread from rye and wheat germ, oatmeal, rice cereal and millet; prohibited baking, buckwheat, corn flakes.
Of all the vegetables are recommended, except olives, peppers and corn, are excluded from the fruit bananas, mangoes, persimmons, oranges, coconut and grenades.
Other banned products.
On a diet give up the ketchup, vinegar, pepper, black tea, orange juice, sunflower seeds.</p>

<p>As you can see, the diet for Type AB is not very strict, so it does not require radically change dietary habits, need only to be upgraded by replacing the fat to lean meat, and other high-calorie and fatty foods to a more appropriate.</p>

<h3>Exercise as an adjunct to diet</h3>

<p>Moderate regular exercise are a great addition to the diet in the fight against excess weight. So, for the first type of people are most effective intense aerobics, skiing, swimming and running, for the second type is more suited calm and focus yoga and tai chi, and for the third and fourth &ndash; balanced sports (swimming, yoga, cycling, walking.</p>

<h3>Cautions on a diet</h3>

<p>It should be noted that the blood type diet, despite their effectiveness, can be harmful to the elderly in relation to age-related changes in the body, as well as for patients with certain health problems.</p>

<p>For example, the first and second type of diabetes, hypertension and cardiovascular diseases need to limit the consumption of meat and increased consumption of raw fruits and vegetables, even one blood type, because if power is not adjusted to reflect these features can significantly harm  Same people with anemia or a lack of protein, on the contrary, increase the consumption of meat in the diet, regardless of the type of.</p>

<p>The call to increase the consumption of dairy products can be harmful in congenital lactose intolerance, and vice versa, limiting them can provoke a lack of calcium and bone problems.</p>

<p>Furthermore, any unbalanced diet is known to cause both a lack of essential nutrients, and their excess that equally good for the body. People suffering from diabetes, liver disease, kidney disease or ischemic heart disease, it is not recommended to strictly adhere to supply the same blood type. Throughout the need to comply with the measure, common sense and strict medical supervision chosen diet.</p>

<p>In conclusion, I would like to point out that we should not scrupulously follow the recommendations listed above, be sure to listen to your body and heed its own individual characteristics. It is important that your food was not painful and agonizing, and strengthened health, pleasure and joy of life.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blood type diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/blood-type-diet/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-02T20:45:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/blood-type-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/blood-type-diet/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/blood-type-diet/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Blood type diet, blood type diet first, blood type diet second&rsquo; &lsquo;Blood type diet&rsquo;" > Blood type diet, authored by an American doctor, naturopath Peter J. Adamo, has received wide popularity around the world because it helps not only lose weight but also to normalize the body&rsquo;s metabolism, prevent the development of various diseases and provide excellent health.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>The essence of the blood type diet</h2>

<p>The essence of the blood type diet is that people with different blood types genetically incorporated different digestibility of the same products. Author of the procedure have noticed that, for example, recommended by many nutritionists, vegetarian diets are yielding positive results are not everything &ndash; for some people, they are not only useless, but also significantly impair the health.</p>

<p>In fact, his research has shown that some of the products that can help a person lose weight with one type of blood may even be harmful for people with another type. It is because of incorrectly matched individual menus, according to Dr. D'Adamo, a person gets fat, sick, and does damage to your health.</p>

<p>Since weight gain is usually the result of disturbances in the body metabolism, correctly made diet excludes from the diet is the foods that are toxic to a particular person, poorly digested and can not be absorbed. Thus, the blood type diet, eliminating &ldquo;harmful&rdquo; foods, helps to not only lose weight but also to cleanse the toxins that are known to be deposited in the fat depots. In addition, natural food products that corresponds to the type of blood heals entire gastro &ndash; intestinal tract and allergies disappear.</p>

<h2>The Evolution of blood types</h2>

<p>The Evolution of blood types (from first to fourth) took place gradually over the centuries as a result of adaptation of digestive and immune system to changing environmental conditions. Thus, the first type of blood is the most &ldquo;ancient&rdquo; and initially all the people on Earth were its owners. In those days, they focused solely on hunting, eating meat of dead animals (protein food), so their digestive system was ideally suited for its digestion.</p>

<p>The fourth type appeared relatively recently (about 1500 years ago) as a result of the mixing of the second and third types, and she is very rare and occurs only in 5% of the population.</p>

<p>Based on this classification, Dr. Peter D'Adamo were developed separate recommendations for weight loss and maintenance of health for all four varieties:</p>

<h2>Blood type diet of the first (type 0)</h2>

<p>Representatives of the first type (33% of the population) are natural carnivores genetically, they have increased the acidity of gastric juice, so that protein foods quickly and fully recycled and not deposited as fat. Therefore, the basis of 0 blood type diet should be lean meat (except pork and goose) &ndash; at least 5-6 times a week, fish and seafood. It is also very useful seaweed, liver, greens, lettuce, spinach, radish, radish, broccoli.</p>

<p>Due to the high acidity of the gastric juice of people with first blood often suffer from gastric ulcer, intestinal disorders and allergies, as the mucous membranes eventually begin to ulcerate. Therefore, blood type diet first should include vegetables and fruits, which have an alkaline reaction.</p>

<p>Include vegetables such properties are artichoke, cauliflower, broccoli, artichoke, onion, garlic, parsley, horseradish, parsnips, spinach and beet leaves. Of fruit is recommended to include in the diet of prunes, figs, plums, dark cherries, as well as lemon and grapefruit, which show an alkaline reaction in the stomach, despite its sour taste.</p>

<p>A from the strawberries, oranges, tangerines and strawberries should be abandoned, as these fruits excessively increase the acidity of gastric juice. The same recommendations apply to vegetable and fruit juices, beverages and condiments. Absolutely contraindicated in cabbage and apple juice, black tea, coffee, and ketchup, vinegar and mayonnaise, which are the enemies of the stomach acidity. It is recommended to drink plenty of water, green tea decoction of rose hips, peppermint and lime.</p>

<p>Dairy products should be used with caution, because the body is not adapted to their full absorption. For example, whole milk and processed cheese should be excluded altogether, as yogurt, low-fat sour cream and yogurt can be included in the menu is not more than 1-2 times a week. Eggs are a valuable source of protein can be eaten 3-4 times a week, but not more than 1 piece per day.</p>

<h2>Blood type diet second (type A)</h2>

<p>Blood type diet second includes mainly fresh and natural plant products (mainly cereals and vegetables), because the digestive system of people of type A is ideally suited for the use of vegetarian food and very poorly digested and absorbed by meat and dairy products. For example, dairy products, especially whole milk, inhibit the metabolism in the body and causes multiple allergic reactions, and therefore they should be replaced by soy or milk.</p>

<p>Because of the low acidity, characteristic of this type of people, their stomach can not digest meat, so its use contributes to the deposition of fat and a slower metabolism. So if you can not completely eliminate it from the diet, limit consumption of chicken or turkey, but rather go on unsalted fish, such as perch, carp, cod, trout, sardines or mackerel. In addition, because of delicate mucous membrane of the stomach should be excluded from the menu spicy and salty foods, sausages and smoked meat, pepper, vinegar, ketchup, mayonnaise, spices, sour fruits and berries, potatoes.</p>

<p>The source of protein in type A should be soy products, eggs and cheese. As you can eat unlimited amounts of whole cereal grains (except wheat), vegetables (except potatoes, tomatoes, olives and eggplant), fruits (except bananas, which are high in calories and too heavy for digestion) and legumes, which are useful to pre-germinate. Salads dressed with olive desirable or linseed oil, and the use of rye bread or on a wheat germ.</p>

<p>Very useful vegetable and fruit juices, such as apricots, cherries, plums, carrots, grapefruit, pineapple and celery. In addition, to prevent the causes of constipation and remove mucus from the intestines is recommended to drink plenty of water (at least two liters a day) and drink every morning on an empty stomach a glass of warm water with the juice of freshly squeezed lemon.</p>

<p>The people of type A is usually a weak immune system open to all infections, sensitive and delicate digestive tract, as well as the increased sensitivity of the nervous system. They often suffer from heart diseases and cancer, as well as tend to pathologies of the gallbladder, liver and symptoms of type 1 diabetes. For them, the recommended diet for a second type of blood is extremely important, because in vegetarian diet immune and digestive system will work more efficiently and be able to prevent the emergence of symptoms of gallstone disease and other serious illnesses.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banana diet for 3 days and 7 days]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet-for-3-days-and-7-days/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:41:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet-for-3-days-and-7-days</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/banana-diet/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/banana-diet/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;banana diet, banana and milk, cottage cheese-banana, kefir-banana&rsquo; &lsquo;Banana diet for 3 days and 7 days. Menus, reviews, results&rsquo;" > Banana Diet &ndash; minus 5-6 pounds per week. Banana Diet is one of the most popular short-term mono-diet of fruit, allow a few days without much trouble to get rid of extra pounds. An estimated nutritionists, 3 days prior to the banana diet lost 3 &ndash; pounds overweight, and this week &ndash; about 5 &ndash; 6 pounds.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>Banana Diet Reviews and contraindications</h2>

<p>Reviews of the banana diet for both patients and physicians, the most positive. The fact that by means of bananas can not only &ldquo;eat&rdquo; and satisfying lose weight, but also greatly improve the condition of the gastro &ndash; intestinal tract, cardio &ndash; vascular system and blood circulation.</p>

<p>From &ndash; due to the high content of potassium in the pulp of banana (360 mg per 100 g product), magnesium (27 mg), and fiber, this miracle &ndash; the fruit greatly improves the water &ndash; salt metabolism in the body, good displays excess fluid (edema), toxins, toxins, excess glucose and bad cholesterol and stimulates the smooth operation of the intestine.</p>

<p>Because bananas almost do not cause allergic reactions, are an excellent source of energy and the supplier of many essential vitamins and minerals, they are often included as complementary foods into the diet of infants, pregnant women and nursing mothers. Assign them as well as dietary and impaired postoperative patients, the elderly and athletes.</p>

<p>In addition, bananas are useful for depression (from &ndash; for the content of pleasure hormone serotonin), chronic fatigue syndrome, hypertension, intestinal problems (constipation, diarrhea), gastritis, reduced hemoglobin, diseases of the bladder and biliary tract, arthritis, heartburn.</p>

<p>Banana days, in contrast to other severe handling fruit monodiets days (cucumber, apple, carrot), due to the presence of large amounts of natural fruit sugars (fructose, glucose, sucrose) are less hungry and promote more rapid and prolonged saturation.</p>

<p>Do not stick to the banana diet for people with individual intolerance to bananas, as well as in diseases of thrombophlebitis and varicose veins. The fact that bananas are a group of products, thickening the blood, so they should be avoided when varicose veins and circulatory disorders of blood vessels. List of products, blood thinners and advice on therapeutic nutrition to varicose veins, read the article on our website.</p>

<p>In diabetes of both types of banana diet is not contraindicated, but because of the high sugar content, it must be agreed upon with the attending physician to correctly calculate individual daily amount of carbohydrates (bread units BU) and eliminate sudden increases in blood glucose levels. Detailed treatment recommendations for patients with diabetes first and second types are described in the articles about diets for diabetics.</p>

<h2>Features choice of fruit for the banana diet</h2>

<p>Pick the fruit for banana mono-diet is of great importance. Slimming perfect ripe &ldquo;fruit&rdquo; Bananas &ndash; rich yellow color, soft, thin-skinned and of medium length. If you bought a slightly unripe fruit, do not rush to use them, first wrap in plastic paper and leave for a few days in a dark place to ripen.</p>

<p>Do not buy so-called &ldquo;feed&rdquo; bananas &ndash; long, green and thick rind and dried, which is several times high-calorie fresh. Before use, the fruit must be thoroughly clean not only on the skin, but also on the white threads, leaving only the pulp of a ripe.</p>

<h3>Strong banana diet for 3 days</h3>

<p>Banana diet for 3 days, often referred to as a banana &ndash; milk diet is the easiest and one banana a strict diet. Daily menu milk &ndash; banana diet consists of 3 &ndash; bananas and 3 &ndash; cup of skim milk or yogurt (1%).</p>

<p>Divide the specified amount of food for 5 &ndash; 6 portions and eat at regular intervals throughout the day &ndash; split meals to avoid the appearance of a strong sense of hunger. Fruits and dairy products can be used as separate from each other, and as a banana yogurt or neck &ndash; whip banana yogurt or milk using a blender.</p>

<p>Additionally, throughout the day as possible drink plain water and herbal teas without sugar, it promotes better bowel cleansing and normalization of the gastro &ndash; intestinal tract. The last meal plan no later than 3 hours before bedtime.</p>

<h3>Banana Diet 7 days</h3>

<p>The seven-day option is not as strict as three days, and does not limit the amount of fruit consumed &ndash; are allowed to eat per day to 1.5 kg of peeled ripe bananas. However, slimming process in this embodiment is quite effective for night out on average about 1 kilogram of body weight.</p>

<p>As soon as you feel hungry, Eat one fruit at once. If it is a very &ldquo;hungry&rdquo;, as a source of complete protein can be added to the menu 1 boiled egg. From drinks are allowed in unlimited quantities of water and herbal tea without sugar, consumption of dairy products with the exception.</p>

<h3>Curd &ndash; banana diet</h3>

<p>Curd &ndash; banana slimming option for up to 4 days, involves alternation of banana and cheese fasting days and makes it quite effectively reduce weight, up to 3 &ndash; 4 pounds. Since cheese is quite a varied and useful product, banana &ndash; curd alternation transferred easily and is therefore very popular with losing weight.</p>

<p>The first and third days &ndash; cheese:</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; 120 g low-fat cottage cheese (up to 5% fat), fruit;
Lunch &ndash; 120 g cottage cheese, vegetable salad without oil;
Dinner &ndash; 120 grams cottage cheese, grapefruit.</p>

<p>The second and fourth days &ndash; banana:</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; banana, 120 g low-fat yogurt or cottage cheese;
Lunch &ndash; 2 banana, 1 boiled egg;
Dinner &ndash; 200 grams of cooked lean meat, 1 &ndash; 2 bananas.</p>

<h2>Exit after the banana diet tips and advice</h2>

<p>Longer than the recommended 3 &ndash; 7 days to comply with the banana mono-diet is not recommended. First, despite the usefulness of the product, banana slimming, like any other mono-diet is not completely balanced and can cause serious injury.</p>

<p>A in &ndash; Second, our body is designed wisely and in a few days can adapt to any conditions and, if necessary, the power-saving mode. Therefore, for more than the recommended terms of losing weight is not only harmful but also impractical because the weight will fall either very slow or it hard to stand still &ndash; nutritionists effect of this phenomenon is called a &ldquo;plateau&rdquo; (described in more detail in the diet roller coaster diet and Ladder).</p>

<p>Exit after kefir &ndash; the banana diet, as well as following any diet, despite the achieved effect, must be smooth and gradual &ndash; is necessary in order to permanently fix the result. Within a week, gently insert the usual foods and observe moderation &ndash; if you start to eat off of hungry days, the weight comes back very quickly.</p>

<p>If losing weight on bananas was comfortable for you, start to practice weekly unloading banana days &ndash; this will easily support the weight without the stress and shocks. To the menu was not too severe, it offers a variety of delicious and hearty recipes.</p>

<p>Banana &ndash; fruit salad &ndash; cut slices of banana and add the slices of apple, pear or peach. The second option salad &ndash; add walnuts and lettuce.</p>

<p>Oatmeal with banana &ndash; Boil water for oatmeal, add back milk and finely chopped banana slices.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[American diet for weight loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/american-diet-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:39:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/american-diet-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left <a" src="href="http://medusanews.com/images/diet-roller-coaster-diet-dinner-minus/image.jpg">http://medusanews.com/images/diet-roller-coaster-diet-dinner-minus/image.jpg</a>" width="200" height="150" title="&lsquo;Diet roller coaster, diet dinner minus&rsquo; &lsquo;American diet for weight loss. Roller coaster and minus the dinner diets&rsquo;" > Diet Rollercoaster allows you to securely lose weight by speeding up metabolism.</p>

<p>Diet roller coaster developed by American nutritionist Martin Cathan more than 30 years ago and in that time has gained wide popularity. It is one of the most effective ways to reduce weight and allows the presence of physical activity, reduce up to 7 pounds in a week.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>The essence of the diet roller coaster</h2>

<p>There is a simple explanation. The fact is that our body is able to quickly adjust and adapt to any diet. To do this, it is enough to just a few days, after which it includes saving mode (power saving), so the metabolism (metabolism) slows down and stops weight plummeted.</p>

<p>Dr. Martin Katan take into account this feature, and developed the technique in such a way as to literally &ldquo;confuse&rdquo; the body, preventing it &ldquo;remember&rdquo; the amount of calories consumed and not allowing to adapt to the new regime.</p>

<p>Recommended them daily caloric intake ranges up &ndash; down, from minimum to maximum, which gave the name of a popular diet roller coaster ride. Through this approach to nutrition he managed to lose about 30 pounds of dead weight and to help numerous people lose weight.</p>

<h2>Diet Rollercoaster menu</h2>

<p>Follow the diet roller coaster is simple, you have to do only the willpower to break away and not to follow through, and meticulous counting calories. Product Composition, unlike most other programs weight reduction is not critical. That is, you can eat all you want, above all, to keep within the recommended number of calories.</p>

<p>The most severe and difficult from a psychological point of view, are the first three days, which are allowed to eat only 600 calories. These days will be very hungry all the time and will want to eat, but you have to strictly follow your plan and understand that it will be easier. To do this, try to choose the daily caloric not chocolates, biscuits and light carbohydrate and low-calorie vegetables, fruits, low-fat dairy products and cereals on the water.</p>

<p>Since these products are made up of fiber and slowly digestible carbohydrates, they provide a feeling of satiety for a long time and do not give a break to &ldquo;Jordania&rdquo;. In addition, fiber helps avoid the inevitable with insufficient food constipation, thoroughly clean the intestines and populate it useful microflora.</p>

<p>Do not forget about the copious drinking regimen, drink plenty of simple and non-carbonated mineral water and herbal tea (without sugar). This will not only enhance the cleansing process in the intestine, but also help to avoid excessive hunger. Because we all know that people often confuse hunger with a feeling of thirst. Sometimes it is enough to drink a glass of water, and there is no longer want to.</p>

<p>Thus, the scheme of alternation calories, designed for 3 weeks:</p>

<p>The first &ndash; the third day &ndash; 600 calories;
Fourth &ndash; the seventh day &ndash; 900 calories;
The eighth &ndash; the fourteenth day &ndash; 1200 calories;
The fifteenth &ndash; seventeenth day &ndash; 600 calories;
Eighteen &ndash; twenty-one days &ndash; 900 kcal.</p>

<p>Daily menu, as already mentioned, can be anything from any of the products, dishes and combinations. But to you it was easier to navigate, give an approximate daily food intake by 600, 900 and 1200 kcal. You can take it as a basis and change the components in its sole discretion, according to the energy value of foods (see table on the caloric content of products and labels) and the individual taste preferences.</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; unsweetened tea, a small piece of rye bread;
Lunch &ndash; 100 grams of boiled beef and cooked rice, a salad of radish and cucumber without oil;
Dinner &ndash; 1 boiled egg and a glass of low-fat yogurt.</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; black tea (you can add 1 liter. sugar) with rye crackers, apple green;
Dinner &ndash; boiled or steamed fish, pasta and vegetable salad (100 g). Tea (sugar content not exceeding 1 tsp);
Dinner &ndash; 1 boiled egg, 100 grams of cottage cheese (low-fat), and a small banana.</p>

<p>Breakfast &ndash; 200 grams of oatmeal (on the water and no oil), tea (sugar 1 tsp) with rye croutons;
Dinner &ndash; boiled chicken (200 g), buckwheat porridge with a small piece of butter (100 g);
Dinner &ndash; Assorted fruit salad of apples, grapes, bananas, pineapple.</p>

<p>During the day, between meals, snacks are permitted &ndash; 1 cup low-fat yogurt, a small banana.</p>

<p>After a full course of 21 days, you can gradually return to your normal diet. According to Dr. Katana, during this period can not reliably &ldquo;confuse&rdquo; the body, so the result is stored for a long period of time and will have to repeat the whole cycle will not soon.</p>

<p>It should be noted that to observe the &ldquo;roller coaster&rdquo; only healthy people, the beauty and harmony should not be achieved at the expense of health. Slimming prohibited under the scheme &ldquo;600-900-1200&rdquo; with the gastro &ndash; intestinal tract, pregnant women, nursing mothers, as well as any chronic illnesses. Even if you feel perfectly healthy, losing weight before check with your doctor.</p>

<p>Despite the fact that physical exercise can significantly, by almost 2-fold, to enhance the effect of the diet (with exercise you can lose up to 10 pounds, without them &ndash; to 6 pounds), heavy physical exertion banned because they can lead to a sharp deterioration  It is useful to practice yoga, walking, pilates, aerobics and leisurely cycling. To distract from the food, walk a little more in the fresh air and get enough sleep, at least 8 &ndash; 9 hours a day.</p>

<h2>American diet &ldquo;Dinner minus&rdquo;</h2>

<p>The American Diet Dinner minus does not promise weight loss in 3 days, but it is very comfortable to compliance and requires meticulous counting calories eaten each piece as a roller coaster. In addition, during the follow-up system, &ldquo;dinner minus&rdquo;, the body produces the correct and healthy eating habits &ndash; consume a major amount of fat in the first half of the day, when the active hormones are responsible for their split.</p>

<p>It is based on the familiar childhood postulates that at night there are harmful and need to be fed in accordance with the well-known saying &ldquo;Eat breakfast yourself, share dinner with a friend, a dinner give to the enemy.&rdquo; That is, the authors offer a methodology completely forget about this concept as dinner and after 17 hours is recommended to drink only ordinary water.</p>

<p>Thus, the basic principles of the diet minus dinner:</p>

<ul>
<li>Copious drinking regime &ndash; drink at least 2 liters of water daily;</li>
<li>Last meal be carried out not later than 17 hours;</li>
<li>Decrease in the consumption of animal fat diet, replacing them with vegetable. Just keep in mind that fats can not be completely ruled out, suitable for all common sense;</li>
<li>Choose a menu for only quality products without trans fats, dyes, preservatives, emulsifiers, preferring fast food nutrition healthy homemade food.</li>
</ul>


<p>Composing your diet, avoid distortions in any direction. If you strongly want something sweet, do not deny yourself &ndash; eat a small piece of dessert in the first half of the day. Do not focus only on choosing low-calorie foods, pay more attention to their usefulness and naturalness. Remember, the beauty and harmony can only give a healthy body, provided a balance of everything necessary for the normal functioning &ndash; proteins, fats, carbohydrates, vitamins and trace elements.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
