<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Dietology | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/dietology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-01-11T22:26:00+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[For What Needed Amino Acids?]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-06T10:55:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/for-what-needed-amino-acids</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/for-what-needed-amino-acids/img.jpg" title="For what needed amino acids?" alt="amino acids, how to make amino acids, amino acids for weight loss, essential amino acids, amino acids for muscle growth, what are amino acids">Amino acids - are chemical compounds that comprise proteins. When the human digestive tract gets protein foods, using special enzymes, it is split into amino acids. Only then it can be assimilated. Small-sized molecules penetrate the amino acids from the intestine into the blood, and then the body can use them for their own purposes.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Amino acids perform many important functions in the body. They can be divided into plastic and energy. Plastic functions are built from amino acids of the protein molecules that make up all the tissues of our body. Because amino acids are not only bodies, but also biologically active substances: enzymes, certain hormones, neurotransmitters. The energy function is the splitting of the amino acids in order to release energy.</p>

<p>To maintain human life he needed only 20 species of amino acids, although they exist in nature much more. They are divided into three groups:</p>

<ul>
<li>Interchangeable - can be synthesized in the body from chemical compounds having a non-protein origin;</li>
<li>Conditionally replaceable - are synthesized in a limited number;</li>
<li>Essential - are not synthesized in the body.</li>
</ul>


<p>Man receives daily amino acids from food. Most of them are found in meat, fish, eggs, milk and other animal products. The richest vegetable source of protein is soy and other legumes, but they contain less essential amino acids.</p>

<h2>What are amino acids common man?</h2>

<p>Everyone needs amino acids. None of these chemical compounds, we can not synthesize protein. If the amino acids are no longer come from the outside, the body begins to break down its own tissues and organs, to compensate for their deficits. The absence of even one essential amino acid in the human diet leads to severe disease.</p>

<p>The source of these materials were previously only foods. Today amino acids produced by many pharmaceutical companies as supplements or drugs. Some of them are designed for the treatment of certain diseases, others are used by athletes to build muscle. With the purpose of treatment of amino acids into the reception - this is an expensive and inefficient pleasure.</p>

<p>There are many medications on the basis of amino acids, which are used for parenteral nutrition patients. If a person can not eat food alone, he poured the amino acid solutions intravenously. Often because of these drugs the doctors save patient lives, as in the period of severe illness when the body&rsquo;s plastic processes are active, the body needs protein more than usual.</p>

<h2>What are amino acids during training?</h2>

<p>Most athletes who are engaged in bodybuilding, taking protein powders. They use it as an additional source of protein to build muscle mass quickly. Alternatively the protein amino acid solutions are applied. Pharmaceutical companies argue that they are more effective than the protein obtained from food as well as familiar to most athletes protein powders.</p>

<p>True or not? Most companies that produce amino acids for athletes, convince us of the veracity of this information. But their interest is obvious: the amino acids of the protein are much more expensive, so bring more income from sales. For the successful promotion of the product on the market was invented so-called &quot;protein window&quot; or &quot;protein corridor&quot;.</p>

<p>&quot;Protein box&quot; - a period of time after the workout, which is considered optimal for protein <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a>. It is 40-50 minutes. During this period the athlete should learn the most protein to gain muscle growth. If the late bodybuilder, muscles will grow more slowly. But the protein from foods like protein powders, slowly digested, so the athlete has only one chance to catch up to the closing &quot;window of protein&quot;. To do this, take the amino acid solution.</p>

<p>Unlike the protein, amino acids absorbed from the intestine immediately without pretreatment with proteolytic enzymes. Their concentration in the blood rises sharply after 15-20 minutes after taking the supplements. Thus, a person has time to deliver the amino acids in muscle, while &quot;protein window&quot; remains open.</p>

<p>It is quite logical to study the benefits of amino acids in protein loved athletes. Very often in the specialized literature for bodybuilders can find information about the &quot;protein window&quot;. But studies have shown that intake of protein and amino acids provides identical results athletes during training. &quot;Protein window&quot; hardly exists, although the myth about him still wanders from book to book, stimulating the sale of free amino acids.</p>

<p>BCAA - three amino acids, most commonly used in the training. These include isoleucine, valine and leucine. It is these amino acids are part of the majority of sports supplements for bodybuilders. The main effects of BCAA:</p>

<ul>
<li>The accelerated build-up of muscle mass;</li>
<li>Increasing strength athlete;</li>
<li>Reduction of body fat mass.</li>
</ul>


<p>There is no doubt the benefits of BCAA bodybuilder. With them he will reach sports results. They are rapidly absorbed and have high bioavailability, are easy to use. But the lack of supplements based on amino acids BCAA is the price. They are expensive, but a similar result can be obtained by an athlete using whey protein.</p>

<p>Amino BCAA available in different dosage forms. There capsules and solutions, but less likely to take the supplement in powder form. It is recognized that the powder is less convenient to use: it is poorly soluble in the liquid and has a bitter taste. Ready amino acid solutions are tastier, more convenient to use and transport, but are more expensive.</p>

<p>Take BCAA recommended 1 teaspoon (4-5 grams), from 1 to 3 times a day. Amino acids are allowed to be combined with any other sports nutrition. Of course, it makes no sense to take them together with protein, since these additives have the same mechanism of action, although some people do it to save money.</p>

<p>Amino acids - are chemical substances, of which built all the proteins in our body. A person must receive them regularly with food to stay healthy. Athletes who are building up the muscles need additional source of amino acids. Especially important for them leucine, valine, isoleucine, which are abbreviated as BCAA. Supplements containing amino acids, convenient to use and easily digested. However, they are expensive, so as a source of amino acids most athletes use a cheaper but equally effective protein powder.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Soybeans: Benefits and Harms, Doctor Review]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-04T15:52:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review/black-soybeans-benefits-and-harms-doctor-review.jpg" title="Black soybeans: benefits and harms, doctor review" alt="Black soybeans">Black soybean - a product that is used in traditional Chinese medicine. It is considered a source of balance. Therapeutic effects: replenishes blood levels, nourishing yin, expels wind, strengthens weakened, normalizes the activity of the channels of stomach and spleen. In Russia, black soybeans also find healing, but its effect is usually described using different terminology, more understandable to our man.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Black soybean useful in exactly the same extent that and soy white or yellow. This is a common legume has a high protein content and insoluble dietary fiber. There is hardly any sense to use it as a medicine. Black soybean much more suitable for use in food. Nevertheless, she decided to attribute the following useful properties:</p>

<ul>
<li>Normalizes nervous activity;</li>
<li>Cures cancer (probably not in the world of plants, which it does not cure, according to admirers of traditional medicine);</li>
<li>To protect people from the harmful effects of the environment;</li>
<li>Reduces the level of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a> in the blood;</li>
<li>Promotes weight loss.</li>
</ul>


<p>All these inventions. This can be read on virtually any product of plant origin. Perhaps black soy and healthy if its systematic use in food, but cancer or diabetes, it is certainly not cures.</p>

<p>Black soybean contains no toxic compounds for the organism. The damage is only possible with overeating or the presence of diseases of the digestive system. Disadvantages of the product:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>High calorie</strong> - do not pass at a weight problem;</li>
<li><strong>High fiber content</strong> - possible bloating, changes in the frequency and stool consistency;</li>
<li><strong>Small size, dense texture, slippery edge</strong> - a man with a deficit of intelligence can strangle if Bob gets into the respiratory tract.</li>
</ul>


<p>People with normal mental development and good health black soybeans can not hurt anything. Eat without fear for their health.</p>

<p>On the Internet a lot of popularity gained supplement for weight loss called &quot;black soybeans&quot;. The advertisement says that it is delivered directly from Japan. It is not clear why they are doing, because it is a good idea in Russia is growing.</p>

<p>At sells website reported that the secret of longevity of the Japanese, finally revealed! It turns out the high life expectancy - a consequence of regular consumption of black soya.</p>

<p>Take supplements you offer for the following purposes:</p>

<p><strong>1. Weight Loss.</strong> The main purpose of black soya. Weight reduction is due to increasing the activity of fat cells. Those allegedly begin to burn fat, regardless of the amount of food consumed by you, including, if you have no physical activity. In addition, thanks to soy protein, according to advertising, the muscles grow without any training.
<strong>2. Improvement by saturating the body with useful substances.</strong> The site Product asserts that certain vitamins, minerals and amino acids are contained only in black soybeans. Nowhere in nature, they are no more. I wonder what kind of minerals are? If you would like Mendeleev heard, he probably would have got out of the coffin to burn his table of chemical elements.
<strong>3. Rejuvenation.</strong> It is due to dietary fiber (which, incidentally, are in any plant food). The body is rejuvenated as a result of lightning elimination of toxins under the influence of black soy from Japan. After that, according to the suppliers of goods, there is a surge of energy forces in the cell, and you feel much better.</p>

<p>Due to what effect this wonder-drug that reduces weight and rejuvenate the body? If you believe the official site, as part contains the following components:</p>

<p><strong>Proteins.</strong> Present in any food products. They are a source of calories. Promote weight loss, but only if used in place of fatty and sugary foods, not in addition to it.</p>

<p><strong>Vitamins A and E.</strong> So these vitamins, which are found nowhere else in nature, except for black soy! Or is there? Yes, still there. Vitamin A is full in carrots and other yellow vegetables, and vitamin E in abundance found in vegetable oils. Both components are useful for health, weight loss but not in any way contribute.</p>

<p><strong>B vitamins</strong> are present in many other foods. Good for your health, but they do not lose weight and look younger.</p>

<p><strong>Alimentary fiber.</strong> In fact contribute to weight loss. But only if the abundance of dietary fiber in the diet causes decrease in consumption of other foods. By themselves, they do not burn fat.</p>

<p><strong>Amino acids.</strong> This protein structural components, so that in fact when transferring the composition manufacturer repeats the same material twice. As mentioned above, from the proteins do not lose weight if they are a supplement, not a substitute for the usual ration.</p>

<p><strong>Trace elements.</strong> What kind of minerals are in the black soybeans - the manufacturer is not recognized. Given that nowhere in other products do not, in general, these micronutrients to mankind is not known, to evaluate their real impact on the shape and health is very difficult.</p>

<p>Black soybean are sold as a concentrate. You will receive a jar of powder. It must be diluted in a glass of water and drink before each meal, three times a den.Takoe use of black soya will help in weight loss, as it will reduce appetite.</p>

<p>Of course, this will not happen because of the presence of this plant amazing fat-burning properties. Hunger subsides as the day before the meal in the stomach will be less space. As a result, you eat less. If this happens regularly for at least several months, you will eventually be able to normalize the figures.</p>

<p>Black soybeans - is one of hundreds or thousands of useless goods for figure and health that is actively circulating on the Internet. It pacifiers in a beautiful package. They are sold on the colorfully decorated sites and skillfully advertised, but because demand. Nevertheless, the man who would be able to lose weight and rejuvenate with the help of black soybean, the world does not know.</p>

<p>This product is recommended to buy the people:</p>

<ul>
<li>The rich - who do not consider $ 40 money, worthy of attention;</li>
<li>Curious - who are used to check for yourself;</li>
<li>Stupid - who believed in a bright, but not the most convincing and reasoned advertising;</li>
<li>Desperate - who wants nothing to do with his own figure and wants to clear his conscience, allegedly fighting <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a> even with the help of useless supplements.</li>
</ul>


<p>The rest of the people recommended to use other methods of weight loss. There are supplements better. However, keep in mind that without the support of the diet and increase physical activity, no medication is not going to work.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protein Diet. Sample Menu Protein Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-04T05:15:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet.jpg" title="Protein diet. Sample menu protein diet" alt="Protein diet">The most common protein diet try to choose those who are engaged in fitness, or who can not give up meat and fish, but calmly dispenses with flour and sweet.</p>

<p>The basic idea of protein diets is that we create a shortage of carbohydrates in the body, are considered the main source of energy for the organism. As a result, the metabolism starts to rebuild, and the body will consume fat.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The bulk of the protein diet involves almost complete rejection of carbohydrate foods, and consumption of products containing large amounts of protein.</p>

<p>The diet protein diet usually includes meat and fish, eggs, cottage cheese, yogurt and low-fat cheeses.</p>

<p>Sometimes, for example, egg diet, the diet can include citrus fruits (grapefruit, oranges, and the like), which are positioned as a source of vitamins.</p>

<p>The main disadvantage of all protein diets - it is unbalanced diet.</p>

<h2>We can not exclude carbohydrates completely!</h2>

<p>For weight loss on the protein diet is usually used following recommendations may be included on the menu only lean chicken, fish, egg whites and low-fat cottage cheese (it is desirable to have 4 meals, at a time that the output of 25-30 g of protein) and a drink sugar and other products should be deleted (except Citrus).</p>

<p>This menu can not be considered a balanced&hellip; In most cases the authors of these methods is recommended to keep a diet for 2 weeks, ostensibly for &quot;changes in metabolism&quot;. In practice, the rejection of carbohydrates is harmful to the body. The complete absence of ñontaining carbohydrates foods in the diet and an excess of junk food can cause ketosis (increased content of ketone bodies in the tissues of the body).</p>

<p>Ketosis is a kind of unmistakable indication that the process of lipolysis. Reach ketosis state - the main goal of many low-carb diets.</p>

<p>Typically ketosis appears when the amount of carbohydrates is less than 100 grams per day. In some people, ketosis occurs only with reducing carbohydrates to 40 g per day.</p>

<p>To determine the presence of ketone bodies can use the urine test.</p>

<p>Some authors protein diets claim that the complete rejection of carbohydrates - a necessary condition for weight loss, because ketosis state body draws its energy mainly from the fat reserves.</p>

<p>It is believed that the ketogenic diet is very harmful and even dangerous for your health. Indeed, the ketogenic diet can be dangerous, it all depends on the individual person&rsquo;s health status.</p>

<p><strong>However, current research tells us this:</strong></p>

<p><em>&quot;A diet rich in protein products should not be carbohydrate-free. That, as far as we lose weight, largely depends on the daily caloric intake and what we consume carbohydrates during the day and at what time (in the morning or late afternoon), how much protein per 1 kg of body weight comes from food&quot;.</em></p>

<p><strong>If you are not ready to compete in fitness or bodybuilding, so what&rsquo;s the point to exhaust yourself? To reduce the percentage of body fat, you can go for less severe measures, albeit the result will be noticeable not so fast.</strong></p>

<p>Carbohydrates - a major supplier of food for the nervous system.</p>

<p>If they are missing, the following <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/" title="symptoms">symptoms</a>: fatigue, loss of efficiency, reduction of attention, irritability.</p>

<p>Eat 4-6 times a day, the first meal - 20-30 minutes after the lift, the last reception for 2-3 hours before bedtime. Each meal should consist of a portion of protein (20-30 g) and other low-calorie foods. Till one o&rsquo;clock permitted to 1-2 servings of complex carbohydrates. This 8-10 tablespoons of buckwheat or oatmeal. Or the same amount of boiled brown (brown) rice. Ñontaining carbohydrates from other products on time, weight loss will need to be abandoned. After 13 hours of the day should be protein products will have only non-starchy vegetables: cucumbers, tomatoes, cabbage, zucchini, etc. Fruit is consumed sparingly and preferably in the morning. Allowed 2 unsweetened apple or 1 grapefruit. Drink at least two liters of plain water a day.</p>

<p>Take vitamins after breakfast (can be sports, such as: Opti-Vites or Daily Formula).</p>

<p>Limit fats permitted to 40 g per day.</p>

<h2>How to make the correct protein diet?</h2>

<p>During a diet to lose weight you need to eat one of these foods at each meal:</p>

<ul>
<li>150-200 g skinless chicken breast;</li>
<li>150-200 g lean fish (flounder, cod, pollock, tuna);</li>
<li>100 g turkey, beef or veal;</li>
<li>150-200 g fat-free yogurt.</li>
</ul>


<p>These protein products must be consumed in an amount which indicated above.</p>

<p>Also you can include in your diet: 1-2 servings of whey protein per day.</p>

<p>200-250 ml (1 cup) of skim milk or plain water, one scoop (30 grams of protein).</p>

<p>1 serving of protein shake - this one meal. Very handy if you do not have time to prepare write.</p>

<p>It is recommended to drink in the morning, after 1.5 hours after exercise (if you want to lose weight), and (or) at night.</p>

<p>Choose whey isolate firms: Dymatize or Syntrax.</p>

<h2>Menu protein diet</h2>

<p>We offer you a rough menu for women who exercise regularly (3-5 times a week) and perform cardio + work in the gym.</p>

<p><em>The first meal (breakfast)</em>: 4-5 tablespoons of oatmeal with cinnamon, 6 egg whites with spinach, apple half. Unsweetened tea or coffee.</p>

<p><em>The second meal (lunch)</em>: 150 grams of cooked breast, served with 4-5 tablespoons of cooked brown rice.</p>

<p><em>The third meal (a dinner)</em>: 150 g of tuna and a salad of non-starchy vegetables, season with olive oil (1 tablespoon).</p>

<p><em>The fourth meal (afternoon snack)</em>: 200 g fat-free cottage cheese with vegetable salad (you can add lemon juice).</p>

<p><em>Fifth meal (evening meal)</em>: 150 g of fish with steamed green beans, protein shake or a cup of yogurt.</p>

<p><strong>Protein diet</strong> can help lose weight, and virtually all its effectiveness is increased by an order if you do weights and cardio in the gym.</p>

<p>It should be noted that during the period of weight loss and the use of refined foods alcohol is not allowed.</p>

<p>To prevent disruptions once a week (for example, every Sunday) you can eat a small portion of your favorite product.</p>

<p><strong>Protein diet: -70 kg for 60 months</strong></p>

<p>Before you start the protein diet, you should consult with your doctor!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tea Weight Loss Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/tea-weight-loss-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-01-02T09:53:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/tea-weight-loss-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/tea-weight-loss-diet/tea-weight-loss-diet.jpg" title="Tea weight loss diet" alt="Tea weight loss diet">Tea diet - it is a method of losing weight by drinking tea for several days. It is presented in different versions, and almost all of them are designed for rapid weight loss due to the complete failure of the food or the strong reduction of caloric intake. Estimated fat burning effect is achieved both through the restrictions in food, and because of the beneficial effects of tea on the figure.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The essence of the most popular tea diet is only one use of tea for 3 days. There are many versions of this diet where the drink is chosen black or green, used with or without sugar, restricted or permitted in any quantity.</p>

<p>There are varieties of tea diets designed for a longer period - 7 or 14 days, and some embodiments include, in addition to the use of beverage foodstuffs. But the most common is still a tea diet for 3 days. Its rules:</p>

<ul>
<li>The day you can drink six cups of tea;</li>
<li>Black tea should be taken - in which case an additional fat-burning effect is provided by the presence of caffeine in it;</li>
<li>Relies on a cup of tea spoon of sugar.</li>
</ul>


<p>This diet is too short to be able to talk about significant weight loss. Maybe it can help you get rid of 0.5 kg of fat per 3 days, but better results can hardly count. Although the scale, you will see more impressive numbers, in fact pitches due to a greater extent the devastation of the intestine, for you for three days without eating, although there continue to visit the toilet.</p>

<p>Positive aspects of the tea diet:</p>

<ol>
<li>Quick results. Tea diet can be used in cases where the 3 days you will visit an important event where you want to look a little better than it really is. Due to the devastation you have multiple bowel reduced belly, which will get into smaller clothes. But keep in mind that after the return of the form of diet, because the intestine is filled again.</li>
<li>With respect to good tolerability when compared to other diets generally do not provide meals. Lack of strong hunger is provided on one side of caffeine contained in tea leaves, on the other - sugar. It comes in small portions at regular intervals, thereby allowing time to time to reduce hunger by increasing the level of glucose in the blood.</li>
<li>A small duration. Tea diet is harmful to health. Well, it only lasts for 3 days. Perhaps, during this time you will not have time to earn gastritis and disrupt your metabolism.</li>
</ol>


<p>There is a diet in which the tea is used in conjunction with milk. It is believed that it itself has fat burning properties and impact positively on the figure even without dieting. But this is nothing more than rumors - milk tea has the same effect on weight, such as milk and tea, drunk alone.</p>

<p>Recipe tea with milk to the diet is very simple: take the tea leaves, place in a teapot, but does not fill with water as you usually do, and boiled milk.</p>

<p>There are plenty of diets based on the consumption of tea with milk. They mainly involve the reception throughout the day 1.5 liters of the drink without eating food. The difference lies in the duration. Sometimes diet offered to observe three days, sometimes - 5 or 7 days.</p>

<p>Some advise once a week to arrange a fasting day on milk and tea, and this option is the most preferred. It is not harmful to health, reduces the total number of calories consumed per week, and most importantly - constantly promotes weight loss and long-term, if you practice these regularly fasting days.</p>

<p>Most tea diets are stupid, harmful and ineffective. They come only to those who are on his body only 1-2 kg of excess weight. In this way, they can be quickly reset, and this is really hungry enough for only 3-4 days. All other tea diet, including the use of milk is not recommended because:</p>

<ul>
<li>The effect of these weak and temporary;</li>
<li>Such diets harmful to health;</li>
<li>A number of consecutive days, hungry and poorly tolerated at all discourage the human desire for further weight loss.</li>
</ul>


<p>Thus, from the tea diet can get more harm than good. Moreover, not only for health but also for the figure, because the diet with poor tolerability undermine motivation.</p>

<p>However, the above does not apply to schemes slimming day using the tea with sugar or milk. Fasting days on this drink once a week to help control weight. In combination with other measures aimed at reducing body weight, they contribute to the full normalization of the figure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banana Diet for 3 Days and 7 Days]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet-for-3-days-and-7-days/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-19T19:41:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/banana-diet-for-3-days-and-7-days</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/banana-diet/image.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="banana diet, banana and milk, cottage cheese-banana, kefir-banana" alt="Banana diet for 3 days and 7 days. Menus, reviews, results"> Banana Diet &ndash; minus 5-6 pounds per week. Banana Diet is one of the most popular short-term mono-diet of fruit, allow a few days without much trouble to get rid of extra pounds. An estimated nutritionists, 3 days prior to the banana diet lost 3 &ndash; pounds overweight, and this week &ndash; about 5 &ndash; 6 pounds.</p>




<!-- more -->




<h2>Banana Diet Reviews and contraindications</h2>




<p>Reviews of the banana diet for both patients and physicians, the most positive. The fact that by means of bananas can not only &ldquo;eat&rdquo; and <span class="demo-button-click" id="demoT7">satisfying lose weight</span>, but also greatly improve the condition of the gastro &ndash; intestinal tract, cardio &ndash; vascular system and blood circulation.</p>




<p>From &ndash; due to the high content of potassium in the pulp of banana (360 mg per 100 g product), magnesium (27 mg), and fiber, this miracle &ndash; the fruit greatly improves the water &ndash; salt metabolism in the body, good displays excess fluid (edema), toxins, toxins, excess glucose and bad cholesterol and stimulates the smooth operation of the intestine.</p>




<p>Because bananas almost do not cause allergic reactions, are an excellent source of energy and the supplier of many essential vitamins and minerals, they are often included as complementary foods into the diet of infants, pregnant women and nursing mothers. Assign them as well as dietary and impaired postoperative patients, the elderly and athletes.</p>




<p>In addition, bananas are useful for depression (from &ndash; for the content of pleasure hormone serotonin), chronic fatigue syndrome, hypertension, intestinal problems (constipation, diarrhea), gastritis, reduced hemoglobin, diseases of the bladder and biliary tract, arthritis, heartburn.</p>




<p>Banana days, in contrast to other severe handling fruit monodiets days (cucumber, apple, carrot), due to the presence of large amounts of natural fruit sugars (fructose, glucose, sucrose) are less hungry and promote more rapid and prolonged saturation.</p>




<p>Do not stick to the banana diet for people with individual intolerance to bananas, as well as in diseases of thrombophlebitis and varicose veins. The fact that bananas are a group of products, thickening the blood, so they should be avoided when varicose veins and circulatory disorders of blood vessels. List of products, blood thinners and advice on therapeutic nutrition to varicose veins, read the article on our website.</p>




<p>In diabetes of both types of banana diet is not contraindicated, but because of the high sugar content, it must be agreed upon with the attending physician to correctly calculate individual daily amount of carbohydrates (bread units BU) and eliminate sudden increases in blood glucose levels. Detailed treatment recommendations for patients with diabetes first and second types are described in the articles about diets for diabetics.</p>




<h2>Features choice of fruit for the banana diet</h2>




<p>Pick the fruit for banana mono-diet is of great importance. Slimming perfect ripe &ldquo;fruit&rdquo; Bananas &ndash; rich yellow color, soft, thin-skinned and of medium length. If you bought a slightly unripe fruit, do not rush to use them, first wrap in plastic paper and leave for a few days in a dark place to ripen.</p>




<p>Do not buy so-called &ldquo;feed&rdquo; bananas &ndash; long, green and thick rind and dried, which is several times high-calorie fresh. Before use, the fruit must be thoroughly clean not only on the skin, but also on the white threads, leaving only the pulp of a ripe.</p>




<h3>Strong banana diet for 3 days</h3>




<p>Banana diet for 3 days, often referred to as a banana &ndash; milk diet is the easiest and one banana a strict diet. Daily menu milk &ndash; banana diet consists of 3 &ndash; bananas and 3 &ndash; cup of skim milk or yogurt (1%).</p>




<p>Divide the specified amount of food for 5 &ndash; 6 portions and eat at regular intervals throughout the day &ndash; split meals to avoid the appearance of a strong sense of hunger. Fruits and dairy products can be used as separate from each other, and as a banana yogurt or neck &ndash; whip banana yogurt or milk using a blender.</p>




<p>Additionally, throughout the day as possible drink plain water and herbal teas without sugar, it promotes better bowel cleansing and normalization of the gastro &ndash; intestinal tract. The last meal plan no later than 3 hours before bedtime.</p>




<h3>Banana Diet 7 days</h3>




<p>The seven-day option is not as strict as three days, and does not limit the amount of fruit consumed &ndash; are allowed to eat per day to 1.5 kg of peeled ripe bananas. However, slimming process in this embodiment is quite effective for night out on average about 1 kilogram of body weight.</p>




<p>As soon as you feel hungry, Eat one fruit at once. If it is a very &ldquo;hungry&rdquo;, as a source of complete protein can be added to the menu 1 boiled egg. From drinks are allowed in unlimited quantities of water and herbal tea without sugar, consumption of dairy products with the exception.</p>




<h3>Curd &ndash; banana diet</h3>




<p>Curd &ndash; banana slimming option for up to 4 days, involves alternation of banana and cheese fasting days and makes it quite effectively reduce weight, up to 3 &ndash; 4 pounds. Since cheese is quite a varied and useful product, banana &ndash; curd alternation transferred easily and is therefore very popular with losing weight.</p>




<p>The first and third days &ndash; cheese:</p>




<p>Breakfast &ndash; 120 g low-fat cottage cheese (up to 5% fat), fruit;
Lunch &ndash; 120 g cottage cheese, vegetable salad without oil;
Dinner &ndash; 120 grams cottage cheese, grapefruit.</p>




<p>The second and fourth days &ndash; banana:</p>




<p>Breakfast &ndash; banana, 120 g low-fat yogurt or cottage cheese;
Lunch &ndash; 2 banana, 1 boiled egg;
Dinner &ndash; 200 grams of cooked lean meat, 1 &ndash; 2 bananas.</p>




<h2>Exit after the banana diet tips and advice</h2>




<p>Longer than the recommended 3 &ndash; 7 days to comply with the banana mono-diet is not recommended. First, despite the usefulness of the product, banana slimming, like any other mono-diet is not completely balanced and can cause serious injury.</p>




<p>A in &ndash; Second, our body is designed wisely and in a few days can adapt to any conditions and, if necessary, the power-saving mode. Therefore, for more than the recommended terms of losing weight is not only harmful but also impractical because the weight will fall either very slow or it hard to stand still &ndash; nutritionists effect of this phenomenon is called a &ldquo;plateau&rdquo; (described in more detail in the diet roller coaster diet and Ladder).</p>




<p>Exit after kefir &ndash; the banana diet, as well as following any diet, despite the achieved effect, must be smooth and gradual &ndash; is necessary in order to permanently fix the result. Within a week, gently insert the usual foods and observe moderation &ndash; if you start to eat off of hungry days, the weight comes back very quickly.</p>




<p>If losing weight on bananas was comfortable for you, start to practice weekly unloading banana days &ndash; this will easily support the weight without the stress and shocks. To the menu was not too severe, it offers a variety of delicious and hearty recipes.</p>




<p>Banana &ndash; fruit salad &ndash; cut slices of banana and add the slices of apple, pear or peach. The second option salad &ndash; add walnuts and lettuce.</p>




<p>Oatmeal with banana &ndash; Boil water for oatmeal, add back milk and finely chopped banana slices.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
