<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Dietology | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/dietology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2017-03-17T19:04:03+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diet for the Skin]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-for-the-skin/"/>
    <updated>2017-02-25T18:50:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-for-the-skin</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/diet-for-the-skin/img.jpg" alt="Diet for the skin">
There are contraindications, consult your doctor.</p>

<p>Every woman wants to have a clean, beautiful, well-groomed, youthful skin. The youngest must be skin on the face, as her <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="every day">every day</a> see the surrounding. To be beautiful, a woman uses cosmetics and skin care products, but this is not always enough. To skin remains smooth and youthful, you need proper <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-on-cellulose/" title="nutrition">nutrition</a>.</p>

<!--more-->




<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Usually <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/" title="diet">diet</a> does not last long - a week, two weeks, a month, sometimes more. Still, any diet sooner or later ends. For beautiful skin one week or one month is not enough nutrition. Follow dietary recommendations you have for life.</p>

<p>Through nutrition, you can not stop the aging process of your skin. You still will be wrinkles, whatever you do. Nature is relentless, and with the passage of time it takes away from the <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet/" title="beauty">beauty</a> of women. But for sure you pay attention, that in 50 years, a woman looks like an old woman, while for the other, the same age as her, still invited on a date a man.</p>

<p>Someone facial skin aging earlier, and someone later. Diet - is one of the ways to keep the skin in good condition. You should consume enough of:</p>

<ol>
<li><p><strong>Vitamins</strong>. Have you ever noticed that the writing on the banks with vitamins pharmaceutical companies? Usually there can be read, that multivitamin preparation will improve the condition of your skin. However, the vitamins can be obtained not only from the cans. They are full of in food. Eat more vegetables, fruits. Regularly eat liver - it has accumulated a huge amount of vitamins.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Water</strong>. When the body lacks fluids, skin becomes dry, limp, ugly. It is necessary to drink water regularly. If your body is constantly in a state of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/dehydration.html" title="dehydration">dehydration</a>, the skin of your face will quickly become flabby and wrinkled.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>PUFAs</strong>. Polyunsaturated fatty acids should be present continuously in the diet. The use flaxseed oil and fish as their source.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Iron</strong>. Do not iron deficiency in the body. It is part of the protein hemoglobin, which carries oxygen. Naturally, the chronic oxygen <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/starvation.html" title="starvation">starvation</a> of the skin over time is not well reflected in your face. Iron is found in:</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Antioxidants</strong>. The substances that destroy free radicals, slow down skin aging. Therefore, your diet must be present in large quantities fruits contain antioxidants in abundance. Many of them also present in green tea.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>Women with problem skin constantly have to deal with the emerging pigmentation in the face, red spots, inflammatory elements. She sweats, gaining weight, and shows the black dots and white pimples. To face skin looked normal, you need to use cosmetics, do cosmetic procedures. But diet is also able to assist in the fight against skin problems.</p>

<p>The following products should be restricted:</p>

<ol>
<li><p><strong>Sweets</strong>. It is believed that the confectionery increase the likelihood of skin inflammatory elements. It is not known, however, these or not. But in any case, limit sweets will not be superfluous, since it is well reflected not only on the face, but also in the <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/" title="figure">figure</a>.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Water in the evening</strong>. Water is essential to the skin of the face lacked moisture. It should not dry. But excess water in the evening will cause swelling on the face in the morning. The more frequently in the morning you will suffer from edema, the faster you will have wrinkles. Therefore, from late teas should be abandoned.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Alcohol</strong>. Alcoholic drinks are harmful to all organs and systems. Of course, alcohol and harm the skin. If you do not believe me, look, it looks like the skin of women who abuse alcohol. 40 They are worse than some 60.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Coffee</strong>. On some sites, you can read that coffee appear on the skin pigmentation. Apparently, this assumption is due to the black beverage. It is unlikely that coffee you will have pigmentation on the face. But for problem skin drink it is harmful, because it enhances the separation of sebum.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Sol</strong>. From her appear edema. For this reason, if you have problem skin, better to limit the intake of salt. This does not mean that you should eat salted insufficiently dishes. Just give up salted fish, chips, cheese suluguni and other products containing salt in excessive quantities.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>There diet for cleaning intestines, kidneys, blood, or whole organism. Diet for cleansing the face too. Another thing is how effective it is? A woman who wants to clean the skin, it is recommended to use:</p>

<p>There are diets that have a duration of 3, 7 or 10 days, and the alleged need to make your skin cleaner. In fact, to purify it, it is not enough food. To do this, you need:</p>

<ul>
<li>treating the skin with special lotions;</li>
<li>visit a beautician and perform cleaning procedures.</li>
</ul>


<p>None of these products, you make eating the skin of your face clean. First of all, you should pay attention to skin care and lifestyle that you lead.</p>

<p>Oily skin - a real problem for women. It should not just wipe the face with a napkin, as a person immediately becomes unkempt appearance. For oily skin, constantly emerging inflammatory elements, and it can not please women. Unfortunately, this problem can not be solved with diet. The skin does not become less oily, if you limit the amount of fat in their diets.</p>

<p><em>You may want to reduce the consumption of the following products:</em></p>

<p>Theoretically, such a diet can make your skin a little less fatty. But in practice, no significant difference you will likely not see. Therefore, use cosmetics, drugs to reduce sebum production, regularly visit a beautician. The only way to significantly reduce the oiliness of the skin and the amount of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dermatology/acne.html" title="acne">acne</a> on the face.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glycemic Index Diet]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/glycemic-index-diet/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-19T13:23:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/glycemic-index-diet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/glycemic-index-diet/img.jpg" alt="glycemic index diet">The nutrition system based on controlling carbohydrates receipts called glycemic index diet: It allows you to quickly lose weight without causing harm to the body.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Diet with a low glycemic index foods: essence, the benefits and features</h2>

<p>The glycemic index (GI) - a measure of the speed of fission products to the further formation of the primary energy source - glucose.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>The higher the glycemic index of the product - the more rapidly digested and glucose is the formation of fatty deposits.</p>

<p>Talking about what is on the glycemic index diet, should take into consideration all its stages:</p>

<ul>
<li>In the first stage we have to eat foods with a low GI, and at that time is the most active fat burning. Duration - two weeks or more, until the desired result is achieved;</li>
<li>In the second stage glycemic index diet meals are resolved with an average GI to consolidate the results. Duration is also not less than 14 days;</li>
<li>The third stage is the output, and at this time permitted high GI foods, but in small quantities. The diet should be based on foods with middle- and low-index.</li>
</ul>


<p>What are the features of a diet with a low glycemic index:</p>

<ul>
<li>Its menu consists of a low-calorie foods, so weight loss is achieved due to the fact that the body produce more energy than it receives;</li>
<li>All simple carbohydrates are replaced by the complex.</li>
</ul>


<p>Advantages diet based on the glycemic index impressive of all dieters:</p>

<ul>
<li>Even in the first stage <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/starvation.html" title="starvation">starvation</a> practically impossible, since it is based on principles of nutrition;</li>
<li>This method helps to enhance metabolism, improves bowel and has a favorable effect on the functioning of internal organs, so it can be used all my life;</li>
<li>The nutrition system is suitable even for pregnant women and nursing mothers, as well as those who suffer from chronic or serious illnesses.</li>
</ul>


<p>Perhaps the only drawback is the fact that throughout the weight loss glycemic index diet foods will have to consult with the special GI table, but after some time to get accustomed to this.</p>

<h2>How much can you lose on a glycemic index diet</h2>

<p>It is worth noting that this method of weight loss is not fast, so for a month of its application can throw no more than 10 kg. This <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/" title="figure">figure</a> also depends on physical activity and energy intake - it should not be higher than 1700 kcal per day.</p>

<h2>Glycemic index diet for weight loss: compliance rules, menu, table, recipes</h2>

<p><em>Terms glycemic index diet for weight loss:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>It is best to give preference to products with low GI and high nutritional value, and not vice versa;</li>
<li>It is not recommended to use fried food: it is best to cook, bake or eat fresh salads;</li>
<li>Water increases the rate of excretion of excess fluids, but drink it in such volumes as often stated in other techniques, is not necessary.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Low glycemic index foods</h3>

<p><strong>Foods with a high glycemic index (GI of 70 and above)</strong></p>

<table width="100%">
    <thead>
        <tr>
            <th>Product</th>
            <th>GI</th>
        </tr>
    </thead>
    <tbody>
        <tr>
            <td>Beer</td>
            <td align="center">110</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Dates</td>
            <td align="center">103</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Glucose</td>
            <td align="center">100</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Modified starch</td>
            <td align="center">100</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Toast of white bread</td>
            <td align="center">100</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Swede</td>
            <td align="center">99</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Buns</td>
            <td align="center">95</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Baked potato</td>
            <td align="center">95</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fried potatoes</td>
            <td align="center">95</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Potato casserole</td>
            <td align="center">95</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Rice noodles</td>
            <td align="center">92</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Canned apricots</td>
            <td align="center">91</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Gluten-free white bread</td>
            <td align="center">90</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>White (glutinous) rice</td>
            <td align="center">90</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Carrots (boiled or stewed)</td>
            <td align="center">85</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Hamburger Buns</td>
            <td align="center">85</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cornflakes</td>
            <td align="center">85</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Free sugar popcorn</td>
            <td align="center">85</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Rice pudding with milk</td>
            <td align="center">85</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Mashed potatoes</td>
            <td align="center">83</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cracker</td>
            <td align="center">80</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Muesli with nuts and raisins</td>
            <td align="center">80</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sweet donut</td>
            <td align="center">76</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pumpkin</td>
            <td align="center">75</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Watermelon</td>
            <td align="center">75</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>French baguette</td>
            <td align="center">75</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Rice porridge with milk</td>
            <td align="center">75</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Lasagna (from soft wheat)</td>
            <td align="center">75</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Savoury waffles</td>
            <td align="center">75</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Millet</td>
            <td align="center">71</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Chocolate bar ("Mars", "Snickers", "Twix" and the like)</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Milk chocolate</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sweet drinks ("Coca-Cola", "Pepsi-Cola" and the like)</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Croissant</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Noodles of soft wheat</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pearl barley</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Potato chips</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Risotto with white rice</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Brown sugar</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>White sugar</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cuscus</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Munk</td>
            <td align="center">70</td>
        </tr>
    </tbody>
</table>


<p><strong>Products with an average glycemic index (GI of 50 to 69)</strong></p>

<table width="100%">
    <thead>
        <tr>
            <th>Product</th>
            <th>GI</th>
        </tr>
    </thead>
    <tbody>
        <tr>
            <td>Wheat flour</td>
            <td align="center">69</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh pineapple</td>
            <td align="center">66</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Instant oatmeal</td>
            <td align="center">66</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Orange juice</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Jam</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Beetroot (boiled or stewed)</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Black yeast bread</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Jujube</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Muesli with sugar</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Canned pineapple</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Raisins</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Maple syrup</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Rye bread</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Potatoes cooked in their skins</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sorbet</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sweet potato</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Whole wheat bread</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Canned vegetables</td>
            <td align="center">65</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pasta with cheese</td>
            <td align="center">64</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Wheat sprouts</td>
            <td align="center">63</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pancakes from wheat flour</td>
            <td align="center">62</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pizza on thin wheat dough with tomato and cheese</td>
            <td align="center">61</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Banana</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Chestnut</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Ice cream (with sugar)</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Long-grain rice</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Lasagna</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Industrial mayonnaise</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Melon</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Oatmeal</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cocoa powder (sweetened)</td>
            <td align="center">60</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Papaya fresh</td>
            <td align="center">59</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Arab pita</td>
            <td align="center">57</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sweet corn, canned</td>
            <td align="center">57</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Grape juice (sugar free)</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Ketchup</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Mustard</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Spaghetti</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sushi</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Bulgur</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Canned peaches</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Shortbread</td>
            <td align="center">55</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Basmati rice</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cranberry juice (sugar free)</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Kiwi</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pineapple juice without sugar</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Lichee</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Mango</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Persimmon</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Brown crude rice</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Apple juice (without sugar)</td>
            <td align="center">50</td>
        </tr>
    </tbody>
</table>


<p><strong>Foods with a low glycemic index (GI of 49 or less)</strong></p>

<table width="100%">
    <thead>
        <tr>
            <th>Product</th>
            <th>GI</th>
        </tr>
    </thead>
    <tbody>
        <tr>
            <td>Cranberries (fresh or frozen)</td>
            <td align="center">47</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Grapefruit juice (sugar free)</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Canned green peas</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Brown basmati rice</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Coconut</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Grapes</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Orange fresh</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>A toast of wholemeal bread</td>
            <td align="center">45</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Whole grain breakfast cereals (without sugar and honey)</td>
            <td align="center">43</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Buckwheat</td>
            <td align="center">40</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Dried figs</td>
            <td align="center">40</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pasta, cooked "al dente"</td>
            <td align="center">40</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Carrot juice (sugar free)</td>
            <td align="center">40</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Dried apricots</td>
            <td align="center">40</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Prunes</td>
            <td align="center">40</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Wild (black) rice</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Chick-pea</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
            </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh apple</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Meat and beans</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Dijon mustard</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Dried tomatoes</td>
            <td align="center">34</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh green peas</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Chinese noodles and vermicelli</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Sesame</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh orange</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh plums</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh quince</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Soy sauce (without sugar)</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Low-fat yogurt</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Ice cream with fructose</td>
            <td align="center">35</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Beans</td>
            <td align="center">34</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh nectarines</td>
            <td align="center">34</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Garnet</td>
            <td align="center">34</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh peach</td>
            <td align="center">34</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Compote (without sugar)</td>
            <td align="center">34</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Tomato juice</td>
            <td align="center">33</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Yeast</td>
            <td align="center">31</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Soy milk</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh apricots</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Brown lentils</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh grapefruit</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Green bean</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Garlic</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh carrots</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh beets</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Jam (no sugar)</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>fresh Pear</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Tomatoes (fresh)</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cottage cheese low fat</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Yellow lentils</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Blueberries, cranberries, blueberries</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Dark chocolate (70% cocoa)</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Almond milk</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>  
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Milk (any fat content)</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Passionfruit</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh mandarin</td>
            <td align="center">30</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Blackberry</td>
            <td align="center">20</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cherry</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Green lentils</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Golden bean</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh raspberries</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Red currant</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Soy flour</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Strawberry, wild-strawberry</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pumpkin seeds</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Gooseberry</td>
            <td align="center">25</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Peanut butter (no sugar)</td>
            <td align="center">20</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Artichoke</td>
            <td align="center">20</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Eggplant</td>
            <td align="center">20</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Soy yogurt</td>
            <td align="center">20</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Almond</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Broccoli</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cabbages</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cashew</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Celery</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Bran</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Brussels sprouts</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Cauliflower</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Chilli</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Fresh cucumber</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Hazelnuts, pine nuts, pistachios, walnuts</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Asparagus</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Ginger</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Mushrooms</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Squash</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Onion</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Pesto</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Leek</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Olives</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Peanut</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Salty and pickled cucumbers</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Rhubarb</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Tofu (bean curd)</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Soy</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Spinach</td>
            <td align="center">15</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Avocado</td>
            <td align="center">10</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Leaf salad</td>
            <td align="center">9</td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>Parsley, basil, vanilla, cinnamon, oregano</td>
            <td align="center">5</td>
        </tr>
    </tbody>
</table>


<h3>Low glycemic index diet: Menu</h3>

<p>You can use this example to the right to make your own menu:</p>

<ul>
<li>For breakfast we eat oatmeal with berries with the addition of a low GI, drink green tea;</li>
<li>After 2 hours, a snack dates;</li>
<li>Lunch soup with vegetable broth, eat a salad with sausage;</li>
<li>Afternoon snack citrus juice;</li>
<li>For dinner, leave vegetable salad.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Montignac Diet on Glycemic Index</h3>

<p>French Diet Montignac M. dietitian for weight loss is recommended to eat as follows:</p>

<ul>
<li>We have breakfast any fruits with a low GI, as we eat low-fat yogurt;</li>
<li>At lunch consume protein foods: cottage cheese, boiled eggs, yogurt, chicken;</li>
<li>Lunch grilled fish and salads of vegetables;</li>
<li>Afternoon snack with yogurt;</li>
<li>We have supper at the latest 19.00 boiled beans and meat.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Glycemic index diet recipes</h3>

<p><em>The recipe for stewed chicken with mushrooms:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Cut into pieces of chicken, onions shinkuem, spread all on a buttered pan;</li>
<li>Next, add the peeled and chopped mushrooms, salt and pepper, fry 5 minutes;</li>
<li>Add 100 ml of water, cover with lid and simmer for 15 minutes.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Recipe for vegetable salad:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Tear hands lettuce, sliced tomatoes, cucumbers and greens;</li>
<li>Mix all dressed with olive oil and mustard sauce.</li>
</ul>


<p><em>Soup recipe:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Fill with water to 300 grams of lean meat, put the stew;</li>
<li>Chop and fry the onion, carrot, tomato and pepper;</li>
<li>Shred cabbage, cut into bars potatoes, spread them in a ready-made broth;</li>
<li>After 10 minutes, add to the pan roasting, parsley, bay leaf and spices;</li>
<li>Boil 5 minutes, then turn off.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Losing weight on a low-glycemic index foods: reviews, the results of losing weight</h2>

<p>Doctors in most cases favor food with a low glycemic index, but the duration of the first stage should not be more than three weeks. This is due to the fact that the human body still needs slow carbohydrates, which limits this technique.</p>

<p>As a result of diet on the basis of the glycemic index of the products can be substantially reduced weight as well as to stabilize and improve the metabolism of the bowels. In order to continue to not score dropped weight, you must eat at the table of products with an average GI, occasionally allowing himself to eat any food with a high GI, and further to do fasting days.</p>

<p>Out of glycemic index diet is happening even in the third stage, when the allowed foods high in GI, while eat only it is not recommended.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diet on Cellulose]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-on-cellulose/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-14T13:19:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-on-cellulose</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/diet-on-cellulose/img.jpg" alt="Diet on cellulose">There are many effective diets for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/watermelon-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>. But people in the majority of cases they do not lose weight because they refuse to low-calorie food in just a few days after the decision on the fight against <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>. Blame - hunger, tormented man due to reduced caloric intake. To avoid it, and to increase the effectiveness of the diet, cellulose can be used. Let&rsquo;s talk about how it works, and what kind of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/model-diet/" title="weight-loss">weight-loss</a> schemes are applied to cellulose to date.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>
Perhaps you&rsquo;ve read online that cellulose reduces appetite, cleanses the body of toxins, normalizes metabolism, restores hormonal balance, metabolism. Most of this information - is not true. Cellulose fills the stomach, and this is its main function.</p>

<p>The real benefits of using cellulose in the diet to lose weight:</p>

<ul>
<li>prolongs the feeling of satiety;</li>
<li>It reduces the rate of <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-reduce-the-acidity-of-the-stomach/" title="digestion">digestion</a> of carbohydrates.</li>
</ul>


<p>Cellulose does not burn fat. This is just a means of improving portability of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/low-calorie-diet.html" title="low-calorie diet">low-calorie diets</a>. You can reduce caloric intake, and thereby lose weight. Cellulose will reduce hunger and significantly reduce the probability of failure of the diet.</p>

<p>For any diet on cellulose itself, you will need cellulose. Where to get it? It is sold in pharmacies in the form of medicines or bioactive agents. Method of production - powders that are dosed spoons or pills. The last is more expensive but more convenient dosing, and, moreover, do not contain extra <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/" title="calories">calories</a>.</p>

<p>Cellulose is simple to manufacture, has a low cost, so it is produced by many companies.</p>

<p>Siberian cellulose can not be purchased at pharmacies, but can be purchased from the members of this network of the company or to order via the Internet. Please note that the price may vary significantly at different sites and by different retailer. But in any case, such a cellulose is cheaper than microcrystalline cellulose from the pharmacy.</p>

<p>There are many diets on the cellulose and yogurt. Some of them - short designed for 1-3 weeks. Others - long recommended for use over several years or even a lifetime. Let us discuss a few of these diets.</p>

<p><strong><em>Diet for a week.</em></strong> Within 7 days of the foundation of the diet of yogurt and cellulose. In total you need every day to drink 4 glasses of fermented milk beverage. It should add 2 tablespoons cellulose. Do not forget that the whole week you should drink plenty of water - preferably up to 2.5 liters per day. As a snack between meals, you are allowed to eat per day 200 g of raw vegetables or fruits.</p>

<p><strong><em>The diet for 3 weeks.</em></strong> In the morning you eat porridge without salt. At lunch - steamed vegetables and chicken breast. At dinner - only a cup of yogurt with cellulose. Also, one glass should drink 15 minutes before breakfast and dinner. Thus, all your daily diet consists of two meals and 3 glasses of yogurt with cellulose.</p>

<p><strong><em>Fasting days.</em></strong> The essence of the method of losing weight is by organizing weekly fasting days, during which time allowed for the day to drink a liter of yogurt. On the glass is necessary to put 1-2 tablespoons of cellulose.</p>

<p><strong><em>Long-term diet.</em></strong> One of the power supply circuit is recommended for long-term use. Diet is used as long as the weight reaches the desired values for you. Further it can be applied in the &ldquo;light&rdquo; mode to maintain body weight within acceptable limits. The essence of this diet is that the size of portions is reduced by half, and before every meal you take a cup of yogurt with 1-2 tablespoons of cellulose.</p>

<p>The power supply circuit, where the basis of the diet is protein foods and cellulose, is one of the variants of the <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/protein-diet-sample-menu-protein-diet/" title="protein diet">protein diet</a>. Weight loss occurs to a greater extent by limiting carbohydrates less - because of the reduction of the total caloric intake. For this diet is not used in the pharmacy purchased cellulose - the organism gets her vegetables, fruits, mushrooms and other plant foods.</p>

<ol>
<li><p>Each meal should consist of foods that contain large amounts of cellulose and protein foods (meat, fish, milk, eggs, legumes, seafood).</p></li>
<li><p>Prohibited fatty and carbohydrate-rich foods (sweets, flour products, cereals, potatoes).</p></li>
</ol>


<p>Diet lasts up to a full normalization of weight. It has both advantages and disadvantages. Pluses diet on protein and cellulose:</p>

<ul>
<li>good tolerability - varied menu, tasty food, no hunger;</li>
<li>a gradual but steady weight loss effect.</li>
</ul>


<p>Lows in the diet cellulose and protein:</p>

<ul>
<li>harmful to health (it is better not to sit on such a diet with liver disease, kidney disease, endocrine abnormalities);</li>
<li>the need for specialized knowledge (need to have data on the chemical composition of food and products - to know how much they contain cellulose, protein, carbohydrate, cellulose);</li>
<li>high cost (protein food are more expensive cereals, pasta, potatoes).</li>
</ul>


<p>It should be borne in mind that the diet should be held in a total ban on the carbohydrate-rich foods, especially pastries. The slightest deviation from this rule leads to the complete ineffectiveness of diet.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Milk Diet for Weight Loss]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/milk-diet-for-weight-loss/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-08T11:19:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/milk-diet-for-weight-loss</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/milk-diet-for-weight-loss/img.jpg" alt="Milk diet for weight loss">Everyone in their own way refers to different products. Someone like olives, some do not; someone loves caviar, and someone can not understand what&rsquo;s so special. So it is with milk: it has both fans and haters. However, in some form or other dairy products they consume almost everything and most people refer to it quite bearable. If you - among them, and want to lose a few extra kilos, you can get acquainted with several options dairy diet, which will be discussed in this post.</p>

<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<p>Thus, the basis of dietary food in this case is milk. And, as varieties of this product, there is quite a lot, and opinions diverge about the choice.</p>

<p>Most dieters claim that, once go on a diet, it is necessary to choose only low-fat product or a maximum of 0.5-1.5% milk, which contains only 39-47 <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/figs-diet-for-weight-loss/" title="calories">calories</a> per 100 ml. However, we advise you to seek the smallest <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/" title="figure">figures</a>, because in the process of normalization (bringing the milk to the desired fat content), it partially loses its valuable properties. The fact that the fat-soluble vitamins useful and other components partially extracted from it, together with the &quot;surplus&quot; fats. Moreover, milk fat is not as dangerous as &quot;normal&quot; animal, which is contained in fat and fat meat. Its main components are useful phospholipids rather than potentially threatening <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/cardiology/atherosclerosis.html" title="atherosclerosis">atherosclerosis</a> <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/when-to-calibrate-their-cholesterol-triglyceride-and-hdl-cholesterol/" title="cholesterol">cholesterol</a>.</p>

<p>Thus, you can not pay so much attention to the choice of issues. Will suit you like milk with 1.5%, and the &quot;standard&quot;, with 2.5% fat content, which can be found in every store. Although, of course, if you do opt for the 6% of the product or liquid cream, it is unlikely to benefit figure.</p>

<p><strong>As milk diet effect on the body?</strong></p>

<p>This in itself has a low calorie milk and contains small amounts of protein required in the diet body. Actually, that&rsquo;s all, what are its advantages when it comes to <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/watermelon-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a>. Fat is not mobilized, a depressing effect on the appetite does not, on the blood sugar level is not affected. It&rsquo;s just a useful product small calorie, which can be used as a dietary. The effect of a diet is to ensure that the diet is severely limited energy value.</p>

<p>Itself milk diet, in whatever form it is employed, is rigid and is usually not perfectly balanced, so it is not recommended for a long time.</p>

<h2>Types of milk diet</h2>

<p>If we approach the issue of transfer of dairy diet with all the responsibility, you can find a dozen different versions of it, in which as the dominant power component acts milk. But the most commonly used are 3 types.</p>

<p>It is intended for use during the day (as the handling of the day), the most healthy people are allowed to use it for 3 days. On day <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="slimming">slimming</a> offered 1 liter of milk; moreover, it can drinking ordinary water and mineral. That is, in fact, mono-diet on milk is <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/starvation.html" title="starvation">starvation</a>.</p>

<p>During the day it takes about 500-700 g of weight, three days you can lose up to 2 kg. But, in any case, it requires the observance of the human ideal health, and sit on it longer than strictly prohibited.</p>

<p>By the choice of food it can be characterized as a protein, because during its compliance permitted only various embodiments of dairy products. You can drink milk, yogurt, fermented baked low-fat, low-fat cottage cheese has, diet cheese, unsweetened yogurt. Glazed cheese, ice cream, yoghurt, sweet, cream, sour cream - all this, of course, prohibited.</p>

<p>Ingestion performed 5-6 times per day total caloric intake calculated individually for women - not less than 1200 kcal, if it is supposed to adhere for 1 week, and not less than 1500 kcal, when it is planned to extend for 14 days.</p>

<p>Longer &quot;sitting&quot; on the expanded dairy diet is contraindicated, since such power marked a clear shortage of fats and carbohydrates, which can lead to adverse effects on the part of health. As for the results, then a week on it, you can lose about 2-3 kg.</p>

<p>From the listed options for the most useful and safe. It consists in the fact that, along with the milk (1-1.5 liters per day), a person is allowed to eat fresh fruits and vegetables, salads and boiled or baked vegetables. Excluded are only those plant foods that contain too much sugar and starch (corn, potatoes, grapes). Should be fed 4-6 times a day, calculated calorie in the same manner as the previous embodiment diet.</p>

<p>Since vegetables and fruits generally lower in calories than the milk-based products, the amount of power becomes greater, and diet quite easily tolerated. But more than 2 weeks of her stay is not necessary, you need to take a break for at least 10 days. And another recommendation: if you are planning a meal with the addition of fresh fruits and vegetables, do not drink milk immediately after use, it is better do it in an hour and a half. Due to the high acid content in vegetable products in such a combination may cause <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/symptoms/diarrhea.html" title="diarrhea">diarrhea</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diet Aphrodite]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite/"/>
    <updated>2016-06-07T14:41:00+05:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/diet-aphrodite</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/diet-aphrodite/img.jpg" alt="Diet Aphrodite">In Greek mythology, Aphrodite - the goddess of love and <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/nine-day-diet/" title="beauty">beauty</a>. Therefore its name is often referred to as a <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/watermelon-diet/" title="weight loss">weight loss</a> diet, as an integral feature of female attractiveness is a slim figure. Variants of Aphrodite, there are many diets. Most often, the so-called power scheme, which is based on the use of Mediterranean cuisine.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Menu Diet Aphrodite is strongly reminiscent of a Mediterranean menu. Eat only a useful and <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/pineapple-diet/" title="health">health</a>y food. Carbohydrates, which are the direct cause of <a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/dietology/obesity.html" title="obesity">obesity</a>, severely limit. The source of fats are fish, seafood, and vegetable oils, which are allowed to be added to vegetable salads.</p>

<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins><script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script></p>

<ol>
<li>The diet of many fish and seafood.</li>
<li>It is recommended to the regular inclusion of seaweed menu.</li>
<li>Shrimp - one of the basic diet products. They need to eat at least twice a week, and if it allows the thickness of the purse, then more often.</li>
<li>Chicken should be a priority meats.</li>
<li>Lactic acid products need to drink before bedtime.</li>
<li>Allowed to eat eggs, but it is recommended to separate the yolk - it has a lot of fat.</li>
<li>In many dishes is recommended to add the celery.</li>
<li>Fruits and juices can be drunk in unlimited quantities.</li>
<li>Sweets and flour products are excluded from the diet.</li>
<li>Cereals and bread can be eaten only in the morning.</li>
</ol>


<p>In this embodiment Aphrodite diet has no restrictions on duration, caloric intake, the number of meals. But to know the measure, of course, necessary. Despite the dominance of the diet of protein foods and vegetables, plump with overeating can even be on these products.</p>

<h2>Diet Aphrodite with goat cheese</h2>

<p>The Internet is widely distributed another version of Aphrodite&rsquo;s diet with goat cheese. She is short, only lasts three days and is designed for <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/how-to-lose-weight-at-home/" title="rapid weight loss">rapid weight loss</a>. Menu of such a diet is clearly laid out by day. Power - Four.</p>

<p><strong>The first day:</strong></p>

<ol>
<li>Goat cheese - 100g of bread - 50 g.</li>
<li>A glass of yogurt.</li>
<li>Soup, which consists of mushrooms, cucumber, goat cheese and olive oil.</li>
<li>Vegetables and Goat Cheese.</li>
</ol>


<p><strong>Second day:</strong></p>

<ol>
<li>Oatmeal and dried fruits.</li>
<li>A glass of yogurt and an apple.</li>
<li>Vegetables and shrimp.</li>
<li>Goat cheese and scrambled eggs with tomatoes.</li>
</ol>


<p><strong>Day Three:</strong></p>

<ol>
<li>Egg, cucumber, 100 g of goat cheese.</li>
<li>100 grams of cottage cheese, a piece of fruit.</li>
<li>Goat cheese with mushrooms.</li>
<li>Vegetables.</li>
</ol>


<p>With such a diet can really lose weight. However, to do it for three days is not possible, but it is not designed for a long life. Therefore, a diet of Aphrodite on the goat cheese is unlikely to radically change your figure.</p>

<h2>Greek diet Aphrodite</h2>

<p>Probably the most stupid diet should be considered as the Greek Aphrodite. It is designed for weight loss, but the diet based on - carbohydrates, while protein-containing foods is limited. Menu options Aphrodite Greek diet consists mainly of:</p>

<ul>
<li>vegetables;</li>
<li>cereals;</li>
<li>pasta;</li>
<li>fruits;</li>
<li>nuts and seeds;</li>
<li>dairy products;</li>
<li>of bread;</li>
<li>legumes;</li>
<li>olive oil;</li>
<li>wine.</li>
</ul>


<p>These foods should be consumed daily. An intermediate position is occupied by the food recommended to be put on the table, no more frequently than every other day:</p>

<ul>
<li>honey;</li>
<li>chocolate;</li>
<li>seafood;</li>
<li>a fish;</li>
<li>eggs.</li>
</ul>


<p>Finally, in the least favored by the creators of the meat of the Greek diet. Oil-rich generally prohibited. But chicken or veal to use as possible, but not more than three times a month. What thoughts <a href="http://medusanews.com/articles/why-should-you-run-benefits-and-harms-of-running/" title="running">running</a> through my head of people who compose this diet, we do not know. But if you do not want to multiply the fat reserves on your stomach, it is better to give it up.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
