<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Allergology | Med USA News]]></title>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/categories/allergology/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://medusanews.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-05-21T16:52:30+05:00</updated>
  <id>http://medusanews.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[medusanews]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[38% of Americans Have a Child Who Suffers From an Allergy]]></title>
    <link href="http://medusanews.com/articles/38-percent-of-americans-have-a-child-who-suffers-from-an-allergy/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-26T13:36:00+06:00</updated>
    <id>http://medusanews.com/articles/38-percent-of-americans-have-a-child-who-suffers-from-an-allergy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="left" src="http://medusanews.com/images/38-percent-of-americans-have-a-child-who-suffers-from-an-allergy/0.jpg" width="200" height="150" title="allergy, allergic child" alt="38% of Americans have a child who suffers from an allergy">The results of the FIFG/Stallergenes Foundation study revealed that 38% of Americans have a child who suffers from allergies.</p>




<p><strong>Among these allergic children, 28% suffer from respiratory allergies, 12% develop food allergies and 12% of drug allergies.</strong></p>




<p>This is more than 1 in 3 children.</p>




<!--more-->


<script async src="//pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/js/adsbygoogle.js"></script>


<!-- post_first -->


<p><ins class="adsbygoogle"
     style="display:block"
     data-ad-client="ca-pub-8970873924341937"
     data-ad-slot="8187327206"
     data-ad-format="auto"></ins></p>

<script>
(adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
</script>




<h2>Allergies strong growth</h2>




<p>&ldquo;Children are a slice of the population at risk because more sensitive to allergens, chemicals as well as viral infections&rdquo; explains Dr. Pham Thi Nhan, allergist, pneumo-pediatrician, Necker Hospital &ndash; Sick Children, New York.</p>




<p>According to the results of the FIFG/Stallergenes Foundation study, 94% of Americans believe that there are more allergies now than in the past. Confirmed by a WHO felt. In France, from 25 to 30% of people suffer from allergies, or double the number 20 years ago, particularly among children and adolescents. More worryingly, the WHO predicts that by 2050, 1 in 2 will be allergic in the world. &ldquo;It is known that severe cases of allergies are increasing worldwide. This is not only due to a more accurate diagnosis but phenomena that progress in the population&rdquo;, declare the allergist.</p>




<p>What are the factors responsible for the increase in allergies?</p>




<ul>
<li>73% of Americans people point the finger at pollution;</li>
<li>34% pesticide use;</li>
<li>28% changes in supply mode;</li>
<li>25% overprotection of infants;</li>
<li>22% increase in awareness of the organization;</li>
<li>18% climate change.</li>
</ul>




<p>&ldquo;Pollution is a co-precipitant and aggravating allergies: it increases our sensitivity and our susceptibility to the environment and therefore increases the risk of developing allergies. When pollution peaks in March, we have seen an impressive number of allergies: new cases and cases of severe rhino<a href="http://medusanews.com/diseases-and-conditions/ophthalmology/conjunctivitis.html" title="conjunctivitis">conjunctivitis</a> including pollens, excluding asthma attacks. The days that followed pollution peaks, the number of health care utilization has risen sharply&rdquo;, says Dr. Nhan Pham Thi.</p>




<h2>Good reflexes to reduce allergens</h2>




<p>In addition to the necessary consultation with a specialist and the establishment of appropriate treatment following the allergen to which the child is sensitive, simple steps can significantly reduce the impact of respiratory allergies.</p>




<p>It is recommended that parents of children with respiratory allergies:</p>




<ul>
<li>ventilate the room (84%);</li>
<li>do not put carpet (69%);</li>
<li>to regularly clean (62%);</li>
<li>do not use a pillow or feather duvet (52%);</li>
<li>to avoid contact with dogs/cats (32%);</li>
<li>not to houseplants or some trees in the garden (30%).</li>
</ul>




<p>&ldquo;Patient education is a mainstay of treatment that allows to change lifestyle to adapt to his new state of sensitivity requires support chronic and often long if not life treatment. A food allergic must learn to avoid food and control its aid kit. For a child with chronic rhinitis, nasal care are needed daily. Finally, asthma, adherence background is essential&rdquo; said Dr. Pham Thi Nhan.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
